<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4088" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-04-14</startdate>
<enddate>2006-10-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">The Third: Aoi Hitomi no Shoujo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">THE THIRD ~Girl with the Azure Eyes~</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="synonym">The Third; Meisje met de blauwe ogen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">The Third - Aoi Hitomi no Shoujo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">The Third ~Aoi Hitomi no Shoujo~</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">The third~苍之瞳的少女</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">The Third</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ザ・サード 蒼い瞳の少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Third: The Girl with the Blue Eye</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">The Third</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5911" approval="38" total="59">Koukaku no Regios</anime>
<anime id="2166" approval="9" total="15">Sunabouzu</anime>
<anime id="53" approval="8" total="17">Trigun</anime>
<anime id="2326" approval="3" total="11">Grenadier: Hohoemi no Senshi</anime>
<anime id="3408" approval="1" total="9">Shakugan no Shana</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="390120">One of sleeper hits for anime. Kinda good anime to kill time or you have nothing to watch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="22160" type="Original Work">Hoshino Ryou</name>
<name id="6920" type="Music">Oohashi Megumi</name>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="5509" type="Character Design">Yamaoka Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="2961" type="Series Composition">Oonishi Shinsuke</name>
<name id="4605" type="Direction">Kamiya Jun</name>
</creators>
<description>In the distant future, because of an interplanetary war that has continued on for centuries, the civilizations were ruined. Human beings have lost everything, and only 1/5th of the population survived. Pseudo-humans, The Third, are said to have appeared just after the war. They have a third red astral Eye on there forehead. Hence the third. Using them, they can control computer systems and so on, and rule the world by their superior intellect and abnormal abilities.
In this dark world, there is a girl named http://anidb.net/ch4649 [Honoka]. She is a master-of-all-trades, and she accepts any job except taking a human life. She is also a master of chi and swordsmanship and is known by most as the Sword Dancer.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2223">6.29</permanent>
<temporary count="2244">7.60</temporary>
<review count="5">6.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>14245.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6466</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>944</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3596</identifier>
<identifier>dapzap</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.xebec-inc.co.jp/anime/third/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Third</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ザ・サード</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>864</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>325162</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8134</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="235" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-05">
<name>waitress</name>
<description>A female attendant who serves customers in a restaurant, café, or similar.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>163704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="509" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-19">
<name>clone</name>
<description>This character is grown from a single somatic cell or cell nucleus and genetically identical to it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1528" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-12">
<name>artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligence of machines and the branch of computer science that aims to create it. AI textbooks define the field as "the study and design of intelligent agents" where an intelligent agent is a system that perceives its environment and takes actions that maximize its chances of success. John McCarthy, who coined the term in 1956, defines it as "the science and engineering of making intelligent machines."
The field was founded on the claim that a central property of humans, intelligence—the sapience of Homo sapiens—can be so precisely described that it can be simulated by a machine. This raises philosophical issues about the nature of the mind and the ethics of creating artificial beings, issues which have been addressed by myth, fiction and philosophy since antiquity. Artificial intelligence has been the subject of optimism, but has also suffered setbacks and, today, has become an essential part of the technology industry, providing the heavy lifting for many of the most difficult problems in computer science.
AI research is highly technical and specialized, and deeply divided into subfields that often fail to communicate with each other. Subfields have grown up around particular institutions, the work of individual researchers, the solution of specific problems, longstanding differences of opinion about how AI should be done and the application of widely differing tools. The central problems of AI include such traits as reasoning, knowledge, planning, learning, communication, perception and the ability to move and manipulate objects. General intelligence (or "strong AI") is still among the field`s long term goals.</description>
<picurl>71305.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1999" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-29">
<name>tomboy</name>
<description>A girl who acts and dresses like a boy and enjoys rough, noisy activities traditionally associated with boys.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2467" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-22">
<name>sword</name>
<description>A sword is a long, edged piece of metal, used as a cutting, thrusting, and clubbing weapon in many civilizations throughout the world. Before firearms became commonplace, and fast enough to render other weapons pointless in the battlefield, they were the main kind of weapon for war and duels alike. A sword fundamentally consists of a blade and a hilt, typically with one or two edges for striking and cutting, and a point for thrusting. That aside, however, they may come in all sorts of designs: the medieval European swords used to be big, heavy weapons that did not actually cut but instead broke the enemy`s bones under their armor; conversely, the Chinese jian sword (called "ken" in Japanese) attempted to exploit the armor`s joints and perforate the enemy`s flesh in those places, but was useless against the armor itself, and did not take the strikes, preferring to redirect them, to this day being considered a highly "circular" weapon and associated to taijiquan; on the other hand, the Japanese katana was a balanced all-purposes weapon that could be used even in an axe-like way, but which a master swordsman could use in many other, more elaborate manners.</description>
<picurl>127113.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2491" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-09">
<name>nurse</name>
<description>For hentai shows, it`s enough if a http://anidb.net/t884 [nurse costume] is worn without the female character actually working as a nurse.
For ecchi shows, the nurse profession must play a big enough part in the overall setting.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
<picurl>160445.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2745" parentid="1773" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>mechanical tentacle</name>
<description>Same as tentacles, but instead of being fleshy-slimy, they`re made of metal or perhaps plastic, doesn`t really matter, as long as they look mechanical.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2875" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>ecology</name>
<description>Nature and ecology are a central theme of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2893" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>female teacher</name>
<description>Any kind of female teacher will do, even if she only does home visits. Female teachers imply mature women (even if they sometimes look like schoolgirls) dressed in what women would typically wear when doing official business (like a blouse, pinstripe dress with side front slit), but of course, not limited to that. Furthermore, school nurses also count as female teachers unless they`re actually wearing a nurse outfit, which they almost never are.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2906" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>nanomachines</name>
<description>The anime features sub-microscopic (nano = 10E-9 = one billionth) machines, machines that float in the bloodstream and affect the human body. They can be used both for good (repairing human cells in situ) or for evil (nano-machine warfare, attacking human cells in situ).</description>
<picurl>183210.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3326" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-18">
<name>jumping very high</name>
<description>The character can jump unnaturally high.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3696" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-28">
<name>off-model animation</name>
<description>Anime shows tend to most often run on an already tight budget; some have even tighter ones. Thus, over the years it became a norm to invest more time and money into the first and last episode, leaving many episodes in the middle to stand severe budget restrictions. This sometimes results in episodes which particularly stand out due to the drop in artwork or animation quality; bar some basic framework, they often have little in common with the rest of the series.
One clue to upcoming off-model animation is the noticeable addition of many Korean names in the production credits, as farming out more animation to Korean artists is a nearly universal indicator of a production company trying to save money in all possible ways.
This effect is often called yashigani, after the infamous http://anidb.net/e4682 [fourth episode] of http://anidb.net/a403 [Lost Universe], Yashigani Hoburu. Another prominent term describing the same effect is "QUALITY animation", with capital letters meant to show contrast to actual quality. http://anidb.net/a4531 [Yoake Mae yori Ruriiro na: Crescent Love] is another legendarily terrible offender: the TV airing of its http://anidb.net/e63752 [third episode] had a perfectly spherical ball in place of what should be a cabbage; the "cabbage" was so egregious that it became closely associated with the anime itself, to a point the show would henceforth be nicknamed "Cabbage Love" among Western viewers.
One should not confuse the yashigani effect with art shifts that stem from guest staff, changes in main staff, intentional art shifts, and similar effects. Another effect one shouldn`t confuse this one with is the so-called DVD/BD enhancement, which is when a studio scrambles to meet the deadline for a TV airing and airs a half-finished episode but eventually fixes it for a disk release; for example, http://anidb.net/cr792 [Shaft] is particularly infamous for its disk enhancements, to a point it has become known as "Shafting", and they prominently feature intentionally weird character models, but they don`t often leave bad artwork on the disk release. Additionally, it should also not be confused with intentional lack of detail on background plane characters; this effect is instead when even the foreground has art quality shifting over time due to the aforementioned budget restrictions.</description>
<picurl>29532.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3798" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>giant insects</name>
<picurl>222266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4024" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-16">
<name>optic camouflage</name>
<description>Optic camouflage is a type of camouflage that distinguishes itself for actively altering optical properties around itself in order to make the wearer invisible. This could be said to be a high-tech form of "invisibility cloak".</description>
<picurl>191325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4042" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-17">
<name>odd jobs</name>
<description>A character (or several of them) in the anime takes on various jobs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4277" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>nuclear weapons</name>
<description>A nuclear weapon is an explosive device that derives its destructive force from nuclear reactions, which release vast quantities of energy from relatively small amounts of matter. Nuclear weapons are considered weapons of mass destruction, and their use and control have been a major focus of international relations policy since their debut.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4566" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-08">
<name>transforming weapons</name>
<description>This anime features transforming weapons, this can either be cars or household appliances that transform into weapons, such as transformers or weapons that themselves transform into bigger badder shapes to deal more and more damage.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4804" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-11-15">
<name>poetry</name>
<description>The anime is based upon, around or contains significant references to poetry</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5784" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-27">
<name>hirable protagonist</name>
<description>The protagonist in the anime will do just about anything... for the right price, of course.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6623" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-04-02">
<name>tank warfare</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4649" type="main character in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="14">6.54</rating>
<name>Honoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Honoka is a cheerful young girl who works as a freelancer. She`ll take on almost any job, though she doesn`t really care for mercenary work. Because she spent most of her childhood in the desert, she`s a bit of a tomboy (and is often teased about it). Bogie, her A.I. partner, has been with her since she was very young, and she`s come to care about him just as much as he does for her. Honoka has many layers to her personality; she`s strong yet gentle, aggressive yet vulnerable.</description>
<picture>20756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4650" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="5">3.44</rating>
<name>Iks</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iks is a mystery. He was alone when Honoka found him, quietly watching the fireflies at night. The moment their eyes met, Honoka was struck by his presence... and she hasn`t quite been able to figure out why. Iks is compassionate, kind, and very calm. He also possesses a strange power that allows him to heal wounds. The Third seem to be particularly interested in Iks, for reasons that they aren`t willing to share.</description>
<picture>20757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4651" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="4">8.45</rating>
<name>Bogie</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bogie is Honoka`s partner. He`s an A.I. unit that acts as Honoka`s guide, guardian, and friend. The actual casing he resides in isn`t very large, but he`s usually fixed into Honoka`s tank to act as its pilot. He has a very straightforward personality and is often strict with Honoka, especially when it comes to her safety. He seems to nag a bit when she doesn`t wake up on time, or follow a specific course of action... but perhaps that`s to be expected of a computer. Regardless, Bogie cares about Honoka a great deal.</description>
<picture>20758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4652" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="2">4.36</rating>
<name>Joganki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joganki is a high-ranking member of The Third`s council. He`s collected and confident, but not overly so. Joganki has a strong interest in Honoka, and they seem to have some sort of history - but Honoka wants nothing to do with him. She grumbles and complains about his constant "interference"... yet Joganki still continues to keep a watchful eye on her from his lofty seat in Hyperius.</description>
<picture>20759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4653" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-06">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Zankan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zankan is a brilliant mechanic that lives out in the desert with his daughter, Millie. Mankind is not allowed to possess advanced technology, thanks to The Third and their law, the "Technos Taboo" - but that hasn`t stopped Zankan. His living outside of town and ignoring the technology laws has allowed him to hone his craft to its utmost potential. He`s a kind man who, for years, has been both a mechanic and a friend to Honoka.</description>
<picture>20760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="284" picture="225436.jpg">Tanaka Masahiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4654" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="6">3.95</rating>
<name>Millie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Millie is Zankan`s daughter. She`s a pretty typical young girl, who likes to laugh and play more than anything else. Living out in the desert has been a bit hard for her, and sometimes she`s jealous of the machines that Zankan spends so much time with... but she loves her father, and is always happy to see Honoka.</description>
<picture>20761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1887" picture="77579.jpg">Sakata Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4655" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<name>Fila Marique</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fila is another council member of The Third. She and Joganki have a close working relationship, but they don`t always agree. Fila is often impetuous, coming to quick decisions that are a bit harsher than Joganki might like. And Joganki often lets his interest in Honoka colour his actions, which Fila just can`t understand. But in the end, the two respect each other completely. Fila is very serious and formal, almost like royalty - but despite her frosty appearance, she does have her own quiet form of kindness.</description>
<picture>20755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4656" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="2">3.06</rating>
<name>Blue Breaker</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Blue Breaker (also known as STW-9000) is an infamous auto-enforcer created by The Third. Blue Breaker has a complex AI system and a fighting prowess far beyond normal auto-enforcers. He also has a stealth coat, an energy field that makes him completely invisible - which means that many of his victims never see their killer. A cold assassin with no remorse, he is The Third`s final punishment for those who refuse to follow the law.</description>
<picture>20754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4657" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="11">6.31</rating>
<name>Paife</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Paife, like Honoka, does freelance work for the Emporium Administration. On the side, she also works as a nurse at the school Millie attends. Paife has sort of a mixed personality. On one hand, she`s the tough-talking, gun-slinging, heavy-drinking kind of woman you`d picture her to be. On the other hand, she`s got a playful streak that she only reveals in Honoka`s company. Unfortunately for Iks, she takes an immediate disliking to him, declaring that she "hates men."</description>
<picture>20751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4658" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<name>Gravestone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gravestone is a weapon of mass destruction left behind from the Great War. He was built with the ability to wreak terrible devastation and despair... but curiously, he was also given the form of a small boy. Gravestone, dormant for ages, has recently begun to stir and as his power continues to grow, so too does his craving for revenge...</description>
<picture>20749.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4659" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-06">
<name>Nor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Nor is a physician in Emporium. He`s a good friend of Honoka`s, despite the fact that he drives her crazy with his poking and prodding about her love-life. Nor is intelligent, sincere, carefree, and rather irresponsible - it`d be a stretch to call him a medical "professional" - but he certainly is good at what he does.</description>
<picture>20752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4660" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="2">3.97</rating>
<name>Rona Fauna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>From the darkness of her hidden stronghold, Rona Fauna built up a secret army and has now seized control of the Wormhole Driver, single-handedly throwing her people into chaos. Though she seems cool and detached as she puts her strange plans into motion, it`s easy to see that Rona is driven by some deep, powerful emotion... and she cannot rest until her task is at its end.</description>
<picture>20748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4661" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<name>Kevin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kevin is a mercenary who works out of Emporium. He`s a bit gruff, but not a bad guy. Every so often he`ll show up to give Honoka a key piece of information, or to pass on the latest rumours among the mercenary crowd - after teasing her a bit, of course. Though he tends to butt heads with Honoka, it`s all in good fun.</description>
<picture>20750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4662" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="2">6.46</rating>
<name>Joey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joey is a mechanic who lives and works in Emporium. Ever cheerful, he`s a feisty, down-to-earth kind of guy. He and Honoka have a close, casual friendship (though he does seem to get a little jealous when Honoka`s around other guys...). Joey is great with machines, and dreams of one day becoming a great Technos, as skilled as Zankan.</description>
<picture>20753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4663" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="2">2.94</rating>
<name>Leon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leon used to be part of an old organisation known as the Monster Troop. He`s currently tracking down the desert fairy, a creature of legend, for reasons unknown. One thing`s for sure though - for him, the hunt is life and death. Leon is dangerous, power-hungry, and will kill anyone who gets in his way.</description>
<picture>20747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69951" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-14">
<name>Yousei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A fairy collecting the genetic life of earth to spread into other parts of the galaxy.</description>
<picture>160841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69952" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-14">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Kamui</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A powerful wolf travelling the desert in search of the fairy.</description>
<picture>160843.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="48908" update="2006-04-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">1.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49099" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="13">3.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソード・ダンサー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sword Dancer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sword Dancer</title>
<summary>In a devastated world overrun by monstrous bugs and ravaged by outlaws, there`s only one person to call when you really need a job done right: Honoka. With a sixth sense for danger, sword skills that are second to none, and a smart-aleck A.I. tank by the name of Bogie, she`s ready to tackle any job and solve any problem for her clients. But while crossing the desert one night, she finds a young man alone in the wasteland.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735945</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="49124" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">慌しい一夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Eventful Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Awatadashii Ichiya</title>
<summary>Honoka isn`t ready to return to town, so she and her new traveling companion arrange to meet up with the mechanic Zankan and his young daughter, Millie. However, their plans are disturbed by some unexpected guests.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735947</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="49337" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂漠の街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desert Town</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabaku no Machi</title>
<summary>Honoka returns to Emporium and parts ways with Iks. After hearing rumors in town that The Third has bulked up the Inspection Force, it suddenly occurs to her that it might be related to her new acquaintance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735949</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="49929" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼い殺戮者(ブルー・ブレイカー)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Breaker</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blue Breaker</title>
<summary>Honoka and Bogie pick up the long-awaited PSP from Zankan. Just after parting ways, she senses an alarming presence pass overhead. It`s the Auto-Enforcer "Blue Breaker," whose name is synonymous with terror -- and it`s heading right toward her friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735951</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50323" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼い天宙眼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blue Astral Eye</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Tenchuugan</title>
<summary>Somehow, Honoka managed to drive Blue Breaker away, but with her bandanna stripped away, her secret is revealed. Honoka talks to Iks about her past, but right now, the unconscious Millie concerns her more.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735953</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50641" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大地に吹く風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wind That Sweeps the Land</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daichi ni Fuku Kaze</title>
<summary>The unmistakable heat signature of Blue Breaker rapidly closes in on Honoka and her friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735955</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50642" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜明けまで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Until Dawn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoake made</title>
<summary>After leaving Millie in the care of a relative and parting ways with Iks, Honoka and Bogie head back out to the desert for another job. While they are camped out, Honoka is awakened with the news that an armored ant is clinging to the tank.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735957</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50644" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンポリウムの午後</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Afternoon in Emporium</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Enporiumu no Gogo</title>
<summary>Honoka and Bogie cross paths with a herd of stampeding sand dragons. Meanwhile, The Third are rushing to counter a growing danger to the planet. What is this mysterious threat that even they fear?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735959</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50648" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">&amp;#12497;&amp;#12452;&amp;#12501;&amp;#12454;</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paife</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Paifuu</title>
<summary>The white light The Third continue to monitor is expanding rapidly. It`s a spatial distortion created by Gravestone, an ultimate weapon left over from the Great War. Meanwhile, Honoka is on a job for Emporium`s chief administrator. On her way to the sand dragon nest, a dune buggy catches up to the tank, and the strange woman Honoka met earlier in town steps out...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735961</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50649" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂漠の墓碑(グレイヴ・ストーン)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gravestone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gravestone</title>
<summary>When Honoka`s group catches up with Iks, he takes her aside aside and suggests they turn back. But aside from the fact she`s out on a job, Honoka has another reason for refusing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735963</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50650" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻影との戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battling Against Illusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gen`ei to no Tatakai</title>
<summary>Honoka and the others come face to face with the dome of light, which continues to expand. But despite Paife and Iks` pleading, Honoka continues to advance toward it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735965</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50651" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの理由</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Their Respective Reasons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Riyuu</title>
<summary>While Honoka and Paife are engaged in their respective battles, Iks attempts to talk with Gravestone. Time is swiftly running out...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735967</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50652" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="9">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂漠の伝説(フォークロア)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desert Folklore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabaku no Folklore</title>
<summary>Honoka decides to take Millie on a short vacation out in the desert after Paife tells her Millie was found asleep at school. At the same time, a hunter named Leon seeks out Honoka. He wants her to guide him in his search for the legendary "fairy" of the desert...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735969</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="57792" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精幻視</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fairy Visions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei Genshi</title>
<summary>Honoka and Millie continue their travels, but Iks can sense there is still a rift between the two girls. As they battle the desert`s dangers, Millie hears a gentle voice...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735971</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="57793" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂嵐の夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Night of the Sandstorm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sunaarashi no Yoru</title>
<summary>After three days of pursuing the fairy and the wolf through the desert, Honoka and Millie are still unable to bridge the emotional gap between them, but there is a sandstorm on the horizon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735973</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="57794" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乱舞する生命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life Dancing Wildly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ranbusuru Seimei</title>
<summary>Millie and the others look on as a seriously injured Honoka hangs on the brink of death. During this time, the Wolf suddenly appears and escorts Millie further into the desert, but for what reason?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735975</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="57795" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ローナ・ファウナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rona Fauna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rouna Fauna</title>
<summary>The Wormhole Driver has been hijacked! Unresponsive to The Third`s attempts to regain control, it fires and eradicates a huge portion of a mountain range. Meanwhile, Honoka meets with an unexpected potential client: Fila Marique. From Fila`s tone, it seems something strange is going on among The Third...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735977</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="57796" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">発動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Engage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsudou</title>
<summary>As Honoka`s group is about to depart, Fila reveals she has one more companion for them: Zankan`s killer, the most powerful autonomous soldier on the frontier, Blue Breaker.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735979</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="57797" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強行突破</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Breaking Through Enemy Lines</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoukoutoppa</title>
<summary>Honoka, in her PSP, and Blue Breaker split up from the group and carefully make their way to where Rona Fauna awaits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735981</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="57798" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死線を越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing Down Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shisen o Koete</title>
<summary>The Tank Killer, a specialized anti-tank chopper, appears before Iks, Paife and Bogie! In the meantime, Honoka and Blue Breaker investigate the inside of the facility...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735983</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="62390" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かぬ思い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emotions That Fall Short</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokanu Omoi</title>
<summary>Having narrowly managed to win against Rona Fauna`s combat model, a severely injured Paife returns to the tank and entrusts Iks to the rest. Meanwhile, Honoka discovers Rona`s body preserved in a vessel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735985</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="62391" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">還らざる魂の蜃気楼(ミラージュ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mirage of a Soul Never to Return</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaerazaru Tamashii no Mirage</title>
<summary>Deep inside the facility, Honoka finally confronts Rona Fauna. Rona tells Honoka that she`s killed Joganki and challenges her to a fight.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735987</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="62392" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鋼の谷へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Steel Gorge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hagane no Tani e</title>
<summary>After saying goodbye to Iks, Honoka visits Joey and discovers he`s been barred from working because he infringed upon the Technos Taboo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735989</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="62393" update="2017-05-11">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これから始まる物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Story That Begins Here</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore kara Hajimaru Monogatari</title>
<summary>Honoka meets up with Iks on her way to the Steel Gorge. When they arrive, they discover a great army of The Third`s units, led by Joganki, are waiting for them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735991</identifier>
<identifier>the-third-the-girl-with-the-blue-eye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131874" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Toyoguchi Megumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131875" update="2011-07-13">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Namikawa Daisuke</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131876" update="2011-07-13">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">About Millie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131877" update="2011-07-13">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">About Joganki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131878" update="2011-07-13">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">About Iks</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131879" update="2012-06-16">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">About Honoka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131880" update="2011-07-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">About Bogie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131881" update="2011-07-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131882" update="2011-07-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131883" update="2011-07-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
