<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="412" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2001-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Z.O.E Dolores,i</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ゾーン オブ エンダーズ ドロレス・アイ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">dolores</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">zoed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">zoe tv</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Zone of the Enders: Dolores</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="408" type="Prequel">Z.O.E. 2167 Idolo</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2858" approval="3" total="3">Solty Rei</anime>
<anime id="23" approval="2" total="9">Cowboy Bebop</anime>
<anime id="171" approval="2" total="3">Seihou Bukyou Outlaw Star</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2"/>
<url>http://www.vap.co.jp/zoe/tv/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="4333" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Shin</name>
<name id="1546" type="Character Design">Horii Kumi</name>
<name id="11110" type="Main Character Design">Hirayama Madoka</name>
<name id="5502" type="Direction">Watanabe Tetsuya</name>
<name id="2302" type="Music">Nanase Hikaru</name>
<name id="47286" type="Original Work">KCE Japan</name>
</creators>
<description>49-year-old http://anidb.net/ch16506 [James Lynx] was an officer (LEV pilot) in the United Nations global arm. One day he received notification that his http://anidb.net/ch16510 [wife] - a Martian scientist - was killed during a lab experiment.
Hateful and resenting him for letting her go, his children blamed him and cast him aside. Depressed and in despair, James quit the military and took up a job as a transporter between Earth and Mars. He had a slight hope his wife was still alive, so to find her he wanted to be out there. After a few years had mostly given up all hope and turned to drinking, until one day he receives an orbital frame by the name of Dolores, sent by his dead wife. With this, he began to hope he might find her and set off on a wild adventure to find the truth and reunite his family.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="805">5.87</permanent>
<temporary count="812">7.20</temporary>
<review count="2">6.91</review>
</ratings>
<picture>133568.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1249</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>318</identifier>
<identifier>txqpeo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=99</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Z.O.E._Dolores,i</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Z.O.E_Dolores,_i</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1150</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234290</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4548</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2378" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>hard-working</name>
<description>Describes someone, who is constantly, regularly, or habitually active or occupied.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2765" parentid="2660" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Mars</name>
<description>Mars is the fourth planet from the Sun and the second-smallest planet in the Solar System after Mercury. In English, Mars carries a name of the Roman god of war, and is often referred to as the "Red Planet" because the reddish iron oxide prevalent on its surface gives it a reddish appearance that is distinctive among the astronomical bodies visible to the naked eye. Mars is a terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere, having surface features reminiscent both of the impact craters of the Moon and the valleys, deserts, and polar ice caps of Earth.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214389.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2802" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-14">
<name>action game</name>
<description>Any game where reflexes are the key to the gameplay, violence is optional.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3529" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>space elevator</name>
<description>A needle-like structure placed on the equator of a planet connecting the surface with a low planetary orbit in about 200-300km height (it may even reach out into a geostationary orbit). Very efficient way to move mass "out of" a planet`s gravity well — much more efficient than e.g. chemical rockets.
Alas it is not yet possible to build a space elevator, because all know materials would be crushed under their own weight. There is a faint hope that carbon-based nano-tubes may be a usable material in the future though.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16502" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<name>Axel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45882.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10152" picture="37480.jpg">Tetsuno Masatoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16503" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<name>Baan Dorlfoum</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high-ranking WIRED officer, and a racist who thinks Martians (Enders) "stink, shouldn`t exist." He chases the fugitive Links family far and wide, always addressing James Links as "John Carter". Though he primarily serves as comedic relief for the series, he is quite ruthless and probably insane.</description>
<picture>45883.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2244" picture="52187.jpg">Nagashima Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16504" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Cindy Fiorentino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An Earthling journalist reporting about poor conditions in Mars, she fancies herself a courageous reporter who will stop at nothing to get "exciting" news.</description>
<picture>45884.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4754" picture="180151.jpg">Ochiai Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16505" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="3">8.76</rating>
<name>Dolores</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Orbital Frame Dolores` A.I. Unlike ADA (Jehuty`s AI), who was designed as an efficient combat assistant, she is apparently designed to act like well-behaved child. Her programming recognizes James as her "Uncle", and she admires him and his value. James, though a little awkward at first, finally accepts her and treats her like his own children. Among her few memories is a lullaby only known by the Links family- this memory is what drives James to renew the search for his wife.</description>
<picture>45885.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16506" type="main character in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="4">10.00</rating>
<name>James Links</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A misfortuned space-trucker who gets his hands on something that he does not really want, but which is intensely desired by nearly everyone else: the Orbital Frame called Dolores. He`s rather naïve and blunt when dealing with his family, although he`s very dedicated to them, valiantly trying to uphold "family values." A UNSF veteran, his piloting and battle skills are remarkable. He is also remarkably resourceful. He is married to a martian, Rachel Links, but was separated from her when she left to work on Mars. He does not believe there are differences between Martians and Earthlings, unlike most UNSF officers shown in ZOE universe.</description>
<picture>45886.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16507" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-09">
<name>Naphth Pleminger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A businessman, he uses his appearance as cover to hide his secret identity as BAHRAM military leader. He has reasons for hating the UNSF.

In truth, Napth is in fact Radium Lavans, the pilot of the first Orbital frame, and the fiancée of Dolores Hayes. After the Deimos incident, he was resurrected and rebuilt into a cyborg by BAHRAM.</description>
<picture>45887.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16508" type="main character in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Noel Links</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>James`s daughter, she works as a construction worker on earth. Though she sometimes cannot understand her father`s antics, she is more accepting of him than her brother is. She is dependable and mechanically skillful.</description>
<picture>45889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4436" picture="244738.jpg">Hidaka Narumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16509" type="main character in" update="2010-04-07">
<name>Leon Links</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>James`s son, he works as programmer for a large firm before the events of the series. He despises his father because of problems he causes, and especially for leaving his mother. He is somewhat cowardly and less self-assured than his sister.</description>
<picture>45888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16510" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Rachel Stewart Links</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>James`s wife, reportedly dead, and chief designer of Idolo, Dolores/Isis, and Hathor. Though she loved James, her dedication to her countrymen on Mars caused her to leave him. She believed that her skills and knowledge could help Mars to gain independence from Earth`s oppression. A little naïve at times, not unlike her husband.</description>
<picture>45891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16511" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="2">2.80</rating>
<name>Rebecca Hunter</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young BAHRAM pilot (fifteen years old) who is captured by James during their fight on Mars. She is a rather intense person, although somewhat naïve and inexperienced with life in general. As she has been indoctrinated to consider every Earthling as enemy, she feels uneasiness that James actually treats her kindly. Although a skilled pilot, her lack of experience is apparent when fighting James. She loves her adopted father/ commander Napth Pleminger very much, and accepts everything he says as truth.</description>
<picture>45892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16795" picture="170424.jpg">Nakanishi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16512" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<name>Rully</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7068" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16513" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<name>Sameggi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A WIRED officer, and Baan`s assistant. Though he admires his superior to some extent, Baan`s racist views and his increasingly alarming antics force him to reconsider.</description>
<picture>45894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16541" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-08">
<name>Gazeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16542" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-08">
<name>Isaac Barrett</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3383" picture="24325.jpg">Oobayashi Ryuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16543" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-08">
<name>Mitchum Cervantes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3321" picture="228645.jpg">Tsujimura Mahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16544" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-08">
<name>Nikolai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16545" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-08">
<name>Norman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16546" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-08">
<name>Raia Starfield</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2405" picture="23217.jpg">Shioya Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16547" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-08">
<name>Rutger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20" picture="16599.jpg">Kitagawa Katsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16548" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-08">
<name>Yan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2489" picture="22426.jpg">Suzuki Taimei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16549" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-08">
<name>Zack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4185" picture="224827.jpg">Ushiyama Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16552" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-08">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Dolores Hayes</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Assistant to Dr. Rachel Links and girlfriend to Radium.</description>
<picture>45953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16555" type="appears in" update="2010-04-08">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Viola Gyunee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Radium is her only and closest friend, which she hides a love for. Her only devotion is the military as she lost everything to the UNSF.</description>
<picture>45956.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="88041" type="appears in" update="2017-03-04">
<name>Pete</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199147.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="88042" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-04">
<name>Linda Roland</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88043" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-04">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Melinda Gargoyle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21545" picture="55611.jpg">Yanaga Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88044" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-04">
<name>Basilico Basilisk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88054" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-04">
<name>Dantes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3064" picture="24692.jpg">Asou Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88055" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-05">
<name>Mary</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199189.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="88056" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-05">
<name>Romero Dickson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3251" picture="24230.jpg">Hara Yasuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88057" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-05">
<name>Pao Ron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88537" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-27">
<name>Joey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88723" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-08">
<name>Sean Barret</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4910" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロスト・イン・スペース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lost in Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lost in Space</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4911" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">仁義の墓場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Grave of Humanity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jingi no Hakaba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4912" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンタッチャブル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Untouchable</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Untouchable</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4913" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">GET AWAY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Away</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Get Away</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4914" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死への逃避行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Runaway Trip to Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi e no Touhikou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4915" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファイナル・カウントダウン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Countdown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Final Countdown</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4916" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レオンの選択</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Leon`s Choice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Leon no Sentaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4917" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死刑台のエレベーター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Elevator of Capital Punishment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikei Dai no Elevator</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4918" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジェイムズの災難</title>
<title xml:lang="en">James` Misfortune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">James no Sainan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7593" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂の器</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Container for Sand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suna no Utsuwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11448" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイ・ハード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Die Hard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Die Hard</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11449" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイト・ロープ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tightrope</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tightrope</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11450" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い砂漠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Desert</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Sabaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11451" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トータル・リコール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Total Recall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Total Recall</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11452" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レベッカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebecca</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rebecca</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12803" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならマーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye Mars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Mars</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12804" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">北北西に進路を取れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Set Course for North, North West</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kita Hokusei ni Shinro o Tore</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12805" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バニシング・ポイント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vanishing Point</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Vanishing Point</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12806" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大いなる幻影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Massive Illusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooi Naru Genei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12807" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12808" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真昼の決斗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown at Noon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahiru no Ketsu to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12809" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会の時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Time of Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai no Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12810" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘆きの天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sorrowing Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nageki no Tenshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12811" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">動乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Upheaval</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Douran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12812" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">家族ゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Family Game</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazoku Game</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12813" update="2006-08-09">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">武器よさらば</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell to Arms</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Buki yo Saraba</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
