<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4120" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-01-22</startdate>
<enddate>2006-04-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gin`yuu Mokushiroku Meine Liebe Wieder</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Wandering Revelations Meine Liebe Wieder</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Моя Любов: Нови откровения 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">ML2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Meine Liebe 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Meine Liebe Wieder</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">吟游默示录II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mlw</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">吟遊黙示録 マイネリーベ wieder(ウィーダ)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2599" type="Prequel">Gin`yuu Mokushiroku Meine Liebe</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="749" type="Animation Work">Bee Train</name>
<name id="2459" type="Character Design">Shiba Minako</name>
<name id="2457" type="Character Design">Yamashita Yoshimitsu</name>
<name id="4304" type="Series Composition">Omode Akemi</name>
<name id="13267" type="Music">Minobe Yutaka</name>
<name id="12348" type="Direction">Kawatsura Shin`ya</name>
</creators>
<description>The Strahl candidates are enjoying a brief holdiay in their various homes. However, many surprises await them when they finally come back to their elite boarding school: Rosenstolz Academy. There is a new headmaster, and his policies are not necessarily to the advantage of the main characters.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="288">4.49</permanent>
<temporary count="292">6.75</temporary>
<review count="1">8.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10333.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6509</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>771</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3572</identifier>
<identifier>fkxfrv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Meine_Liebe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>吟遊黙示録マイネリーベwieder</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324163</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7892</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3996</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="14757" type="main character in" update="2010-02-04">
<name>Eduard Markgraf von Sekt Nahe Braunschweig</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eduard is nicknamed "Ed" by most of the people around him. His title, Markgraf means Marquis and is pretty low. His father had an illegal affair with a woman of a lower rank, resulting in Ed and his little sister Elaine. After his mother died, his father took him into his house. However, he was already married with three girls, all of whom older then Ed. Henriette Braunschweig, Ed`s step-mother, hated Ed because she wasn`t able to give birth to a male heir to the Braunschweig family assets. She even told her daughters not to speak with their two step-siblings. It became so bad that Ed`s father had Elaine removed from the house, and her whereabouts are unknown. Ed is still burdened by this because he promised his sister he would protect her, and was unable to fulfill that promise.
Ed`s appearance is unlike the other nobles in the series. He goes with his neck uncovered, he is more tanned then the others and has an earring. Ed is very cheerful and likes to take things easy. He is also the comic relief throughout the series, with his attempts at meditation and kendo. He makes friends easily and wears his heart on his sleeve, though he doesn`t care what other people think about him. He is a good swordsman but is not above using his fists in a fight, another thing that distinguishes him from the other nobles.
Source: Wikipedia and Meine Liebe Manga</description>
<picture>42473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14758" type="main character in" update="2010-02-04">
<name>Orpherus Furst von Marmelade Nahe Gorz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Orpherus is nicknamed "Orphe" by most of the people around him. He`s title Fürst is the highest of all characters and means a prince, but neither the anime nor the manga shows that he is really royalty and that`s because when it comes to royal and noble ranks in Germany the highest is Emperor (Kaiser). Despite all that, little is known about his house or his parents. All that is known is that they have a butler and that Orphe had a sister, named Robertine, who died when he was 15. Orphe was devastated after her death, and has the habit of caressing the pendant Robertine`s fiancé gave her and which Orphe took from the rubble of the explosion site. He blames himself for not accompanying her to buy the wedding dress, despite the fact that she insisted on going alone.
Orphe is a very idealistic person. Isaac reprimands him on this, saying that he`s unconnected to today`s society and that words alone would not stifle the sparks of war. According to his way of thinking it can be said that he`s also a idealist. He likes politics and holds women in higher regards then most of the men in his time. He`s prone to winning and strives to excel in everything he does. He decided to become a Strahl candidate after meeting the king as a boy.
Source: Wikipedia and Meine Liebe Manga</description>
<picture>42472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14759" type="main character in" update="2010-02-04">
<name>Ludwig Herzog von Mohn Nahe Liechtenstein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ludwig is often nicknamed as "Lui" by the people around him, though most still refer to him as Ludwig because they are afraid of him and respect him. His title Herzog is the second highest title among the nobles, and means Duke. His father is a Duke as well, but his mother is the king`s sister, making the king of Kuchen his uncle. His other uncle on his mother`s side is the king`s (rebellious) younger brother, Helbert. His uncle on his father`s side is Camus` father, making the two of them cousins. It is known that he has two housekeepers, Augusta and Clemence, a younger sister and a younger brother. Also, he is left-handed.
Lui appears cold-hearted most of the time. He is very arrogant and yet he knows what is expected of him by his rank and position in the world of those times, and accepts it with cold indifference. He often leaves his friend shocked at his words when he voices his thoughts. However, Lui is a good judge of character and seems to know what to say to help the people he is fond of solve problems on their own. He likes challenges, as long as they are fair towards both ends. Lui claims he is not like the others, insinuating that he is cold hearted and calculated, and compares himself to Orphe by saying that he can not grasp an opportunity and fight for it like Orphe does. Isaac reprimands Lui for his way of thinking, claiming that it was too dangerous.
Source: Wikipedia and Meine Liebe Manga</description>
<picture>42475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="46692" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">序曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prelude</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jokyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46921" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">革命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakumei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46946" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Victor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shousha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46960" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">焦燥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Impatience</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shousou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46993" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冷雨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cold Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reiu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47141" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakuen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47342" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">起点</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starting Point</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiten</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48003" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陽光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunshine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48004" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃亡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toubou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48547" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">錯綜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intricacy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakusou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48672" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">An`ei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49154" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対峙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confontration</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49155" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">希望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kibou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
