<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4121" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-07-10</startdate>
<enddate>2006-12-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">NHK ni Youkoso!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Welcome to the NHK</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Bienvenue à la NHK</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Benvenuti alla NHK!</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Welcome to the NHK</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">¡Bienvenidos a NHK!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Добро пожаловать в NHK!</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Witaj w NHK!</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="synonym">Välkommen till NHK!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">أهلاً و سهلاً بكم في الأن أتش كيه</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Bem-vindo à NHK!</title>
<title xml:lang="ca" type="synonym">Benvinguts a NHK!</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="synonym">Kαλωσήρθατε στο NHK</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">ยัยตัวร้ายกับนายโหลยโท่ย</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">NHK`ya Hoşgeldiniz!</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Ласкаво просимо до NHK!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">歡迎加入NHK!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">欢迎来到NHK!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">nhk</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">NHKにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Welcome to the N.H.K</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Welcome to the N.H.K</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Welcome to the N-H-K</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">NHK에 어서오세요!</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">สมาคมคนหนีโลก</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">!به ان اچ کی خوش آمدید</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1783" approval="79" total="141">Genshiken</anime>
<anime id="9582" approval="25" total="46">Watashi ga Motenai no wa Dou Kangaete mo Omaera ga Warui!</anime>
<anime id="7243" approval="13" total="26">Yojouhan Shinwa Taikei</anime>
<anime id="7525" approval="9" total="29">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai</anime>
<anime id="13345" approval="6" total="13">Netojuu no Susume</anime>
<anime id="11074" approval="5" total="11">Relife</anime>
<anime id="8883" approval="3" total="13">Chuunibyou demo Koi ga Shitai!</anime>
<anime id="8564" approval="1" total="15">Inu x Boku Secret Service</anime>
<anime id="13581" approval="1" total="6">3D Kanojo: Real Girl</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="74">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="547997">Funny, sad, weird, and a great soundtrack.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="66502">Very nice anime. To understand a kikomori.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="265516">This anime is a great anime it covers all the aspects of a usual conspiracy that goes on with new and old generations. THe conspiracies that keep us from opening up to the new societies of the world.((O_^))</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="272616">really funny anime, only the end sucked a bit, but overal a very good one&lt;br /&gt;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372636">This is probably the best and most intelligent anime I`ve seen. And the one with most heart. ANYONE who desires a little more than just gore and violence from an anime should give it a try - `cause this is a 10 pointer.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="389161">The character developments are deep; worthy of my mention. I do wish of a better ending... Otherwise, a very packed and intricate storyline that I`ve enjoyed (and learn what it is to be a hikky).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="359130">Interesting anime about a hikikomori and it deals with many elements many animes today don`t talk about.  Very good series!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="83424">Good overall. Not as much dementia as I was expecting. Lots of filler in the middle (could have been a 13 episode series without loosing much. Yes, I know its based on a manga and a novel).
Also, can be fairly depressing if you life is somewhat less than you dreamed it would be.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="505082">If you can make it past a sometimes gringeworthy amount of otaku-fandom, a true masterpiece about the importance of self-esteem unfolds.
A small cast of really fleshed out characters, a well chosen story and good production values make for an overall very enjoyable and meaningfull experience.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="135091">great anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="163070">Amazing series. It`s dark, yet funny and it`s got something almost any type of geek can relate to. There`s an episode about MMOs, one about hentai games, there`s even one about a suicide cult. It was a totally fresh experience. I`ve never watched anything quite like it before.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="808614">https://twitter.com/Timofey_ikki/status/1161271054305771521</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="312729">Sorting my favourites list I realised I hadn`t recommended this masterpiece! This anime takes you on such an amazing journey, it`s just incredible and completely one of a kind. One of the few series that I have watched more than twice - great stuff, great comedy (think main character from steins gate) although not a drugs heavy as LN it`s an absolute must see!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="456964">This anime is just perfect
And who like `hikikomori` people MUST SEE
It will gives you very impression of life
Fantastic work of Gonzo.
Reminding the LIFE`s meaning.
If you like watching anime, YOU JUST MUST SEE IT</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="527728">Incredible anime for all fans. Blends together both humour and sadness to make an incredible final product you don`t want to miss.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="296782">probably all male otakus can be able to relate to this anime! (well I`m not really sure bout the girls)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="590343">Fantastic show. The characters are so effed up, but lovable and relatable. Really fantastic drama, great comedy.

A couple weaker arcs, but as a whole this is a must-see show. It`s dark, it`s light, it`s sad, it`s happy. The show is literally just as schizophrenic and psychopathic as the lead characters themselves. 

This is one hell of a story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="376567">Though this series has already aged, it`s message has just grown stronger. I recommend you to enjoy the show and think about all those who seriously believe in the NHK.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="497799">One of the 1st few Animes I watched years ago. It was kinda creepy and weird because it paints a picture of hardcore gamers whom never leave their homes. It`s incredibly realistic, and, with an Excellent Storyline ~ Paints Gamers a realistic image of their hard core lives and what their future will be like. I LOVE NHK! ^_^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="366008">One of the best series out there, talking about how to deal with our lives and how to change it. Very touching. A must see for anyone who watches anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="459074">This anime honestly really surprised me. I started out watching this with few expectations and was even more disappointed with the first couple episodes, but soon i was shown a great deal of emotion, romance, grief, joy and sorrow, all things i never would have expected from this anime. I really encourage people to watch this, and continue watching it, even if the first episodes aren`t to your liking.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="97733">Definitely a must see for anyone who likes anime, very well made, can`t see how anyone can not enjoy this show!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="76759">Do I even have to recommend this? If you haven`t watched it yet, you`re a failure as a human.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="422137">Gives you an idea of what`s important in life with great sense of humour and characters that have something to say,everyone with his/her own problems and past.A food for thought series.Do NOT miss it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="498834">This is a masterpiece but not for everyone if you can somewhat relate to the characters then I suggest it but if you think life is sunshine and rainbows then this is not for you</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="485609">for NEET only.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="503773">words cant do this anime justice!
all i can say is watch it, you will not regret it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="319919">One of the best out there, IT critizies a major problem nowdays. Must see by every Anime fan and non</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="239259">Quote-
by aelfwyne on2012-09-13 08:05
Do I even have to recommend this? If you haven`t watched it yet, you`re a failure as a human.
-----
The above said it all</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="224094">It can be kinda rocky at times, but overall it`s a great anime; one that is greater than the sum of its parts.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="283662">Hold your breath...you may begin breathing again after you start to watch this series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="232437">Who doesn`t love to watch a person who has gone completly nuts and is a magnificent specimen of how a hikikomori that is a NEET behaves.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="548594">While at first sight it may appear to be just a comedy based around otaku culture, Welcome to the NHK is in reality a much deeper story about facing the challenges of life as an extremely introverted person. Boasting a dense plot and superbly well-written characters, Welcome to the NHK is well worth a watch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kadokawa.co.jp/hikky/</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="3661" type="Series Composition">Nishizono Satoru</name>
<name id="2932" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shitaya Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="4163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoshida Takahiko</name>
<name id="9201" type="Original Work">Takimoto Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="5004" type="Music">Pearl Kyoudai</name>
<name id="4163" type="Character Design">Yoshida Takahiko</name>
<name id="6520" type="Direction">Yamamoto Yuusuke</name>
<name id="7424" type="Original Work">Ooiwa Kenji</name>
<name id="3754" type="Character Design">Ishihama Masashi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a novel by http://anidb.net/cr9201 [Takimoto Tatsuhiko], turned into a manga with illustration by http://anidb.net/cr7424 [Ooiwa Kenji].
http://anidb.net/ch2808 [Satou Tatsuhiro], a 22-year-old socially withdrawn loner, barricades himself in his apartment, subsiding on a meagre allowance sent by his parents, only venturing to the outside world to buy food under cover of darkness. One day, afraid he might miss the utility person, he opens the door to find a cute, mysterious girl, accompanying an elderly religious solicitor.
Through what seems to be a chain of coincidences, the girl, http://anidb.net/ch2809 [Nakahara Misaki], enters Tatsuhiro`s life, and promises him that she will cure him of his anti-social condition, provided that he follows the rules that she sets out for him.
This takes Tatsuhiro from a desperate attempt at creating a galge computer game, to unwittingly joining a suicide cult, to participating in a pyramid scheme, to immersing himself in a MMORPG, along the way touching upon everything between http://anidb.net/t876 [hikikomori] and otaku culture, existentialism, solipsism, theology, suicide, sacrifice and love.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9920">8.47</permanent>
<temporary count="10073">8.49</temporary>
<review count="17">7.70</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221069.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6357</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1210</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3583</identifier>
<identifier>iefcng</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/nhkniyoukoso/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kadokawa.co.jp/hikky/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Welcome_to_the_N.H.K.</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>NHKにようこそ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>916</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>325566</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8267</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1240</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>NHK에_어서_오세요!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>歡迎加入NHK！</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="178" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-28">
<name>insane</name>
<description>Insanity, craziness, or madness is a spectrum of behaviors characterized by certain abnormal mental or behavioral patterns. Insanity may manifest as violations of societal norms, including a person becoming a danger to themselves or others, though not all such acts are considered insanity; likewise, not all acts showing indifference toward societal norms are acts of insanity.
In modern usage, insanity is most commonly encountered as an informal unscientific term denoting mental instability, or in the narrow legal context of the insanity defense.
A more informal use of the term insanity is to denote something or someone considered highly unique, passionate or extreme, including in a positive sense. The term may also be used as an attempt to discredit or criticise particular ideas, beliefs, principles, desires, personal feelings, attitudes, or their proponents, such as in politics and religion.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3316" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>despair</name>
<description>Involves characters that may be lost in negatively emotional atmospheres created through feelings of hopelessness and suffering.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3328" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>melancholic</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4640" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-14">
<name>social outcast</name>
<description>Someone who has been rejected or excluded from the majority, or all of the social groups in an area (school, work, etc.). A person that does not fit in society.
They typically look slightly high or depressed and they are usually alone most the time. Some are alone because they are too snobbish and see themselves above everyone else. Others are alone because they want to be. 
They are usually the victims of every negative stereotype and rumour. Some might even be called “freaks”.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4851" parentid="4340" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>group suicide</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5640" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-16">
<name>video game development</name>
<description>Part of the anime`s story relates to creating video games.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2808" type="main character in" update="2016-11-09">
<rating votes="139">8.49</rating>
<name>Satou Tatsuhiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The story`s protagonist, at twenty-two-years-old, he has entered his third year of being a hikikomori and is a NEET. One to have psychotic thoughts, he believes that his unemployment and dropout are the works of NHK`s conspiracy. He lives in his rented apartment, but depends on his parents for money. Under the influence of his neighbor, Kaoru Yamazaki, he has become a lolicon otaku, and helps Yamazaki on the script of their adult game. [Spoiler]However, near the end of the series when Misaki is about to commit suicide he confesses she is important for him, trying to stop her from commiting suicide. It is assumed at the end of the anime that he and Misaki will support each other until Sato saves enough money, Misaki finishes high school, and they both have finished college.[/Spoiler]
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>60738.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1510" picture="49914.jpg">Koizumi Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2809" type="main character in" update="2015-11-10">
<rating votes="162">8.80</rating>
<name>Nakahara Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious girl who claims to be a volunteer from a "charity project" to help hikikomori like Tatsuhiro. She has the tendency to lie and hides facts such as the fact that she dropped out of high school, but she does not mean any harm. She tells Tatsuhiro whatever it takes to make him pay attention to her. She seems to have a deep attachment to Tatsuhiro, and often shows symptoms suggesting she has a borderline personality disorder. She makes a contract with Tatsuhiro in order to believe that she is needed by somebody and therefore not an unwanted person who only makes others around her unhappy. Her biological father died when she was very young and her mother died by falling off the cape in her hometown. It is never revealed if the cause of death was suicide or if the wind had knocked her off. After her mother`s death, she was forced to live with her abusive stepfather who constantly beat her. [Spoiler]Due to this experience, when Tatsuhiro is about to hit her following the events at the island, she flinches by instinct. She loves Sato and tries to make it seem like he needs her more but in reality she is even more lonely than him to the point where she attempts to commit suicide after Sato refuses her feelings in a second contract she makes. She is seen at the end of the anime getting help from Sato to finish her high school degree, so that she and Sato can go and finish college in order to start their life (relationship) officially together.[/Spoiler] Misaki`s personality greatly differs between the manga and the anime, in the manga she appears more sarcastic and doesn`t hesitate to reprimand Tatsuhiro while in the anime, she has an introverted personality.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>25750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2810" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="57">7.05</rating>
<name>Yamazaki Kaoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuhiro`s former kouhai (Junior) in high school, who is an otaku. Tatsuhiro once stood up for him when he was still in middle school being beat up by some bullies, since then, he respected him greatly and decided to join the literature club with him when he went into high school. He is currently Tatsuhiro`s neighbor and a college student aspiring to be a game creator. He made Tatsuhiro join his doujin soft eroge project, and was also responsible for turning Tatsuhiro into an otaku. His family owns a sizable farm in Hokkaidou. [Spoiler]Later, he is forced to return to the farm due to his father`s sickness; at that point, realizing he has no hope of continuing any aspect of his life in Tokyo, he drives away his crush, Nanako. In the end of the story, he is living happily at his parent`s farm and also currently dating a girl who looks exactly like Nanako whom he hopes to marry in the future.[/Spoiler]</description>
<picture>26755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2811" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="34">5.48</rating>
<name>Kashiwa Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuhiro`s senpai in high school, now a public servant. Due to stress, Hitomi develops a dependence on drugs. Hitomi met Tatsuhiro when she persuaded him to join the Literature Club, though most of the time they only ever played card games. She has always been fascinated by the concept of conspiracy theories and is one of the reasons Tatsuhiro suspects the conspiracy against himself by the N.H.K. [Spoiler]Also, it is also noted in the anime that she had sex with Tatsuhiro during the last day of school before she graduated because Tatsuhiro kept her company in literature club for her last two years of high school. She attempts a suicide through an internet suicide pact called the Offline Meeting Notice (an offline meeting is a slightly slang term for a meeting of people who have met on the Internet, not really having much to do as a pun for "shutting one`s life off like a computer"). However, she changes her mind after her boyfriend proposes to her. She gets married and has a healthy kid, though before her marriage on new years she asks Tatsuhiro if he wants to have an illicit affair with her and have sex in a love hotel they were standing in front of, but Tatsuhiro reminds her that since she`s happy she should have a good life.[/Spoiler] Her role in the novel is minor, and she is not given a name.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>26756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2812" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="28">2.66</rating>
<name>Kobayashi Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuhiro`s classmate in high school, was the class representative back then. They meet frequently in manga, but none of them realizes the existence of each other until later. After her father died, she had to work in order to support herself and her brother, who is also a hikikomori, though ended up entangled in a shady pyramid scheme. During school, she had a very uptight personality which Tatsuhiro commented about himself to her face. After high school, she retains much of this personality, though has also become somewhat manipulative in order to survive.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>26757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7776" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="12">5.09</rating>
<name>Pururin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Purin is the main character of a famous anime in the world of NHK ni Youkoso!. She is a Magical Girl who can transform in some objects, like a pudding or a little barrel. This character is important into NHK ni Youkoso because Yamazaki is in love with Purin, despite she is only a 2-D cartoon.</description>
<picture>26759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7777" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="13">5.07</rating>
<name>NHK Agents</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The make-believe characters working in the NHK (Nihon Hikkikomori Kyokai) in Satou Tatushiro`s fantasy during his anti-social years. In Satou`s imagination, this group of blue goblins with pink sleeping caps are part of a conspiracy that tries to ruin his life.</description>
<picture>26761.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7778" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="9">4.97</rating>
<name>Midorikawa Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7779" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="7">4.26</rating>
<name>Satou Shizue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3947" picture="25762.jpg">Shou Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="51921" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="54">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロジェクトにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Project!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">01 - Welcome to the project</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Project ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Sato’s totally convinced that he’s been turned into a recluse through the media manipulation of the N-H-K. When mysterious Misaki enters his world, she claims she can help him tame his inner-demons.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="51925" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="40">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリエイターにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Creator!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">02 - Welcome to the creator</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Creator ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Even as Misaki reaches out to help him, Sato tries to convince her that he’s got his life in order. But after he claims to be working as a video game creator, Sato’s neighbor takes steps to turn his lies into truth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="51926" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="35">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美少女にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Beautiful Girls!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">03 - Welcome to the beautiful girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bishoujo ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Instead of working to develop the game, Sato’s busy doing research for the project. Unfortunately for Kaoru, all that means is watching his partner spend hours playing sexy games and looking at porn.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="51927" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="36">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新世界にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the New World!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">04 - Welcome to the new world!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsekai ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Kaoru has succeeded in turning Sato into a total otaku, but he hasn’t succeeded in inspiring him to work. A trip to Akihabara might remedy the situation - if they can stay out of the maid cafes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="51928" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="35">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カウンセリングにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Counseling!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">05 - Welcome to the Counselling!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Counseling ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Misaki finally gets what she wants when Sato confesses the truth of his reclusive excuse for a life. The contract is signed and the counseling begins - and Sato immediately makes the session awkward.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="56157" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="33">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クラスルームにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Classroom!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">06 - Welcome to the Classroom!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Classroom ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Even though a raging panic attack is practically guaranteed, Sato journeys out into the world to investigate rumors that Kaoru might have a cute girlfriend at school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="56158" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="31">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モラトリアムにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Moratorium!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">07 - Welcome to the Moratorium!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moratorium ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Sato’s mom is about to invade his space. Fearing what she’ll think when she sees his reclusive lifestyle,  Sato spins a web of lies in which Kaoru and Misaki find themselves tangled.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="56159" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="32">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">中華街にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to China Town!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">08 - Welcome to the Chinatown!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chuukagai ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Sato overhears his mother telling Misaki that she knows the truth behind her son’s lifestyle. But rather than clear the air, all three continue the ruse, allowing for some awkward moments.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="61033" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="32">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の日にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to a Summer Day!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">09 - Welcome to the summer days!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Hi ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Kaoru gets rejected when he asks a girl out, and Sato’s feeling pained by his changing feelings for Misaki. Maybe showcasing their game at the upcoming con will distract them from their girl troubles.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="62124" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="30">8.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダークサイドにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Dark Side!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">10 - Welcome to the dark side!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dark Side ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Sato and Kaoru begin tailing Misaki after they grow more and more suspicious of the mysterious girl’s true motivation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="62125" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="30">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陰謀にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Conspiracy!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">11 - Welcome to the conspiracy!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inbou ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>With the game finished and ready to go, Sato and Kaoru gear up for their trip to the con. Unfortunately, they find their plans in jeopardy after a call from Hitomi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="62398" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="31">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オフ会にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the "Off" Meeting!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">12 - Welcome to the offline meeting!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Off-kai ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Sato joins Hitomi’s internet group for a real world trip to a sandy island, but the group’s dark vibes have him thinking that fun in the sun is the last thing on anyone’s mind.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="63187" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="40">9.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天国にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Paradise!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">13 - Welcome to Heaven!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tengoku ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Sato’s gotten himself wrapped up in a suicide pact! If his friends can’t figure out what’s really happening and make it to the island, Hitomi’s internet group will be logging out for good.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="63188" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="31">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">現実[リアル]にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Reality!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">14 - Welcome to the reality!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Real ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>After the island, the members of the group are given a trip to a hot springs resort where each will face loved ones eager to prove life is worth living. Can Misaki do the same for Sato?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="64066" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="30">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファンタジーにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Fantasy!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">15 - Welcome to the fantasy!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fantasy ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Sato’s need for cash drives him to join a MMORPG. His plan: sell virtual goods for real world money. As his time in-game begins to interfere with his day to day life, he meets and forms a party with Mia.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="64067" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="32">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲームオーバーにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Game Over!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">16 - Welcome to the game over!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Game Over ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Sato’s back to his reclusive ways, but just as Misaki and Kaoru decide to intervene, the world of online fantasy comes  crashing down - it turns out Mia is actually someone Sato knows!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="64068" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="31">3.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はぴねすにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Happiness!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">17 - Welcome to the happiness!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Happiness ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Megumi vows she can help Sato overcome his antisocial ways, but when she takes him to a run-down building where he finds only a sales pitch, Sato has to figure out what the girl’s real motives are.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="64069" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="32">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノーフューチャーにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to No Future!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">18 - Welcome to no future!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">No Future ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Sato sees that Megumi has swindled him, and when he confronts her, she somehow manages to trick him and his friends again! When they knock on her door to end the mess once and for all, Sato’s worlds collide!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="65067" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="34">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青い鳥にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Blue Bird!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">19 - Welcome to the bluebird!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Tori ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>With Megumi locked up, her little brother’s forced to fend for himself. When he lands a new job, Megumi starts seeing that she might need to rethink her life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="65068" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="27">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冬の日にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Winter Days!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">20 - Welcome to Winter Days!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuyu no Hi ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>With Kaoru leaving Tokyo soon to return to his life on the farm, he and Sato have to step it up if the game is to be completed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="65376" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リセットにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Reset!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">21- Welcome to a reset!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reset ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Sato is left to his usual ways  just in time for Misaki to test his progress on a New Year’s Eve outing. While out on the town, Sato loses Misaki - and finds Hitomi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="65377" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="29">8.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神様にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the God!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">22 - Welcome to God!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamisama ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>Finally reunited on New Year’s Eve, tension grows between Misaki and Sato after he lies about spending time with Hitomi - and the tension grows even more when the lies continue at their next session.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="65434" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="32">8.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">岬にようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Misaki!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">23 - Welcome to Misaki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misaki ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>After she tests him with a macabre quiz, Misaki tells Sato their plans for the next day: the graduation exam. No matter the outcome, their relationship is about to change.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="65435" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="40">8.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">N・H・Kにようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the N.H.K.!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">24 - Welcome to the N-H-K</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">N.H.K ni Youkoso!</title>
<summary>After desperation drives them to the edge of a cliff, Sato and Misaki find they might have finally killed the parts of themselves that cause so much pain and agree to continue living on their own terms.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="78529" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78530" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78531" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CD Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78533" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Pururin Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78534" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78535" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78536" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78537" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85010" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making Clip 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85011" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making Clip 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85012" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making Clip 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85013" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making Clip 04</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
