<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4151" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-07-15</startdate>
<enddate>2006-07-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Toki o Kakeru Shoujo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-unk" type="synonym">Cô gái đi xuyên thời gian</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Girl Who Cut Time</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Little Girl Who Conquered Time</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">La ragazza che corre nel tempo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Девочка, перепрыгнувшая время</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">الفتاة التي قفزت عبر الزمن</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">A Menina que Corre Através do Tempo</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">A Garota que Salta Através do Tempo</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">הילדה שזינקה מבעד לזמן</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">הילדה שקפצה בזמן</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Mergina, keliavusi laiku</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Mergina, kuri persikėlė laike</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Zamanda Sıçrayan Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="sk" type="synonym">O dievčati, ktoré preskočilo čas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Toki wo Kakeru Shoujo</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Дівчинка, що стрибала крізь час</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">穿越时空的少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">TGWLTT</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">tokikake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">twks</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">時をかける少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Girl Who Leapt Through Time</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Das Mädchen, das durch die Zeit sprang</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">La traversée du temps</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">La Ragazza che Saltava nel Tempo</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">La chica que saltaba a través del tiempo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Девочка, покорившая время</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">시간을 달리는 소녀</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">O dziewczynie skaczącej przez czas</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">O dívce, která proskočila časem</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">กระโดดจัมพ์ ทะลุข้ามเวลา</title>
<title xml:lang="sl" type="official">Dekle, ki je skočilo skozi čas</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Tüdruk, kes hüppas läbi aja</title>
<title xml:lang="hr" type="official">Putovanje kroz vrijeme</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">跳躍吧! 時空少女</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">跳跃吧! 时空少女</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">La chica que saltaba a través del tiempo</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6249" approval="205" total="283">Summer Wars</anime>
<anime id="336" approval="37" total="56">Mimi o Sumaseba</anime>
<anime id="570" approval="29" total="58">Sennen Joyuu</anime>
<anime id="12605" approval="14" total="16">Uchiage Hanabi, Shita kara Miru ka? Yoko kara Miru ka?</anime>
<anime id="11370" approval="5" total="31">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu</anime>
<anime id="738" approval="5" total="12">Munto</anime>
<anime id="4568" approval="3" total="12">Byousoku 5 Centimeter</anime>
<anime id="4191" approval="3" total="11">Paprika</anime>
<anime id="13174" approval="2" total="9">Mirai no Mirai</anime>
<anime id="12422" approval="1" total="9">Sagrada Reset</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="53">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="179678">Nice captivating story</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="52807">perfect!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="332265">gud</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="159595">nice</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="292539">Fantastic movie. Wish there were more like this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="142606">i love it... wow i want to see more at the end.&lt;br /&gt;beautiful movie..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="344788">Great movie. Great story. Great... well, great everything.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="179096">Cute, Funny, Sad, little Movie&lt;br /&gt;Worth a Watch For any one able to put up with Teen Drama and Romance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="135541">Really nice comedy, very interesting characters with realistic voice acting and interesting personalities. The plot is interesting and entertaining. The soundtrack could have been better, and the ending should have had better drama and better conclusion, instead of a weird one.

All in all, watch it for great characters and comedy, and the cool concept of time traveling.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="270473">Um belo filme, com uma história bem trabalhada e e um trabalho artístico espetacular, a MAD HOUSE sempre faz grandes produções.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="516692">my first favorite anime movie. Plot, setting, characters, songs are perfect.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="386693">Maybe the best anime movie I have ever watched! Awesome story with great animation. And (for me) really impressive and little sad end.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="404463">One of the 5 best anime movies i ever watched, highly recommended for all kinds</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="254003">One of the best anime ever seen.&lt;br /&gt;Recomended to all.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="494966">This is a MUST SEE... trust me, you wont regret it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="599558">As awesome as Wolf children and A letter to momo &amp;lt;3 must see i reapeat a must see film</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="346690">Enjoyable, a few comical scenes, and parts leaving you holding your breath, this movie has it all.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="466317">One of the best animated movies I`ve seen before the end of 2010. I`ve watched it so many times that even the funny part still makes me laugh out loud and the sad parts can make me teary-eyed in an instant. The romance between the two main characters, however subtle and simple, still made a great impact and was definitely the driving force behind the story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="180200">Wow! Really awesome! Great story, nice development, unpredictable up to the end... Beautiful!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="298465">Must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="292763">One of my rare 10!! It really make me cry at the end of the movie. A must watch movie for everyone XD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="176802">i loved this!  i`ve watched it lots of times.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="323986">To me it`s just perfect....</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="120720">I was moved by the story, the pacing was great, and best of all I wanted more at the end.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="354894">This is a beautiful story that captures the essence of summer and of youth.  Anyone who enjoys soft, warm storytelling will enjoy this film.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="304934">This is actually very interesting the story, music, and the background is amazingly done. I am sure that anyone sees this will love.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="296309">This is the best animation movie i have ever seen in my life!! It`s awesome! A beautiful love story! A great movie about love and friendship!! Do not miss this movie!! Definitely a must see!!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kadokawa.co.jp/tokikake/</url>
<creators>
<name id="50" type="Direction">Hosoda Mamoru</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="1389" type="Character Design">Sadamoto Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="8685" type="Work">Maruta Jungo</name>
<name id="6782" type="Music">Yoshida Kiyoshi</name>
<name id="8944" type="Original Work">Tsutsui Yasutaka</name>
</creators>
<description>Life for 17-year-old http://anidb.net/ch2748 [Konno Makoto] is filled with fun days at school and hanging out with her two best friends, http://anidb.net/ch2749 [Chiaki] and http://anidb.net/ch2750 [Kousuke]. But then she finds herself with an ominous ability to leap back in time. A truly strange ability that at first saves her life, but then allows her to not be late at school, to know the answers on any surprise exams and to avoid any troublesome mishaps. It is only when Makoto chooses to use this ability to avoid some of the more personal issues that arise with her friends, that events become both complex and painfully difficult — the simple gift that she began to take for granted suddenly becomes a troublesome burden.
Note: Winner 6th Annual Tokyo Anime Awards (2007) — Anime Movie, and 2006 Winner of Mainichi Award (http://anidb.net/cr5602 [Oofuji Noburou] Award).</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="10687">8.61</permanent>
<temporary count="10793">8.51</temporary>
<review count="12">8.01</review>
</ratings>
<picture>134156.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6733</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2236</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3594</identifier>
<identifier>ralvoq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kadokawa.co.jp/tokikake/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Girl_Who_Leapt_Through_Time_(2006_film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>時をかける少女_(アニメ映画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1197</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2804</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324826</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8200</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>시간을_달리는_소녀_(2006년_영화)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>跳躍吧！時空少女</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01GJ9DNYA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4584" parentid="2637" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-13">
<name>time machine</name>
<description>A machine (or sometimes a living being) that accomplishes time travel. The details (what travels in which direction in time and how far) vary wildly from anime to anime.</description>
<picurl>214767.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5384" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-15">
<name>put right what once went wrong</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2748" type="main character in" update="2009-02-27">
<rating votes="73">8.14</rating>
<name>Konno Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>19918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4165" picture="26269.jpg">Naka Riisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2749" type="main character in" update="2009-02-27">
<rating votes="31">7.92</rating>
<name>Mamiya Chiaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>19919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9612" picture="170524.jpg">Ishida Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2750" type="main character in" update="2009-02-27">
<rating votes="21">7.21</rating>
<name>Tsuda Kousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>19920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9034" picture="186763.jpg">Itakura Mitsutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2751" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-16">
<rating votes="13">5.90</rating>
<name>Yoshiyama Kazuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42884" picture="171592.jpg">Hara Sachie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2752" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="11">5.40</rating>
<name>Fujitani Kaho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26700.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3782" picture="25315.jpg">Tanimura Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2753" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="7">4.19</rating>
<name>Hayakawa Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9615" picture="35882.jpg">Kakiuchi Ayami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2754" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="15">4.38</rating>
<name>Konno Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9613" picture="35879.jpg">Sekido Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="52406" update="2006-07-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2006-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="41">9.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64070" update="2010-03-28">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178077" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Storyboard</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
