<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4156" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-03-22</startdate>
<enddate>2006-03-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ar-Tonelico Sekai no Owari de Utai Tsuzukeru Shoujo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ar tonelico: The Girl Who Sings at the End of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Ар Тонелико: Момичето, което пее накрая на света</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">ar tonelico</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Ar-Tonelico</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アルトネリコ 世界の終わりで詩い続ける少女</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="277189">The OVA has an awesome soundtrack, and so does the game. I love them both.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://ar-tonelico.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="17958" type="Original Work">Banpresto</name>
<name id="6243" type="Character Design">Shida Tadashi</name>
<name id="1136" type="Work">Trans Arts</name>
<name id="9883" type="Direction">Andou Ken</name>
<name id="40184" type="Original Work">Gust</name>
<name id="40184" type="Series Composition">Gust</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on Ar Tonelico RPG game for the PlayStation 2.
At a time when http://anidb.net/ch54394 [Aurica] is saddened over her inability to fulfill her role as a Reyvateil, or one who can control magical powers through singing Songs, http://anidb.net/ch54399 [Lyner`s] airship comes crashing down upon her from the sky. Both of them search for an engineer to repair his airship, meeting http://anidb.net/ch54395 [Krusche]. In the process, Lyner inadvertently teaches Aurica that the key to singing a successful Song is to want to help others from the bottom of one`s heart.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1374">3.79</permanent>
<temporary count="1385">6.48</temporary>
<review count="3">6.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10154.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6277</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1202</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3633</identifier>
<identifier>vhqcam</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ar-tonelico.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ar_tonelico:_Melody_of_Elemia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アルトネリコ_世界の終わりで詩い続ける少女</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324299</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10785</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>700</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2091" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>blimp</name>
<description>An blimp or dirigible balloon is a type of aerostat or lighter-than-air aircraft that can navigate through the air under its own power. Aerostats gain their lift from large gas bags filled with a lifting gas that is less dense than the surrounding air.</description>
<picurl>221611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2461" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>domestic cat</name>
<description>The cat (Felis catus or Felis silvestris catus), also known as the domestic cat to distinguish it from other felines and felids, is a small, usually furry, domesticated, and carnivorous mammal. Cats are valued by humans for companionship and their ability to hunt vermin and household pests, and are often kept as indoor pets, in which case they are also called housecats; they have been associated with humans for at least 9,500 years and are currently the most popular pet in the world, being found almost everywhere on Earth.
Cats are similar in anatomy to the other felids, with light, strong and flexible bodies, excellent hearing, sense of smell, and near darkness eyesight, quick reflexes, sharp retractable claws, and teeth adapted to killing small prey. They are skilled predators and hunt over 1,000 species for food. Despite being solitary hunters, cats are a social species, with communication means that include pheromones, body language and a variety of vocalizations, such as meowing, purring, trilling, hissing, growling and grunting.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>41283.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2837" parentid="2628" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>floating island</name>
<description>A floating island is an island either floating in the sky, or actually floating in the ocean (mobile). The island`s flotation can be powered either by magic or science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="54394" type="main character in" update="2013-03-27">
<rating votes="2">5.44</rating>
<name>Aurica Nestmile</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aurica Nestmile is a a 3rd generation Reyvateil. Because of her birth circumstances, she is classified as a Class-D Reyvateil, the lowest rank. She appears inferior and gloomy at first but is getting more cheerful after met with Lyner.</description>
<picture>134339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="184" picture="23381.jpg">Miyazaki Ui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54395" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-27">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Krusche Elendia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Krusche Elendia is a Grathmelder specializing in airship repairs. She is sometimes bold and lacks some softness, and she wields a huge chainsaw in combat.</description>
<picture>134340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54396" type="appears in" update="2013-03-27">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Shurelia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shurelia is the administrator of Platina and the leader of the Knights of Elemia. As her direct subordinate, Lyner both admires and respects her. She wears a Linkage costume.</description>
<picture>134341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="448" picture="158105.jpg">Sakai Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54397" type="appears in" update="2013-03-27">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Spica Neal</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Spica Neal is a merchant with wide resources and influence in the Ar tonelico world.</description>
<picture>134346.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54398" type="appears in" update="2013-03-27">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Fayma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fayma is a Reyvateil. She was Radolf`s partner and lover before he reached the Cardinal rank.</description>
<picture>134345.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54399" type="main character in" update="2013-03-27">
<name>Lyner Barsett</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lyner Barsett is the protagonist of the first Ar tonelico game/anime, Sekai no Owari de Utai Tsuzukeru Shoujo. He was born in Platina, a city situated on the mid-upper level of the tower. He is a member of Knights of Elemia and protects the city with Shurelia.</description>
<picture>134338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40394" picture="158127.jpg">Fuse Masahide</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54400" type="appears in" update="2013-03-27">
<name>Radolf Schneizen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Radolf Schneizen is a cardinal in the Elemia Church. He has looked after Aurica for some time. He is also a Reyvatiel supporter, unlike many other characters in the game. He is a very serious man, but he also is very stubborn and will not take back the words that he says easily. He fights using a Grathnode-enhanced spear. Radolf also used to have a partner Reyvateil and lover called Fayma, but he was separated from her once he reached the Cardinal rank.</description>
<picture>134343.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42679" picture="170582.jpg">Handa Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54401" type="appears in" update="2013-03-27">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Misha Arsellec Lune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misha Arsellec Lune is a β pure-blood Reyvateil, also known to the Teru Tribe as the Hoshiyomi or Star Singer. Her main purpose in life is to sing the song Chronicle Key to suppress Mir. She has been friends with Lyner since their childhood in Platina. It`s worth noting that, despite being older than Aurica, she is trapped in a 12-year old girl body until her Song is recovered. After that, she regains her true form.</description>
<picture>134342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="313" picture="158104.jpg">Nogawa Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="48561" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87754" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2006-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Tiny hymmnos concert</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109765" update="2009-11-27">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
