<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4158" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-12-10</startdate>
<enddate>2005-12-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Pale Cocoon</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Бледный кокон</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Blankusis Kokonas</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Tổ Kén Xám</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Бледа какавида</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Блідий кокон</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">记忆裂痕</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ペイル・コクーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pale Cocoon</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Pale Cocoon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Pale Cocoon</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5132" type="Other">Eve no Jikan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5132" approval="100" total="116">Eve no Jikan</anime>
<anime id="104" approval="47" total="60">Hoshi no Koe</anime>
<anime id="4346" approval="36" total="50">Mizu no Kotoba</anime>
<anime id="7249" approval="18" total="21">Eve no Jikan Gekijouban</anime>
<anime id="10576" approval="4" total="8">Glass no Hana to Kowasu Sekai</anime>
<anime id="4708" approval="3" total="6">Freedom</anime>
<anime id="8857" approval="3" total="5">Sakasama no Patema</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="422884">Very...confusing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="368986">good sci fi
not recommended for limp brain</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="392207">visually stunning. the story is deep (somewhat warm) and focus on personal conflict and that`s the best part of this anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="435098">It`s hard to follow. Make time to see it and enjoy it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="421127">I thought this was great, not confusing at all, and left me wondering why people thought it so confusing. The story was quite simple when you get down to it. I think it`d have been better in a much longer format where they would have been able to delve into details more.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="394766">beautiful , very beautiful .  it has interesting end. i didn`t see any ova so far.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://studio-rikka.com/pale/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1265" type="Work">Yoshiura Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="1265" type="Original Plan">Yoshiura Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="1265" type="Direction">Yoshiura Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="6449" type="Music">Okada Tooru</name>
</creators>
<description>In the far future when the continuity of the history has been lost, humans live in an ever more deteriorating completely artificial and enclosed world. The sea and the sky have disappeared, and the only window to "living" scenery exists in the records from the past, excavated in the relic.
The Bureau of Record Excavation is an organization responsible for this task. http://anidb.net/ch10037 [Ura] works for the 92nd office of the bureau. He is absorbed by the restoration of various records and fascinated by world of the past. http://anidb.net/ch10039 [Riko] keeps a little distance to watch him, but averts her eyes from the records, believing that sometimes people just want things to stay the same.
Everyone in this world knows that to know the past means to know the misery of this world, the present reality. But one day, Ura restores a strange video...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4293">7.13</permanent>
<temporary count="4313">7.71</temporary>
<review count="6">8.38</review>
</ratings>
<picture>160916.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6352</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>770</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3631</identifier>
<identifier>fqknoz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://studio-rikka.com/pale/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Pale_Cocoon</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ペイル・コクーン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>323997</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8308</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3804" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-04-08">
<name>beauty in simplicity</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5561" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-08-16">
<name>lonely atmosphere</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10037" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="9">7.13</rating>
<name>Ura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ura works at the Archive Excavation Department 092, an almost deserted government institution. He restores degraded files about the world that once was, mostly pictures. Even though the Department was once fully employed and everyone would rejoice at the sight of a new file, Ura is now the only one left, as his colleague tells him he`s going to join the others in the lower levels.</description>
<picture>30242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3997" picture="77673.jpg">Nakao Michio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10039" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="11">6.11</rating>
<name>Riko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Riko is a analysis technician. She`s very smart and already anticipates what happened to Earth, even before Ura restores the video of Yoko Yamaguchi. She spends most of her time at the bottom of a tall staircase.</description>
<picture>30244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5868" picture="30327.jpg">Kawashima Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="44932" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45314" update="2005-12-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">3.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
