<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="416" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-10-08</startdate>
<enddate>2000-03-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Blue Gender</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">الجنس الأزرق</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">虫袭</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブルージェンダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Blue Gender</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Blue Gender</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Blue Gender</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Blue Gender</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Blue Gender</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Blue Gender</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Синята раса</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="771" type="Summary">Blue Gender: The Warrior</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9892" approval="21" total="23">Sidonia no Kishi</anime>
<anime id="518" approval="12" total="19">Gunparade March: Aratanaru Kougunka</anime>
<anime id="8549" approval="12" total="17">Muv-Luv Alternative: Total Eclipse</anime>
<anime id="10713" approval="8" total="9">Sidonia no Kishi: Daikyuu Wakusei Sen`eki</anime>
<anime id="7031" approval="6" total="11">King of Thorn</anime>
<anime id="1719" approval="6" total="9">A.LI.CE</anime>
<anime id="10439" approval="5" total="7">Terra Formars</anime>
<anime id="1370" approval="3" total="3">Kikou Souseiki Mospeada</anime>
<anime id="240" approval="2" total="4">Gasaraki</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="353741">I can`t believe there is so many hate comments about this anime... It`s absolutely amazing! Definitely one of my favorites! The action is very realistic, the dramas are very close to real life, cool storyline! ABSOLUTELY AMAZING ANIME!!! Watch it, you won`t regret it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="353610">Show grew on me quickly, watched an episode every day until I finished. I really liked the main characters love interest story, the way she was the `strong` rescuer/protector character and he was the one who had to become emotionally strong.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="185992">If you like a post apocalyptic world where humans are on the run than this is a good watch. It has an interesting premise and setting. My only gripe is that they put to much focus and emphasis on a few plot elements when it could have been put to use elsewhere. The show emphasizes a lot on the relationship between the protagonist and the heroine. It also has a lot of angst in regards to how the protagonist copes with whats happening all around him and as he tries to find purpose. Its good for what it is but it certainly could have been more interesting if they flushed out the universe that is Blue Gender.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="292763">It`s good but not that great. There are nothing memorial about this anime. First half of the anime the story pick up great then start to get worse later half. Mecha? post apocalypse? Blue? Overall are really nice but,seriously, there are nothing outstanding here. In conclusion, It`s great for a pass time watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="736643">Interesting plot! Had a nice underlying message. But the ending is kind of confusing. Another issue was some of the episodes were dragging (I guess, that`s the seinen effect).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="293382">Another great sci-fi.  If you are not into futuristic anime that kills bugs, then you`d be better off not watching this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="354949">Good music ambiance, animation, english voice acting for the dub matching their characters.

Interesting plot, meaningful flashbacks, sensible dialogue and no filler episodes.  I recommend to watch this at night when you can relax after a long day.

Watch the series, not the movie as it is a butchered compressed version.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.anime-int.com/works/bluegender/tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="102" type="Character Design">Kizaki Fuminori</name>
<name id="4152" type="Series Composition">Hasegawa Katsumi</name>
<name id="102" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kizaki Fuminori</name>
<name id="6228" type="Direction">Abe Masashi</name>
<name id="2318" type="Music">Haishima Kuniaki</name>
<name id="732" type="Animation Work">AIC</name>
</creators>
<description>Yuji, a high school teenager, discovers that he has an new incurable virus. With life looking very bleak, he`s left only one option - hope that the future may hold a cure. With his decision made, he opts to undergo artificial hibernation...
When Yuji awakes, the world he knew is gone. The year is 2031 - an era of war, despair and death. While he`s been sleeping, the Earth has been taken over by BLUE, a mysterious creature that eats anything for food including human beings.
Hunted and on the verge of extinction, Mankind has fled. Now, their only chance for survival is to destroy BLUE! Now, Yuji must fight not only for his own survival, but for that of the entire Human race!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2418">5.17</permanent>
<temporary count="2444">7.06</temporary>
<review count="13">7.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>150331.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>253</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>58</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>79</identifier>
<identifier>thibvf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.anime-int.com/works/bluegender/tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Blue_Gender</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Blue_Gender</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1013</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159507</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3225</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2131" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-19">
<name>psychotic</name>
<description>People suffering from psychosis can be described as having lost their contact with reality and deteriorated their social functioning to the point of becoming deranged. Sometimes, these people will try to achieve some absurd goal through trampling on other people, and that`s the point they become villains. Usually, psychotic villains will not show themselves to suffer from mental disorders at first, and will seem like completely normal people; however, as their story unfolds and the show progresses towards its climax, it is usual to have psychotic villains become more and more deranged, to the point of being best described by "batshit insane".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3394" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>environmentalism</name>
<description>Environmental protection is a practice of protecting the natural environment on individual, organizational or governmental levels, for the benefit of both the natural environment and humans. Due to the pressures of population and technology, the biophysical environment is being degraded, sometimes permanently. This has been recognized, and governments have begun placing restraints on activities that cause environmental degradation. Since the 1960s, activity of environmental movements has created awareness of the various environmental issues.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3516" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>insects of doom</name>
<description>Concerns insects, be them biological, magical or robotic in nature, that are either the bane, or a major stepping stone in the way of the main character(s) of the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3648" parentid="2637" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-25">
<name>person from the past</name>
<description>Possibly via stasis or cryogenic chamber, a person from the past will reawaken into a future present.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3798" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>giant insects</name>
<picurl>222266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4626" parentid="3394" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-18">
<name>nature strikes back</name>
<description>Humanity continues to pollute and waste the land. Until at some point (usually in the future), nature "has had it" and devises a way to countermand this dire situation. This cleansing of the Earth may well take out humanity, though.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16747" type="main character in" update="2011-11-26">
<rating votes="17">7.27</rating>
<name>Kaidou Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaidou Yuuji worked at a gas station, in what used to be the near future (2009), until a life-threatening disease (later discovered to be B-cells) required him to be put into cryogenic stasis so that his state would not get worse. He awakens in the future to find that the Blue have destroyed everything he knew. He then begins his journey to Second Earth, learning to defend himself and others on the way. His mental state changes greatly during the series, as he sees more of the ruined earth and meets all the people left behind.</description>
<picture>77675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16748" type="main character in" update="2014-06-06">
<rating votes="31">9.01</rating>
<name>Marlene Angel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marlene Angel was orphaned at the age of ten because her parents were killed by the Blue, Marlene was one of the few lucky ones to make it to Second Earth. Since then, Marlene has dedicated and trained herself to defeat the Blue. Though seeming very cold in the earlier episodes, as time progresses, Yuji opens up Marlene`s emotions. Towards the end of the series, she conceives Yuji`s child.</description>
<picture>77676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16749" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="8">4.86</rating>
<name>Alicia Whistle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alicia Whistle is another sleeper on Second Earth who is paired with Tony. She immediately gravitates towards Yuuji, seeing Marlene as an obstacle to a relationship with him. She is very young and often naive. Her death is one of the many that troubles Yuuji.</description>
<picture>46353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4630" picture="51962.jpg">Yasuda Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16750" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="6">4.10</rating>
<name>Brenda Miren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12454" picture="132869.jpg">Shimamura Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16751" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="5">5.95</rating>
<name>Dice Quaid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16752" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="4">3.11</rating>
<name>Doug</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20" picture="16599.jpg">Kitagawa Katsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16753" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="7">6.04</rating>
<name>Elena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16754" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-26">
<rating votes="8">5.17</rating>
<name>Joey Heald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2226" picture="23215.jpg">Suganuma Hisayoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16755" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="6">5.07</rating>
<name>Lu Li Chang</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4747" picture="171418.jpg">Hagimori Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16756" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="8">2.31</rating>
<name>Rick Kilmer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2224" picture="21768.jpg">Itou Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16757" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="7">4.55</rating>
<name>Seamus Han</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5104" picture="29292.jpg">Hanada Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16758" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="10">7.86</rating>
<name>Seno Miyagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seno Miyagi is a high-ranking member of the science division on Second Earth. He suggests that Marlene and Yuuji are kept together in order to get the best results from Yuuji in the sleeper program. Not agreeing with the High Council`s leadership of Second Earth or its reckless use of the sleepers, he eventually forms a group called The Ark, which would later overthrow the High Council`s "government" on Second Earth. Seno would subsequently become the leader of Second Earth, but only for a brief time. His order to abandon Earth eventually results in a revolt and his execution by citizens whom wanted to return to Earth.</description>
<picture>46363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="710" picture="228657.jpg">Hori Katsunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16759" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="5">3.75</rating>
<name>Su Li Chang</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4747" picture="171418.jpg">Hagimori Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16760" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="4">2.44</rating>
<name>Ted</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16761" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="4">6.39</rating>
<name>Tony Frost</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tony Frost is another sleeper brought to Second Earth before Yuuji. A very powerful sleeper, Yuuji strives to improve himself to be able to beat Tony. Tony seems to have no emotion, and is set on destroying the Blue. It becomes apparent in later episodes, however, that he sees himself as a Messiah when his B-cells initiate, and has his own plans for the fate of humanity.</description>
<picture>46366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3235" picture="25824.jpg">Satou Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16762" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="3">3.65</rating>
<name>Victor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16763" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="10">4.83</rating>
<name>Yung</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16764" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="12">4.94</rating>
<name>Amick Hendar</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17081" picture="46372.jpg">Yonemoto Chizu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39067" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-12">
<rating votes="7">4.57</rating>
<name>Robert Bradley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4686" picture="171399.jpg">Hori Yukitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39068" type="appears in" update="2012-02-12">
<rating votes="3">3.60</rating>
<name>Keith Bean</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103539" type="appears in" update="2019-06-15">
<name>Minnie White</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42909" picture="172039.jpg">Takeda Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4926" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Collapse</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Collapse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Effondrement</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Összeomlás</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Colaps</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Collapse</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4927" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Káosz</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Haos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chaos</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4928" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Eclosion</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eclosion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Éclosion</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Elszántság</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Ecloziune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eclosion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4929" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">A Sign</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Sign</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un signe</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A jel</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Un semn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Sign</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4930" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Calm</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Calme</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Csak semmi pánik</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Calm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Calm</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4931" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Set</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Set</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mise en place</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A játszma</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Stabilit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Set</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4932" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Confirm</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confirm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Confirmation</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Válaszút</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Confirmarea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Confirm</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4933" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Heresy</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heresy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hérésie</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Parancsmegtagadás</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Erezie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heresy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4934" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Oasis</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oasis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Oasis</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Oázis</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Oaza</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oasis</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4935" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Progress</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Progress</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Progression</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A következmény</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Progres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Progress</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4936" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Sympath</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sympath</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Compassion</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A magányos farkas</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Compasiune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sympath</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4937" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Go Mad</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go Mad</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vers la folie</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Őrület</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Nebunia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Go Mad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4938" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Relation</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Relation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Relation</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Emlékek</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Relaţie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Relation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4939" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Tactics</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tactics</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tactiques</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A manőver</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Tactica</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tactics</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4940" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="13">3.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Let Me</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let Me</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Laisse-moi</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Végjáték</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Lasă-mă</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Let Me</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4941" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Priority</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Priority</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Priorité</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Áldozat</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Prioritate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Priority</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4942" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Adagio</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adagio</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adage</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Az alagút</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Adagio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Adagio</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4943" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Agony</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Agony</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Agonie</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Vívódás</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Agonie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Agony</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4944" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Compass</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Compass</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Boussole</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Fogadalom</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Compas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Compass</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4945" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Trial</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trial</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mise à l`essai</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Próbatétel</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Încercarea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4946" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Soliste</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soliste</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Soliste</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Leszámolás</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Solist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soliste</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4947" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Cry</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cry</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pleurs</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Áttörés</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Plânge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cry</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4948" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dogma</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dogma</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dogme</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Csalódás</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Dogma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dogma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4949" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">One day</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un jour</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A vég kezdete</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">O zi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">One Day</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4950" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Joker</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Joker</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Joker</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Túlélők</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Jocher</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joker</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4951" update="2008-01-04">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Versus</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Versus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Versus</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Ellentétek</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Confruntarea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Versus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30334" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30335" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112739" update="2010-01-08">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Extended Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120222" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">English Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
