<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4161" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1984-07-21</startdate>
<enddate>1984-07-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Radio City Fantasy: Machikado no Maerchen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-unk" type="synonym">Machikado no Märchen</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Radio City Fantasy 街角のメルヘン</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Radio City Fantasy: Machikado no Meruhen</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">RADIO-CITY FANTASY 街角のメルヘン</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7336" approval="1" total="1">Noel no Fushigi na Bouken</anime>
</similaranime>
<creators>
<name id="2234" type="Chief Direction">Nishikubo Mizuho</name>
<name id="6236" type="Character Design">Yuza Kazue</name>
<name id="6468" type="Character Design">Amano Yoshitaka</name>
<name id="5112" type="Original Plan">Shudou Takeshi</name>
<name id="8512" type="Music">Virgin VS</name>
</creators>
<description>A boy with a drawing book meets a mysterious girl in the streets of Tokyo. They become friends and enjoy each other`s fantasies.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="35">7.49</permanent>
<temporary count="35">6.77</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>10373.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>893</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11221</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3253</identifier>
<identifier>fmecen</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>街角のメルヘン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88841</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4533</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="45031" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>1984-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
