<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4168" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-07-27</startdate>
<enddate>2004-07-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED: Harukanaru Akatsuki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">機動戦士ガンダムSEED スペシャルエディションII 遥かなる暁</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED Special Edition II: Harukanaru Akatsuki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GS SE II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GS Special Edition II</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機動戦士ガンダムSEED -遥かなる暁-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam SEED: Movie II - The Far-Away Dawn</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4165" type="Sequel">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED: Meidou no Sora</anime>
<anime id="4169" type="Prequel">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED: Kokuu no Senjou</anime>
<anime id="252" type="Full Story">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="620" type="Character Design">Hirai Hisashi</name>
<name id="7988" type="Series Composition">Morosawa Chiaki</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="621" type="Direction">Fukuda Mitsuo</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
</creators>
<description>* The second in a trilogy of re-edited specials to the http://anidb.net/a252 [Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED] television series, loosely covering episodes 22 to 40.
The http://anidb.net/ch1507 [Archangel], still on the run, enters the Red Sea, where a new menace awaits http://anidb.net/ch1 [Kira] and the rest of the crew: ZAFT`s amphibious mobile suits. During a patrol flight in the Sky Grasper, http://anidb.net/ch304 [Cagalli] is forced to crash-land and runs into http://anidb.net/ch300 [Athrun], who survived her attack on a transport plane and finds himself stranded on the very same island. Not long after this surprise meeting, the Archangel once again has to fight Team Zala, with a fatal outcome. Meanwhile, http://anidb.net/ch1692 [Patrick Zala] is appointed the new PLANT Supreme Council Chairman; he sets into motion a plan to crush the Earth Alliance forces once and for all, but meets opposition from http://anidb.net/ch302 [Lacus Clyne].
Note: This special follows http://anidb.net/a4169 [The Empty Battlefield], which was aired earlier in March 2004. It was aired in two parts on Japanese TV on July 27, 2004 and July 28, 2004 and received a DVD release on September 24, 2004. While the story is overall the same, there are some changes to it; it was re-edited, leaving out scenes from the original series but also adding some newly produced cuts, and featuring a new dub.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="492">6.68</permanent>
<temporary count="498">7.34</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>10167.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3565</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2269</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mobile_Suit_Gundam_SEED:_Special_Edition</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>機動戦士ガンダムSEED#.E3.82.B9.E3.83.9A.E3.82.B7.E3.83.A3.E3.83.AB.E3.82.A8.E3.83.87.E3.82.A3.E3.82.B7.E3.83.A7.E3.83.B3.EF.BC.88.E7.B7.8F.E9.9B.86.E7.B7.A8.EF.BC.89</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>380</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6946</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/916</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1286" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-28">
<name>megalomaniac</name>
<description>Megalomania is a psychopathological condition characterized by delusional fantasies of power, relevance, and omnipotence, and by inflated self-esteem.&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>70559.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="726">7.13</rating>
<name>Kira Yamato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The young civilian who becomes the pilot of the prototype http://anidb.net/ch1577 [Strike Gundam]. Kira is a first-generation Coordinator whose parents are Naturals, and his family has taken refuge in the neutral territory of the resource satellite Heliopolis to avoid the war. However, Kira finds himself drawn into the conflict when Heliopolis is attacked by http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] forces, and he remains aboard the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance] warship http://anidb.net/ch1507 [Archangel] in order to protect his friends and loved ones. As a Coordinator, Kira has remarkable mental and physical abilities, and his computer programming talents enable him to rewrite the http://anidb.net/ch1577 [Strike Gundam`s] operating system in mid-battle to adapt to new combat conditions.</description>
<picture>52595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="300" type="main character in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="400">6.55</rating>
<name>Athrun Zala</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Athrun Zala is a member of the elite Le Creuset team which attacks Heliopolis, Athrun subsequently becomes the pilot of the captured Aegis Gundam. As a child, Athrun attended a preparatory school on the moon, where he became good friends with Kira Yamato. Now, with his father leading the most warlike faction of the PLANT Supreme Council and his mother among the casualties of the "Bloody Valentine" tragedy, Athrun is determined to defeat the treacherous Earth Alliance - and shocked to discover that Kira is fighting on the side of the enemy. Athrun has a talent for mechanical tinkering, and has created numerous robot pets for his friends and acquaintances.</description>
<picture>52590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="302" type="main character in" update="2014-09-27">
<rating votes="758">7.93</rating>
<name>Lacus Clyne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of PLANT Supreme Council chairman Siegel Clyne, whose career as a pop star has made her the idol of the Coordinators. Dispatched to join a memorial service on the anniversary of the "Bloody Valentine" tragedy, Lacus is left drifting in space when her ship is attacked by Earth Alliance forces, and her lifepod is subsequently retrieved by the Alliance warship Archangel. Lacus treats friend and foe alike with kindness and respect, and even her fiancé Athrun Zala is sometimes perplexed by her apparent naïveté.</description>
<picture>161846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="304" type="main character in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="304">5.58</rating>
<name>Cagalli Yula Athha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This tomboy princess is the daughter of Lord Uzumi, one of the leaders of the neutral Orb Union. Despite her aristocratic upbringing, Cagalli is tough and headstrong, and her impulsive nature often leads her to take bold risks. Learning that her nation is secretly aiding the Earth Alliance, she travels to the resource satellite Heliopolis to see the evidence for herself, and after escaping the satellite`s collapse she makes her way to Earth to join the Desert Dawn resistance group in northern Africa. By the time she returns to Orb aboard the warship Archangel, Cagalli has formed strong bonds with both Strike Gundam pilot Kira Yamato and his estranged friend Athrun Zala.</description>
<picture>52589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1489" type="appears in" update="2011-11-30">
<rating votes="41">8.99</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X10A Freedom Gundam</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The ZGMF-X10A Freedom Gundam is one of the new Gundam designs built by ZAFT. The Freedom Gundam is equipped with a wide variety of powerful weapons for use in its HiMAT (High Mobility Aerial Tactics) mode. One of these weapons is the twin "Balaena" plasma beam cannons, which are stored in the wings and mounted over the shoulders during use. The Freedom Gundam`s other main armament consists of twin hip-mounted "Xiphias" rail cannons. Other standard armaments include head vulcans, twin beam sabers and a beam rifle. The Freedom Gundam is also capable of using something far more powerful: the METEOR support system. This mobile weapons platform is designed specifically for use by the Freedom Gundam and ZGMF-X09A Justice Gundam and is stored aboard the support ship Eternal. By using the METEOR, the Freedom Gundam can deliver a blitzkrieg attack utilizing various cannons, missile launchers and two long beam swords.
The Freedom Gundam is first used in May C.E. 71 when Kira Yamato steals it with the help of Lacus Clyne. Kira uses his new suit to travel to Earth and join the battle between ZAFT and the Alliance at Alaska. Following the battle, Kira rejoins his comrades on the Archangel and travels to Orb after Murrue Ramius decides to defect from the Alliance. There, Kira fights to protect Orb from the Alliance and is later joined by his old friend and former enemy Athrun Zala piloting his new ZGMF-X09A Justice Gundam. Following the defeat of Orb, Kira returns to space and is joined by Lacus Clyne and her stolen support ship Eternal, which provides Kira with his METEOR support system. Along with Athrun, Kira uses his METEOR to save the PLANTs from destruction by nuclear missiles. At the war`s end on September 27, the Freedom Gundam is heavily damaged in a battle against Rau Le Creuset`s ZGMF-X13A Providence Gundam. After the war, the Freedom Gundam is secretly repaired and hidden in Orb. In late C.E. 73, the Freedom Gundam is reactivated by Kira to fight off a squad of UMF/SS0-3 ASH mobile suits used by a group of special ops Coordinators sent to assassinate Lacus. In early C.E. 74, PLANT Supreme Council Chairman Gilbert Durandal orders the destruction of the Archangel and Freedom Gundam after their interference in several battles between the Alliance and ZAFT. Soon after, ZAFT then initiates "Operation Angel Down," and during that battle the Freedom Gundam is destroyed by Shinn Asuka`s ZGMF-X56S Impulse Gundam.</description>
<picture>77823.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1501" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="30">8.60</rating>
<name>Orb Union</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An island nation in the southern Pacific Ocean, which possesses considerable industrial and military power despite its small size and lack of natural resources. Its assets include high technology, an abundant supply of geothermal energy thanks to its numerous active volcanoes, and a policy of nondiscrimination against Coordinators which has enriched Orb`s talent pool. The Orb Union also has its own mass driver and controls its own space colony, the resource satellite Heliopolis.
In Orb`s complex political system, power is shared between an elected assembly and representatives of the five noble families who originally ruled over the islands.</description>
<picture>16027.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1507" type="appears in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="110">5.81</rating>
<name>LCAM-01XA Archangel</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>While the Earth Alliance plays a game of catch up with ZAFT on mobile suit development, it also designs a new type of battleship to complement their mobile suits. Developed in conjunction with Orb`s Morgenroete company, the design of the Archangel class is based on that of Orb`s Izumo class. In addition to carrying mobile suits, the Archangel features many new technologies not seen in other Alliance vessels. The Archangel is capable of atmospheric entry, thanks to an ablative gel that can be spread across the hull. The Archangel also features laminated armor, making it very difficult to seriously damage in battle. In terms of weaponry, the Archangel is a mobile fortress. Its main weapon is the dual "Lohengrin" positron blaster cannon housed in the `legs` at the forward end of the ship. The Archangel`s armament includes an array of other weapons, such as "Gottfried" beam cannons, "Valient" linear cannons, "Igelstellung" vulcan guns as well as missile launchers.</description>
<picture>16039.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1508" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-08">
<rating votes="223">6.84</rating>
<name>Murrue Ramius</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1509" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="48">6.01</rating>
<name>ZAFT</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The military forces of the PLANTs. ZAFT is a militia made up of civilian volunteers, and the organization has no formal rank structure, so its members are instead addressed by descriptive titles like "commander" and "captain." The ZAFT forces are organized into independent teams named after their commanders, and much like the modern-day U.S. Marines these teams can operate equally well on land, at sea, in air, or in outer space. Since ZAFT`s membership is made up of genetically enhanced Coordinators, its forces are more than a match for the numerically superior Earth Alliance.
ZAFT was originally a political organization called the Zodiac Alliance, which was founded in C.E. 50 by Siegel Clyne and Patrick Zala. The Zodiac Alliance took on its present name in C.E. 65, and three years later it was reorganized to become an explicitly military organization equipped with the revolutionary new weapons known as mobile suits. The ZAFT forces are currently subject to the authority of the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council], and report directly to the chairman of the National Defense Committee.</description>
<picture>16042.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1542" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="24">1.64</rating>
<name>Earth Alliance</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An international coalition formed by the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANT] sponsor nations and their terrestrial allies to battle the forces of http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT]. The Earth Alliance is not a single political entity, but rather a collaboration between several individual nations, which regard each other as potential adversaries even though they are currently united against a common foe. The dominant powers within the Earth Alliance are the http://anidb.net/ch1594 [Atlantic Federation], the http://anidb.net/ch1595 [Eurasian Federation], and the http://anidb.net/ch1598 [Republic of East Asia], all three of which invested heavily in the construction of the PLANTs. The South African Union and the United States of South America are junior partners in the Alliance, with the latter having been forcibly annexed by the Atlantic Federation at the start of the war.
The Earth Alliance was formally established on February 7, C.E. 70, two days after final negotiations between the PLANTs and the sponsor nations were disrupted by a terror bombing at the lunar city of Copernicus. The Alliance was created as a successor to the former United Nations, whose leadership was wiped out in the Copernicus attack, and like its predecessor it`s nominally an international organization headed by a moderate secretary-general. However, in practice it`s little more than a military alliance dominated by the Atlantic Federation and its fellow PLANT sponsor nations.
The Earth Alliance is headed by a moderate Secretary-General, but the real leaders of the Earth Alliance are http://anidb.net/ch1579 [Blue Cosmos] and its http://anidb.net/ch1578 [Logos] benefactors.
At the beginning of C.E. 71, the Alliance is headquartered at the JOSH-A Base in Alaska. At the beginning of C.E. 71 its other major strongholds include the Kaohsiung spaceport in Taiwan, the Panama spaceport in Central America, the Victoria spaceport in eastern Africa, and the Ptolemaeus Lunar Base. After the destruction of JOSH-A and the Ptolemaeus Base in the first war, their functions are transferred to Heavens Base in Iceland and the Arzachel Lunar Base.</description>
<picture>1777.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="1547" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="10">5.99</rating>
<name>O.M.N.I. Enforcer</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The formal name of the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance`s] military forces, which are more commonly referred to as the Earth Alliance Forces, or simply Earth Forces.</description>
<picture>16082.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1554" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="22">3.23</rating>
<name>PLANT Supreme Council</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The executive committee which governs the PLANTs and controls the ZAFT forces. The dozen members of this supreme council serve as elected representatives of the twelve sectors, or "cities," into which the PLANTs are grouped. The council itself meets at Aprilius One, the administrative capital of the PLANTs.
Each member of the council is assigned to one of its five specialized committees - Administrative, Diplomatic, Judicial, Legislative, or National Defense. Each of these committees has its own chairman, and the overall council is chaired by a Supreme Council chairman. The council is also divided along political lines, with a roughly even split between radicals who seek to escalate the war, and moderates who hope to end the conflict through negotiation.</description>
<picture>16231.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1571" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="24">4.99</rating>
<name>PLANT</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A new type of space settlement, created chiefly by Coordinators. Roughly 120 of these constructs are gathered at Lagrange point 5, a gravitationally stable area in Earth orbit, and these settlements have become a new homeland for Coordinators fleeing the persecution they experienced on Earth. As their name suggests, the PLANTs were created to serve as research and manufacturing sites, but their unique design also enables them to recreate a lush natural environment, with abundant vegetation and open water.
These hourglass-style structures consist of two disc-shaped living areas, each ten kilometers in diameter, which rotate around a central hub to produce artificial gravity. Each living area is anchored to the hub by a 30-kilometer central shaft and a network of high-tension strings, and a high-speed elevator runs up the central shaft to provide access to the hub. A set of external mirrors, attached to the central hub, are used to reflect sunlight into the inner surfaces of the living areas.
The PLANTs are grouped into twelve sectors, or "cities," each with its own scientific or industrial speciality. These cities are named after the months of the Roman calendar, and each is made up of roughly ten individual PLANT settlements, which are referred to as Januarius One, Januarius Two, and so forth.
The construction of the PLANTs began in C.E. 38, with funding supplied by the Atlantic Federation, the Eurasian Federation, and the Republic of East Asia. The PLANT settlements were initially managed by a directorate controlled by these sponsor nations, but in C.E. 53 their inhabitants formed a http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council] to represent them in their dealings with the directorate. With the start of open hostilities between the PLANTs and the Earth Alliance in C.E. 70, the PLANTs effectively became an independent nation, governed solely by the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [Supreme Council].
After the first war between Earth and the PLANTs, the citizens of the PLANTs adopt a new name for their space settlements to reflect their independent status, and this acronym is redefined to mean People Liberation Acting Nation of Technology.</description>
<picture>1778.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="1576" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Morgenroete Incorporated</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A semi-nationalized munitions company based in the http://anidb.net/ch1501 [Orb Union], which also maintains facilities at the resource satellite Heliopolis. Although its primary clients are the armed forces of the neutral nation Orb, Morgenroete has been secretly collaborating with the Atlantic Federation on its Gundam development project and on the construction of the warship Archangel. On January 20, C.E. 71, five prototype Gundam mobile suits are rolled out at the company`s Heliopolis factory, and five days later the facility is attacked by http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] commandos, drawing http://anidb.net/ch1 [Kira Yamato] and his friends into the conflict.
Beam weapons, second-generation mobile suit operating systems, the Lohengrin positron blaster cannon (later adapted by ZAFT as the Tannhäuser installed in the bow of the assault ship Minerva), Variable Phase Shift Armor and the Mirage Colloid cloaking device were all developed at Morgenroete either entirely or in part during the war or immediately after, partly under the aegis of chief designer Erica Simmons. More esoteric technologies were also developed at Morgenroete under the aegis of the Sahaku twins, including energy-draining weaponry.</description>
</character>
<character id="1577" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<rating votes="8">4.99</rating>
<name>GAT-X105 Strike Gundam</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>With the outbreak of war, the Earth Alliance`s Atlantic Federation begins a secret project to develop mobile suits to counter ZAFT`s mass-produced ZGMF-1017 GINN as well as operate free of interference from the N-Jammers. The GAT-X105 Strike Gundam is one of five initial prototype suits secretly developed in conjunction with Orb`s http://anidb.net/ch1576 [Morgenroete] defense company. Whereas the other Gundams are designed for specific roles, the Strike Gundam is intended to operate in various configurations through the use of Striker packs. Like the other prototype Gundams, the Strike Gundam is equipped with the new Phase Shift (PS) armor technology. When in Phase Shift mode, the Strike Gundam is nearly impervious to attacks from shell-firing artillery or melee weapons. However, use of Phase Shift for extended periods of time is a massive drain on the energy battery. The basic version of the Strike Gundam is nearly identical to the GAT-X102 Duel Gundam`s initial configuration. Its armament consists of two "Igelstellung" vulcan guns, a 57mm beam rifle, a shield and two "Armor Schneider" combat knives. Other optional armaments include a bazooka designed for underwater combat. In addition to the first unit, Orb later constructs an improved version from spare parts, the MBF-02 Strike Rouge. The Alliance also constructs a third unit, which is later upgraded into the GAT-X105E Strike E. The Strike Gundam is later followed by the mass production GAT-01 Strike Dagger and GAT-01A1 Dagger.
The first Strike Gundam enters combat in January 25, C.E. 71, when ZAFT attacks Orb`s space colony Heliopolis in an attempt to steal the Gundam prototypes. Although ZAFT succeeds in capturing four units, the Strike Gundam remains in Alliance control and is initially (and ineffectively) used by Murrue Ramius. However, young Coordinator Kira Yamato is able to modify the incomplete operating system and make the Strike Gundam combat ready. Following the destruction of Heliopolis, Kira becomes the Strike Gundam`s default pilot and joins the crew of the Archangel. While heading for the Alliance`s Alaskan headquarters, the Strike Gundam is severely damaged in battle on April 17 by Athrun Zala`s self-destructing GAT-X303 Aegis Gundam. The Strike Gundam is later repaired by Orb and passed on to ace pilot Mu La Flaga, while Kira upgrades to ZAFT`s ZGMF-X10A Freedom Gundam. The Strike Gundam serves as Mu`s personal mobile suit after the Archangel defects from the Alliance and joins the Orb forces and Clyne faction to form the Three Ships Alliance. At the war`s end on September 27, the Strike Gundam is damaged in a duel with Rau Le Creuset`s ZGMF-X13A Providence Gundam and later destroyed while Mu is protecting the Archangel from an attack by the Alliance battleship Dominion. Two years after the war, the versatile design of the Strike Gundam serves as the basis for ZAFT`s ZGMF-X56S Impulse Gundam.</description>
<picture>16117.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1579" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="22">1.25</rating>
<name>Blue Cosmos</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The most radical of the anti-Coordinator activist groups formed by resentful Naturals. According to the Blue Cosmos ideology, genetic modification is a violation of the natural order, and all Coordinators must be exterminated "for the preservation of our blue and pure world."
Blue Cosmos was originally an environmental pressure group, but after the revelation of George Glenn`s secret in C.E. 15, the organization launched a campaign of terror and assassination against Coordinators and the medical professionals who were working to create them. It is believed that the group is supported by the Azrael Conglomerate, a powerful industrial concern which is one of the Atlantic Federation`s major military contractors.
After the first war between Earth and the PLANTs, Lord Djibril becomes the new leader of Blue Cosmos, and the organization continues to create conflict between Naturals and Coordinators.</description>
</character>
<character id="1594" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Atlantic Federation</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>This nation is the dominant power in the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance], and the creator of the http://anidb.net/ch1507 [Archangel] and the prototype Gundams. Before the war, the Atlantic Federation was the most influential of the sponsor nations which funded the construction of the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] and then forced their Coordinator inhabitants into economic bondage. When the leadership of the United Nations was wiped out by a terror attack at the lunar city of Copernicus, the Atlantic Federation took the lead in organizing the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance] and issuing a declaration of war against the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs].
The Atlantic Federation was originally formed from the nations of Britain and North America. At the beginning of the first war it expanded its territory by annexing the http://anidb.net/ch1601 [United States of South America], but this conquest is eventually undone when the Junius Treaty restores South America`s independence.
During the first war the Atlantic Federation`s major military base, the JOSH-A facility in Alaska, doubles as the headquarters of the Earth Alliance forces. After the destruction of JOSH-A, its functions are transferred to Heavens Base in Iceland.</description>
</character>
<character id="1595" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Eurasian Federation</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of the leading powers within the Earth Alliance, this nation is a longtime rival, and now uneasy ally, of the Atlantic Federation. Originally formed from the nations of Europe and northern Asia, the Eurasian Federation is governed by a federal council dominated by the nations of the European region. Among its strategic assets is the space fortress Artemis, located at Lagrange point 3.
When a new war breaks out between Earth and the PLANTs, the Eurasian Federation once again sides with the Atlantic Federation. Meanwhile, its citizens become increasingly vocal in their demands for independence. As the war continues, ZAFT forces begin to intervene on behalf of these independence movements, liberating their homes and cities from Eurasian Federation control.</description>
</character>
<character id="1598" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Republic of East Asia</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The third major power within the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance]. Along with the http://anidb.net/ch1594 [Atlantic Federation] and http://anidb.net/ch1595 [Eurasian Federation], the Republic of East Asia was one of the primary sponsors of the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANT] construction project. Though its political influence is no match for that of the Alliance`s leading powers, its large population gives it a high industrial production capacity. Originally made up of the modern-day nations of China, Japan, and Korea, the Republic of East Asia encompasses much of the Asian region.</description>
</character>
<character id="1600" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>South African Union</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The fourth member of the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance] is a collective formed by the nations of southern Africa. Unlike the Alliance`s other member nations, the South African Union was not a sponsor of the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANT] construction project, and thus has no economic stake in the conflict. Instead, its participation in the war appears to have been motivated by its antagonism towards the PLANT-aligned African Community. However, the South African Union has fared badly in the fighting, and is now in the process of dropping out.</description>
</character>
<character id="1601" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>United States of South America</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A nation which formerly controlled much of Central and South America, and collaborated with the http://anidb.net/ch1594 [Atlantic Federation] in the construction of the Porta Panama mass driver. Before the outbreak of war, the United States of South America had aligned itself with the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] and made arrangements to covertly exchange shipments of food and manufactured goods, and it refused to join the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance] once open hostilities began. On February 19, C.E. 70, Alliance forces launched an armed invasion of this nation, and its territory was annexed by the http://anidb.net/ch1594 [Atlantic Federation]. However, its independence is restored with the conclusion of the Junius Treaty on March 10, C.E. 72.</description>
</character>
<character id="1603" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>African Community</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An economic and military cooperative formed by the nations of the northern half of the African continent. Friendly to the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] and hostile to the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance], the African Community is now effectively http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] territory. Nonetheless, a handful of local resistance groups, like the Desert Dawn group based in the Libyan desert, continue to fight a guerilla war against the http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] occupation.</description>
</character>
<character id="1605" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Oceania Union</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A union whose territory encompasses the Australian continent and its neighboring nations. Since it wasn`t one of the sponsor nations that profited from the economic exploitation of the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs], the Oceania Union was quick to ally itself with them as tensions increased between the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] and their terrestrial sponsors. In C.E. 68 the Oceania Union agreed to covertly exchange shipments of food and manufactured goods with the PLANTs, and on February 20, C.E. 70, it formally declared its support for the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] in their struggle against the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance]. The Oceania Union went on to host the Carpentaria Base, http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT`s] first terrestrial stronghold.</description>
</character>
<character id="1649" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="19">1.32</rating>
<name>Muruta Azrael</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fanatical leader of the secret society http://anidb.net/ch1579 [Blue Cosmos], which seeks to exterminate all Coordinators. Azrael is also the president of a major weapons manufacturing conglomerate and a director of the Defense Industry Association, and as a result he has great influence over the leadership of the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance]. After he convinces the Alliance to attack the neutral http://anidb.net/ch1501 [Orb Union], Azrael then accompanies the invasion force to supervise the operation and observe his newest weapons in action.</description>
<picture>16191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1680" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">5.25</rating>
<name>Clyne Faction</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>After the theft of the http://anidb.net/ch1489 [Freedom Gundam], former http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council] chairman Siegel Clyne is branded a traitor. Clyne and his followers become fugitives, waging an underground campaign of resistance to the radical leadership of Patrick Zala. The Clyne Faction carries on the fight even after Siegel himself is gunned down, working within the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] to thwart Patrick Zala`s plans.
http://anidb.net/ch302 [Lacus Clyne] takes over the command of Clyne Faction after the death of her father.</description>
</character>
<character id="1686" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="11">6.05</rating>
<name>Siegel Clyne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The chairman of the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council] that governs the Coordinator homeland. Although Clyne once worked side by side with Patrick Zala to create http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] and win independence for the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs], over the years the two have become political rivals, and Clyne now leads a moderate faction of the Supreme Council which seeks to end the war through peaceful negotiation. Clyne represents the PLANTs of Aprilius City, which specialize in space sciences, and is the father of pop star http://anidb.net/ch302 [Lacus Clyne].</description>
<picture>16230.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1688" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="16">4.31</rating>
<name>Eileen Canaver</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest member of the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council]. As one of http://anidb.net/ch1686 [Siegel Clyne`s] most trusted allies, Canaver serves as deputy leader of his moderate faction, and thanks to her position on the Supreme Council`s Diplomatic Committee she plays a key role in the ongoing efforts to negotiate an end to the war. Canaver represents the PLANTs of September City, which specialize in artificial intelligence and information sciences.
Eileen Canaver became the temporary leader of PLANT Supreme Council in the form of PLANT Provisional Supreme Council which takes control after the second Battle of Jachin Due and negotiates a peace treaty with the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance]. After the conclusion of the Junius Treaty, the Provisional Supreme Council is dissolved and Gilbert Durandal replaces Canaver as chairman of the PLANT Supreme Council.</description>
<picture>20674.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1692" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="10">1.54</rating>
<name>Patrick Zala</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council] who serves as chairman of its National Defense Committee, and is thus the commander in chief of the http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] forces. Having lost his wife Lenore in the Bloody Valentine tragedy, Zala is intent on revenge against the Naturals, and he is the leader of a radical faction of the Supreme Council which seeks to escalate the war against the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance]. Zala represents the PLANTs of December City, where the http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] forces are headquartered, and is the father of http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] soldier http://anidb.net/ch300 [Athrun Zala].</description>
<picture>16242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1699" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="10">5.25</rating>
<name>Ake no Sabaku</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A resistance group based in northern Africa, in modern-day Libya, which fights against the http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] forces who have effectively taken control of the http://anidb.net/ch1603 [African Community]. The group is led by the grizzled guerilla fighter http://anidb.net/ch1700 [Sahib Ashman], and its members are recruited from local towns like Tassil and Moula, as well as the city of Banadiya.</description>
</character>
<character id="1700" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="10">5.99</rating>
<name>Sahib Ashman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The grizzled leader of the Desert Dawn resistance group, a ragtag band of guerilla soldiers drawn from the townships of northern Africa. Although he has little use for the arrogant superpowers which make up the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance], Sahib makes common cause with the http://anidb.net/ch1507 [Archangel] crew against their mutual enemy. As an old friend of http://anidb.net/ch304 [Cagalli`s] family, Sahib is one of the few resistance members who knows the secret of her true identity.</description>
<picture>56588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="418" picture="17270.jpg">Hirose Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1701" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="9">5.28</rating>
<name>Ahmed El Fasi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young member of the http://anidb.net/ch1699 [Desert Dawn] resistance group who serves as http://anidb.net/ch304 [Cagalli`s] driver and sidekick. Ahmed has a poorly-disguised crush on the tomboyish http://anidb.net/ch304 [Cagalli], which drives this brave lad to take foolish risks in hopes of impressing her.</description>
<picture>2074.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3702" picture="25829.jpg">Numata Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12914" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="110">8.35</rating>
<name>Mu La Flaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A famous ace pilot of the Earth Alliance, who brings his Moebius Zero mobile armor aboard the Archangel after his original mothership is destroyed. Mu earned the nickname "Hawk of Endymion" by singlehandedly shooting down five ZAFT mobile suits in one of the war`s early battles. Aside from his piloting skills, tactical abilities, and extensive combat experience, Mu`s greatest contribution to the Archangel is probably the morale boost provided by his relaxed and lighthearted personality.</description>
<picture>2799.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14305" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-28">
<rating votes="33">7.77</rating>
<name>Rau Le Creuset</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rau Le Creuset is the Commander as well as a natural who constantly has to take drugs in order to help with the defects in his DNA that casues him to age rapily. He seems to be an extremely intelligent leader, but also believes that because ZAFT and Earth Alliance want to fight, they should be able to do so. In addition, Rau Le Creuset is also clone of his father, Al Da Flaga.He never appears in public without his distinctive face mask, and his actual appearance - like the nature of his apparent rapport with Earth Alliance ace Mu La Flaga - thus far remains a secret.
Created illegally as a Coordinator by Al Da Flaga while also carrying the NewType gene from his father, he is the son of Al Da Flaga, who had named him as his son over Mu La Flaga. Due to unfortunate circumstances, their house burned down and Rau Le Creuset became enlisted in the ZAFT military because of his relations to Patrick Zala. Rau Le Creuset has a bit of an aging problem that causes him to grow up and develop at a faster rate than everyone else, which is why he must take blue and white pills in order to slow down his aging process. In the ZAFT military, Rau Le Creuset becomes the commander of one of the most greatest teams of ZAFT, the Le Creuset Team, which is sometimes envied by others for their skill as they have ZAFT`s topguns in their ranks .He is a ruthless and enigmatic commander of the elite ZAFT team that attacks Heliopolis and then relentlessly pursues the Archangel. Raw Le Creuset also plays a key role in the ZAFT Military as he reports directly to Patrick Zala since Partrick`s son Athrun Zala is in his team.
While he has a somewhat a good personality on the outside, it acts like more of a veil that covers up his true intentions, which are somewhat psychotic. He desires world peace and realizes the situation between the Earth Alliance and ZAFT as they both want to destroy each other. Thus, what he believes, is that he should help them achieve that by any means necessary similar to the modern age and nuclear missiles. Once again, despite his craziness, he is very refined and reasonable on the outside in making orders.
He is extremely skilled at piloting any mobile suit or Gundam of any type and a very good strategist. He makes long term plans for his peacemaking operation throughout a large span of time, and manages to pull them off.</description>
<picture>41814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17721" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="22">6.84</rating>
<name>Yzak Joule</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Le Creuset team which raids Heliopolis, who becomes the pilot of the captured Duel Gundam. A second-generation Coordinator whose mother sits on the PLANT Supreme Council, Yzak is fiercely proud of his elite status, and regards his teammate Athrun Zala as his chief rival. After clashing with the Strike Gundam, Yzak becomes even more intent on defeating the Archangel and its resident mobile suit, and the injuries he sustains in battle serve to further fuel his hatred.
In Gundam SEED Destiny:
The former Duel Gundam pilot now leads the Joule Team and wears the white uniform of a ZAFT commander. As the new conflict escalates, Yzak participates in the Junius Seven demolition operation and helps defend the PLANT homeland from the vengeful Earth Alliance.</description>
<picture>3266.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20355" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-30">
<rating votes="21">5.43</rating>
<name>Dearka Elsman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dearka Elsman is an arrogant pilot of ZAFT`s Rau Le Creuset team who looks down on Naturals. He was part of the crew that invaded Heliopolis to steal mobile suits and piloted the GAT-X103 Buster. During the course of the series, Dearka is captured by the Archangel where he meets Kira`s friends which prompt him to change his opinions about Naturals. Seeing how both the Earth Alliance and ZAFT had become controlled by genocidal individuals such as Muruta Azrael and Patrick Zala, Dearka retakes his Buster and fights alongside the Archangel. During the SEED series, Dearka begins a relationship with Miriallia Haw which ends shortly after. In Gundam SEED Destiny, Dearka is shown in a regular ZAFT soldier uniform. His seiyu is Akira Sasanuma and his English voice actor is Brad Swaile.</description>
<picture>52581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2936" picture="75539.jpg">Sasanuma Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20365" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="20">4.69</rating>
<name>Miriallia Haw</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She lives in Heliopolis, a space colony in Orb where she is enrolled in the technical college with Kira, Sai, Flay, Tolle and Kuzzey. She is inseparable with her boyfriend Tolle, almost attached at the hip, but they do not show their affection in public. Her personality is mature and well rounded.</description>
<picture>52600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20369" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="7">4.13</rating>
<name>Kojiro Murdoch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The chief mechanic of the Earth Alliance warship Archangel, whose small cadre of talented engineers keep the ship and its fighting vehicles in fine working order. Murdoch is gruff and informal, with a fatherly concern for the pilots who depend on his skills, and he always keeps an eye out for the young and inexperienced Kira.</description>
<picture>52604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20370" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="8">3.21</rating>
<name>Arnold Neumann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The ranking non-commissioned officer of the Earth Alliance warship Archangel, and one of the few survivors of the ship`s original crew. After the attack on Heliopolis, Neumann takes over as the ship`s pilot. Quiet and professional, he`s usually overshadowed by his charismatic superiors, but when the Archangel is locked down at the space fortress Artemis he takes charge and breaks the ship free.</description>
<picture>52605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20371" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="7">3.87</rating>
<name>Dalida Lolaha Chandra II</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10626" picture="38527.jpg">Toriumi Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20375" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="8">4.26</rating>
<name>Ledonir Kisaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An officer of the 21st Airborne Unit of the Orb Union`s ground forces. Kisaka was born in the town of Tassil in northern Africa, and when Cagalli travels to northern Africa to fight alongside the Desert Dawn resistance group, Kisaka accompanies her as a bodyguard. Well aware that it`s pointless trying to keep Cagalli out of trouble, he calmly tags along wherever she goes, in the process making sure that she doesn`t inadvertently reveal her true identity.</description>
<picture>52611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22114" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="5">2.87</rating>
<name>Crot Buer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clotho Buer is a talkative and quarrelsome person who is constantly arguing with his teammates. While he fights in his GAT-X370 Raider, he enjoys shouting out video game-inspired battle cries. Between missions he spends his time playing on a portable game system called the "Great Wonder Swan XXX (unknown number)".</description>
<picture>55974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4586" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22116" type="appears in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="71">1.86</rating>
<name>Flay Allster</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Flay, the daughter of Atlantic Federation Vice Foreign Minister George Allster, is a pretty, popular, and to some extent spoiled, Heliopolis technical college student. Her fiancé is Sai Argyle, as arranged for by their parents. She has received a love letter from Sai, which was mentioned in episode 1 of Gundam SEED. The only one of his friends she seems familiar with is Miriallia Haw, with whom she shares idle gossip shortly before ZAFT attacks Heliopolis. She only knows Kira Yamato as "Sai`s friend". She escapes the destruction of Heliopolis in a lifeboat and winds up on the Archangel when Kira retrieves it while piloting the GAT-X105 Strike.</description>
<picture>55978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22117" type="appears in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="25">7.64</rating>
<name>Natarle Badgiruel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natarle Badgiruel is the executive officer of the Archangel, and supervises the ship`s Combat Information Center. Natarle is stern and operates by the book, though she is willing to do almost anything to reach a certain end, even when it conflicts with Captain Ramius. Nevertheless, Natarle is a superb tactical analyst with keen judgment and a knack for swift decision-making, which made her a valuable asset to the Archangel. After Natarle leaves the Archangel on a transfer order while in Alaska, she is recruited by the Earth Alliance and made captain of the Dominion which forced her to battle against the Archangel. After witnessing the actions of Muruta Azrael of Blue Cosmos, Natarle chooses to defy the Earth Alliance which results in her and Azrael`s death</description>
<picture>55980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22118" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="17">6.26</rating>
<name>Nicol Amalfi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nicol Amalfi is the youngest member of the Le Creuset team; he pilots the GAT-X207 Blitz, which he steals during the raid on Heliopolis. He is mostly calm and good-natured, and becomes friends with Athrun Zala. His thoughts of the war are moderate, and he says in one episode that he joined ZAFT after hearing what happened to Junius Seven, but never really wanted to fight. A gifted musician, his favorite instrument was the piano. While trying to protect Athrun in battle near the Orb Union, Nicol is accidentally killed by Kira Yamato. His seiyu are Mami Matsui for the series and Romi Park in all future appearances.</description>
<picture>55982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22119" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="7">3.61</rating>
<name>Orga Sabnak</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Orga Sabnak is effectively the leader of the three biological CPUs. He uses tactics that are reckless and aggressive, causing him to often nearly hit his teammates while piloting his mobile suit, the GAT-X131 Calamity. He usually spends his time between missions reading paperback novels.[4] He is also the only member of the team to seem to care about the welfare of the other two; when Shani is killed, he screams out his teammate`s name, and tries to attack Yzak, his killer.
Unlike Clotho and Shani, who were killed by Yzak Joule, Orga was killed during the Second Battle of Jachin Due by Three Ships Alliance pilot Athrun Zala in the ZGMF-X09A Justice equipped with the METEOR. Athrun slices Orga in half from behind as he is dodging a beam from Kira.
From flashback sequences in Gundam SEED Destiny, Shinn Asuka`s family is killed by an explosion resulting from a crossfire between Orga`s GAT-X131 Calamity, and the ZGMF-X10A Freedom. It is never made clear which mobile suit, if not both of them, is the direct cause of their deaths.</description>
<picture>55983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30372" picture="79530.jpg">Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22120" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="5">2.84</rating>
<name>Shani Andras</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shani Andras pilots the GAT-X252 Forbidden. Shani is antisocial and prefers to fight alone to avoid interference from his teammates. In between missions, he blocks out the outside world by listening to music via headphones. His eyes are different colors, but his hair, which usually covers the left side of his face, conceals that fact.</description>
<picture>55985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4087" picture="26094.jpg">Miyamoto Shun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22121" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="10">5.58</rating>
<name>Aisha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Andrew Waltfeld`s devoted partner, both on the battlefield and in private life. This glamorous, coquettish young woman is also a capable strategist and mobile suit pilot. When Waltfeld enters battle in his two-seater command mobile suit, Aisha puts her Coordinator abilities to use as his gunner, so that her beloved Andy can concentrate on his piloting.</description>
<picture>55986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3304" picture="186561.jpg">Hirano Fumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22122" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="8">4.52</rating>
<name>Tolle Koenig</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tolle is another one of Kira Yamato`s friends who also lives on the neutral colony Heliopolis and the boyfriend of Miriallia Haw. Tolle was the first one to defend Kira, when Kira`s Coordinator heritage causes the Archangel`s soldiers to point their rifles at Kira. He serves as a co-pilot and operator of the Archangel. Later, he volunteers to pilot the second FX-550 Skygrasper, formerly piloted by Cagalli Yula Athha. He is ultimately killed in action by Athrun Zala.</description>
<picture>55987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6890">Inoue Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22136" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-07">
<rating votes="5">4.81</rating>
<name>Kuzzey Buskirk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22138" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="6">5.13</rating>
<name>Sai Argyle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sai is another friend of Kira Yamato from Heliopolis. When the colony is raided by ZAFT, he ends up with his friends on the Archangel. Sai is put in charge of enemy detection and electronic warfare identification on the CIC of the Archangel. Initially, Sai was in a relationship with Flay Allster but she breaks it off in favor of Kira, which enrages Sai to the point where he tries to move the Strike. Despite his humiliation, Sai does not try to win back Flay and comes to accept that she is with Kira, who is later reported MIA. With Kira gone, Flay attempts to restart her relationship with Sai, denying she ever felt any emotions for Kira but Sai refuses to believe her. Later, Flay is transferred from the Archangel before Operation Spit Break while Sai and the rest of the crew defect to Orb after they are saved by Kira in the stolen ZGMF-X10A Freedom. Sai makes peace with Kira, and the two of them remain on good terms for the remainder of their enlistment together. Sai continues to serve at his post on the Archangel throughout the rest of the war. During that time, he realizes Flay still cares for him in some respects when she calls his name specifically while trying to communicate with the Archangel, and he is deeply saddened when Flay dies at the hands of Rau Le Creuset. A short OVA set after the series shows him going back to a civilian life, one that apparently involves computers. He still keeps pictures of himself with Flay, despite their tumultuous history, and seems content with this new life.</description>
<picture>56032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22139" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">7.09</rating>
<name>Uzumi Nara Athha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uzumi Nara Athha, is the leader of the United Emirates of Orb and the adoptive father of Cagalli Yula Athha. He is known to be dedicated to the well-being of his nation and uncompromising on his own ideals and the ideals of Orb. When the Earth Alliance invades Orb to acquire their mass driver, Uzumi reveals to Cagalli that Kira Yamato is her brother and forces her to leave Orb before he self detonates it to prevent the Earth Alliance from using their equipment for war.</description>
<picture>56033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34697" type="appears in" update="2011-07-16">
<rating votes="3">3.04</rating>
<name>Erica Simmons</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9654" picture="49080.jpg">Yanagisawa Michiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34698" type="appears in" update="2011-07-16">
<rating votes="4">5.43</rating>
<name>Jackie Tonomura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4388.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="13050" picture="171761.jpg">Shibuya Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34699" type="appears in" update="2011-07-16">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Ray Yuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="632" picture="18159.jpg">Mito Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="44953" update="2005-12-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2004-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44954" update="2006-03-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2004-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44955" update="2005-12-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2004-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
