<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4187" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-04-15</startdate>
<enddate>2006-04-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Meitantei Conan: Tantei-tachi no Requiem</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Detective Conan - Requiem of the Detectives</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Detective Conan: The Private Eyes` Requiem</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Détective Conan - Film 10</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Детектив Конан: Реквиемът на Детективите</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">侦探们的镇魂歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Case Closed: Movie 10</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Detective Conan: Movie 10</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">名探偵コナン 探偵たちの鎮魂歌[レクイエム]</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Detektiv Conan - 10. Film: Das Requiem der Detektive</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Detective Conan: Requiem Per Un Detective</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ยอดนักสืบจิ๋วโคนัน เดอะมูฟวี่ 10 ตอน บทเพลงมรณะแด่เหล่านักสืบ</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Detective Conan 10 - El réquiem de los detectives (2006)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="266" type="Parent Story">Meitantei Conan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.conan-movie.jp/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="474" type="Original Work">Aoyama Goushou</name>
<name id="782" type="Animation Work">Tokyo Movie</name>
<name id="3743" type="Character Design">Sudou Masatomo</name>
<name id="3743" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sudou Masatomo</name>
<name id="4487" type="Direction">Yamamoto Yasuichirou</name>
<name id="4325" type="Music">Oono Katsuo</name>
</creators>
<description>Kogoro and Conan came to Yokohama according to a request from a mysterious man. But that was a trap of this man. Ran and the Detective Boys will be taken as hostages. If they don`t solve the request of the man within 12 hours, the bombs attached to the hostages will explode. Furthermore, the man know that Conan`s true identity is Kudo Shinichi. Also Hattori Heiji, the High School Detective of the West, and Kaito Kid enter the stage. Will they be able to solve the mystery within the time limit and save Ran and the others? And who in the world is the client?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="616">7.64</permanent>
<temporary count="627">7.80</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>231558.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6346</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7305</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1506</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3609</identifier>
<identifier>pmbnkr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20060630172813/http://www.conan-movie.jp/index2.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Case_Closed:_The_Private_Eyes'_Requiem</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>名探偵コナン_探偵たちの鎮魂歌</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>518</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324260</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8009</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1561</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>명탐정_코난_극장판_10기_-_탐정들의_진혼가</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>名偵探柯南_偵探們的鎮魂歌</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9690</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2260" type="main character in" update="2012-02-12">
<rating votes="1562">7.54</rating>
<name>Edogawa Conan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81480.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2263" type="appears in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="724">7.91</rating>
<name>Kudou Shin`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2343" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-03">
<rating votes="1032">7.69</rating>
<name>Mouri Ran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mouri Ran is one of the main characters in Detective Conan. She is the daughter of Mouri Kogoro, a famous but lazy detective. She is also friends with Kudo Shinichi, another famous detective, who is still in high school. She is the captain of the high school karate team, and is very strong willed.</description>
<picture>65742.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="321" picture="17158.jpg">Yamazaki Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8163" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="513">6.60</rating>
<name>Mouri Kogorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kogorou was once with the police, but due to an incident that involved his wife Eri as well, he quit. Due to the same incident, he and Eri split up.
He`s got custody of his daughter Ran who lives with him in an apartment that is at the same time his detective agency, on top of a café named Coffee Poirot. Despite of having been a good policeman, he`s a bad detective - but still very famous. That only comes due to the fact that Conan is "abusing" this adult`s sedated body to deduct his theories for the sake of outing the high amount of murderers whose crimes he solved.
Kogorou might be a smoking, drinking, good-for-nothing loudmouth with a high affection to idol Okino Youko, but he still is a good guy when it comes to handling his daughter or wife.
Due to Conan having made him famous as the Sleeping Kogorou, he sometimes gets over his head and just believes he`s the big shot everybody else thinks he is.
Kogorou finally accepts Conan as a "lodger", when Conan`s "mother" gave him access to an account filled with 10.000.000 Yen (about 90.000€/122.500$).
His voice is Number 59 on Conan`s bowtie.</description>
<picture>54062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8164" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-15">
<rating votes="255">3.94</rating>
<name>Agasa Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Agasa Hiroshi  is a good friend of Shin`ichi / Conan who invents several devices to help him out, such as the voice changing bowtie or the watch with which Conan can tranquilize people.
Note: His name Hiroshi is written with the kanji 博士, which can also be read `Hakase` (Professor)</description>
<picture>27247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8165" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-03">
<rating votes="987">8.25</rating>
<name>Haibara Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8167" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-23">
<rating votes="352">5.86</rating>
<name>Yoshida Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27250.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1623" picture="171605.jpg">Iwai Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8168" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-23">
<rating votes="138">2.86</rating>
<name>Tsuburaya Mitsuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8169" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-23">
<rating votes="106">4.42</rating>
<name>Kojima Genta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8170" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="388">5.35</rating>
<name>Suzuki Sonoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sonoko is Mouri Ran`s best friend and is the girlfriend of http://anidb.net/ch8180 [Kyougoku Makoto].
Source: detectiveconanworld.com</description>
<picture>28515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8172" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="54">7.65</rating>
<name>Kisaki Eri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kisaki Eri is Ran`s mother and the ex-wife of her childhood-friend Kogorou.
She`s also a famous lawyer.
Even though they`re divorced, Eri is still wearing her wedding ring. When asked by Ran about that, she answers that it keeps "other dirty men" away.
Ran hopes that her parents will find back together.</description>
<picture>27255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8173" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="109">5.22</rating>
<name>Tooyama Kazuha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazuha is a girl from Osaka. She`s been childhood friends with Heiji, and could be referred to as his girlfriend - even though they`re too shy / childish to admit it already.
When she meets Ran for the first time (episode 118) she directly explains to her that Heiji is off limits, and that the girl/woman that wants to get to him has to go through her fast - which makes her either protective or possessive of Heiji.
Later on Ran and Kazuha become really good girl friends.
Kazuha`s father, like Heiji`s, also works for the Osaka police.</description>
<picture>27256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="164" picture="16962.jpg">Miyamura Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8176" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-18">
<rating votes="4">9.77</rating>
<name>Hakuba Saguru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hakuba Saguru is another teenage detective, just like http://anidb.net/ch2263 [Kudou Shin`ichi] and http://anidb.net/ch8178 [Hattori Heiji]. However, he does a lot of his work in England, as well as Japan, and has maybe even handled more cases than Shin`ichi and Heiji.</description>
<picture>161184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8178" type="main character in" update="2010-01-31">
<rating votes="129">6.38</rating>
<name>Hattori Heiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="132" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8181" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-30">
<rating votes="82">8.55</rating>
<name>Takagi Wataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takagi Wataru (named after his voice actor who ad-lipped his own name in a scene) is a police officer from the Investigation Division (1st Division).</description>
<picture>29517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8182" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-03">
<rating votes="13">1.75</rating>
<name>Chiba-keiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8183" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-10">
<rating votes="62">3.55</rating>
<name>Megure Juuzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inspector Juuzou is a veteran police officer who has been working with http://anidb.net/ch2263 [Kudou Shin`ichi], http://anidb.net/ch8175 [Kudou Yuusaku] and http://anidb.net/ch8163 [Mouri Kogoro]. He always wears his hat to hide an old scar which reminds him of a special case from 20 years ago, during his early police days which involved his wife, http://anidb.net/ch16583 [Midori].</description>
<picture>27267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8184" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-10">
<rating votes="61">8.58</rating>
<name>Shiratori Ninzaburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28336.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8185" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-03">
<rating votes="127">5.46</rating>
<name>Satou Miwako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="580" picture="17973.jpg">Yuya Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8190" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-16">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Nakamori Ginzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inspector of the Police Headquarter`s Criminal Investigation Squad 2.</description>
<picture>30853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8191" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-28">
<name>Tooyama Ginshirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tooyama Ginshirou is the Head of the Oosaka Police Department.</description>
<picture>58193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="544" picture="238510.jpg">Ogawa Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8192" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-03">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Hattori Heizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4683" picture="27279.jpg">Koyama Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8193" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-03">
<name>Ootaki Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8200" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-03">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Yokomizo Juugo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8219" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-03">
<rating votes="218">8.44</rating>
<name>Kaitou Kid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9187" type="appears in" update="2009-07-07">
<rating votes="6">6.08</rating>
<name>Kuriyama Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s Kisaki Eri`s Secretary.</description>
<picture>30687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="628" picture="188442.jpg">Dodo Asako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10849" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-01">
<name>Miyama Souichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3093" picture="38195.jpg">Nojima Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10850" type="main character in" update="2009-08-01">
<name>Takada Masao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="275" picture="17102.jpg">Tahara Aruno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10851" type="appears in" update="2009-08-01">
<name>Ryuu Achiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10852" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-01">
<name>Homeless Kazu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10853" type="appears in" update="2009-08-01">
<name>Uranaishi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fortune teller.</description>
<picture>32380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2890" picture="23182.jpg">Sugiyama Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10854" type="appears in" update="2009-08-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>CRY Buin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2205" picture="186188.jpg">Hanba Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10855" type="appears in" update="2009-08-01">
<name>CRY Buin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10856" type="appears in" update="2009-08-01">
<name>Hittakuri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10857" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Shimizu Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3304" picture="186561.jpg">Hirano Fumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10858" type="main character in" update="2009-08-01">
<rating votes="2">1.35</rating>
<name>Itou Suehiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="49317" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2006-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50685" update="2006-06-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63183" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2006-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63184" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2006-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116950" recap="true" update="2010-03-17">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
