<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4191" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-09-02</startdate>
<enddate>2006-09-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Паприка</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">盗梦侦探</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">红辣椒</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">パプリカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Paprika - Sognando un sogno</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Paprika: Detective de los sueños</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Паприка</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">파프리카</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Papryka</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">פפריקה</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ลบแผนจากรรมคนล่าฝัน</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Паприка</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Paprika</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1265" approval="75" total="84">Mousou Dairinin</anime>
<anime id="154" approval="60" total="74">Perfect Blue</anime>
<anime id="570" approval="60" total="72">Sennen Joyuu</anime>
<anime id="6677" approval="19" total="38">Kuuchuu Buranko</anime>
<anime id="1834" approval="11" total="24">Mind Game</anime>
<anime id="4151" approval="3" total="11">Toki o Kakeru Shoujo</anime>
<anime id="4054" approval="2" total="8">Tekkon Kinkreet (2006)</anime>
<anime id="61" approval="1" total="12">Ghost in the Shell</anime>
<anime id="812" approval="1" total="4">Roujin Z</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="26">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372851">This is a very strange but good movie. It was a bit hard to understand some parts though.
In the end it was worth watching it.

If you like strange movies then this is something for you!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="97207">Definitely recommended! Very psychological, and touches some of the same themes as the Hollywood movie "Inception". Watch it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="218935">Suprising, and damn good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="54185">Brilliant music, story and animation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="317067">Very Satoshi Kon. I have a feeling I need to watch it again to fully grasp it, but beautifully done, amazingly animated and all the rest. Very good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="219874">Awesome</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="282922">really nice movie , must see ^_^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="8855">Thank God for anime!..that`s all I`ll say...such titles are rare but they save me from watching Hollywood crap. A must see my friend.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="188783">A wonderful mix of surrealism and brains, it is neigh impossible to predict the story development. Fast pace, involving, invigorating.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="208034">If ever there has been a better example of how to visualize dreams, I have yet to see it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="230513">To begin a totally masterpiece, must see! For people who like well through thought work. Awesome story line, awesome soundtracks. I do "recommend" it to people who have some anime experience or the fast "mindfuck" storytelling will be to much for ya. But totally worth in the end!

Dp</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="235114">What can I say, except that only Satoshi Kon can do this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="105473">Satoshi Kon at his finest here
OST and visuals are amazing</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://www.sonypictures.jp/he/815804</url>
<creators>
<name id="54" type="Direction">Kon Satoshi</name>
<name id="2974" type="Music">Hirasawa Susumu</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="8944" type="Original Work">Tsutsui Yasutaka</name>
<name id="4486" type="Character Design">Andou Masashi</name>
</creators>
<description>A beautiful therapist named http://anidb.net/ch15462 [Chiba Atsuko] and a genius scientist http://anidb.net/ch15464 [Tokita Kosaku] work for a psycho-medical institute. Tokita invented the DC-mini. It is an epoch-making device that brings them into a patient`s dream and enables them to monitor the patient`s inner world in order to cure him or her.
However, one day, the device was stolen by someone. Since then the dreams of those concerned with the project have been attacked one by one, and something is starting to go terribly wrong. Chiba begins to investigate the matter, using another identity though. She becomes the Dream Detective http://anidb.net/ch15461 [Paprika] who synchronizes with other peoples` dreams to remove their trauma. She rises against the dream terrorist who uses the DC-mini that is strong enough to destroy ones personality. But who is this criminal, and why commit these crimes? When the manipulated dream connects with the reality, an inner world no one has ever seen is revealed...
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="6123">7.80</permanent>
<temporary count="6165">7.98</temporary>
<review count="8">7.43</review>
</ratings>
<picture>228328.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6142</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1943</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3833</identifier>
<identifier>wtttsy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/2006-2005/works_movie_paprika.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.sonypictures.jp/he/815804</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sonyclassics.com/paprika/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Paprika_(2006_film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>パプリカ_(アニメ映画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2025</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>325630</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8748</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/4298</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>파프리카_(2006년_영화)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>盜夢偵探</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9718</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B000ZJ0AGU</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5335" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>dreams and reality</name>
<description>This genre of anime is typically set in both the world as we know it (reality) and a world of dreams, mythology or imagination.
Sometimes this dreamworld is actually real, sometimes it is not. Other times what we think is the real world is the dreamworld, and vice versa. They are not always easy to distinguish from each other, neither by the characters nor the viewer.
Whatever is real, and whatever is reality, both worlds are integral in shaping both the plot of this anime and the development of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15461" type="main character in" update="2010-03-03">
<rating votes="28">8.69</rating>
<name>Paprika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Under the guise of her alter ego Paprika she treats her clients inside their dreams.</description>
<picture>44033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15462" type="main character in" update="2010-03-03">
<rating votes="20">5.99</rating>
<name>Chiba Atsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiba Atsuko is the head of the DC Mini development team.</description>
<picture>44034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15463" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="11">6.23</rating>
<name>Konakawa Toshimi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konakawa Toshimi is a detective haunted by a recurring dream that stems from an anxiety neurosis.</description>
<picture>44035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15464" type="main character in" update="2010-03-03">
<rating votes="9">4.21</rating>
<name>Tokita Kosaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tokita Kosaku is a morbidly obese child-at-heart genius and the inventor of the DC Mini.</description>
<picture>44036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15465" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-03">
<rating votes="5">3.94</rating>
<name>Inui Seijirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The chairman of the Institute for Psychiatric Research.</description>
<picture>44037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15082" picture="44408.jpg">Emori Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15466" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-03">
<rating votes="1">1.99</rating>
<name>Himuro Kei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Colleague of Tokita. He worked under Tokita and helped him in his production of the DC Mini, but got jealous and disappeared.</description>
<picture>44038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15467" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">2.05</rating>
<name>Osanai Morio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Osanai Morio is a colleague of Atsuko.</description>
<picture>44039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15468" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-03">
<rating votes="6">4.66</rating>
<name>Shima Toratarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A gifted psychiatrist and the head of the department which is developing the DC Mini.</description>
<picture>44040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="710" picture="228657.jpg">Hori Katsunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="53545" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2006-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65256" update="2006-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">7.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88169" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<rating votes="2">8.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsutsui And Kon`s Paprika (Behind-the-scenes Feature)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88170" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Art Of Fantasy (Interview With Art Director Nobutaka Ike)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88171" update="2008-02-10">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">9.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">A Conversation About The `Dream`</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88172" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dream CG World</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97055" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2006-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97056" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2006-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
