<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="42" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>1998-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shadow Skill (1998)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">シャドウスキル</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shadow Skill TV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shadow Skill - Eigi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sstv</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ss tv</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">SHADOW SKILL ~影技~ (1998)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shadow Skill</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Shadow Skill</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Shadow Skill - Frère et sœur d`armes</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2977" type="Sequel">Shadow Skill: Kuruda-ryuu Kousatsu-hou no Himitsu</anime>
<anime id="348" type="Alternative Setting">Shadow Skill (1996)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="144215">Excellent old school anime</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sotsu-co.jp/property/details/021.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="4395" type="Music">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="102" type="Character Design">Kizaki Fuminori</name>
<name id="1411" type="Series Composition">Sogo Masashi</name>
<name id="1899" type="Original Work">Okada Megumu</name>
<name id="1924" type="Direction">Sunaga Tsukasa</name>
</creators>
<description>The Warrior Kingdom of Kuruda is home to the fiercest fighters in the world, men and women who live solely for the chance to fight, and become the greatest in the world. And no one is so intent on this goal as the young http://anidb.net/ch28743 [Gau Ban], who dreams of becoming a new generation of warrior. He and his adopted sister http://anidb.net/ch10160 [Elle Lagu], their companions, and the legendary http://anidb.net/ch28751 [Scarface] (Vai Low) train and battle for the mastery of the Shadow Skill.
Note: Shadow Skill began with the http://anidb.net/a2543 [pilot OVA], which was followed by the http://anidb.net/a348 [OVA series prequels]. This TV series begins the story anew and covers the same ground.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="873">5.54</permanent>
<temporary count="883">7.18</temporary>
<review count="4">6.24</review>
</ratings>
<picture>152881.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>729</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>441</identifier>
<identifier>okpcjq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shadow_Skill</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>SHADOW_SKILL</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88274</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1679</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10160" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="37">7.50</rating>
<name>Elle Lagu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elle Lagu is the 59th Sevaar of Kuruda. Though she is not the only female Sevaar in history - a title roughly equivalent to a high warrior, as an ordinary warrior is known as a Vaar - she does hold the distinction of being the youngest female ever to be awarded the title of Sevaar, at age 14, 3 years prior to the start of the series. Her fighting nickname Shadow Skill is also the name of her martial arts style.
Elle has an older brother: Diaz Lagu, a blacksmith and a Vaar of Kuruda. Their parents both died from a rampaging disease when Elle was still young, and she too contracted the same illness. Diaz immediately set out on many dangerous missions in order to raise the money needed for his sister`s medicine. Elle was saved, but Diaz` body was severely weakened by his ordeal, to the point that he had to give up on being a warrior, instead devoting himself to crafting his Black Wing boomerangs. Elle continues to feel guilt for this fact to this day, believing it should have been him to win this title, and not her. She also has a reputation as both a heavy drinker and a brawler, often acting without considering the consequences. A running joke throughout the series is how deeply in debt she is, and how any windfalls of money she might come into, always immediately go into either paying off the damages to her surroundings, or else into debts accumulated for the same reason.</description>
<picture>30532.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28739" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Iba Sutra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iba Sutra is the 55th Sevaar and is a master of Open Skill, and the twin brother of Jin Stolla, the leader of Septia troupe Phantom. He was once defeated in personal combat by Vai Low, which enabled Scarface to become the second High-Sevaar after Hawk Eyes, and was also the subject of an assassination attempt by G, Kain Phalanx, the rogue 58th Sevaar, who Scarface killed in defense of the king`s honor. He is the mentor of Scrib Lowengrin and guardian of his grand-niece Kyuo Luo, whom he took under his wing after her grandfather was killed when the monster kwown as the Moon King massacred the rest of their group of demon-beast-hunters.</description>
<picture>65875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28740" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<name>Kaira lu Luka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65873.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28741" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Kain Phalanx</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kain Phalanx is the 58th Sevaar of Kuruda, and goes by the moniker of G, the seventh letter in the Latin alphabet which symbolizes the strongest.</description>
<picture>65874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28742" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Kai Shink</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kai Shink, also known as Crimson and Raza Reme Silver Sword, is the 56th Sevaar. He is a master bladesman, wealthy businessman, and high-ranking officer of the Kurodan government. In addition to his status as a Sevaar, he is also a Raza Reme (the only sevaar ever to do so), a master of the divine power of Souma, and is the magical representative of his home country of Kuroda at the Holy City of Juliannes. He worked with Darkness to resurrect Black Wing, recipient of Ashliana`s highest honor, after Dias Rague died in a duel in which he defeated Darkness. Despite being the closest associate of his successor Scarface, he was responsible for giving him his famous scar when they fought in a duel before Vy Low became the 57th Sevaar.</description>
<picture>65880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28743" type="main character in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="5">5.37</rating>
<name>Gau Ban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gau Ban, also known as Black Howling, is a Vaar of Kuruda and Elle Lagu`s adopted brother.
His origins differ slightly between the OAV and anime. In the anime, Gau is ten when the attack occurs. Seeing his parents murdered in front of him, Gau snaps and attacks the bandits. He kills most of them, but then his luck runs out. Elle shows up before he himself is killed, and finishes off the remaining bandits. In the OAV, bandits attacked his home village when he was nine years old, slaughtering everyone, including Gau`s parents. Over the next year, Gau exercised guerrilla-style attacks against the bandits for revenge. He eventually encounters Elle on the road by chance.
Since Gau is the only survivor of his village, Elle takes him with her. Originally, Gau only intended to follow Elle in order to steal all her money and discover the source of her powers. However, after some time, Gau came to care for Elle like an older sister. Over the years, Gau has trained side by side with Elle in an effort to become strong. With his dedication and signs of promise, he quickly catches the attention of the 57th Sevaar, Scarface, who decides to help Gau improve, albeit only indirectly. Many incidents that Gau encounters are in some way or another engineered by Scarface, for the purpose of driving him to improve and become stronger.
He also catches the love-interest of Kyuo Lyu, however Gau is completely oblivious to her intentions. In an ironic turn of events, Scrib Lowengren, King Iba Sutra`s apprentice in Open Skills and effectively Gau`s rival in the race to become the next Sevaar, falls in love with Kyuo at first sight and a love triangle develops. The two of them battle each other several times, Gau eventually coming out the overall victor. In respect, Lowe gives Gau his earrings, which Gau wears during his most important battles.</description>
<picture>65860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29963">Matsuoka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28744" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="21">6.29</rating>
<name>Kyuo Lyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyuo Lyu is a former member of the Septia troupe Phantom, a group of trained hunters who tracked down demon-beasts, capturing and taming them for use in society. Her grandfather, Jin Stolla, was the leader of Phantom and considered to be one of the greatest Septias ever. When Phantom decided to go after the legendary demon beast, the King of the Moon, they had no idea what they were up against. The King of the Moon, whose powers of strength and regeneration were unstoppable while under the moonlight, destroyed an entire village. The Phantom unit tried to stop the beast but they were all wiped out just in one night. In the morning, Kyuo found the corpses of her teammates and buried them.</description>
<picture>65863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28745" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Scrib Lowengren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Scrib Lowengren is seen in minor roles in Shadow Skill parts 1 and 2. He is the personal apprentice to the Kuruda King, Iba Stol. Upon hearing of Gau`s emerging talent, Low challenged him at least twice. One challenge ended in a draw, the other ended in Gau forgetting all his fear and releasing the full power of Shadow Skill on the older boy. Now they are good friends, and two sides of an uneven love triangle involving Kyou. (Low likes Kyou, Kyou likes Gau. At least in the TV series. The manga has a different take on things.) He wears big, red, cherry-like earrings which play a role in Gau`s most crucial fight at the end of the series.</description>
<picture>65869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28746" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="3">9.67</rating>
<name>Diaz Lagu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diaz Lagu, known by his fighting name the Black Wing, is considered one of the strongest fighters that Ashlianna has ever seen. Thirsting for strength ever since he was a boy, Diaz earned a reputation during the war as a cold-blooded killing machine, he didn`t care who he fought or killed. He fought side-by-side with Kai Shinks and Vy Low, the 56th and 57th Sevaars Crimson and Scarface, eventually becoming close friends with both.
When Diaz turned 16, he was on his way to becoming the 58th Sevaar when his parents contracted a rare disease and died. Later on, his younger sister Elle was also infected. After losing both his parents, he would not stand by and watch his sister die. He decided to put his ambitions aside and went to fight as a mercenary so he could earn enough money to buy medicine for Elle. He succeeded and was able to save Elle`s life, but as a result of the extra battles that he fought in, his body was greatly weakened and had to give up his dreams of becoming a Sevaar. Because of this, the title of 58th Sevaar went to Kain Phalanx. Elle, feeling guilty about this, decided that she would take her brother`s place and become Sevaar and several years later, succeeded in becoming the 59th Sevaar.</description>
<picture>65871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28747" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<name>Feorina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21555">Takenouchi Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28748" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="8">5.54</rating>
<name>Faurinkmeier Plasmatizer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28749" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="2">6.75</rating>
<name>Lilbelt lu Viju</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28750" type="appears in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Lunaris Anbra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1436" picture="18822.jpg">Takagi Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28751" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="2">7.39</rating>
<name>Vai Low</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vai Low, the 57th Sevaar known as Scarface, is the most powerful warrior in the history of Kuruda. Receiving the title of High-Sevaar at the age of 16 when he defeated King Iba Sutra, the 55th Sevaar Hawk Eyes, in combat, he became the heir to the throne and a role model for the new generation of Vaar to follow. He seems to take a liking to Gau and Elle, Gau most especially. Like all Sevaar, he tends to put up an aloof air whenever he is in public, not even glancing at his own wife, Folstise, the Ordo Codex of Juliannes. He also seems to have something of a drinking problem, always having an extra bottle of booze sneaked into his cape.
When Gau Ban first traveled to Kuruda, Vai immediately recognized his potential. Throughout the series, he has played a prominent role in the molding of young Gau. He usually influences Gau in an indirect manner, such setting up battles for him to fight. At other times he would act like a father figure and give him advice that is completely in contrast to the ones given by Diaz. He is actually obsessed in making Gau in to the ultimate warrior, and as such he constantly seeks to test him somehow. Unbeknownst to Gau and the others, Vai is actually the elder son of Shere Kahn, founder of Yin-ryuu, and the older brother of Gau.</description>
<picture>65861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="252" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">我が一撃は無敵なり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Power of My Blow has No Equal!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waga Ichigeki wa Muteki Nari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7967" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決闘者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duelists</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kettousha-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7974" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファントムの忘れ形見</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom`s Keepsake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Phantom no Wasuregatami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8104" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父が遺したもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What My Father Left Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi ga Nokoshita Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8180" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誇り高き戦場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Proud Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokoritakaki Senjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8373" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白と黒の閃光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White and Black Flash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiro to Kuro no Senkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8735" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿命の対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Destined Confrontation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukumei no Taiketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8856" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間凶器.北へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dangerous Human Weapon. To the North</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningen Kyouki. Kita e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9537" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖都爆烈す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Violent Bombing of the Holy City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seito Bakuretsusu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9634" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白と黒の衝突</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash of White and Black</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiro to Kuro no Shoutotsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10159" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">侵攻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invasion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10618" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒き咆哮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Howling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroki Houkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10924" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友の心とともに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With the Heart of a Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo no Kokoro to Tomo ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11157" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月影神殿</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Temple of Moonlight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukikage Shinden</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11818" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亡霊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bourei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12085" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去からの襲撃者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Attacker From the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako kara no Shuugekisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12320" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅蓮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crimson</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guren</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12321" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第七の暁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seventh Dawn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dainana no Akatsuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12322" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">牙, 二代</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fang, 2nd Generation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiba, Nidai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12323" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇と死と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Darkness and Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami to Shi to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12324" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神音 -カノン-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cannon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12325" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あね, おとうと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Older Sister, Younger Brother</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ane, Otouto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12326" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚悟を決めろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prepare Yourself</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakugo o Kimero</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12327" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神の拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fist of God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami no Kobushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12328" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陰流の魔徒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ying-style Demon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12329" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">修練闘士[セヴァール]への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Path of a Sevaar</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120869" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120870" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120871" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
