<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="422" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-12-20</startdate>
<enddate>1997-12-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan - Ishinshishi e no Requiem</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Samurai X - The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin - Requiem for the Restoration Royalists</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kenshin - Samurai X</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Samurai X - Requiem for Meiji Restoration Patriots</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin: Ishin Shishi e no Requiem</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">RuroKen Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">RK Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">RK: ISnR</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">るろうに剣心 -明治剣客浪漫譚- 維新志士への鎮魂歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Samurai X: The Motion Picture</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Kenshin le Vagabond - Requiem pour les Ishin Shishi</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Kenshin: El Guerrero Samurái - La Película</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="90" type="Parent Story">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="264122">RECOMMENDED</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Movie/TV/Kenshin/eiga/</url>
<creators>
<name id="753" type="Animation Work">Gallop</name>
<name id="4451" type="Character Design">Tsuji Hatsuki</name>
<name id="4451" type="Direction">Tsuji Hatsuki</name>
<name id="8344" type="Music">Iwashiro Tarou</name>
<name id="509" type="Original Work">Watsuki Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="4451" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tsuji Hatsuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Walking around in Yokohama, http://anidb.net/ch443 [Kenshin], http://anidb.net/ch6620 [Sanosuke], http://anidb.net/ch6619 [Kaoru] and http://anidb.net/ch6618 [Yahiko] see a confrontation between some drunken western sailors and a Japanese woman. An armed samurai steps in front to protect the woman and soon a small riot breaks out with the samurai winning. The woman is actually the sister of a person Kenshin had killed at the end of the last dynasty. The samurai who introduces himself as http://anidb.net/ch21245 [Shigure Takimi] is unknown to Kenshin, he is trying to start a new revolution to overthrow the Meiji government.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3271">5.61</permanent>
<temporary count="3305">7.34</temporary>
<review count="1">8.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>204883.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>217</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>46</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>316</identifier>
<identifier>dewpiq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Movie/TV/Kenshin/eiga/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rurouni_Kenshin#Film</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>るろうに剣心#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E6.98.A0.E7.94.BB</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1015</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89728</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1564</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/718</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2692" parentid="2641" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-10">
<name>Bakumatsu - Meiji Period</name>
<description>"Bakumatsu" (幕末, "Late Tokugawa Shogunate") occurred between 1853 and 1867 during which Japan ended its isolationist foreign policy and modernized from a feudal shogunate to the Meiji government. Bakumatsu represents the final years of the Edo period (when the Tokugawa shogunate ended) and preceded the Meiji era. The primary historical significance of Bakumatsu was the conflict between the pro-imperialist "Ishin Shishi" ("nationalist patriots"), and the shogunate forces, including the elite Shinsengumi ("New Selected Corps").
The Meiji Era (including Meiji Restoration) denotes the 45-year reign of Emperor Meiji, running from 23 October 1868 to 30 July 1912. During this time, Japan started its modernization and rose to world power status.
Be aware that this category should only be assigned to anime that take place in Japan during the years mentioned above, and not to every anime that has samurai in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="443" type="main character in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="1034">9.06</rating>
<name>Himura Kenshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Set in a fictional version of Japan, during the pre-Meiji period, Kenshin is a former legendary assassin known as "Hitokiri Battousai". At the end of the Bakumatsu, he becomes a wandering samurai, now wielding a sakabatou ("reverse-blade sword"), a katana that has the cutting edge on the inwardly curved side of the sword, thus being nearly incapable of killing. Kenshin wanders the countryside of Japan offering protection and aid to those in need, as atonement for the murders he once committed as an assassin. In Tokyo, he meets a young woman named Kamiya Kaoru, who invites him to live in her dojo despite learning about Kenshin`s past. Throughout the series, Kenshin begins to establish lifelong relationships with many people, including ex-enemies, while dealing with his fair share of enemies, new and old. Through these encounters and relationships, Kenshin begins to find true atonement for his past enabling him to fully conquer his "Battousai" nature.</description>
<picture>84396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3011" picture="55684.jpg">Suzukaze Mayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6132" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="201">8.89</rating>
<name>Saitou Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saitou Hajime, based on the real-life personage of the same name, was the leader of the 3rd Squad of the Shinsengumi during the Revolution. He has a long-standing rivalry with Kenshin and firmly believes in "Swift Death to Evil".</description>
<picture>23318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6618" type="main character in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="64">4.48</rating>
<name>Myoujin Yahiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Myoujin Yahiko is a young boy, the son of a samurai. When he was younger, both of his parents died, and he was taken in by the Yakuza, who forced him to live as a pickpocket. Once he meets up with Kenshin and Kaoru, he decides to stand up to the Yakuza, and escapes with Kenshin`s help. He joins Kaoru`s dojo to become a stronger swordsman, becoming the first graduate of http://anidb.net/ch21040 [Kamiya Kasshin-ryuu]. Over the course of the series, he becomes a strong warrior. He hates being treated like a child.</description>
<picture>24367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3940" picture="54324.jpg">Tominaga Miina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6619" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="190">6.62</rating>
<name>Kamiya Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamiya Kaoru is a seventeen-year old dojo instructor and the first main character Kenshin meets. Kaoru is a teacher of the Kamiya Kasshin-ryuu style, a swords style used to protect people, and not harm others. Since her father was killed in the war, responsibility for running the family dojo fell to young Kaoru. After defending Kaoru from the fake Battousai and his allies, Kenshin is invited to live at the dojo. Kaoru quickly develops a crush on Kenshin, soon falling in love with him, although she tends to violently deny it. She recognizes that Kenshin, despite his violent past, is a gentle soul who only wants peace by atoning for the lives he stole during the revolution. Although, personality-wise, she is very different than Yukishiro Tomoe, Kenshin`s first love, (i.e. Kaoru is loud, brash, insecure, and cannot cook anything tasty), Kenshin sees that she is also selfless, compassionate, and caring of others almost to a fault. Her understanding of his nature and wanting to help him find the peace he so desires also draws him to her. In the manga, he is able to find atonement (and Tomoe`s smile) by protecting Kaoru`s happiness as well as his new friends. At the end of the series, she and Kenshin marry and have a son together.</description>
<picture>84399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9823" picture="36572.jpg">Fujitani Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6620" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="123">7.47</rating>
<name>Sagara Sanosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sagara Sanosuke is a street fighter who befriends Kenshin early in the series. As a youth, Sanosuke ran away from home to join the Sekiho Army, a group of farmers and merchants who fought for the Ishin Shishi during the Meiji Revolution. When the Sekiho were betrayed and executed by the other revolutionaries, Sanosuke escaped and began to pick fights to vent his anger. He challenges Kenshin, a former Ishin Shishi, but when Sanosuke is defeated he becomes one of Kenshin`s closest friends and strongest allies. Sanosuke enjoys fighting, gambling, and mooching off of other people.</description>
<picture>24369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6624" type="appears in" update="2010-07-28">
<rating votes="6">8.02</rating>
<name>Yamagata Aritomo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamagata Aritomo was one of Kenshin`s comrades. Yagamata grew a mustache since taking position of power in the Meiji government. Yamagata tries to convince Kenshin to stop carrying a sword, but Yamagata realizes that Kenshin`s openly-displayed sword and his actions as a rurouni ensure safety for others. In the anime, he appears again as the assassination target of a corrupt politician, Hashizume, but thanks to Kenshin, he was saved and Hashizume was arrested. Watsuki said that he could not get his version of Yamagata to resemble surviving photographs of the real Yamagata.</description>
<picture>24375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25007" picture="25535.jpg">Kaneko Holly</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20109" type="appears in" update="2010-07-28">
<rating votes="13">6.35</rating>
<name>Oguni Gensai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oguni Gensai is the doctor who takes Megumi as his apprentice. In the anime he has two grandchildren, Ayame and Suzume.</description>
<picture>52090.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20110" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="8">7.53</rating>
<name>Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayame and Suzume are Dr. Gensai`s grandchildren. They appear throughout several episodes in the anime.</description>
<picture>52119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3139">Yuasa Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20111" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="4">5.76</rating>
<name>Suzume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayame and Suzume are Dr. Gensai`s grandchildren. They appear throughout several episodes in the anime.</description>
<picture>52120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="337" picture="223875.jpg">Namiki Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20650" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">8.82</rating>
<name>Tsukioka Tsunan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born Katsuhiro, Tsukioka Tsunan is a survivor of the Sekihou Army after it was disbanded by the government. Called Katsu by Sanosuke, Tsunan became a printmaker after the Meiji Restoration. He is an expert at explosive weapons and gunpowder, and intends to use them against the Meiji government. When he and Sano try to embark on a terrorist campaign against the Meiji government later in the series, they are stopped by Kenshin. Since then, Kenshin buried his bombs and Katsu became a journalist for his own newspaper (in the anime Katsu buried his own bombs). Later on in the anime series, he becomes a valuable source of information for Kenshin and Sanosuke, serving as their intelligence source during the Feng Shui arc. However, he still makes bombs solely as a hobby-he has several to give Sanosuke just before following Kenshin to Kyoto.
Watsuki says that Tsunan originated from a false advertisement, labeled "Mysterious Artist Appears," within the series. When Watsuki created the extra Sanosuke chapters he created a "comrade from the Sekihou Army — lone explosive expert plotting overthrow of the government." Watsuki believed that this alone did not give Tsunan "interesting" qualities, so he added the "fake artist" trait. In Volume 6 Watsuki expressed a desire to use Tsunan at a later point since, at that point, he is the sole character with a "mass media" connection and therefore could have further use at a later point. Despite the fact that Tsunan is "a little depressing," Watsuki likes Tsunan`s "straightforward personality." Tsunan had no design model. Due to a lack of time Watsuki used an earlier concept of a man with dreadlocks; Watsuki believed that the concept "to my surprise, turned out to be just right." The author added that the character could be "a good villain." After making some "tweaks" the design assembled "quickly." Watsuki added the bandanna and the "oddly-patterned" jacket as he wanted "artist-y" clothing.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>53148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20701" type="appears in" update="2010-08-12">
<rating votes="3">4.37</rating>
<name>Kawaji Toshiyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kawaji Toshiyoshi is a government official who assists Ookubo.</description>
<picture>53233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20322" picture="186181.jpg">Shiga Katsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21233" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-30">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Takatsuki Toki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="164" picture="16962.jpg">Miyamura Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21245" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-01">
<name>Shigure Takimi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21246" type="appears in" update="2010-09-01">
<name>Musashino Yasuharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21247" type="appears in" update="2010-09-01">
<name>Kajiki Sadashirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21248" type="appears in" update="2010-09-01">
<name>Tamano Eibin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54271.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21249" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-01">
<name>Takatsuki Gentatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4996" update="2005-09-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>1997-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9489" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1997-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9490" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1997-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45391" update="2005-12-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Movie Promo</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
