<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4224" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>2006-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Soul Link</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ソウルリンク</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Связь душ</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">โซล ลิ้งค์</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">魂链</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sl</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Soul Link</title>
<title xml:lang="id" type="official">Tautan Jiwa</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="81120">really nice</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="473284">This anime is made for people who played and enjoyed soul link for the PC. You`ll be impressed to find some new characters and to see things play out similarly in some ways but find a lot of unexpected differences that keep things fresh. Again, unlike Fate/Stay night, Soul Link is a anime that can only be enjoyed by those who played the visual novel, but those few who this applies to will be in for an enjoyable experience.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="213088">Not bad, for those who like it &amp;gt; try playing the game ...</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="969" type="Animation Work">Picture Magic</name>
<name id="1011" type="Original Work">Navel</name>
<name id="6722" type="Music">Sawano Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="6878" type="Original Work">Suzuhira Hiro</name>
<name id="4540" type="Character Design">Watanabe Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="6209" type="Series Composition">Tokoro Toshikatsu</name>
<name id="6209" type="Direction">Tokoro Toshikatsu</name>
<name id="4540" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="6260" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hayakawa Naomi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a game by http://anidb.net/cr1011 [Navel].
Aries, an old tourist space station outside Earth`s orbit doubles as a preparatory training facility for the Central Military Academy students, the temporary home of http://anidb.net/ch29315 [Aizawa Ryouta], a third year, and his classmates, including his love interest, http://anidb.net/ch29314 [Nagase Sayaka], his unacknowledged rival, http://anidb.net/ch29310 [Nitta Kazuhiko], and the proclaimed genius http://anidb.net/ch29316 [Aizawa Shuuhei], his older brother.
The space station is attacked by the terrorist group, Hallarax, and after helping in the evacuation of the majority of the civilians and staff, Ryouta, his friends, and a handful of others are left to battle for control of the space station as Hallarax threatens Earth with nuclear retribution.
Holed up in a separate section of the station, the group holds their own against the terrorists until the emergence of a third enemy, wrought with treachery and greed, creates unlikely bonds of camaraderie in the struggle to protect themselves, each other, and ultimately, Earth.
— written by Quaenorde</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1572">2.81</permanent>
<temporary count="1606">6.15</temporary>
<review count="5">4.89</review>
</ratings>
<picture>213955.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6469</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>854</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1625</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10373</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3627</identifier>
<identifier>gouuya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Soul_Link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Soul_Link#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>812</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324644</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8110</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>소울_링크</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5820" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-29">
<name>combat butler -- DO NOT ADD -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is meant to be deleted. Please DO NOT add it to further anime. Please tag the relevant characters "butler" and whatever combat- or martial arts-related tag is appropriate. For the already tagged anime, please tag the relevant characters, and then remove this tag from the related anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29306" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="2">6.44</rating>
<name>Karen Tachibana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A terrorist, and former soldier, that is skilled in hand-to-hand combat as well as firearms. An enthusiastic personality. She may seem insubordinate, but she respects Gale, and sees him as a father figure. She grows a liking for Kazuhiko and in the end, she is seen in a dress meeting up with him.</description>
<picture>153862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4613" picture="65544.jpg">Shouji Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29307" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Gale Lantis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1998" picture="21301.jpg">Nagasako Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29308" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="3">4.00</rating>
<name>Cellaria Markelight</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Instructor on the Aries Station. Appears to be very caring towards her students.
She is revealed to be the perpetrator and mastermind of the attack on the station. She ends up betraying the terrorists on the station and takes it over herself, with her Sukyura soldiers. She is considered to be the perfect Sukyura being and controls those who possess the Sukyura cells. She becomes intrigued with Shuhei since he is the only one that she cannot fully control. In the end, she is destroyed by Nanami.</description>
<picture>153857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16799" picture="186162.jpg">Tezuka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29309" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="4">6.78</rating>
<name>Yuu Yamanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A passenger on the Aries Station who is quiet and mysterious.
She was revealed to be a mercenary and seems to have had a relation with Shin when she was younger.</description>
<picture>153863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4945" picture="77631.jpg">Shimakata Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29310" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Nitta Kazuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A brilliant computer specialist and hacker. He builds a rivalry with both Aizawa brothers, though he does have a high respect for Shuhei.</description>
<picture>153860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29311" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="3">4.00</rating>
<name>Sugimoto Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Childhood friend of Sayaka Nagase. A clumsy, but kind personality. Ever cheerful at all times.</description>
<picture>153861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29312" type="main character in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="3">5.57</rating>
<name>Morisaki Nao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morisaki Nao is Aizawa Shuhei`s girlfriend. She isn`t a fighter but is more like a paramedic/nurse. Her personality is very warm and compassionate.</description>
<picture>153856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="568" picture="65531.jpg">Sakuma Kumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29313" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Morimoto Shigemichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Steward of the Aries Station. He takes care of all passengers and acts as the general manager. A helpful personality.
He is revealed to be Sayaka`s father, who had left her when she was just a child. Unfortunately, he is killed before being able to tell her himself.</description>
<picture>153859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29314" type="main character in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="4">5.43</rating>
<name>Nagase Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1888" picture="228611.jpg">Masuda Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29315" type="main character in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="2">6.96</rating>
<name>Aizawa Ryouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3295" picture="38451.jpg">Ogihara Hideki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="1993" picture="158098.jpg">Inoue Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29316" type="main character in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="4">7.77</rating>
<name>Aizawa Shuuhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29317" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="3">4.00</rating>
<name>Inatsuki Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inatsuki Nanami is a strange and young girl found on the Aries Station. She is later found out to be a creation of Sukyura cells and human cells; basically a result of when Shuhei and Nao consummated their relationship (In a way, she is their "child"). She calls Shuuhei, her `father`, and Nao, her `mother`. In the end, she became the one that destroyed Cellaria, as she was the only who can counter Cellaria`s ability to spread Sukyura cells.</description>
<picture>66645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16133" picture="18167.jpg">Yanase Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29318" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="3">4.84</rating>
<name>Nitta Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nitta Aki is the younger sister of Kazuhiko Nitta. An even better computer hacker. She does not have a stable relationship with her older brother, as the two would always argue when they see each other. Although, when they were younger, it seems that she used to look up to Kazuhiko until she realized that her brother was not serious in anything back then. In the end, she and her brother get along, and she once again looks up to him.</description>
<picture>66646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5815" picture="30271.jpg">Oono Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33416" type="appears in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="4">1.66</rating>
<name>Masato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Masato is a litte blue-haired boy who appears in all games and their respective anime adaptations of the eroge maker Navel. He is usually seen mischievously lifting the skirts of the heroines.</description>
<picture>73444.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="87390" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-31">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22083" picture="58333.jpg">Ishikawa Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="47657" update="2006-03-17">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2006-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promotion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47658" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ENCOUNTER -出会い-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Encounter - Deai</title>
<summary>Space Station Aries is a popular sightseeing destination as well as a training ground for military cadets. Newly-minted cadets and childhood friends Ryouta and Nao gets news of a sudden visitor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788304</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="48661" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">CONTACT -接触-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Contact</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Contact - Sesshoku</title>
<summary>Despite the regimented nature of military training on a space station, resourceful young cadets manage to sneak around during training to meet up with an old friend, a brother, and a boyfriend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788305</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="49150" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">OUTBREAK -勃発-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Outbreak</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Outbreak - Boppatsu</title>
<summary>Space Station Aries undergoes an emergency evacuation as terrorists on a shuttle arrive and hack into the station.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788308</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="49341" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BREATHING SPACE -休息-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Breathing Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Breathing Space - Kyuusoku</title>
<summary>After an initial battle, the terrorist group demands that the surviving cadets and other personnel turn themselves in as hostages.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788310</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="49368" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">WATERSHED -分岐点-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watershed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watershed - Bunkiten</title>
<summary>The terrorists make a concerted effort to break into the holdouts` stronghold, but "super-soldier" Shuuhei leads the others in a risky defense.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788312</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="49809" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FAREWELL -別れ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Farewell - Wakare</title>
<summary>Cellaria is captured and the rebel survivors don`t know it, but one of their allies is secretly working with the terrorists.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788313</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="49822" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FLUX -流転-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flux - Ruten</title>
<summary>Shuuhei confronts the traitor and learns what the terrorists are truly after.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788315</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="49995" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DESIRE -願い-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Desire - Negai</title>
<summary>Gale, the deposed terrorist leader, is on the run with former hostage Aya, while Scylla makes pools of slime out of his comrades.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788317</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50431" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ROUSE -覚醒-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rouse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rouse - Kakusei</title>
<summary>Shuuhei has transformed into an unkillable Perfect Scylla, but is held captive by the true enemy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788319</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50522" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">STRAY -迷走-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stray</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Stray - Meisou</title>
<summary>The villain`s backstory is finally revealed, while sibling rivals Kazuhiko and Aki come up with a way for the group to escape the space station.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788322</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50523" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MOURNING -哀悼-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mourning</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mourning -Aitou-</title>
<summary>Half-human hybrid Nanami makes a desperate ploy to prevent the villain from infecting every human being on Earth with Scylla cells.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788325</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50524" update="2019-09-19">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">JOURNEY -旅路-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Journey - Tabiji</title>
<summary>As the remnants of Space Station Aries fall to Earth, some survive and some make the ultimate sacrifice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788327</identifier>
<identifier>soul-link</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51322" recap="true" update="2011-06-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別回想編 CELLARIA/NANAMI</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cellaria/Nanami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Kaisou Hen: Cellaria / Nanami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128232" update="2011-06-09">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぬくもりをずっと 七央×秀平</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Forever Warm - Nao X Shuuhei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nukumori o Zutto - Nao X Shuuhei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128233" update="2011-06-09">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本当の気持ち 亜希×和彦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Feelings - Aki X Kazuhiko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hontou no Kimochi - Aki x Kazuhiko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128234" update="2011-06-09">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の出会い 沙佳×涼太</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meeting of the Two - Sayaka X Ryouta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Deai - Sayaka X Ryouta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128235" update="2011-02-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128236" update="2011-02-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
