<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4239" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>2006-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Simoun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shimuun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Simoon</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Шімун</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">西蒙</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">シムーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Simoun</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="581" approval="29" total="46">Last Exile</anime>
<anime id="10766" approval="10" total="11">Cross Ange: Tenshi to Ryuu no Rondo</anime>
<anime id="5842" approval="7" total="18">Bounen no Xamdou</anime>
<anime id="5970" approval="6" total="13">Strike Witches (2008)</anime>
<anime id="2826" approval="2" total="9">Koukyoushihen: Eureka Seven</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="34249">`</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="131253">Another forgotten gem found!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="178968">Difference in art compared to the norm, epic storyline, with twists and characters that bring out the best out of everything, is a must watch. just endure the first 4 episodes.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.simoun.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="2241" type="Direction">Nishimura Junji</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="4246" type="Character Design">Nishida Asako</name>
<name id="4246" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishida Asako</name>
<name id="25802" type="Original Work">Oyamada Fuukyoushi</name>
</creators>
<description>In the world of Daikuuriku, everyone is born female, and chooses which sex they wish to become at age 17. In this world, the peaceful theocracy of http://anidb.net/ch91322 [Simulacrum] is guarded by magical flying machines called Simoun, which can only be piloted by young girls who haven`t chosen a sex yet. The Simoun can activate a magical power known as Ri Maajon that destroys large numbers of enemies at once. When the industrialized nation of http://anidb.net/ch91320 [Argentum] decides that it needs to invade Simulacrum to acquire the secret of the Simoun, war breaks out, drawing the Simoun Sibyllae (priestesses who fly the Simoun) into a lopsided battle. Because the war is raging, the Sibyllae are granted an exemption from choosing a permanent sex for as long as they`re willing to keep flying. http://anidb.net/ch5104 [Aaeru], a determined young Sibylla with a mysterious past, and http://anidb.net/ch5105 [Neviril], the leader of http://anidb.net/ch91316 [Chor Tempest], Simulacrum`s most elite Simoun squadron, must lead their fellow priestesses through conflict both within their ranks and in the sky.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1517">5.94</permanent>
<temporary count="1537">7.23</temporary>
<review count="6">6.80</review>
</ratings>
<picture>231539.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6287</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>879</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3640</identifier>
<identifier>xzyfyb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.simoun.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Simoun_(TV_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>シムーン_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>835</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324929</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8094</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1456</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2006/simoun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12273</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3550" parentid="6021" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-05">
<name>sex change</name>
<description>Someone in this anime has his/her body changed to the opposite gender.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3818" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-21">
<name>kids in war</name>
<description>When minors participate in armed conflict.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5150" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-11">
<name>asymmetric warfare</name>
<description>Asymmetric warfare is war between conflicting groups whose relative military power differs, or whose strategy or tactics differ significantly.
Asymmetric warfare can describe a conflict in which the resources of two groups differ in essence, and in the struggle, they interact and attempt to exploit each other`s weaknesses.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6271" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>sister-sister incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between two sisters.</description>
<picurl>210913.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5104" type="main character in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="14">6.54</rating>
<name>Aaeru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A brash young sibylla who joins Chor Tempest as one of three replacements for combat losses in the first battle against Argentum. She immediately takes a liking to Neviril, and pushes to become Neviril`s new Pair after Amuria is lost. Aer fits the stereotype of the fighter pilot, and has little patience for the sibyllae`s role as priestesses. She volunteered for combat after serving as a cadet on the southern front, and possesses an outstanding flying ability. Normally, she flies auriga, whether it`s with Neviril or other sybillae.</description>
<picture>21482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2126" picture="145389.jpg">Niino Michi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5105" type="main character in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="8">6.10</rating>
<name>Neviril</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Sibylla Aurea, and the Regina of Chor Tempest. She has a reputation for being the best Auriga in the entire Simoun fleet, and is the object of admiration of both the other Sibyllae and the cadets aboard Arcus Prima. She is so revered that junior Sibyllae are reprimanded for addressing her without an honorific even in her absence. She is the daughter of Halconf, the chief administrator of Simulacrum`s government.</description>
<picture>21483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="608" picture="18012.jpg">Takahashi Rieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5106" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="4">3.19</rating>
<name>Paraietta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Second-in-command of Chor Tempest, and a respected Sibylla. She flies as an auriga, paired with Kaim. She has a stern, masculine manner, and joined Corps Tempest because she is Neviril`s childhood friend. She remains very loyal to Neviril.</description>
<picture>21484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5107" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="4">5.38</rating>
<name>Kaimu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A diffident sibylla with large round glasses, who flies sagitta aboard Paraietta`s Simoun. She is Alty`s older sister, though she harbours a great hostility towards Alty as a result of their having had sexual relations in the past. Although she can be very nice, she is also alert and easily roused. She harbours an unrequited love for Paraietta.</description>
<picture>21485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2131" picture="29260.jpg">Hosokoshi Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5108" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="4">5.38</rating>
<name>Alty</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Floe`s pair, and wears her hair in a chin-length bob parted in the middle. She harbours a "sister complex" toward her older sister, Kaim. She flies auriga, paired with Floe.</description>
<picture>21486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5109" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="6">5.79</rating>
<name>Floe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An energetic orange-haired sibylla. She flies sagitta with Alty. She is very forward with her feelings, and is not shy about expressing them, much to the chagrin of the stricter sybillae, such as Paraietta.</description>
<picture>21487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2130">Aizawa Michiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5110" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="5">6.24</rating>
<name>Rodoreamon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A gentle, feminine Sibylla from an important family. Everyone addresses her as ojou-sama, be it for respect or in a joking manner, but treats her with a degree of deference and softness. She flies with Elly until Elly leaves to go to the Spring, and has a deep knowledge of sibylla traditions. As children, she and Mamina met, but were divided by the class difference between them.</description>
<picture>21488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5111" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="7">6.84</rating>
<name>Rimone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An extremely young sibylla assigned to Chor Tempest as a replacement for the losses from the first battle. She was promoted to the rank of sibylla at an unusually early age due to her flying ability and sharp intellect. She is very fond of sweets, and can frequently be seen snacking on some treat or other. While truly a genius sybilla, due to her young age, Rimone lacks combat experience and, plagued by an incident occurred due to her past confidence, is initially prone to frighten out. This changes after she is encouraged by Aer and then paired with Dominuura.</description>
<picture>21489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5112" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-11">
<rating votes="6">6.62</rating>
<name>Dominuura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The eldest of all Sibylla. She is connected to ruling circles in Simulacrum, and was the only survivor of the destruction of Chor Dextra after that choir attempted to perform the Emerald Ri Maajon. She joins Chor Tempest at Guragief`s request, to try to sort out Rimone and the rest of the choir, and from there on she flies as a sagitta, paired with Rimone. She has mysterious political connections to a faction within the Simulacran administration. While initially rejected by her pair, she eventually forms a deep bond of affection with Rimone.</description>
<picture>21490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5113" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="4">5.90</rating>
<name>Morinas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another of the replacement Sibylla who joins Chor Tempest after the first battle of the war. She pursues Neviril for a time when she first joins the choir, but eventually gives up. She has a keen interest in understanding how the helical motors that power the Simoun work, and is a compulsive flirt.</description>
<picture>21491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5114" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="6">5.64</rating>
<name>Amuria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Neviril`s Sagitta until the first battle against Argentum. She was a very determined sibylla, keenly interested in the Simoun as instruments of power. She and Neviril had been a pair, and romantically partnered, ever since Neviril first joined Chor Tempest.</description>
<picture>21492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5115" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="3">6.31</rating>
<name>Guragief</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The overall commander (or "Dux") of the Simoun forces aboard Arcus Prima, which consist of Chor Tempest, Chor Rubor, and Chor Caput. He is responsible for personnel decisions, and dispatches the Simoun fleet on their missions. He is very empathetic, and cares deeply about the Sibyllae in his care.</description>
<picture>21493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5116" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="3">7.00</rating>
<name>Anubituf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of the Arcus Prima. He is a responsible, determined warrior and a wise commander. He and Guragief were Sibyllae together before they went to the Spring, and the two have remained close ever since.</description>
<picture>21494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2128" picture="216210.jpg">Kiuchi Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5117" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<name>Onasia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The High Priestess of the Tempus Spatium, and presides over the gender selection ceremony at the Spring. Daikuurikans are born female, and choose a sex at age 17; in Simulacrum, this is done by going to the Spring at the temple of Tempus Spatium. As head of Simulacrum`s High Council, she serves as head of state. She is the last survivor of Chor Dextra, and has lived for many generations; she once had another name, and part of the mystery of the series is to discover who she is.</description>
<picture>21495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5118" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="8">8.70</rating>
<name>Mamina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A skilful but haughty sibylla, formerly assigned to Chor Ignis aboard the Arcus Niger, who joins Chor Tempest at Halconf`s request. Her parents were servants to Roatreamon`s family. Despite her humble origins, she was promoted to Sibylla rank when she volunteered for combat duty when other Sibyllae refused. Her hobby is cooking, and she also enjoys cleaning and other domestic chores.</description>
<picture>21496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="330" picture="171543.jpg">Morinaga Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5119" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="6">6.48</rating>
<name>Yun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mamina`s sagitta before the two join Chor Tempest. She speaks very bluntly, refers to herself using masculine pronouns, and hates war. She is devoutly religious, sincerely committed to the cause of peace, and loves to read. She holds herself aloof from the rest of Chor Tempest, and is often quiet and no-nonsense with the other sybillae.</description>
<picture>21497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5120" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-22">
<rating votes="2">6.31</rating>
<name>Wapourif</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A maintenance technician for the Simoun aboard the Arcus Prima. He went to the Spring under the temple of Tempus Spatium two years before the beginning of the series, and chose to become male. He had a crush on Floe, but did not become close because she was a Sibylla.</description>
<picture>21498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="238" picture="49561.jpg">Mizusawa Fumie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91291" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Halconf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Halconf is the father of Neviril and the vice-chair of Simulacrum`s high council, second only to Onasia. He is a former sibylla, and takes a keen interest in Chor Tempest and in Neviril`s career.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2049" picture="228615.jpg">Soumi Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91292" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Elly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elly turns 17 shortly after the start of the series, and goes to the Spring under the temple of Tempus Spatium. She is friends with Neviril, and ask her to accompany her to the Spring, because she has not made up her mind as to which sex she prefers to be.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91293" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Vura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vura is a member of Chor Rubor, and is assigned to be Aaeru`s roommate aboard Arcus Prima. She develops a rivalry with Chor Tempest at first, but grows to respect them. She`s the substitute of Mamina after her death.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4663" picture="27209.jpg">Hayasaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91294" type="appears in" update="2017-09-08">
<name>Anglas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anglas is a priestess of the deity "Animus" from the neighbouring country of Plumbum. When Plumbum and Simulacrum hold a peace conference, she is seconded to Chor Tempest for a time on the theory that Animus and the Tempus Spatium are the same deity.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91295" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Wauf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wauf is the captain of the old-timer patrol-ship Messis. He went to the Spring under the temple of Tempus Spatium long ago, and looks like a middle-age man. He has brilliant skill and knowledge of tactics, and cares for his new passengers, the Simoun sybillae of Chor Tempest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="685" picture="24841.jpg">Takano Urara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91308" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Mastif</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mastif is one of the soldiers stationed on Messis during their joint mission with Chor Tempest. He and Floe are mutually attracted to each other, but their relationship is cut off, when he witnesses the destructive power of Simoun in his hometown.</description>
<picture>206910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91309" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Kyuushu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Chief Priestess is the second highest religious official in Simulacrum. She is in conflict with the High Council, because she believes that Simoun shouldn`t be used for warfare.</description>
<picture>206914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91310" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Shiheiin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Defence Minister is responsible for military policy in Simulacrum.</description>
<picture>206915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="693" picture="226546.jpg">Igarashi Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91311" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Aaeru no Sofu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91312" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Chor Caput</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="91313" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Chor Rubor</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="91314" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Chor Ignis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="91315" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Chor Dextra</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Chor Dextra is a legendary choir created only for the sake of completing the Emerald Ri Maajon. Eventually most of its members died, and it was disbanded without fulfilling its goal.</description>
</character>
<character id="91316" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Chor Tempest</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="91317" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Arcus Niger</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>206917.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="91318" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Messis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>206918.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="91319" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Arcus Prima</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>206919.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="91320" type="appears in" update="2017-10-25">
<name>Argentum Shoukoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Argentum is the most scientifically advanced country of Daikuuriku. At the same time air pollution is becoming a serious problem for it, and as a solution it`s trying to acquire the Simoun of Simulacrum. Unlike Simulacrum its citizens` gender is determined as soon as they are born through medication and surgery.</description>
</character>
<character id="91321" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Plumbum Reikoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Plumbum is a theocracy, where a god called Animus is worshipped. It`s a cold country where every winter many freeze or starve to death.</description>
</character>
<character id="91322" type="appears in" update="2017-09-09">
<name>Simulacrum Kyuukoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Simulacrum is a theocracy where Tempus Spatium is worshipped. It is invaded by its neighbouring countries, because it`s the only country where Simoun are excavated. It doesn`t have a large military, but it manages to protect itself due to the Simoun`s overwhelming power on the battlefield.</description>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="47919" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promotion (1:51)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47920" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">堕ちた翼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fallen Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ochita Tsubasa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48700" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青い泉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Izumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48701" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠い戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distant War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tooi Sensou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48702" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">近い戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nearby War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikai Sensou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49691" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白い孤独</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Solitude</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Kodoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49692" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傷と痛み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wounds and Pain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizu to Itami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49915" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">公海上空にて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Above the Open Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukai Joukuu nite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49932" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祈り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prayer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50295" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">審問</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hearing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinmon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50574" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">籠の鳥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Caged Bird</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kago no Tori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50575" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">共同戦線</title>
<title xml:lang="en">United Front</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoudousensen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50576" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">姉と妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Elder and Younger Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ane to Imouto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50925" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">理</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reason</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotowari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51070" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冒さざるもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inviolate Object</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okasazaru Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51368" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一人, また一人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One by One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitori, Mata Hitori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51535" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">翠玉のリ・マージョン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Emerald Ri Maajon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigyoku no Ri Maajon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52049" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遺跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ruins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52050" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">葬列</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Funeral Procession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souretsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52051" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シヴュラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sibylla</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sibylla</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57246" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘆きの詩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Elegy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nageki no Uta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57247" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新天地への扉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Door to a New World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Tenchi e no Tobira</title>
</episode>
<episode id="58269" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sortie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="58270" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eternal Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62126" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選択</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Selection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62127" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pair</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62128" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女達の肖像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Their Portrait</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo-tachi no Shouzou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134986" update="2011-12-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134987" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135133" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143912" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (Pre-air, 0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197633" update="2018-03-31">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツッコミ映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Skit Clips</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukkomi Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197634" update="2018-03-31">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2007-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">純二と亜沙子のよくわかる! シムーン講座3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Junji and Asako`s Easy to Understand Simoun Lesson 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junji to Asako no Yoku Wakaru! Simoun Kouza 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197635" update="2018-03-31">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">純二と亜沙子のよくわかる! シムーン講座2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Junji and Asako`s Easy to Understand Simoun Lesson 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junji to Asako no Yoku Wakaru! Simoun Kouza 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197636" update="2018-03-31">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2006-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">純二と亜沙子のよくわかる! シムーン講座1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Junji and Asako`s Easy to Understand Simoun Lesson 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junji to Asako no Yoku Wakaru! Simoun Kouza 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197653" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2007-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SIMOUN 月刊! アフレコ通信 #5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Simoun Monthly! Post-Dub Transmission #5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Simoun Gekkan! Af-Reco Tsuushin #5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197654" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2007-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SIMOUN 月刊! アフレコ通信 #4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Simoun Monthly! Post-Dub Transmission #4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Simoun Gekkan! Af-Reco Tsuushin #4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197655" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2006-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SIMOUN 月刊! アフレコ通信 #3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Simoun Monthly! Post-Dub Transmission #3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Simoun Gekkan! Af-Reco Tsuushin #3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197656" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2006-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SIMOUN 月刊! アフレコ通信 #2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Simoun Monthly! Post-Dub Transmission #2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Simoun Gekkan! Af-Reco Tsuushin #2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197657" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2006-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SIMOUN 月刊! アフレコ通信 #1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Simoun Monthly! Post-Dub Transmission #1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Simoun Gekkan! Af-Reco Tsuushin #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197658" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2006-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月刊! アフレコ通信すぺしゃる SIMOUN シビュラ・アウレア争奪パル対抗ゲーム大会!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Simoun Monthly Post-Dub Transmission Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekkan! Af-Reco Tsuushin Special: Simoun Sibylla Aurea Soudatsu Pair Taikou Game Taikai!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197659" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (Airing, 0:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197660" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (Pre-air, 0:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197661" update="2018-04-01">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (Airing, 0:15)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
