<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4240" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-04-13</startdate>
<enddate>2006-07-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hime-sama Goyoujin</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Princess Be Careful</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Princess Beware</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Будьте осторожны, принцесса</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">公主请小心</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">himehime</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">姫様ご用心</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="795721">I like the character design. The opening song is kinda stuck in my brain. Not much to say tbh. If you like slapstick humor, you probably like this anime.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.himehime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1055" type="Original Work">Nomad</name>
<name id="3644" type="Character Design">Koga Makoto</name>
<name id="3644" type="Chief Animation Direction">Koga Makoto</name>
<name id="7012" type="Original Work">Takayanagi Shigehito</name>
<name id="7012" type="Direction">Takayanagi Shigehito</name>
<name id="9947" type="Music">Harada Katsumichi</name>
<name id="1055" type="Animation Work">Nomad</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch16917 [Himeko] is supposed to be a common high school student... until she happens to obtain a crown and she becomes a princess. Since then, http://anidb.net/ch16913 [Nana], the true princess, follows her around to take the crown back. In addition, http://anidb.net/ch16909 [Leslie] and http://anidb.net/ch16907 [Karen], the thieves, appear to rob her of the crown, and her peaceful life turns into turmoil.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="193">3.71</permanent>
<temporary count="193">6.12</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>10289.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6417</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1884</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3641</identifier>
<identifier>btyhoa</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.himehime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hime-sama_Goyōjin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>姫様ご用心</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>828</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324877</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7994</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>小心啊公主</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16904" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-16">
<rating votes="2">2.01</rating>
<name>Adron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16905" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-21">
<rating votes="2">3.07</rating>
<name>Banana</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16906" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-16">
<rating votes="2">2.01</rating>
<name>Imo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16907" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-21">
<rating votes="3">4.98</rating>
<name>Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16908" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-16">
<rating votes="2">1.57</rating>
<name>Kode Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16909" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-21">
<rating votes="2">2.01</rating>
<name>Leslie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="622" picture="214429.jpg">Tadano Youhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16910" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-16">
<rating votes="1">2.88</rating>
<name>Miss Yoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16911" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-21">
<rating votes="4">3.66</rating>
<name>Misuzu Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46674.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2032" picture="186151.jpg">Yoshizumi Kozue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16912" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-21">
<rating votes="4">5.00</rating>
<name>Nabana Sobana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16913" type="main character in" update="2010-04-21">
<rating votes="3">2.88</rating>
<name>Nana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="184" picture="23381.jpg">Miyazaki Ui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16914" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-21">
<rating votes="1">1.69</rating>
<name>Oz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16915" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-16">
<rating votes="1">2.53</rating>
<name>Rasse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216265.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16916" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-16">
<rating votes="1">1.69</rating>
<name>Tsubaki Ebine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216264.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16917" type="main character in" update="2010-04-21">
<rating votes="5">3.22</rating>
<name>Tsubaki Himeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16918" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-16">
<name>Tsubaki Sanjurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="49239" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オカン王冠こりゃあかん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Mother. My Crown. My goodness.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okan Oukan Korya Akan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57770" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あやうしテニスの王女様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch Out For The Princess Of Tennis!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayaushi Tennis no Oujo-sama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57771" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お客は刺客で絶体絶命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Guest Is An Assassin Driven Mad!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okyaku wa Shikaku de Zettai Zetsumei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57772" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしの彼はさわぎすぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Boyfriend Makes Too Much Noise!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no Kare wa Sawagisugi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57773" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">姫子誰の子ニャン子の子!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Himeko Is Who`s Child? A Cat`s!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himeko Dare no Ko Nyanko no Ko!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57774" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニャンコの国のナーナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Na-Na From The Kingdom Of Cats</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyanko no Kuni no Na-Na</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57775" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝手に指定, 師弟に決定!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Arbitrarily Decided, Teacher-Student Relationship!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katte ni Shitei, Shitei ni Kettei!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57776" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝訴? 敗訴? 言ってみそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Victory? Defeat? Try And Guess!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouso? Haiso? Ittemiso!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57777" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バイトヤバイと知らないと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Didn`t Know Part-Time Work Was This Dangerous!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baito Yabai to Shiranai to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57778" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">取れた王冠ばれたらいかん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fact That The Crown Can Be Taken Off Must Be Kept Secret!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totareta Oukan Baretara Ikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57779" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナーナのために世界はあるの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This World Exists Just For Na-Na!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Na-Na no Tame ni Sekai wa Aru no</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57780" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界はいいかげんで良(い)い加減</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This World Is Right ...For a Change!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai wa Ii Kagen de Ii Kagen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125484" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125485" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
