<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="427" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>5</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-12-21</startdate>
<enddate>2004-10-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Macross Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Макросс Зеро</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">마크로스 Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Macross 0</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Макрос Зеро</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">MZ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">m0</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mzero</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マクロス ゼロ</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">마크로스 제로</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="77" type="Sequel">Choujikuu Yousai Macross</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9556" approval="39" total="51">Suisei no Gargantia</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="210645">Must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="284802">Don´t ask just watch:)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="738147">Have very cool transformation and fight scenes. Great mecha series to watch. Wow worthy. Aside from the Alien plot thing, everything works out pretty good.

Recommended for mecha/jet fighter/macross/transformable fans</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="93928">1 word: excellent</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="476533">Most awesome animation and graphics ever.  You will love this if you are a mecha fan.  Absolutely a must see!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.macross.co.jp/zero/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="152" type="Direction">Kawamori Shouji</name>
<name id="38090" type="Character Design">Saitou Takuya</name>
<name id="38090" type="Chief Animation Direction">Saitou Takuya</name>
<name id="1126" type="Original Work">Studio Nue</name>
<name id="2318" type="Music">Haishima Kuniaki</name>
<name id="152" type="Original Work">Kawamori Shouji</name>
</creators>
<description>In the year 1999 a huge extraterrestrial battleship crash-landed on Earth, bringing the human race in contact with very advanced technology. Human short-sightedness and the greed to be the only one to possess this technology led to the war between the UN and the Anti-UN Eight years have passed since then, killing so many veteran pilots that even boys in their teens had to be recruited to fight the war.
http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Kudou Shin], a young UN F-14 pilot is shot down by an unknown enemy fighter plane during a sortie and crash-lands on a solitary island.
Coincidentally, an unusual energy surge is detected on this island. Both sides of the conflict suspect the surge originated from remnants of the Proto-culture`s advanced technology, left behind by extraterrestrial beings in ancient times. As it turns out this technological legacy is very similar to the recovered fallen extraterrestrial battleship that crashed eight years ago.
Now, both the UN and the Anti-UN struggle to be the first to recover the technology of extraterrestrial origin by invading the island... bringing death and destruction to the peaceful islanders.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3798">7.52</permanent>
<temporary count="3840">8.02</temporary>
<review count="7">8.30</review>
</ratings>
<picture>83856.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>939</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5165</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5164</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>194</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1129</identifier>
<identifier>ydnqvj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.macross.co.jp/zero/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Macross_Zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マクロス_ゼロ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2752</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239548</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5887</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5767" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Itano circus</name>
<description>The Itano circus is named after Itano Ichirou, a Japanese animator, and refers to a highly stylized and acrobatic method of depicting aerial combat and dogfights in many anime, particularly the Macross series, where it was utilised by Itano for the first time and was ground-breaking.
The Itano circus is characterized by detailed, fluid shading of the mecha, the close-range acrobatic moves the duelling fighters make in combat, as well as twisting contrails left by fighters and missiles. It is also commonly used in specific reference to an attack where a mecha or spaceship launches a large swarm of missiles with meticulously animated spiralling smoke trails and erratic trajectories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10505" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-14">
<rating votes="33">8.56</rating>
<name>Roy Focker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roy Focker is an American who was born and lived in the United States in the late 20th century. During his college school days he had interest in prehistorical civilizations and archeology studies, and was in a relationship with his senior http://anidb.net/ch14115 [Aries Turner]. However, after being left by her, Roy dropped his studies and became a stunt pilot in the air circus led by http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru]`s father. Some time later he decided to join the U.N. Spacy after most of his friends died in the U.N. Wars. His flight instructor during this time was D.D. Ivanov.
During the war Roy became a talented and strong-willed fighter pilot, known for his love of women and alcohol. Focker was selected later as one of the first test pilots for the development of the variable fighters by the U.N. Forces. In 2008 he is deployed as a squadron commader with the Skull Team aboard the stealth carrier CVN-99 Asuka II on a secret mission in the South Pacific and flies the VF-0 Phoenix in battle against the SV-51s of the Anti-U.N. Forces. The work done on the VF-0 helps the coinciding development of the VF-1 Valkyrie.
Despite his long absence during the U.N. Wars and the death of http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru]`s father, http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] still remained a close friend to Roy and considered him his sempai (upperclassman/big brother figure). After the end of the U.N. Wars, Focker involved himself in the VF-X development project flying both the VF-X and the VF-X-1 (non-transformable and transformable flight test prototypes of the VF-1 Valkyrie), and his flight experience earned him the command of the VF-1 Skull Squadron aboard the super-large-scale semi-submersible attack aircraft carrier http://anidb.net/ch48774 [CVS-101 Prometheus].
During Space War I Roy Focker is still a smoking, drinking womanizer who constantly defies death and, when not on another desperate mission, enjoys life and its pleasures to the fullest. He has a relationship with http://anidb.net/ch10509 [Claudia LaSalle], an officer stationed on the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] bridge.Roy dies in episode 18 ("Pineapple Salad"), from wounds sustained while defending http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] from http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia Fallyna]`s force of Queadluun-Rau battle suits. Instead of going to the hospital to treat his wounds, he chooses to play the guitar while waiting for http://anidb.net/ch10509 [Claudia LaSalle] to finish her pineapple salad; while she`s cooking for him, he collapses from a sudden internal bleeding and passes away few minutes later. To http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru]`s chagrin given his then shaken self-confidence in his flying skill in war, he is promoted as the new leader of Roy`s squadron, using his mecha as well.
In http://anidb.net/a996 [The Super Dimension Fortress Macross: Do You Remember Love?] 1984 film adaptation of the original TV series, the character Roy Focker dies aboard an alien Zentradi ship while fighting http://anidb.net/ch10516 [Quamzin Kravshera]. In the movie Roy sacrifices himself to let both http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru] and http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase Misa] escape.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>31541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14110" type="main character in" update="2012-11-10">
<rating votes="4">6.30</rating>
<name>Kudou Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kudou Shin is a Japanese/American fighter pilot flying for the UN. As a child in 1999, he witnesses the fall of the Macross and the following U.N. Wars. His family is killed before his eyes, a memory that would haunt him and turn him into a quiet and untrusting person. He joins the U.N. Spacy as an F-14 fighter pilot. During a mission he is shot down by the anti-U.N.`s transformable SV-51 and lands in Mayan Island. He later flies the VF-0 Phoenix variable fighter under the tutelage of http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker]. Aside from his rear-seat radar intercept officer, http://anidb.net/ch14116 [Edgar LaSalle], he has few friends and is slow to trust. His interactions with the cheerful http://anidb.net/ch14112 [Mao Nome] and his growing attraction to her more reserved sister, http://anidb.net/ch14111 [Sara], help him open up.During the final episode, the extraterrestrial object known as http://anidb.net/ch50522 [Tori no Hito] by the Mayan people awakens, assimilating http://anidb.net/ch14111 [Sara] into the cockpit located at its head. He manages to break through the http://anidb.net/ch50522 [Tori no Hito]`s attacks and makes http://anidb.net/ch14111 [Sara] realise that it is Shin instead of an evil spirit (called a "Kadun" by the Mayans). The UN forces, however, see the http://anidb.net/ch50522 [Tori no Hito] as a liability and launch reaction weapons at it. http://anidb.net/ch14111 [Sara] sacrifices herself to save Shin and the rest of the Mayan Island which would have been destroyed by the nuclear fallout. The http://anidb.net/ch50522 [Tori no Hito] is critically damaged from the blasts and shoots off into space incredibly fast in what appears to be a space fold. Shin`s VF-0 suffers engine damage from the blasts and plunges towards the ocean. He is seemingly saved from certain death by http://anidb.net/ch14111 [Sara]. Finally, an amazed http://anidb.net/ch14112 [Mao Nome] watches Shin and his damaged fighter ascending into space in the same way that the http://anidb.net/ch50522 [Tori no Hito] did, supposedly to be with http://anidb.net/ch14111 [Sara]. In the tenth episode of the 2007 sequel http://anidb.net/a5415 [Macross Frontier], the events of Zero are portrayed in a movie. Frontier protagonist http://anidb.net/ch2167 [Saotome Alto], a former kabuki actor, agreed to appear as Kudo during an underwater sequence that the original actor refused to do.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>79233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14111" type="main character in" update="2012-11-10">
<rating votes="8">6.70</rating>
<name>Sara Nome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Since childhood Sara Nome has been groomed to become Mayan Island`s priestess/shaman, a position of great spiritual importance to the people of the secluded island. It also means having the "mystical power" of interacting with the island`s mysterious alien ruins, a little-understood ability that she manifests through singing an ancient Mayan chant. She also gets occasional visions into the future. This power seems to run through her family`s blood as her little sister Mao also displays the same abilities to a lesser degree.</description>
<picture>41482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14112" type="main character in" update="2012-11-10">
<rating votes="26">6.23</rating>
<name>Mao Nome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Mayan people who live in an island on the South Pacific, Mao initially knows nothing but her home, like her older sister http://anidb.net/ch14111 [Sara]. Mao`s fascination with the technology that the outsiders bring masks her deep mystical link to the island`s mysterious alien ruins, a link she shares with her sister. The sudden arrival of http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Kudou Shin] to the island in 2008 sparks dreams of freedom in eleven year old Mao, who then yearns for a life in the cities beyond the island. Unlike her older sister http://anidb.net/ch14111 [Sara], she is carefree and spritelike. She becomes infatuated with http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Shin], impressed by his skill in manipulating and repairing the island`s scarce machinery.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>41483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="83" picture="38901.jpg">Nanri Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14113" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-10">
<rating votes="2">4.53</rating>
<name>D.D. Ivanov</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As a former U.N. Spacy pilot, D.D. (or "Daisy" as he is affectionately known by his friends and comrades) was http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker]`s instructor. After defecting to the Anti-U.N. side, D.D. becomes the leader of a squadron of experimental SV-51 variable fighters. The reason for his defection remains unknown. Sent by the Anti-U.N. as part of the team investigating the alien ruins in Mayan Island, the mission brings him into conflict with his former student, http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Focker]. An intense rivalry develops between the two as they continue to dogfight to a standstill throughout the whole campaign.Ivanov was later killed when his SV-51 was blown apart by the power of the http://anidb.net/ch50522 [Tori no Hito] while attempting to avenge the death of his lover and wingman http://anidb.net/ch14114 [Nora Polyansky].Source: wiki</description>
<picture>41485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14114" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-10">
<rating votes="3">6.66</rating>
<name>Nora Polyansky</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nora Polyansky debuts as a 25-year-old Anti-U.N. variable fighter pilot who single-handedly takes down a squadron of U.N. Spacy F-14`s, including one piloted by protagonist http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Kudou Shin], with the new Anti-U.N. SV-51 variable fighter. Highly skilled in both flying and close quarters combat, she is dedicated to the defeat of the U.N. forces who have killed her family and inflicted a huge scar, both physical and mental, upon her. She is attached to the SV-51 squadron led by http://anidb.net/ch14113 [D.D. Ivanov] and acts as his wingmate, right hand pilot and lover. Ruthless in her mission, she represents http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Shin]`s chief rival in the sky and on the ground.She is killed in the final episode of the series by an energy blast from the Protoculture biomecha known as the http://anidb.net/ch50522 [Tori no Hito] while attempting to shoot down http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Shin]`s VF-0.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>41486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14115" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-10">
<rating votes="3">4.18</rating>
<name>Aries Turner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 26-year-old government researcher known for her genius-level intelligence. She studies and gives top secret seminars about the Protoculture research being undertaken by the U.N. She has known http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker] in the past, before the events that will take place in the South Pacific Ocean one year before Space War I.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>41487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14116" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-10">
<rating votes="2">4.53</rating>
<name>Edgar LaSalle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shin`s wingmate and friend.</description>
<picture>41488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6992" picture="31978.jpg">Komori Sousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14117" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-10">
<rating votes="2">4.53</rating>
<name>Nutuk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Mayan Island tribal chief.</description>
<picture>41489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50482" type="appears in" update="2012-11-09">
<name>CVN-99 Asuka II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Asuka II originally began service as a standard-power aircraft carrier with Japan Maritime Self-Defense Force. However the vessel was transferred to operations with the U.N. Forces by the Japanese unification government upon joining the U.N. government. Asuka II was then completed as a nuclear-powered aircraft carrier and deployed as the de facto mobile base of first VF-0 special duty combat test unit (Skull Team) in 2008. In addition, engineers assigned to the VF-0 development and maintenance were transferred aboard the Asuka II to maintain these difficult units.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/asuka.htm</description>
<picture>127876.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50483" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-09">
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<name>Nakajima Raizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakajima Raizou is the chief maintenance officer for the aircraft aboard the http://anidb.net/ch50482 [CVN-99 Asuka II]. The tuning of the VF-0`s conventional jet engines has put his top-ranked mechanical skills to the test. He regards his aircraft and their upkeep above all else. As such, he verbally abuses his aircrafts` pilots--even as he gives them his grudging respect.
Source: http://macross.anime.net/wiki/Raizou_Nakajima</description>
<picture>127877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50484" type="appears in" update="2012-11-09">
<name>F-14A++ Super Tomcat</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Two-seat main carrier-based fighter for fleet defense and attack. First flight of development aircraft 1970 December 21. Total number produced: 575. Service life extended with upgrades implementing Overtechnology in avionics and other areas.
Source: http://macross.anime.net/wiki/F-14_Tomcat</description>
<picture>127886.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50485" type="appears in" update="2012-11-09">
<name>MiG-29</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Mikoyan MiG-29 (Russian: Микоян и Гуревич МиГ-29; NATO reporting name: "Fulcrum") is a fourth-generation jet fighter aircraft designed in the Soviet Union for an air superiority role. Developed in the 1970s by the Mikoyan design bureau, it entered service with the Soviet Air Force in 1983, and remains in use by the Russian Air Force as well as in many other nations. The NATO name "Fulcrum" was sometimes unofficially used by Soviet pilots in service.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>127885.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50486" type="appears in" update="2012-11-09">
<name>SV-51 Alpha</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>In 2007, the Unification Wars ended badly for the Anti-U.N. and the United Nations Government firmly established itself on Earth. Despite their loss, the A.U.N. held considerable influence and resources, using both to continue espionage against the U.N.G. Armed with OverTechnology illicitly obtained from the U.N.G.`s military programs, the A.U.N. developed their own variable fighter designated the SV-51. Built and flown before the VF-1 series of the U.N. Spacy, the SV-51 is powered by overtuned conventional engines rather than the more powerful thermonuclear reaction engines. Nonetheless, the SV-51 was designed to be a practical combat machine and operational deployment revealed the SV-51`s stability in battle over that of the U.N.G.`s competing VF-0 fighter. In September 2008, the SV-51 entered active service in the A.U.N. and was utilized in a recovery operation of an alien artifact around the island of Mayan in the South Pacific Ocean, the details of this conflict remaining secret for nearly 50 years.
The SV-51 is a large fighter with numerous weapons and fully variable systems. Capable of transforming into both GERWALK and Battroid mode, the SV-51 utilized one Gsh-371 55mm gun pod as its primary weapon. The SV-51 also featured a fixed mini-gun (two in SV-51γ) and six hard points for mounting missile launchers and auxiliary fuel pods. Several additional systems added to the effectiveness of the SV-51 including a high-efficiency active stealth system and two fan jets for VTOL capabilities in fighter mode. In comparison, the U.N.G.`s VF-0 fighter possessed a lower output stealth system and no such VTOL capabilities in fighter mode. Though the SV-51 enjoys numerous advances over last-generation conventional fighters, the craft does suffer from several design flaws. The size of the aircraft places a burden on the transformation actuators leading to a longer transformation time from one mode to the next. Lacking thermonuclear reaction engines needed to properly operate a variable fighter meant the SV-51 has a much shorter range due to high fuel consumption. Rathering than cruising to a destination using it`s own fuel, it was often necessary for the SV-51 to be transported to the operational area, typically by a modified submarine and launched from underwater. The SV-51 was jointly developed by Sukhoi, Israel Aircraft Industries and Dornier and progressed 1-2 years earlier than the VF-0 schedule (reaching a practical stage by the end of the UN War). The SV-51 is first combat-type variable fighter (VF) in history that members of the Anti-UN Alliance developed for combat against giant aliens. Like the VF-0 Phoenix of the U.N. Forces, the SV-51 was a developmental unit. However, the SV-51 was unlike the hastily combat-equipped VF-0 Phoenix in that the Anti-U.N. craft was considered for use in actual combat from the very beginning.
The SV-51 saw very limited production, with 32 mass-production type SV-51α (alpha) units manufactured (a dozen would have been modified for the SV-52). A further 6 two-seater variants were built and a small but unknown number of specially tuned versions designated the SV-51γ. A.U.N. ace pilots http://anidb.net/ch14114 [Nora Polyansky] and http://anidb.net/ch14113 [D.D. Ivanov] flew SV-51γ (gamma) fighters during the events around the island of Mayan in 2008.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/sv-51.htm</description>
<picture>127880.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50487" type="appears in" update="2012-11-09">
<name>SV-51 Gamma</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>In 2007, the Unification Wars ended badly for the Anti-U.N. and the United Nations Government firmly established itself on Earth. Despite their loss, the A.U.N. held considerable influence and resources, using both to continue espionage against the U.N.G. Armed with OverTechnology illicitly obtained from the U.N.G.`s military programs, the A.U.N. developed their own variable fighter designated the SV-51. Built and flown before the VF-1 series of the U.N. Spacy, the SV-51 is powered by overtuned conventional engines rather than the more powerful thermonuclear reaction engines. Nonetheless, the SV-51 was designed to be a practical combat machine and operational deployment revealed the SV-51`s stability in battle over that of the U.N.G.`s competing VF-0 fighter. In September 2008, the SV-51 entered active service in the A.U.N. and was utilized in a recovery operation of an alien artifact around the island of Mayan in the South Pacific Ocean, the details of this conflict remaining secret for nearly 50 years.
The SV-51 is a large fighter with numerous weapons and fully variable systems. Capable of transforming into both GERWALK and Battroid mode, the SV-51 utilized one Gsh-371 55mm gun pod as its primary weapon. The SV-51 also featured a fixed mini-gun (two in SV-51γ) and six hard points for mounting missile launchers and auxiliary fuel pods. Several additional systems added to the effectiveness of the SV-51 including a high-efficiency active stealth system and two fan jets for VTOL capabilities in fighter mode. In comparison, the U.N.G.`s VF-0 fighter possessed a lower output stealth system and no such VTOL capabilities in fighter mode. Though the SV-51 enjoys numerous advances over last-generation conventional fighters, the craft does suffer from several design flaws. The size of the aircraft places a burden on the transformation actuators leading to a longer transformation time from one mode to the next. Lacking thermonuclear reaction engines needed to properly operate a variable fighter meant the SV-51 has a much shorter range due to high fuel consumption. Rathering than cruising to a destination using it`s own fuel, it was often necessary for the SV-51 to be transported to the operational area, typically by a modified submarine and launched from underwater. The SV-51 was jointly developed by Sukhoi, Israel Aircraft Industries and Dornier and progressed 1-2 years earlier than the VF-0 schedule (reaching a practical stage by the end of the UN War). The SV-51 is first combat-type variable fighter (VF) in history that members of the Anti-UN Alliance developed for combat against giant aliens. Like the VF-0 Phoenix of the U.N. Forces, the SV-51 was a developmental unit. However, the SV-51 was unlike the hastily combat-equipped VF-0 Phoenix in that the Anti-U.N. craft was considered for use in actual combat from the very beginning.
The SV-51 saw very limited production, with 32 mass-production type SV-51α (alpha) units manufactured (a dozen would have been modified for the SV-52). A further 6 two-seater variants were built and a small but unknown number of specially tuned versions designated the SV-51γ. A.U.N. ace pilots http://anidb.net/ch14114 [Nora Polyansky] and http://anidb.net/ch14113 [D.D. Ivanov] flew SV-51γ (gamma) fighters during the events around the island of Mayan in 2008.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/sv-51.htm</description>
<picture>127881.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50488" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-09">
<name>Robert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127882.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3441" picture="149777.jpg">Sasaki Seiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50489" type="appears in" update="2012-11-09">
<name>VF-0A Phoenix</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>During development of the VF-1 Valkyrie, the U.N. Spacy development teams found it necessary to utilize other variable fighters as test beds and trial production models for the various new OverTechnology systems. The VF-0 Phoenix was one such variable fighter begun in 2002, an experimental series of VF manufactured after inheriting the F-14 Tomcat experimental system group. Delivery of the first completed craft occurred in 2004 and in 2008 the VF-0 Phoenix was utilized in combat when delivery of the thermonuclear reaction engines delayed deployment of the VF-1 Valkyrie. Although the VF-0 was used for various tests and strategic research, it was not considered for combat until reports the Anti-UN Alliance organized a VF experiment combat group. Once the Anti-UN threat of a variable vehicle surfaced, the VF-0 was equipped for actual combat and productions increased rapidly. The transformation mechanisms, energy conversion armor and active stealth capabilities would have a major impact on later VF development and would be placed into practical use after the VF-1 Valkyrie. The Phoenix was deployed around the island of Mayan in the South Pacific Ocean that same year and many VF-0 variable fighters participated in an operation to combat Anti-U.N. forces for the purpose of recovering of an alien artifact.
The VF-0A was the primary fighter of the series, possessing many of what would become the standard variable fighter technologies including the famous three-mode variable transformation system. Unfortunately, the lack of thermonuclear reaction engines meant the VF-0A was deployed with larger conventional (but overtuned) jet engines and dorsal conformal fuel tanks. These problems seriously limited the operational range of the VF-0A and ultimately meant the series would remain a small production model. Nonetheless, the VF-0A was combat worthy and possessed a Mauler laser cannon, one standard Howard GPU-9 35mm gatling gun pod (with 550 rounds) and four underwing hard points with a variety of missile loads. For defense, the VF-0A featured the first incarnation of the energy converting armor system which utilized surplus power to triple fighter mode`s armor strength in battroid mode (a similar system would become standard in all future variable fighters). The VF-0A could also be fitted with the leg/engine nacelle conformal missile/fuel tanks for increased firepower and range, these parts belonging to the VF-1 "Super Pack" that were not yet fully completed.
The VF-0A was a successfully deployed unit, but was only produced in small numbers as production resources were devoted to the more advanced VF-1 Valkyrie that would follow. The U.N. Spacy manufactured 24 VF-0A general-issue single-seater fighters, 4 two-seater fighters and 2 two-seater armed reconnaissance units. Six single-seat types and 18 two-seater types of the delta wing VF-0D units were constructed as well as 4 VF-0S commander versions. Also built was VF-0B two-seater versions of the A type for the UN Spacy produced under trial basis and VF-0C single-seat versions of the D type for testing by the Marine Corps who were struggling with aging aircraft. U.N.G. pilots http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Kudou Shin] and http://anidb.net/ch14116 [Edgar LaSalle] piloted VF-0 fighters as did ace pilot http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker] when conducting operations around the island of Mayan in 2008.
NOTE: During development of the Macross game for the Playstation 2, when the VF-0 was being considered for inclusion, it was named "Phoenix" (ultimately, the VF-0 was not included in the game). This "pet name" was then dropped only to reappear in 2008 on the official Macross Frontier website. The Macross Chronicle (2008) has since made the name "Phoenix" official.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/vf-0a.htm</description>
<picture>127883.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50490" type="appears in" update="2012-11-10">
<name>VF-0S Phoenix</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The VF-0S was a variant of the VF-0 built to be utilized by the more experienced commanders of flight groups. While largely identical to the standard VF-0, the "S" variant featured a new head unit with two Mauler laser cannons rather than a single cannon on the "A" variant. In addition, the VF-0S removed the integrated control system`s limiters by default allowing skilled pilots to maximize their control of the VF-0S in all modes. Renowned ace pilot http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker] piloted a VF-0S during the events surrounding the island of Mayan in 2008. Although only an estimated 4 units of the VF-0S were manufactured, the variable fighter was utilized in a number of sorties and http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Focker] himself piloted several modified variants including a FAST Pack equipped version and the VF-0S Reactive Armor unit.
NOTE: During development of the Macross game for the Playstation 2, when the VF-0 was being considered for inclusion, it was named "Phoenix" (ultimately, the VF-0 was not included in the game). This "pet name" was then dropped only to reappear in 2008 on the official Macross Frontier website. The Macross Chronicle (2008) has since made the name "Phoenix" official.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/vf-0s.htm</description>
<picture>127904.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50499" type="appears in" update="2012-11-10">
<name>VF-0D Phoenix</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The VF-0D Phoenix is a two-seat variant of the standard VF-0 variable fighter and features larger main wings for improved range. For maneuverability, the VF-0D has two large canards mounted ahead of the main wings and two ventral stabilizers near the intakes. The increased surface are of the main wing allows the VF-0D to carry 20% greater maximum payload than the VF-0A/S variants and is capable of mounting most former United States/NATO standard aviation weaponry. http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Kudou Shin] and http://anidb.net/ch14116 [Edgar LaSalle] piloted a VF-0D during the events surrounding the island of Mayan in 2008.
NOTE: During development of the Macross game for the Playstation 2, when the VF-0 was being considered for inclusion, it was named "Phoenix" (ultimately, the VF-0 was not included in the game). This "pet name" was then dropped only to reappear in 2008 on the official Macross Frontier website. The Macross Chronicle (2008) has since made the name "Phoenix" official.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/vf-0d.htm</description>
<picture>127902.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50500" type="appears in" update="2012-11-10">
<name>Auerstadt</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Auerstädt was a refitted super-scale nuclear missile submarine (formerly of the Russian armed forces) that was operated by the Anti-United Nations. Deployed as a submarine aircraft carrier, the Auerstädt carries SV-51 variable fighters in pressure-resistant capsules. When carrying several SV-51 units specially modified for underwater launching the Auerstädt can deploy its variable fighters while submerged (surfacing only to effect retrieval). The submarine carrier is also equipped with advanced radar systems and is capable of defense using torpedoes. The Auerstädt proved an elusive weapon of the Anti-U.N. Forces during operations near the island of Mayan in 2008.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/auerstadt.htm</description>
<picture>127906.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50501" type="appears in" update="2012-11-10">
<name>ADR-03-Mk.III Cheyenne</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Destroid Cheyenne is an anti-air interception robot designed for use as both fixed and mobile defense aboard carriers. With wheels built for added mobility and high capacity ammunition drum, the Cheyenne was both a respectable offensive unit and a tenacious defensive system. The Cheyenne was also produced in a anti-air missile variant with two missile launching pods similar to the http://anidb.net/ch48997 [SDR-04-Mk.XII Phalanx] (replacing the gatling gun arm units). The Destroid Cheyenne was highly reliable and cheap to mass-produce with existing technology. During UN Spacy operations around the island of Mayan in September 2008, the Destroid Cheyenne was deployed aboard the aircraft carrier http://anidb.net/ch50482 [CVN-99 Asuka II].
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/cheyenne.htm</description>
<picture>127907.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50502" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-10">
<name>Katie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katie is a marine currently in the U.N. Forces. Due to her previous experience in close combat, she is training to be assigned to the VF-0 team. Her physical strength and can-do spirit complements http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Kudou Shin]`s own attributes as the two train together.
Source: http://macross.anime.net/wiki/Katie</description>
<picture>127908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50510" type="appears in" update="2012-11-10">
<name>QF-2001 Ghost</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The QF-2001 is an unmanned stealth fighter produced before the United Nations Wars began in 2000. As a predecessor to the http://anidb.net/ch48793 [QF-3000E] used in Space War I (circa 2009) and the http://anidb.net/ch48628 [Ghost X-9] (circa 2040) the QF-2001 Ghost pioneered many of the conventional technologies for modern unmanned stealth fighters. The Ghost`s large single engine, low mass and upward-canted forward-swept cranked gull wing makes the unmanned fighter very fast and agile. The armament of the QF-2001 Ghost remains classified however, observers have noted two open ports on the forward ventral hull along side the forward landing gear as well as four closed ports that resemble micro-missile launcher doors on either side of the rear ventral fuselage. QF-2001 Ghost fighters were depoyed aboard the http://anidb.net/ch50482 [CVN-99 Asuka II] during the events surrounding the island of Mayan in 2008.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/qf-2001-ghost.htm</description>
<picture>127918.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50511" type="appears in" update="2012-11-10">
<name>Octos</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Octos is a variable amphibious destroid designed and built by the Anti-United Nations forces to fight in the U.N. Wars. The Octos is capable of functioning in two mode; one, a submarine for operations at sea and a second ground combat quadruped mode which allows the Octos to operate on land. The Octos was built with numerous weapon systems which allowed the robot to fight effectively in a variety of environments and against any kind of adversary from enemy ground and air vehicles to enemy infantry. Like the http://anidb.net/ch50501 [Cheyenne Destroid] of the U.N. Forces, the Octos was also equipped with wheels for much more rapid mobility on land. Production costs for the Octos were high and thus only a small number were manufactured. Even with some failures, the Octos earned a reputation as a sturdy unit in combat. The first roll-out of the Octos happened in 2006 and by the end of the U.N. Wars, 92 Octos machines had been produced. The U.N. Forces continued production of the Octos, producing some 28 units until Space War I when the production line was destroyed.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/octos.htm</description>
<picture>127919.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50519" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-10">
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<name>Dr. Hasford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Hasford is an old scientist who advocated the "Protoculture interference hypothesis," which postulated that an ancient extraterrestrial civilization exerted an influence on the evolution of Earth life and humans. He traveled to the island of Mayan numerous times to prove this idea, and he had no qualms about sidestepping other people`s sensibilities in his pursuit. As a mentor to http://anidb.net/ch14115 [Aries Turner], he exerted a profound influence on her current efforts to uncover the mysteries of Mayan.
Source: http://macross.anime.net/wiki/Dr._Hasford</description>
<picture>127932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3380" picture="187130.jpg">Nozawa Nachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50520" type="appears in" update="2012-11-10">
<name>QF-2200D Ghost</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The QF-2200D is a small, lightweight, high-maneuverability stealth unmanned reconnaissance fighter whose mass production began in 2002. After exhausting skilled pilots in the chaos of the early stages of the U.N. Wars, the U.N. Forces released this to the frontlines in large quantities. Since it was designed and produced with existing technologies and without using almost any OTM, it was suitable for mass production without much manufacturing costs. Deployed aboard http://anidb.net/ch50482 [CVN-99 Asuka II].
It was developed mainly to conduct armed reconnaissance at relatively low altitudes at high speeds. However, because it can use its superior stealth, small lightweight size, mounting of an unusually powerful engine that is nevertheless difficult for detection nets, and the maneuverability to exceed a maximum instantaneous level of 25G since it carries no pilot, it is even utilized for its fighting strength over the main fighters in close-in combat situations.
The ratio of maximum speed to engine thrust is low because its maximum speed is limited, due to how difficult it is to maintain both heat resistance and stealth at higher speeds with existing materials. Control is by an autonomous AI, but of course there is the capability for remote control from the surface or satellite also.
Source: http://macross.anime.net/wiki/QF-2200_Ghost</description>
<picture>127936.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50521" type="appears in" update="2012-11-10">
<name>HWR-00-Mk.IP Prototype Monster</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The destroid Monster Heavy Weight Robot was originally designed as another anti-giant combat system but it first saw action fighting terrestrial threats during the events surrounding the Island of Mayan in 2008. The Mk.I Monster was nearly identical to the later http://anidb.net/ch48862 [Mk.II Monster] and was primarily deployed as a mobile artillery unit. However, the Monster was not designed for missile launchers on either side of the unit and thus the Mk.I had two multi-purpose "arms" for ammunition delivery, firing position adjustment and other duties. When the decision was made to equip the Monster with missile launchers, the unit was renamed Mk.II.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrosszero/monstermki.htm</description>
<picture>127942.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50522" type="appears in" update="2012-11-10">
<name>Tori no Hito</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5015" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2002-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海と風と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ocean, the Wind, and...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi to Kaze to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5022" update="2006-01-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2003-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地上の星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Star on the Ground</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chijou no Hoshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13057" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2003-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼き死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Death Match</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoki Shitou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19884" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2004-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">密林</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jungle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsurin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22658" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25203" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2004-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鳥の人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bird Human</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tori no Hito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135897" update="2012-08-02">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135898" update="2011-12-30">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Eizou Macross Zero Zero</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135899" update="2011-12-30">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">25th Anniversary Campaign Special - All That VF Macross 25th Anniversary Air Show VF-Zero</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135900" update="2011-12-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">25th Anniversary Campaign Special - All That VF Macross 25th Anniversary Air Show -Version F-</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
