<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4286" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>32</episodecount>
<startdate>1993-12-24</startdate>
<enddate>2003-08-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Konpeki no Kantai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Deep Blue Fleet</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">紺碧の艦隊</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4287" type="Same Setting">Kyokujitsu no Kantai</anime>
<anime id="8749" type="Side Story">Konpeki no Kantai Tokubetsu Hen: Sourai Kaihatsu Monogatari</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.jcstaff.co.jp/sho-sai/kon-shokai/ko-index.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="8345" type="Original Work">Aramaki Yoshio</name>
<name id="7229" type="Character Design">Suda Masami</name>
<name id="660" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Ryousuke</name>
<name id="5084" type="Direction">Kanda Takeyuki</name>
<name id="6781" type="Direction">Matano Hiromichi</name>
<name id="4287" type="Music">Makaino Kouji</name>
</creators>
<description>* WW2 revisionism, based on novel series by http://anidb.net/cr8345 [Aramaki Yoshio].
The story focuses on a technologically advanced Imperial Japanese Navy and a radically different Pacific War that was brought about by Admiral Isoroku Yamamoto`s revival in the past due to unexplained circumstances. The series also features real-life 1940s figures whose first names were changed, such as Winston Churchill to Kingston Churchill and Adolf Hitler to Heinrich von Hitler.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="14">5.11</permanent>
<temporary count="15">6.13</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>11998.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7410</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6229</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3495</identifier>
<identifier>saqehd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jcstaff.co.jp/sho-sai/kon-shokai/ko-index.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Konpeki_no_Kantai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>紺碧の艦隊</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159444</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2691" parentid="2641" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-21">
<name>World War II</name>
<description>World War II, or the Second World War (often abbreviated WWII or WW2), was a global military conflict which involved most of the world`s nations, including all great powers, organised into two opposing military alliances: the Allies and the Axis. The war involved the mobilisation of over 100 million military personnel, making it the most widespread war in history. In a state of "total war," the major participants placed their entire economic, industrial, and scientific capabilities at the service of the war effort, erasing the distinction between civilian and military resources. Over seventy million people, the majority civilians, were killed, making it the deadliest conflict in human history.
The start of the war is generally held to be September 1, 1939, with the invasion of Poland by Nazi Germany and subsequent declarations of war on Germany by most of the countries in the British Empire and Commonwealth, and by France. Many countries were already at war before this date, such as Ethiopia and Italy in the Second Italo-Abyssinian War and China and Japan in the Second Sino-Japanese War. Many who were not initially involved joined the war later, as a result of events such as the German invasion of the Soviet Union, the attacks on Pearl Harbor and British colonies, and subsequent declarations of war on Japan by the United States, the Netherlands, and British Commonwealth.
In 1945, the war ended in a victory for the Allies. The Soviet Union and the United States subsequently emerged as the world`s superpowers, setting the stage for the Cold War which continued for the next 46 years. The United Nations was formed in the hope of preventing another world conflict. The acceptance of the principle of self-determination accelerated decolonization movements in Asia and Africa, while Western Europe itself began moving toward integration.
------
About the picture
Top left: Battle of Wuhan
Top right: Second Battle of El Alamein
Middle left: Battle of Stalingrad
Middle right: German dive bombers over Eastern Front winter 1943-1944
Bottom left: Wilhelm Keitel signing German Instrument of Surrender
Bottom right: Invasion of Lingayen Gulf</description>
<picurl>40430.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4538" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>long episodes</name>
<description>Long episodes are regular episodes that are much longer than the standard 25-30 minutes, usually 45-60 minutes. 
Not to be used if a show has occasional 45-60 minute specials. Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="22234" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Adolf Hitler</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="46752" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2002-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超秘匿潜水艦亀天北進せよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 27</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chouhitoku Sensuikan Kameten Hokushin Seyo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46753" update="2011-11-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1993-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の開戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The War of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Kaisen</title>
<summary>In the prologue, scenes are shown of Japan`s eventual defeat after Admiral Isoroku Yamamoto dies on April 18, 1943, but the clock winds back to April 1, 1939. Having retained his original memory and his old surname of Takano, Yamamoto meets with a select group of Navy officers and propose a coup d`etat against the militarist regime. After he narrowly avoids an assassination attempt (plotted by warlords in the IJA), he meets IJA Lt Gen Yasaburo Otaka and explains his rationale for the coup while planning a massive naval rearmament project. All the while, Germany plunges Europe into war and the Tripartite Pact is signed. Yamamoto launches the coup a few days after the Pearl Harbor strike force leaves Hitokappu Bay. With Tojo being held at gunpoint, Otaka becomes the new prime minister and declares war against the US hours before the attack begins at daybreak. The Japanese fleet regroups to find and eliminate the US Pacific Fleet out in Hawaiian waters and lands amphibious forces in Hawaii - all in the space of two days.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="46754" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1995-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">帝都初空襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teito Hatsu Kuushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46755" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1996-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">原爆阻止作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genbaku Soshi Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46756" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2001-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">デカン高原攻防戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dekan Kougen Koubousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46757" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1998-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">独超重爆撃機要撃作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokuchoujuu Bakugeki Kiyougeki Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46758" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2000-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超弩級空母建御雷出撃す!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choudokyuu Kuubokengo Kaminari Shutsugekisu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46759" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1996-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天極作戦発動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tengoku Sakusen Hatsudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46760" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2001-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! 印度南方要塞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Indo Nanpou Yousai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46761" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2003-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜細亜の曙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ajia no Akebono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46762" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1998-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">前原少将危機一髪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maehara Shoushou Kikiippatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46763" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1994-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パナマ運河爆撃す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Panama Unga Bakugekisu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46764" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2001-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">陸海立体作戦カマイタチ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rikukai Rittai Sakusen Kamaitachi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46765" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1995-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天元作戦発令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tengen Sakusen Hatsurei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46766" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2003-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤道大海戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akamichi Daikaisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46767" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2002-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">神聖欧州帝国成立</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsei Ooshuu Teikoku Seiritsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46768" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2000-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">電撃・ロンメル軍団出撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dengeki Rommel Gundan Shutsugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46769" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2002-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">満州視察隠密行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manshuu Shisatsu Onmitsu Kou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46770" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1998-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅海雷撃作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukai Raigeki Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46771" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2003-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鉄十字の鎌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tetsujuuji no Kama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46772" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1998-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海中要塞鳴門出撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaichuu Yousai Naruto Shutsugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46773" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1996-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">風雲マダガスカル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuuun Madagascar</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46774" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2003-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦向けて, 序曲高まる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 29</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen Mukete, Jokyoku Dakamaru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46775" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1996-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新装紺碧艦隊出撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsou Konpeki Kantai Shutsugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46776" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1995-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トレス海峡封鎖作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tres Kaikyou Fuusa Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46777" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1996-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超巨艇欧州を翔ぶ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Gotei Ooshuu o Tobu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46778" update="2011-10-30">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2002-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嗚呼, アイスランド沖海戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 28</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aa, Iceland Oki Kaisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46779" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1996-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一撃轟沈タスマン海戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichigeki Gouchin Tasuman Kaisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46780" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1996-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマス島攻略</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christmas-tou Kouryaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46781" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1998-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">殱滅・独逸水中襲撃艦隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senmetsu Doitsu Suichuu Shuugeki Kantai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46782" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1999-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱風, 印度亜大陸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neppuu, Indoa Tairiku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46783" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1998-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗雲印度洋浪高し!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anun Indoyou Nami Takashi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212517" update="2019-02-10">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">紺碧の艦隊 特別編 蒼莱開発物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kompeki no Kantai Special Episode: Development of the Sorai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konpeki no Kantai: Sourai Kaihatsu Monogatari</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
