<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="430" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-12-18</startdate>
<enddate>2003-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">I`ll/CKBC</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">アイル</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Generation Basket</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Лихая баскетбольная команда Кодзу</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">CKBC</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">I`ll / Crazy KOUZO Basketball Club</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9858" approval="4" total="6">Free!</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>https://www.aniplex.co.jp/lineup/anime/ckbc/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1271" type="Animation Work">M.S.C</name>
<name id="2243" type="Character Design">Sekiguchi Kanami</name>
<name id="4797" type="Direction">Kawasaki Itsurou</name>
<name id="2243" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sekiguchi Kanami</name>
<name id="4410" type="Music">Ike Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="7906" type="Original Work">Asada Hiroyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>This anime is based on "I`ll" (AIRU) manga about basketball. This two volume OVA took the story from the popular chapter of the match between "Kokufutsu (Kouzu?) High School" and "Kokutai Training Camp Association" from the manga. It`s also focusing on the friendship between http://anidb.net/ch21619 [Tachibana Akane] and http://anidb.net/ch21620 [Hiiragi Hitonari].
Very shounen anime about two arrogant guys trying to beat each other. Friends, but also sworn enemies.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="335">4.13</permanent>
<temporary count="337">6.35</temporary>
<review count="2">5.74</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224625.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2158</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1130</identifier>
<identifier>befljx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.aniplex.co.jp/lineup/anime/ckbc/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>I'll</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>I'll</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>874</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239951</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5988</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/725</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8084</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2760" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>basketball</name>
<description>Basketball is Netball for men, the real game that encourages dribbling and other such uncouth behaviour that was sanitised out of the ladies` version. However, it is itself woozy compared to Ulama, as the losing side are seldom publicly sacrificed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="21619" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">6.49</rating>
<name>Tachibana Akane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Player (Shooting Guard) in the Kouzu Basketball Club.
Akane Tachibana is an impulsive, hot-tempered boy. He`s spontaneous, transparent and he has no problem to say what he thinks.
He doesn`t hesitate to beat up anyone who says something wrong.
He`s arrogant and proud. but it`s just for this that he has a strong personality and appears the most original character of the story.
His real interest is not basketball itself, but the opportunity to challenge Hiiragi Hitonari, player of the same team. This purpose stimulate him more than anything else.
In fact, Tachibana and Hiiragi are united by a mysterious special bond of friendship, esteem and competition.</description>
<picture>55119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21487" picture="55557.jpg">Kaneko Noboru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21620" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">5.30</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Hitonari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Point Guard of the Kouzu basketball club.
Hiiragi Hitonari is a very talented basketball player. he`s a mysterious and reserved figure, he finds it difficult to express his feelings.
He feels oppressed by the expectations of his father (famous basketball coach) and brother (famous basketball player), for this reason he joins the kouzu basketball club to demonstrate he`s able to be independent and free to do what he want to do. However, they`ll always try to encourage him to leave the team and play at higher levels.
He`s the worst rival and best friend of Akane Tachibana, another talented member of the kouzu
basketball club.</description>
<picture>55067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22216" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Yamazaki Yoshiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22217" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-08">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Harumoto Akihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5038" picture="51959.jpg">Yoshimizu Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22218" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Kanemoto Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22219" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Shibuya Osami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="484" picture="17476.jpg">Kisaichi Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22220" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-03">
<rating votes="3">4.83</rating>
<name>Minefuji Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22221" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Yoshikawa Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22224" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="2">2.87</rating>
<name>Horii Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22226" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Kondou Yuuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3235" picture="25824.jpg">Satou Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22227" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Masahito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3317" picture="24700.jpg">Kishino Yukimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22228" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Hiiragi Takuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22229" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Takayanagi Gaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22230" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Obata Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="438" picture="25479.jpg">Yanagisawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5054" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2002-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">十字路, いつかの景色</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Standing Cross Road</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juujiro, Itsuka no Keshiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7286" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2003-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年達が空を見上げた日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day When Boys Look up at The Sky. Primitive Rude Flowers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen-tachi ga Sora o Miageta Hi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
