<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4315" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1980-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>1980-04-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ginga Tetsudou 999: Eien no Tabibito Emeraldas</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Galaxy Express 999 TV Special 2: Eternal Voyager Emeraldas</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">銀河鉄道999 永遠の旅人エメラルダス</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="484" type="Full Story">Ginga Tetsudou 999</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="4542" type="Chief Direction">Nishizawa Nobutaka</name>
<name id="4542" type="Direction">Nishizawa Nobutaka</name>
<name id="4808" type="Music">Aoki Nozomi</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="51">7.34</permanent>
<temporary count="51">7.03</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>236484.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3808</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6734</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159304</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3436</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2493" type="main character in" update="2014-12-13">
<rating votes="434">8.57</rating>
<name>Maetel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of Queen Prometheum, ruler of a mechanised empire.</description>
<picture>38136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3703" picture="151656.jpg">Ikeda Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12667" type="appears in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="64">4.76</rating>
<name>Hoshino Tetsurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tetsuro Hoshino is a young boy who was born on Earth into poverty, and who wants nothing more than a machine body. He also wants revenge on Count Mecha, an evil man who was given a machine body and now hunts humans for sport, for killing his mother. As a street urchin, Tetsuro has no means to buy a machine body. However, he has heard that at the end of the Andromeda Galaxy, there exists a planet where such robot bodies are given away for free. All Tetsuro needs to do is get a pass on the Galaxy Express 999, the cosmic railway. And one day, Tetsuro meets the mysterious Maetel, who promises to give him her unlimited use pass for the Express on the condition that she be his travelling companion. Tetsuro happily agrees, and embarks with Maetel on an adventure across the stars. When Tetsuro starts out, he is every bit the whiny, immature, selfish child. However, the adventures he goes with Maetel on, the people he meets, and the sights he witnesses cause Tetsuro to slowly but truly grow into a strong, young man. Tetsuro also grows closer and closer to Maetel, and although the nature of their relationship might not be called romantic, they form a very strong bond of love. Though it is never explicitly stated, it is implied that Tetsuro is Captain Harlock`s son. The evidence for this includes Tetsuro`s mother saying that his father is alive but away for some reason, Captain Harlock`s mysterious attachment to Tetsuro, and simple physical resemblance.</description>
<picture>38140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12669" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="66">5.55</rating>
<name>Shashou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main crew member of the Galaxy Express 999. He is an alien being with an invisible body; only his eyes can be seen while he is wearing his conductor uniform. The Conductor prefers to go `strictly by the book` and frequently cites the Galaxy Express rule book, but occasionally ends up bending the rules and getting into adventures with Tetsurou and Maetel.</description>
<picture>38142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3285" picture="193568.jpg">Kimotsuki Kaneta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12670" type="appears in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="149">8.45</rating>
<name>Emeraldas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emeraldas has been compared many times to Captain Harlock, and the two have some similarities. They also know each other from the days of the Voice of Free Arcadia, when she fought side by side with him and Tochirou, the man who is their common bond. After the Ilumidus resistance, Emeraldas became much like Harlock, sailing the sea of stars and delivering justice in her own unique way.
Emeraldas is one of the few people who know the route of Count Mecha`s Time Castle, and when her ship, the Queen Emereldas, appears next to the Galaxy Express, Tetsuro doesn`t hesitate to get her attention. Emeraldas would`ve killed Tetsuro if it weren`t for two things. First, Maetel (whom she also knows) is with him. Second, Tetsuro has Tochirou`s hat and laser. She listens and then tells Tetsuro where the Time Castle will next appear: Trader`s Fork, on the planet of Heavy Melder.
Some time after she leaves, she realizes something is happening on Heavy Melder, something that had to do with Tochirou. She arrives too late. Harlock tells her he`s already dead. She leaves but later receives a message. It`s from Tochirou, whose soul had been successfully integrated into the Arcadia. Learning that it was Tetsuro who had helped him, she realizes that she owes him a favor, and she proceeds to Andromeda, to repay the favor. She and Tetsuro will cross path a few more times.
Emeraldas is a very lonely soul, especially after the death of Tochirou. Her closest companion, like herself, is a wanderer. You see, the reason she and Maetel know each other...is because they`re sisters. Emeraldas also has a daughter, Mayu, but she rarely sees her.
Source: Absolute Anime</description>
<picture>38143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10386" picture="38265.jpg">Tajima Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="46748" update="2006-02-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1980-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218166" update="2019-06-20">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
