<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4325" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">True Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Настоящие слёзы</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Szczere łzy</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">دموع صادقة</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">דמעות אמיתיות</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Tikros ašaros</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Gerçek Gözyaşları</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">Lacrimi Adevarate</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Искрени сълзи</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Щирі сльози</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">真实之泪</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">true tears</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">True Tears</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10283" type="Other">Utopia</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4404" approval="21" total="38">Kanon (2006)</anime>
<anime id="5508" approval="21" total="28">H2O: Footprints in the Sand</anime>
<anime id="5276" approval="14" total="29">KimiKiss Pure Rouge</anime>
<anime id="5019" approval="8" total="17">Sola</anime>
<anime id="5101" approval="7" total="23">Clannad</anime>
<anime id="5274" approval="5" total="12">Ef - a Tale of Memories.</anime>
<anime id="6025" approval="4" total="14">Akane-iro ni Somaru Saka</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="28">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="523131">The plot is good for romance fans. But I don`t really like Shinichiro and Hiromi. Watch it urself for more details. Btw, the OP &amp; ED song are pretty good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="159527">Painfully slow, and boring. There are only a few good parts, but in between it is hard to stay awake.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="14374">Heart wavering ;]</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="58269">I did enjoy this anime a great deal</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="220843">Simply beautiful!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="451902">Awesome romance story and great animation imo ;]</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="430888">well by looking in it`s name you can think it`s another tearjerker, but it ain`t.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="453003">Overall, a very good anime above many others of the same genre. I clearly recommend it to romantic anime fans!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="23892">I Love It! :o)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="313678">If you`re looking for romance, this is truly the shiet! Made me cry 3 times at least ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="433878">By far one of the best romance anime I have ever seen.
Great character development, coherent storyline, proper ending.
Love comes at a cost, whether or not you`re the one who is cast aside.
I say again; one of the best romance anime ever.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.truetears.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1385" type="Animation Work">P.A. Works</name>
<name id="122" type="Series Composition">Okada Mari</name>
<name id="2240" type="Music">Kikuchi Hajime</name>
<name id="2241" type="Direction">Nishimura Junji</name>
<name id="2243" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sekiguchi Kanami</name>
<name id="2243" type="Character Design">Sekiguchi Kanami</name>
<name id="27835" type="Original Work">La`cryma</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a game by http://anidb.net/cr952 [Broccoli], http://anidb.net/cr1005 [Circus] and GameCRAB.
http://anidb.net/ch887 [Nakagami Shin`ichirou] is a student living in what would be a dream come true for most high school boys, but for him it is mostly frustrating. A well-liked girl in school named http://anidb.net/ch885 [Yuasa Hiromi] has lived in his house for a year along with his family. Her father was a close friend of the family, and when he died they immediately took her in. She is popular and well liked, always smiles, and is talented in sports — but Shin`ichiro knows she must be hiding her sadness deep inside. Having an artistic tendency, he creates watercolours of her and thinks about wishing to ease her tears. Yet he cannot bring up the nerve to talk to her even in his own home. She, too, is quiet and withdrawn in their house, quite unlike at school. Shin`ichiro is also distracted by teasing from his friend http://anidb.net/ch889 [Nobuse Miyokichi] for watching Hiromi from afar, a curse of bad luck from a strange girl named http://anidb.net/ch886 [Isurugi Noe], and being forced to perform Muhiga dancing. By helping Noe he hopes to ease his own problems, yet he seems to have difficulty helping himself.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4283">7.06</permanent>
<temporary count="4330">7.86</temporary>
<review count="4">6.95</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221870.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6257</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9002</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>8230</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2129</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6234</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4155</identifier>
<identifier>gotfps</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.truetears.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>True_Tears_(anime)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>True_tears_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1291</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329465</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9670</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2008/true_tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>트루_티어즈</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>真實之淚_true_tears_(動畫)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="870" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-19">
<name>strict</name>
<description>This character is rigorously conforming to principle, norm or condition.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1179" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-21">
<name>indecisive</name>
<description>This character has trouble taking their own decisions, and may rely on others to do that instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="885" type="main character in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="142">6.10</rating>
<name>Yuasa Hiromi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiromi is a girl Shin`ichirou`s age and goes to the same high school as him. After her father died, she came to live with Shin`ichirou`s family and has already been living with them for a year when the story begins. She has been in the same class as Shin`ichirou since elementary school, though despite being cheerful back then, she now acts cold when living at his home. In contrast, she normally smiles and is popular at school. She often helps out with Shin`ichirou`s father`s work as they are low on man power. She is a very good player on her school`s girl`s basketball team and is number six. It is clear that Hiromi has feelings for Shin`ichirou, but she decided to lock these feelings inside when she began living with Shin`ichirou.
It is suggested that she hides these feelings because Shin`ichirou`s mother told her, prior to the start of the story, that Shin`ichirou is her brother, which is later proven false.</description>
<picture>31466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="886" type="main character in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="105">5.60</rating>
<name>Isurugi Noe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isurugi Noe is an odd girl at Shin`ichirou`s school. He first meets her up in a tree where she is picking silverberries for a chicken she named Raigomaru in a coop on a campus. Shin`ichirou ends up having to catch her as she jumps from the tree since she was stuck and could not get down on her own. She likes chickens, though would only feed one of them since she says "it could fly" while the other cannot. After the chicken gets killed by a raccoon, Noe becomes saddened, but does not cry because she "gave away her tears". She later explains that after her grandmother died, she was unable to cry any more due to her grandmother telling her that when she dies she will take Noe`s tears away with her. Noe has an older brother, Jun, who is a basketball team captain at another high school. Noe is known to have a frank personality and speaks honestly to other people. She seems to be able to judge people`s feelings to a certain extent.</description>
<picture>31465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="887" type="main character in" update="2010-08-25">
<rating votes="44">5.20</rating>
<name>Nakagami Shin`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakagami Shin`ichirou is a male high school student who enjoys drawing, and even starts working on a picture book. He lives with his mother, father, and childhood friend Yuasa Hiromi. She used to smile around him, though does not anymore when at home. Shin`ichirou longs to see her smile again which he loved so much as a kid. He is living a relatively normal life until he meets a strange girl named Isurugi Noe who curses him with misfortune after he teases her a bit, though he reconciles with her soon after. Shin`ichirou is frustrated by not being able to see emotion from Hiromi, and other pressures from his family, such as a traditional Japanese dance he does not want to practice.
However, he eventually gives in to practising hard for the dance due to comments made by Noe. Shin`ichirou receives much confidence from Noe, and even goes out with her for a short time, but in the end he and Hiromi start a relationship.</description>
<picture>31463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="605" picture="226544.jpg">Ishii Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="888" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="42">5.70</rating>
<name>Andou Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aiko is a girl one year older than Shin`ichirou who attends a different school than him. She is going out with his friend Miyokichi Nobuse, but instead has feelings for Shin`ichirou. Aiko continuously tries to get closer with Shin`ichirou, such as asking him to go shopping with her instead of Miyokichi, and when out with Miyokichi she does not have the same vigour as when she is just with Shin`ichirou. Aiko has known Shin`ichirou since they were kids, and was introduced to Miyokichi through Shin`ichirou. She helps out at her family`s Imagawayaki shop named Imagawayaki Ai-chan. She is shorter than Shinichirou, and enjoys teasing him from time to time.</description>
<picture>31472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="889" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="11">4.26</rating>
<name>Nobuse Miyokichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyokichi is Shin`ichirou`s good friend, and has known him since they were kids. They hang out together at school, and Miyokichi often brings up the fact that Shin`ichirou has an eye out for Hiromi when at school. Shin`ichirou introduced Miyokichi to Aiko which eventually led to Miyokichi asking out Aiko, and she agreed, though it is apparent that she agreed reluctantly.</description>
<picture>31471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="890" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="17">6.26</rating>
<name>Kurobe Tomoyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoyo is Hiromi`s friend whom she often hangs out with and fellow member of the girl`s basketball team. She is sure that Hiromi likes Shin`ichirou, but Hiromi constantly denies it. When Hiromi is troubled by something, Tomoyo worries about her.</description>
<picture>31470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="607" picture="241611.jpg">Watanabe Tomomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="891" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="12">1.55</rating>
<name>Isurugi Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jun is Noe`s older brother. He is the captain of the basketball team at his school and is number four in his team. It is hinted that he might have more feelings for Noe than just a normal sibling`s relationship. He asks Shin`ichirou to ask Noe out, but Shin`ichirou merely gets annoyed at him. However, when Shin`ichirou requests that Jun go out with Hiromi in return for going out with his sister Noe, he agrees immediately. He does not hold any feelings for Hiromi, and is merely acting to make Noe happy.</description>
<picture>31467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="606" picture="18011.jpg">Masuda Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="892" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="11">2.81</rating>
<name>Shin`ichirou no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She likes to do what she thinks is best for her son, and tries to look after him. She has been known to read his mail if she deems necessary and often bugs him about things at school, or if his jacket smells. She takes favour over Shin`ichirou and does not consider Hiromi her child. She often shows hostile attitudes to Hiromi, and this has made her distant from her son.
Eventually, she reconciles with Hiromi and tells her that she made up the story about Hiromi being her husband`s child.</description>
<picture>31468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="608" picture="18012.jpg">Takahashi Rieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="893" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="6">4.00</rating>
<name>Shin`ichirou no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He and Hiromi`s father were good friends. After Hiromi`s father died, he took her in. Unlike his wife, he respects his son`s privacy and lets him do as he wishes, saying that "Shin`ichirou is Shin`ichirou". Furthermore, he considers Hiromi to be a member of the family and does not treat her badly like his wife.</description>
<picture>31469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27287" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="2">2.68</rating>
<name>Asami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27288" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Arisawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4908" picture="28313.jpg">Kawano Taketoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27289" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Nagamori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27290" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="2">4.68</rating>
<name>Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144156.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="95" picture="16702.jpg">Horanai Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27291" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Hayashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10990" picture="39455.jpg">Nishi Kensuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27292" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Toukai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27293" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Takaoka Rumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11273" picture="86104.jpg">Miruno Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27294" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Mikiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10424" picture="172872.jpg">Watanabe Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27295" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Noto Tatsusaburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20546" picture="2047.gif">Meguro Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60379" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Sakagura no Shounen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144158.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20552" picture="171304.jpg">Tokura Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60380" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Mugiha Baske-bu 10 ban</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144160.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10424" picture="172872.jpg">Watanabe Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60381" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Mugiha Baske-bu 7 ban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4908" picture="28313.jpg">Kawano Taketoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60382" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Suugaku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144163.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60383" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Noe no Obaa-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144164.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20566" picture="206821.jpg">Senou Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60384" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60385" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Mugiha Baske-bu 8 ban</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="95" picture="16702.jpg">Horanai Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60386" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Untenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4683" picture="27279.jpg">Koyama Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60387" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Bike-ya no Oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60388" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Shinpan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="85780" update="2008-01-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85815" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="23">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私... 涙, あげちゃったから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I... Gave My Tears Away</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi... Namida, Agechatta kara</title>
<summary>While at home, Shinichiro Nakagami laments how he cannot express his feelings for Hiromi Yuasa.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738429</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86561" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私... 何がしたいの...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What... Do I Want to Do?</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Yo... ¿Qué es lo que quiero hacer?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi... Nani ga Shitai no...</title>
<summary>After insisting Shinichiro should believe her about giving her away her tears, Noe tells him of her mission to retrieve them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738431</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86585" update="2011-05-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86734" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どうなった? こないだの話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What About What We Talked About?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dou Natta? Konaida no Hanashi</title>
<summary>When Shinichiro goes to school, he finds red seeds in pink envelopes which Noe has placed in his locker, desk, and around the classroom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738433</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87311" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はい, ぱちぱちってして</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Okay, Blink</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hai, Pachipachi tte Shite</title>
<summary>While walking back to Shinichiro`s house, Hiromi tells him about her crush on Noe`s brother, which hurts Shinichiro.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738435</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87312" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おせっかいな男の子ってバカみたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nosy Boys Are Annoying</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osekkai na Otokonokotte Baka Mitai</title>
<summary>Shinichiro looks for Noe during school, but after she suggests they eat lunch together or go home together, he becomes defensive and lies, telling her that he has dance practice after school and that she should eat with her friends instead of him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738437</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87313" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それ... なんの冗談?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is... That a Joke?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore... Nan no Joudan?</title>
<summary>Aiko tries to tell Shinichiro her feelings but is interrupted when Miyokichi arrives.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738439</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87314" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちゃんと言って, ここに書いて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Say It Clearly, Write It Here</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chanto Itte, Koko ni Kaite</title>
<summary>Noe once again tries to approach Shinichiro at school, but he shrugs her off, telling her that she does not understand his situation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738441</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87315" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪が降っていない街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Town with No Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki ga Futte Inai Machi</title>
<summary>After asking Noe out, Shinichiro tells her about his picture book that he is making about the rooster Raigoumaru.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738443</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87316" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なかなか飛べないね...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Can`t Quite Seem to Fly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naka Naka Tobenai ne...</title>
<summary>Jun and Hiromi crash while on the motorcycle, but they are not harmed. As a result of the accident, both Jun and Hiromi get suspended from school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738445</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87317" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全部ちゃんとするから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Do Everything Right</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenbu Chanto Suru kara</title>
<summary>Shinichiro hears from Miyokichi that he broke up with Aiko, even though he did not want to accept it at first.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738447</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87318" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたが好きなのは私じゃない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Not Me Whom You Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata ga Suki na no wa Watashi ja Nai</title>
<summary>It has been a week since Hiromi moved out and in the meantime has settled into single living. Miyokichi gets a call from Aiko, and the two decide to start over from the beginning as friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738449</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87319" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">何も見てない私の瞳から...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From My Unseeing Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanimo Mitenai Watashi no Hitomi kara...</title>
<summary>After Shinichiro listens to Noe talk to herself at the beach, he goes home but is unable to sleep due to her words.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738451</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87320" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君の涙を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Namida o</title>
<summary>The day after the festival, Shinichiro goes to Jun to apologize for Noe`s broken leg, though Jun says he will not forgive him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738453</identifier>
<identifier>true-tears</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="88362" update="2008-10-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88396" update="2012-08-08">
<epno type="5">P6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">When Shit Hits the fan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97466" update="2009-03-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">true tears 小さいって事は楽しいね(仮)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD1 Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Tears Chiisai tte Koto wa Tanoshii ne (Kari)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97467" update="2009-03-21">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トゥルー ティアーズ ライト(仮)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD2 Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Tears Light (Kari)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97468" update="2009-03-21">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">true tears ss(仮)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD3 Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Tears SS (Kari)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97469" update="2009-03-21">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">true★tears にゃ(仮)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD4 Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Tears Nya (Kari)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97470" update="2009-03-21">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">true tears げきじょう(仮)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD5 Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Tears Gekijou (Kari)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97471" update="2009-03-21">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">true tears A`s(仮)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD6 Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Tears A`s (Kari)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97472" update="2009-03-21">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">true tears ふぉ~えう"ぁ~(仮)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD7 Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Tears Forever (Kari)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117959" update="2010-04-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118576" update="2011-05-25">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Real-world location tour</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118577" update="2010-05-24">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with the cast</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118578" update="2010-05-24">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷轟丸とじべたの物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Story of Raigomaru and Jibeta</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">История Раигомару и Джибеты</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raigoumaru to Jibeta no Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122460" update="2010-09-22">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">第01話~第10話 ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">EP1-10 Digest</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122461" update="2010-09-17">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130873" update="2011-06-13">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130874" update="2011-06-13">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130875" update="2011-06-13">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130876" update="2011-06-13">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130877" update="2011-06-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132195" update="2011-08-04">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Epilogue</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
