<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="433" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>1999-10-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Arc the Lad</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">아크 더 래드</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">Tânărul Arc</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アークザラッド</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Arc the Lad</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Arc, a kölyök</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Arc the Lad</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Animation/Arc/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4304" type="Series Composition">Omode Akemi</name>
<name id="749" type="Animation Work">Bee Train</name>
<name id="1752" type="Character Design">Kikuchi Youko</name>
<name id="4797" type="Series Composition">Kawasaki Itsurou</name>
<name id="4797" type="Direction">Kawasaki Itsurou</name>
<name id="3626" type="Music">Ooshima Michiru</name>
</creators>
<description>The story follows Elk, a bounty hunter in some strange futuristic world. On this world archaic but advanced technology exists side by side with primitive attitudes, beasts and magic. In other words it`s got a bit of everything. It also has an evil conspiracy who are able to produce powerful monsters called chimera, who can also appear as human. Naturally it is not long before Elk has rescued a young female beast-master and gained himself some serious enemies.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="848">3.74</permanent>
<temporary count="860">6.44</temporary>
<review count="2">5.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>80164.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>246</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>55</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>465</identifier>
<identifier>ruvqzs</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Animation/Arc/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Arc_the_Lad#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アークザラッド2#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>125544</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2051</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="201" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>bounty hunter</name>
<description>A bounty hunter is one who hunts and captures targets (be it people, animals, etc.) for monetary gain, preferably without killing/destroying their target. Despite being illegal in most of the world today, it is a legal profession in the United States and Philippines (a former commonwealth of the US), who are known as "bail enforcement agents".
If they are only and constantly hired to kill, they are likely an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3132" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-11">
<name>helpful couple</name>
<description>This is a very low key type of romance in which the main two characters spend a great deal of time hanging out together just helping other people solve problems. The couple`s personal interaction tends to be subtle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4387" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>good vs evil</name>
<description>A theme often used to relay lessons of morality. The fight between two entities, with one side representing all that is good and right and the other one all that is evil and wrong.
It’s one of the most conventional themes in literature, and sometimes considered to be a universal part of the human condition.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="23442" type="main character in" update="2011-05-04">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Arc Eda Ricolne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4108.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4586" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23443" type="main character in" update="2011-05-04">
<rating votes="3">6.01</rating>
<name>Kukuru Lill Wight</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4110.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4960" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23444" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-20">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Poco a Mervil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23445" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-05">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Tosh via Monji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23446" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-20">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Gogen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3321" picture="228645.jpg">Tsujimura Mahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30810" type="main character in" update="2011-05-04">
<rating votes="3">6.01</rating>
<name>Lieza Flora Meruno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4109.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30812" type="main character in" update="2011-05-04">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Elc Kowalapule</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4111.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30814" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-05">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Shu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30816" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-05">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Iga Ramadagia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4006.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30817" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-05">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Chongara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4007.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31849" type="appears in" update="2011-05-04">
<name>Clive</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4112.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5085" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時雨の心地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raining on the Heartland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shigure no Kokochi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5086" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命のはじまり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beginning of Fate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Hajimari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5087" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boy of Flames</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6479" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼き女神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pale Blue Goddess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoki Megami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6812" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犯罪者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Criminal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanzaisha-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8494" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃亡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Runaway</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toubou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8495" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">微笑みの聖母</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Smiling Holy Mother</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hohoemi no Seibo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8496" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">残された友</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friend Who Was Left Behind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nokosareta Tomo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8497" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奪還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reconquer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dakkan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8498" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">精霊の巫女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shrine Maiden Of The Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seirei no Miko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8499" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">焔立つ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blaze Has Stood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Homura Tatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8500" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白い家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White House</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Ie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8501" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤独な勇者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lonely Brave Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodoku na Yuusha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8502" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">名も無き十字軍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crusade With No Name</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namonaki Juujigun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8503" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">波音の彼方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Other Side of Sound of Waves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namioto no Kanata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8504" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">古の守護者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Guardian of Old</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inishie no Shugosha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8676" update="2014-02-14">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の胎動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Quickening Of The Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Taidou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8677" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">輝の少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayaki no Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8678" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖柩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Holy Ark</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seihitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9616" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">凍れる瞳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frozen Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kooreru Hitomi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9617" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真実の在処</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Place Where The Truth Is</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjitsu no Arika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9618" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">影に潜む</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hiding In The Shadows</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kage ni Hisomu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9619" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キメラ使い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chimera Tower</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chimera Tsukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9620" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">両雄対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confrontation Of Two Great Men</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryouyuu Taiketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9621" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meet Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9622" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">緋色の王城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scarlet Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiiro no Oujou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
