<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4335" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2006-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Galaxy Angel Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Galaxy Angel Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Galaxy Angel II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Galaxy Ange-lune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gaII</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ギャラクシーエンジェる~ん</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="108" type="Alternative Setting">Galaxy Angel</anime>
<anime id="1761" type="Character">Galaxy Angel 4th</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/runeangel/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="8933" type="Character Design">Shinohara Kenji</name>
<name id="7464" type="Series Composition">Hayakawa Tadashi</name>
<name id="952" type="Original Work">Broccoli</name>
<name id="4489" type="Direction">Kishi Seiji</name>
<name id="9947" type="Music">Harada Katsumichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the http://anidb.net/cr952 [Broccoli] game by the same name. Features a completely different cast than the first http://anidb.net/a108 [Galaxy Angel].
In the distant future, the city of Transbaal was founded on the planet Celdar in the NEUE galaxy under the affiliation of Planet Transbaal of the EDEN galaxy. There, the Transbaal Army organizes a special squad of five girls, the Rune Angels. They are supposed to be elite pilots, piloting the latest fighters, with important roles to play in the vast universe...
However, they are hard to deal with for they always go their own way creating havoc. What disaster will they cause next?
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="288">3.43</permanent>
<temporary count="292">6.07</temporary>
<review count="1">4.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>154185.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6255</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1600</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3716</identifier>
<identifier>hmgxur</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/runeangel/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Galaxy_Angel_II#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ギャラクシーエンジェる〜ん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>897</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326173</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8549</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>863</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3013" type="appears in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="70">6.81</rating>
<name>Milfeulle Sakuraba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A seventeen-year-old, selfless pink-haired girl who has an incredible amount of good luck with extremely bad luck periodically to counter it. The bad luck can cause disastrous outcomes like destroying a whole planet or even an entire galaxy. Strangely enough, this could be minimized if Milfeulle is happy at those days. She can be stubborn if she doesn`t get her way, but is usually happy-go-lucky. The newest member of the Angel Troupe at the start of the series. Her hobby is making tea and cooking snacks, particularly cake. The flowers on her head can spin and make her fly or hover in the air. Her first name is derived from the name for the French pastry mille-feuille.</description>
<picture>18666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3014" type="appears in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="52">7.05</rating>
<name>Ranpha Franboise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blonde, vain beauty usually featured in a red Chinese dress with remarkable physical strength. Her hobby is fortune-telling, and she`s even successful at times. Her predominant yet ultimately futile obsession is attempting to snag rich (and preferably handsome) men, which rarely appear in the series. Usually when she does meet these men she completely falls apart and makes a total fool of herself. Although apparently pushy she is actually very sensitive, though can come off as domineering. The two metallic things on her head are weapons.</description>
<picture>18668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3015" type="appears in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="77">7.10</rating>
<name>Mint Blancmanche</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An intelligent blue-haired girl who loves to wear full body costumes, but will never, ever be seen by her friends while wearing them (unless it`s work-related). Her family is wealthy and she sometimes comes off snobbish, but she normally has a sincere, distinguished politeness in her voice when in conversations with others. She has a dark side, as she can sometimes be selfish to the point of letting her fellow Angels die rather than be embarrassed, and she likes to play mean pranks on the less-than-bright Ranpha. She also can read minds or emotions in some situations. She has a pair of white rabbit ear-like appendages just above her normal ears that twitch, rise or droop depending on her feelings. The ears also allow her to fly or hover in the air. Her last name is derived from the name for the dessert blancmange.</description>
<picture>18667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3016" type="appears in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="46">6.73</rating>
<name>Forte Stollen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A frank, husky-voiced, boyish redhead in a stylised military uniform complete with hat and monocle. Her hobby is collecting guns and other weapons, and is a strong believer in applied force to many situations. She is scared of and allergic to mice.</description>
<picture>18669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2069" picture="170535.jpg">Yamaguchi Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3017" type="appears in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="77">7.60</rating>
<name>Vanilla H</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A green-haired pale-coloured young girl who rarely speaks, and always in a calm, deadpan voice. Most of the time, when she speaks, she refers to God. She has a strange machine, known as the Nanomachine, in her room and often prays to it. Despite all of this, she is quite caring and always follows orders. She is also apparently the possessor of a hot temper, but keeps it well-hidden. She can heal the injuries of others, the effects made visible by a green glow around her hands, and the red gem at her forehead can sometimes project a powerful beam. She can also speak to various animals like when she talks to monkeys in episode 18. She carries around the stuffed animal in which Normad`s chip has been placed, but she`s not as devoted to Normad as he is to her.</description>
<picture>18670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14902" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Kahlua Marjoram</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kahlua Marjoram is the fourth member of the Galaxy Angel Rune troupe. She has a very quiet, gentle personality, speaking in a slow, rather laid-back tone. Her unique addition to the team is that she can use magic. She is from the Majoram Bloodline, which is a family known for their very powerful sorcery. Ultimately, she is a very powerful sorceress, though she is unable to use much of her power except during times of emotional distress. She sometimes transforms into "Tequila Marjoram", a bright purple-haired girl. Along with a distinct change in personality after the transformation (for example, she is more aggressive and hot-tempered), Tequila is capable of using the full potential of her magic power. Another noticeable difference between them is Tequila`s bust size. The transformation is triggered by Kahlua being exposed to alcohol, though the transformation can also be controlled by the consumption of a medication Kahlua invented. A running gag has Kahlua accidentally ingesting alcohol, bringing a less-than-amused Tequila into the scene.
Her personal color is light green. In battle, she (as Tequila) pilots the new Emblem Frame "Spell Caster", which has high defense and an attack called Hexa Cross-Break.</description>
<picture>42750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14904" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Tequila Marjoram</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tequila is the alter ego to Kahlua. She is different than Kahlua in most regards. For one, while Kahlua cannot effectively utilize all of her magical powers, Tequila can. Tequila also has bright-purple hair as opposed to Kahlua`s blond hair. Overall, Tequila`s character is much different. For example, she is much more daring, aggressive, and hot-headed than Kahlua.</description>
<picture>42752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14905" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Lily C. Sherbert</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lily Caramel Sherbet was the original leader of the Rune Angel Troupe, sporting dark blue hair. She is from a clan of female warriors and was the former leader of the Rune Angel Troupe, but she left on a mission and did not return until the present. At first glance, she appears to be dressed like a young knight. Not surprisingly, she is also quite a skilled swordswoman, and is rarely, if ever, seen without a rapier in hand. Despite this outward appearance, she has quite a diligent personality, sometimes lending money to the other Angels. She is currently working under Forte Stollen and Chitose Karasuma in the Imperial Training academy. In many ways, she is the antithesis to the Moon Angel Troupe`s Forte Stollen, with whom she shares a teacher-student relationship. She is known for her tendency to express approval with "OK-da" and disapproval with "NG-da" (NG standing for No Good). Her running gag has her unexpectedly bursting into tears.
Her personal color is dark blue. In battle, she pilots the new Emblem Frame "Eagle Gazer", a slow sniper that attacks with Extreme Lancer</description>
<picture>42753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1428" picture="18685.jpg">Nakayama Erina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14906" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-08">
<name>Anise Azeat</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fifth member of the Rune Angel Troupe, Anise Azeat is a red-haired girl with blue eyes. She has a very outgoing, active, and competitive personality. She also uses a rather rough talking style, including the use of the male pronoun "ore". While originally from a clan of gypsy pirates and a treasure hunter hired to steal the Brave Heart (Which Nano-Nano tries to stop her from stealing it, she slips and started falling but Anise grabs her hand and saved Nano-Nano. Since then Nano-Nano starts calling her master or big sister) she eventually joins the Angel Troupe, in no small part due to the assistance of Mint Blancmanche. She also looks up to Ranpha Franboise, referring to her as "Nee-san" (literally "Big sister"). Her running gag is a tendency to mispronounce words, especially names. To Mint`s displeasure, Anise once referred to her as "Mint Butamanju" (literally "Mint Porkbun"). She has also been seen to touch Kazuya in familiar ways, such as punching him in the arm, resulting in him calling her `tomboy`, and running away. (Sometimes, even crying.)</description>
<picture>42754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="93" picture="142975.jpg">Hanamura Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14907" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="2">7.83</rating>
<name>Nano-Nano Pudding</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nano-Nano Pudding is the third member of the Rune Angel Troupe. She is significantly different from the other members as she has light blue hair, as well as a long white tail, and rather narrow pupils. At first glance, she appears to be a catgirl, which isn`t entirely false, given her playful, kitten-like personality. Like her name suggests, she is in fact a living piece of lost technology and a Nano-machine generator, giving her the ability to interact with them in much the same way as Vanilla H, who she refers to as "Mama" because it was Vanilla who first discovered her on the Planet Pico. She also has the ability to heal like Vanilla, and it seems that her white tail has the strongest source of nano-machines. During her chapter in the game, she also displays the ability to copy another`s appearance at will (though she highly resents it). She tends to end her sentences with "nano da". She looks up to Anise as a `Master` or `Big Sister` seeing how Anise saved Nano-Nano from falling while stealing the Brave Sword.
Her personal color is sky blue. In battle, she pilots the new Emblem Frame "First Aider", which is also the only Emblem Frame to have TWO special attacks, which can be switched at any time. Repair Wave, a healing special similar to the Harvester`s (Vanilla`s Frame) "Repair Wave", and an offensive special, Needle Flechette.</description>
<picture>42755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14908" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Apricot Sakuraba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Apricot Sakuraba, or Rico for short, is the first member of the Rune Angel Troupe. She also happens to be the younger sister of Moon Angel Troupe ace pilot Milfeulle Sakuraba, whom she loves greatly. Thus, she constantly tries to be just like her as much as possible. While not particularly athletic, Apricot is known for having a superhuman amount of strength, though this only shows itself subconsciously. Despite harbouring a crush on her team leader, she is terrified of boys, and will unintentionally lash out with her full strength should a boy so much as touch her shoulder.
Her personal colour is orange. In battle, she pilots the new Emblem Frame "Cross Caliber", a very small, light Frame that can mode change to attack; its special attack is Hyper Blaster.</description>
<picture>42756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2227" picture="73301.jpg">Inamura Yuuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14909" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="2">7.18</rating>
<name>Natsume Izayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Differently from the visual novel, Natsume is just a princess who decides to live near the Rune Angels because she wants to eat delicious cookies. She has pearl pink hair and retains her sense of justice but also still acts as a child.</description>
<picture>42757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70674" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-16">
<name>Mimolette</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A kind of magical creature, A floating object with black cat face that can speak with anyone the same language. Nano Nano often pulls on the face and knocks it. It`s Kahlua`s partner.</description>
<picture>10706.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1989" picture="21290.jpg">Kobayashi Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70731" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-18">
<name>Isabella Essence</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Army Commander Transbaal in the city. She`s always behind a monitor to give orders to the Rune Angel-tai in the space station, even when she is a bit irresponsible as a commander.</description>
<picture>162887.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71027" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-09">
<name>Kuuhen Bahm</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Officer and housewife of the Rune Angel-tai house. He is a man dressed as a woman who cares much for his appearance and that is why he always has too much makeup. He is also the owner of a bar in which he always tries to seduce some male customers.</description>
<picture>211793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71030" type="appears in" update="2018-04-15">
<name>Dorten Baine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is Mayor of Transbaal`s city, who sometimes calls on the Rune Angel-tai for assistance. He always is covered by a polygon figure and frequently gets frozen.</description>
<picture>216232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2244" picture="52187.jpg">Nagashima Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="63919" update="2006-10-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出撃! 天使のスクランブる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Launch! Angels Scramble-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsugeki! Tenshi no Scramble-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64029" update="2006-10-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激安! グラウンドバザーる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Cheap! Ground Bazaar-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekiyasu! Ground Bazaar-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64271" update="2007-02-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説! 食材サバイバる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legendary! Food Stash Survival-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu! Shokuzai Survival-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64457" update="2007-02-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誘惑! 3時のカフェテーブる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Temptation! Snack Time at Cafe Table-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuwaku! 3-ji no Cafe Table-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64820" update="2007-02-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">和解! 大人のアルコーる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Truce! Adult`s Alcohol-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakai! Otona no Alcohol-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64992" update="2007-02-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誕生! 新人アイドる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Debut! New Idol-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanjou! Shinjin Idol-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65152" update="2007-02-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! 先輩はライバる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle! Senior is a Rival-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Senpai wa Rival-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65153" update="2007-02-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖! 雨の日のコーる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Horrible! Rainy Day Call-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu! Ame no HI no Call-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65154" update="2007-02-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">豪華! セレブのトラベる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Luxury! Celebrity`s Way to Travel-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouka! Celeb no Travel-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65155" update="2007-02-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強襲! 戦場のプロフェッショナる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack! Combat Professional-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoushuu! Senjou no Professional-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65156" update="2007-02-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">的中! 名探偵の推理ファイる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Accurate! Supersleuth`s Case File-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tekichuu! Meitantei no Suiri File-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65157" update="2007-02-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱湯! コマーシャる~ん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burning! Endure the Hot Water for PR-Rune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nettou! Commercial-Rune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65158" update="2007-02-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出現! ワルワルワる~んエンジェル隊!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arrival! An Evil Evil Evil-Rune ~ Angel Troupe!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsugen! Waruwaruwa-Rune Angel Tai!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72620" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125768" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125769" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132137" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132138" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132139" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132140" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132141" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132142" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132143" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132144" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132145" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132146" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132147" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132148" update="2011-08-01">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 13</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
