<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="437" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-08-02</startdate>
<enddate>1997-08-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Slayers Great</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Slayers Movie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スレイヤーズぐれえと</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Slayers Great -The Movie-</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Slayers Great</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Slayers - La città dei Golem</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">슬레이어즈 그레이트</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">秀逗魔导士 剧场版3</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="373" type="Sequel">Slayers Gorgeous</anime>
<anime id="350" type="Prequel">Slayers Return</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2642" approval="2" total="6">Detatoko Princess</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<creators>
<name id="804" type="Unknown Relation">TV Tokyo</name>
<name id="950" type="Unknown Relation">SoftX</name>
<name id="1338" type="Original Work">Kanzaka Hajime</name>
<name id="2744" type="Direction">Watanabe Hiroshi</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="3630" type="Character Design">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="680" type="Music">Hattori Takayuki</name>
<name id="4235" type="Chief Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch1000 [Lina] and http://anidb.net/ch7725 [Naga] travel through a strange town ruled over by two goofy-looking barons, who hate each other`s guts. While travelling through the city, they save a young girl from a rampaging bull golem. They later find out that not only are golems the main export of the town, but that the girl`s father is the legendary http://anidb.net/ch7732 [Galia Einberg], a master golem craftsman.
Both Lina and Naga are just dying to have him make a golem for them (so they can sell it off at a high price, of course) but he has not built a golem in a long time. Instead, he has been fighting with his son, an amateur craftsman who would rather make golems shaped like Venus than the useful and silly looking ones his father makes; until they meet our two heroines, that is.
Galia takes one look at Lina and is enthusiastic about building a golem of her, much to Naga`s chagrin, but his son is completely enamoured by the busty, maniacal laughing sorceress. Both father and son have been commissioned to build a golem for one of the barons, to be pitted against each other in a duel to the death. Though the barons are planning on using the golems to build an invincible army, the craftsmen, in a battle of their own, have other ideas...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1553">5.69</permanent>
<temporary count="1557">7.12</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>127044.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>739</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>868</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>379</identifier>
<identifier>ldvwwb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Slayers_Great</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スレイヤーズ_(アニメ)#.E3.82.B9.E3.83.AC.E3.82.A4.E3.83.A4.E3.83.BC.E3.82.BA.E3.81.90.E3.82.8C.E3.81.88.E3.81.A8</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1496</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>153307</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2343" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-17">
<name>ojou-sama laugh</name>
<description>A type of haughty laughter typical of rich young girls, as well as older rich women. Generally sounds like a high-pitched "OHOHOHOHOHOHO".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4730" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-15">
<name>golem</name>
<description>A golem is an animated anthropomorphic being, magically created entirely from inanimate matter. The word was used to mean an amorphous, unformed material (usually out of stone and clay) in Psalms and medieval writing.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>creepy laugh</name>
<description>At least one character in the show inexplicably and repetitively seems to have the urgent need to laugh in a creepy, loud and usually very annoying way.
For male bad guys this seems to be a must, but some of the uppity (rich) female characters use the laugh as part of their condescending attitude as well.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1000" type="main character in" update="2014-09-22">
<rating votes="1994">9.10</rating>
<name>Lina Inverse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lina Inverse is the primary protagonist and the only character appearing in the whole Slayers-franchise. She is an adolescent but very powerful sorceress, with a great love for money, treasure and food. In the anime and manga (but not in the light novel) Lina uses overly destructive magic recklessly, often with little provocation. She is reputed to be an evil, powerful, destructive, diminutive sorceress (the evil part is arguably not true, though one may consider her greed and general lack of concern for others unless they are in danger of being killed can be considered "evil").
Lina has gained many different nicknames, including "Bandit Killer" and "Dragon Spooker", neither of which she`s very fond of, though to her, her most embarrassing nickname is "Lina the Pink" which is her official title amongst the sorcerer`s guild.</description>
<picture>161200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7725" type="main character in" update="2014-09-18">
<rating votes="341">7.81</rating>
<name>Gracia Ul Naga Seyruun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naga the White Serpent is the self-proclaimed rival and companion of Lina Inverse.
Naga`s real full name is Gracia Ul Naga Seyruun, making her the first daughter of Crown Prince Philionel El Di Seyruun and the older sister of Amelia Wil Tesla Seyruun.
Naga is very skilled in white magic, no doubt because of where she grew up. Lina is often surprised when Naga uses these spells, because Naga does not seem like the kind of person to want to heal people. Naga also specializes in shamanistic magic, especially spells of the earth and water variety. She enjoys creating her own golems (even if they usually don`t turn out very well), and one of her favorite spells to use is Freeze Arrow.
Naga is also able to terrorize people with her obnoxious laughing. She`s extremely proud of her highly developed, self-confident laugh and the effect that it has on unsuspecting people. She also likes to use her body to tease or distract men who are trying to go against her.
Naga carries a large sword, but she is never seen using it, possibly because she is afraid of blood. This phobia was most likely caused by witnessing her mother`s brutal slaughter. The mere sight of blood, even from a small cut, is enough to cause her to faint.</description>
<picture>161192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7727" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="4">3.01</rating>
<name>Laia Einberg</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saved by Lina and Naga, she is compelled to take them home with her. Daughter of Garia and sister to Huey, she`s the only member of the family who works, so she spends a good deal of time lamenting her ill fortune.</description>
<picture>26603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7729" type="main character in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="3">2.23</rating>
<name>Hyui Einberg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son of legendary golem craftsman Garia Einberg, much to their mutual disgust. Unlike his father, his golems are generally studies in female anatomy. Creates the golem "Grand Goddess", a twenty-story rock behemoth which looks all too much like Naga.</description>
<picture>26606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7731" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="3">1.48</rating>
<name>Lord Haizen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of two lords attempting to gain power of a golem-producing city, with the intent of conquering a kingdom with the golems produced there. (Really!) Has a mouth chock full of gold teeth. Employs Garia Einberg and Lina to oppose his counterpart, Lord Granion.</description>
<picture>26607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="480" picture="232940.jpg">Kawakubo Kiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7732" type="main character in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="3">2.23</rating>
<name>Garia Einberg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Legendary golem craftsman. Initially opposes building golems for the purpose of fighting, but is convinced otherwise once hearing of a golem competition. His craftsmanship tends towards super-deformed figures, which leads to hilarious results. He`s the father of Laia and Huey.</description>
<picture>26609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3298" picture="151659.jpg">Katou Seizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7733" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="3">1.48</rating>
<name>Lord Granion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of two lords attempting to gain power of a golem-producing city, with the intent of conquering a kingdom with the golems produced there. Employs Huey Einberg and Naga to oppose his counterpart, Lord Heissen.</description>
<picture>26611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44126" type="appears in" update="2012-05-01">
<rating votes="4">1.65</rating>
<name>Roumadoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8057">Sasaoka Shigezou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44393" type="appears in" update="2012-05-06">
<rating votes="2">1.22</rating>
<name>Granion no Sokkin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5159" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1997-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5160" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9784" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>1997-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175350" update="2016-02-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175351" update="2016-02-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
