<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4385" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-01-05</startdate>
<enddate>2007-06-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Saint October</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Octubre Santo</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">神圣十月</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">セイントオクトーバー</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6788" approval="2" total="2">Anyamal Tantei Kiruminzoo</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.konami.jp/visual/saintoctober/</url>
<creators>
<name id="839" type="Animation Work">Studio Comet</name>
<name id="7016" type="Character Design">Hara Masaharu</name>
<name id="6522" type="Series Composition">Enatsu Yuki</name>
<name id="2336" type="Music">Takaki Hiroshi</name>
<name id="11889" type="Original Plan">Kumasaka Shougo</name>
<name id="15769" type="Direction">Satou Masafumi</name>
</creators>
<description>Whether it is the future or the past... it is the world of fantasy and horror hiding in the shadow of the demon city. In the city, consecutive mysterious incidents that cannot be solved by science have occurred. To solve the incidents, they gather three girl detectives possessing special abilities.
http://anidb.net/ch14665 [Hayama Kotono]. She is an orphan living in a convernt.
http://anidb.net/ch14666 [Shirafuji Natuski]. She is Kotono`s classmate and a pop idol.
http://anidb.net/ch14667 [Hijiri Misaki]. She is a mysterious girl who fights against nightmares of her previous life.
Those who want to bring the Judgment Day to the world.
Those who want to save the world.
Which is justice, and which is evil?
When Kotono encounters a boy who lost his memory, the wheel of the story begins to move but slowly. Then, solving the mysteries, the three girls will confront the fate that will influence the existence of the human beings.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="221">3.68</permanent>
<temporary count="223">6.25</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>59933.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7240</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1724</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3713</identifier>
<identifier>ludkuh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.konami.jp/visual/saintoctober/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Saint_October</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>セイントオクトーバー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>902</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326634</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8741</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>神聖十月</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="14665" type="main character in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="2">6.78</rating>
<name>Hayama Kotono</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kotono is a young, usually cheerful, girl working for the Kuroki Detective Agency. As a child, she was abandoned near a church with no memories of who she was or where she came from. The church`s priest, Joshua, took her in as his own daughter. Her card is Justice and she transforms into Loli Black. Her weapon is a sword which she uses as a final attack on the enemy.</description>
<picture>1285.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9941" picture="37015.jpg">Kataoka Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14666" type="main character in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="2">6.78</rating>
<name>Shirafuji Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuki is Kotono`s good friend of equal age and fellow member of the agency. She comes from a rich family. Her card is Moon and she transforms into Loli White. Her weapon is a pair a nun chucks.</description>
<picture>2974.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14667" type="main character in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="2">6.78</rating>
<name>Hijiri Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaki is a mysterious and agile girl. In the past episodes it was shown that her hometown was attack and that she has a mission. Her card is Strength and she transforms into Loli Red. Her weapon is a bow and arrow.</description>
<picture>1286.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16331" type="appears in" update="2010-04-02">
<name>Goth Loli Shoujo Tantei Dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="66028" update="2007-02-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ誕生! 少女が超ゴスロリに!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Creation! Girl Is a Super Goth-Loli!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Tanjou! Shoujo ga Chou Goth-Loli ni!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66457" update="2007-02-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ吃驚[びっくり]! 噂の美女が超襲来!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Surprise! Rumored Beauties Super Invasion!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Bikkuri! Uwasa no Bijo ga Chou Shuurai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66968" update="2012-08-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ共闘! お嬢様だって超変身!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Joint Struggle! Even Her Highness Has a Super-Transformation!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Kyoutou! Ojou-sama Datte Chou Henshin!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67015" update="2012-08-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ迷惑! 超昼間から吸血鬼!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli-Trouble! Vampire in the Super-Middle of Daytime!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Meiwaku! Chou Hiruma kara Kyuuketsuki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67111" update="2008-05-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ再戦! エルロックの超リベンジ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Rematch! Elrock`s Super Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Saisen! Elrock no Chou Revenge</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67371" update="2008-05-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ結成! ゴスな少女の超探偵団!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Formation! The Super Detective Squad of Gothic Girls!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Kessei! Gothic na Shoujo no Chou Tanteidan!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67597" update="2007-02-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ疑惑! ヨシュア, 超秘められたその愛...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Suspicion! Joshua, His Super Hidden Love...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Giwaku! Joshua, Chou Himerareta Sono Ai...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67618" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ熱投! 何故なの? あなたと超ボーリング!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Devotion! Why? Super Bowling With You!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Nettou! Naze na no? Anata to Chou Bowling!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67932" update="2007-03-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ潜入! その時, TVに映った超大物が!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Infiltration! At That Moment, the Super Big Thing on TV!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Sennyuu! Sono Toki, TV ni Utsutta Chou Oomono ga!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68284" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ初恋! あなたに届け超マイハート!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli First Love! To Deliver You, My Super Heart!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Hatsukoi! Anata ni Todoke Chou My Heart!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68505" update="2007-03-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ激突! 女の意地が超ごっつんこ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Crush! A Woman`s Heart Is Super Hard to Predict!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Gekitotsu! Onna no Iji ga Chou Gottsunko!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69006" update="2007-03-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ純愛! ソフィアの愛は超輝いて...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Pure Love! Sophia`s Love Shines Brightly...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Junai! Sophia no Ai wa Chou Kagataite...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69160" update="2007-03-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69248" update="2007-03-31">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ慟哭! 悩んで迷って, 超乙女!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Lamenting! Troubled and Confused, Super Maiden!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Doukoku! Nayande Mayotte, Chou Otome!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71700" update="2007-04-06">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ復讐! あたちのうらみを超くらうでち!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Revenge! My Super Grudge Will Be Mine!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Fukushuu! Atachi no Urami o Chou Kuraudechi!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71844" update="2007-04-12">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ昔日! 記憶のあなたに超会うために...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Nostalgia! To Super See You from My Memories...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Senjitsu! Kioku no Anata ni Chou Au Tame ni...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72049" update="2010-04-14">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ桃色! フォーリンラブに超ホーミータイトでち!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Pink! Fall in Love and Hold Me Super-Tight!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Momoiro! Fall in Love ni Chou Hold Me Tight dechi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72290" update="2007-05-03">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ抹殺! 山で遭難超二人きり!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Extermination! A Super Couple Stranded in the Mountains!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Massatsu! Yama de Sounan Chou Futarikiri!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72569" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ救出! お嬢の決意が超マグマ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Rescue! A Rich Girl`s Determination Is Super-Magma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Kyuushutsu! Ojou-sama no Ketsui ga Chou Magma!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72570" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ水着! 波に消えた超片思い...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Swimsuits! The Super-Unrequited Love That Vanished in the Waves...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Mizugi! Nami ni Kieta Chou Kataomoi...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73558" update="2007-05-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ救急! 友情? 同情? 過剰に超看病!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Emergency! Friendship? Sympathy? Super-Excessive Nursing!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Kyuukyuu! Yuujou? Doujou? Kajou ni Chou Kanbyou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73692" update="2007-05-26">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ帰国! 世界よ, われに超ひざまづけ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Return! The World Must Super-Kneel Before Me!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Kikoku! Sekai yo, Ware ni Chou Hizamazuke!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73693" update="2007-05-26">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ公開! 超NAZO・NAZOな私のヒミツ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Revelation! My Super-Mysterious and Enigmatic Secret!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Koukai! Chou Nazo Nazo na Watashi no Himitsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75157" update="2007-06-12">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ窮地! いつの間にやら超敵だらけ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Crisis! Before We Knew It, We Were Super-Surrounded by Enemies!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Kyuuchi! Itsu no Ma ni Yara Chou Teki Darake!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75158" update="2007-06-12">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ激怒! 愛を奪還, 超突入!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Wraith! Super Charging In and Taking Back My Love!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Gekido! Ai o Dakkan, Chou Totsunyuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75159" update="2007-06-12">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ激戦! 信じて見つめて超正義!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Pitched Battle! Have Faith and Witness Our Super Justice!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Gekisen! Shinjite Mitsumete Chou Seigi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75160" update="2007-06-12">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ決着! めくるめくあなたと超運命!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loli Conclusion! Dazzling, My Super Destiny with You!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Kecchaku! Mekurumeku Anata to Chou Unmei!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128164" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128165" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128166" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128167" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128168" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128169" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128170" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128171" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128172" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
