<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4397" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-09-17</startdate>
<enddate>2006-09-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Taiyou no Mokushiroku: A Spirit of the Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Taiyo no Mokushiroku: A Spirit of the Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Taiyo no Mokushiroku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Taiyou no Mokushiroku</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">太陽の黙示録 A Spirit of the Sun</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6441" approval="12" total="14">Tokyo Magnitude 8.0</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.wowow.co.jp/anime/taiyo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="1208" type="Original Work">Kawaguchi Kaiji</name>
<name id="6461" type="Music">Honda Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="4327" type="Direction">Kojima Masayuki</name>
<name id="5447" type="Chief Animation Direction">Saijou Takashi</name>
<name id="5447" type="Character Design">Saijou Takashi</name>
</creators>
<description>A big earthquake demolishes the capital of Japan, and it splits the main land into halves. Japan is divided into the northern and the southern parts. They accept aides from two large countries, i.e., United States and China. However, actually, it is occupation named "aid". Many Japanese become refugees to go to foreign countries. But, the recovery from the disaster doesn`t work well, and frictions between the inhabitants and the refugees who can`t go home are getting serious.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="300">6.87</permanent>
<temporary count="302">7.35</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>11016.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6842</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1857</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3721</identifier>
<identifier>dpbtst</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.wowow.co.jp/anime/taiyo/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>太陽の黙示録#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>906</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>325580</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8611</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2924" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>earthquake</name>
<description>*rumble rumble rumble rumble*
Upheaval of the Earth`s crust, usually resulting in widespread destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="17878" type="main character in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Ryuu Genichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4573" picture="2158.gif">Matsuda Youji</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="17477" picture="147103.jpg">Ookubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17879" type="main character in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Zhang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17880" type="main character in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Hata Ryoutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17881" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Chen Li Chun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17882" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Ishikura Shinsuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17883" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Jimichi Ikuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3251" picture="24230.jpg">Hara Yasuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17884" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Jing Ming</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4196" picture="26343.jpg">Takeda Masanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17885" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Kurofuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="144" picture="16904.jpg">Sakuya Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17886" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Madam Xia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16845" picture="162825.jpg">Nozawa Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17887" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Ozu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20526" picture="53943.jpg">Sasaki Umeji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17888" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Ryuu Natsue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2879" picture="170992.jpg">Hino Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17889" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Ryuu Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17890" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Ryuu Takuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19172" picture="189066.jpg">Inagaki Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17891" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Sakamaki Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17892" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Shu Qin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19174" picture="50012.jpg">Kubota Tamie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17893" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-21">
<name>Yang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="61025" update="2006-08-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>80</length>
<airdate>2006-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">前編 -海峡-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1: The Channel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenpen: Kaikyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61026" update="2006-08-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>80</length>
<airdate>2006-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後編 -国境-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2: Borders</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhen: Kokkyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63834" update="2006-10-03">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
