<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4403" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seirei no Moribito</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">精灵守护者</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Guardian of the Sacred Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Хранитель Священного Духа</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="synonym">Guardião do Espírito Sagrado</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Šventosios dvasios saugotoja</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="synonym">Vaimuvalvur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Moribito</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">精霊の守り人</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Moribito: Guardian of the Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Guardian of the Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Moribito, guardián del Espíritu Sagrado</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Moribito, Guardião do Espírito Sagrado</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">精灵守护者</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="26" approval="235" total="275">Juuni Kokuki</anime>
<anime id="2185" approval="126" total="150">Stranger: Mukou Hadan</anime>
<anime id="6187" approval="114" total="158">Kemono no Souja Erin</anime>
<anime id="640" approval="92" total="122">Scrapped Princess</anime>
<anime id="6331" approval="14" total="21">Guin Saga</anime>
<anime id="3427" approval="11" total="26">Utawarerumono</anime>
<anime id="5842" approval="8" total="22">Bounen no Xamdou</anime>
<anime id="1543" approval="4" total="12">Samurai Champloo</anime>
<anime id="5535" approval="4" total="12">Kurenai</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="75">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="376027">It starts interesting and it ends interesting, to bad the 15 episodes in between are kinda dull and lackluster.

The fighting scenes are awesome but also very scarce.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372933">Must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="152042">Story driven fantasy at its best with a female main character(including really good, but rare fight scenes).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="292889">Very good setting, great animation and convincing narration. Not only fans of the genre will find this anime to be a true gem.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="188098">Adventure all the way.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="342518">Amazing, recommended!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="1294">Another show that combines great animation with good directing and a interesting plot.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="240214">Wonderful.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="49266">Story of facing your fears &amp; doing things that feel right. Superb fantasy/adventure Plot, beautiful artwork, memorable characters. If you like an action oriented anime with a good amount of drama, solid soundtrack. A thought provoking `Epic` series. Good direction from Kamiyama Kenji</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="86487">great action</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="328481">At first I feel bored watching this, but slowly as I watch thing happen I didn`t bored anymore. The story is great</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="16524">This anime has a great plot line and has much depth to it.  It has good action scenes.  This is a must to watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="290120">More of my favorite Epic Historical Fantasy. Has a strong female lead and beautiful scenery, as well as mysticism and an adjacent reality.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="180434">its really good</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="302824">Most of the time it was relaxing watching it. When there were battle scenes, they were very well done, and a bit more realistic than most other fight scenes in anime. The ending wasn`t very satisfying to me.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="188268">for best caracter female 2007</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="524135">A mindblowing Anime . A true must see classic</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="691547">If you thought women can`t be like a though guy
then watch this please :)
Woman Power all the way</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="657678">An extraordinary story and powerful characters. This anime has successfully creates an amazing combination of realistic Japanese mythology.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="764835">One of my all time favorite anime`s everything about this series is first class.

Highest recommendation 10/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="264667">Very good Animation, scenery and imagination.&lt;br /&gt;like folklore.&lt;br /&gt;Song in 22th epsode.&lt;br /&gt;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="140864">^_^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="243527">If there was a "Highly recommended/Must see/what are you still here for?" category, this anime would be in it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="257875">An adventure no one should miss. Very immersive, every ep worth watching - no fillers.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="61338">I`ll dare you find any flaws in how the characters are written, how the story is told or how the landscape is portrayed. I couldn`t or even wanted.&lt;br /&gt;This is merely an animated series yet it easily rivals anime movies and fantasy literature in quality.&lt;br /&gt;Ending usually sucks in similar animes. With Moribito you enjoy while it lasts. Bid farewell hoping that, there wouldn`t be a crappy sequel, but a completely new story to be told with same kind of dedication.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="44187">Substance, form, execution, intellectual and emotional appeal. True variety of settings and story threads. Character driven plot development. Intrigue as well as slice-of-life. Fantastic animation. Simply masterful; has brought subtlety back to anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="321348">damn awesome&lt;br /&gt;sofar, this one the best animated !!&lt;br /&gt;and the music too&lt;br /&gt;storyline also awesome !!&lt;br /&gt;hope they make the sequel of it :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="95930">really awesome !&lt;br /&gt;The Story wasn`t bad !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="396387">must see for everyone. If I would be forced to say something more about this anime, mmm: the "epic" tag should be written in arial 72</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="424134">A very well told story with good character development and a good plot. Not so much action but I don`t mind that, the adventure itself is well worth a watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="350281">Although it takes a few liberties with the novel, this anime is solid in all categories and absolutely worth watching.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="360204">Simply a masterpiece.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="404473">slow-paced at the start yes, but extremely well told, intriguing characters, and awesomely drawn, great music too, very heartwarming&lt;br /&gt;great fantasy anime!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="312303">Absolute enjoyment</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="270767">I can`t believe I missed this when it came out but its amazing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="325967">10/10 from me.

If you`re like me and don`t like female leads in action anime you should still give this a shot, the artwork, story, side characters and fight scenes are all perfect, or near to perfect.

While the lead is female, she doesn`t act it, if you watch it, give it atleast 3-5 episodes before deciding to stop.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="296097">masterpiece!! all the action, humor, and plot are top notch. definitely a must see!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="476533">This anime is beautifully drawn and contains a rich fantasy world that blends Japanese and Chinese cultures wonderfully.  It is truly a gem, an anime that is nearly flawless.  It`s not for one-track-minded action-lovers.. this is an anime for the more mature audience who can appreciate a real story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="516146">One of the finest animes I have seen. Great animation, great story, great characters, great voice acting (well, in Japanese), this anime should be destined to be a classic. Watch it if you enjoy anime with some depth. I think you might be surprised!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="455302">gr8 anime. very few like this are the ones that balance a good story, drama, action and animation. i wud hav liked to see more spear fights, but whatever amount of it was in the anime was just about right. I`m not a fan of action, but god! i loved the fight scenes. specially the fight between Jiguro and the 2nd assasin. gr8 moves. everything was nicely written and executed. thanks to the creators! 
a MUST WATCH indeed!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="284037">Probably one of the best anime I ever watched. I like almost every episode, though there some fillers, but they`re interesting though. Many elements are absent in this anime, such as romance &amp; ecchi. But this anime is one of the best despite that. If you like adventures, this anime is perfect for you. It has good environment, great background music (what you should`ve expect from Kawai Kenji :p), and smooth storyline. Mainly, this anime focused more on motherly love, character development, conflict, &amp; a bit of politics. Enjoy. :p</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="380535">Made with great taste! Everything about it is graceful!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="471794">I just can`t describe in words how great is this one. It is perfect in every aspect: artwork, animation, plot, soundtrack (the theme music is one of my favorites). Just watch and see for yourself.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="387097">Solid deep stroy, well made animations, great fighting scenes, good  pacing &amp; progress of the story, some dull moments but overall it`s one of the best shows out there.

A must see for any anime fan.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.moribito.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="205" type="Direction">Kamiyama Kenji</name>
<name id="6977" type="Original Work">Uehashi Nahoko</name>
<name id="31688" type="Character Design">Asou Gatou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a fantasy novel by http://anidb.net/cr6977 [Uehashi Naoko] &amp; Futatsugi Saki.
Once every 100 years, a water spirit implants an egg into a person who then becomes the Guardian of the Sacred Spirit. This time, the responsibility falls on http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum], the Second Prince of the New Yogo Empire. The Emperor, fearing that the spirit`s possession of Chagum could destroy the prestige of the royal family, attempts to have Chagum killed. As a result, the Second Empress secretly asks a female bodyguard, http://anidb.net/ch8748 [Balsa], to abscond with Chagum.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7080">8.49</permanent>
<temporary count="7186">8.51</temporary>
<review count="16">8.90</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224594.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6634</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1827</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3723</identifier>
<identifier>ldcqbc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/moribito/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.moribito.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Moribito:_Guardian_of_the_Spirit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>守り人シリーズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>956</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>325501</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8826</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>수호자_시리즈#텔레비전_애니메이션</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>守護者系列#電視動畫</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9994</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00N32JHN8</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5093" parentid="2867" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>royal intrigue</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8748" type="main character in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="177">9.08</rating>
<name>Balsa Yonsa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Balsa is a skilled warrior from the faraway land of Kanbal. Balsa claims to be a simple bodyguard-for-hire; in reality she wields her spear in order to save lives in atonement for the eight lives that were taken to protect her when she was a child.</description>
<picture>49474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4897" picture="67088.jpg">Andou Mabuki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8750" type="main character in" update="2009-07-27">
<rating votes="24">7.58</rating>
<name>Chagum</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chagum is the second prince of the Imperial Family. Chagum bears the egg of the water spirit. At first it is believed to be the reincarnation of a demon defeated by his ancestor, the first Emperor. Convinced that it would bring misfortune and destruction to the country, Chagum`s father secretly condemns him to death. However, before they could assassinate him, his mother, the Second Empress, hired Balsa to hide and protect him.</description>
<picture>28090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4437" picture="26711.jpg">Adachi Naoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8751" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="29">8.58</rating>
<name>Tanda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tanda is an herbalist who lives in the mountains. His skill as a shaman is lacking, but he is a good doctor due to always having to stitch up Balsa after her many battles. He also works as a traveling medicine man, trading his wares with the local towns and cities.</description>
<picture>28091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8752" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-08">
<rating votes="22">7.69</rating>
<name>Torogai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Torogai is an old shaman and Tanda`s teacher. A master of the old ways, she is in-tune with the spirit world, Nayug. It is this relationship that allowed her to discover the spirit`s true identity. She is capable of communicating with denizens of the spirit realm through water.</description>
<picture>28092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2820" picture="22867.jpg">Mayama Ako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8755" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-08">
<rating votes="31">9.00</rating>
<name>Jiguro Musa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jiguro is Balsa`s mentor, caretaker, and bodyguard. Originally the leader and strongest member of the king of Kanbal`s `Nine Spears`; he `betrayed` his country to save Balsa`s life. After fleeing Kanbal, they were pursued by the other eight `Spears`. In a series of pitched battles, Jiguro was forced to kill the men he considered his best friends. He also trained Balsa to wield a spear and she later `inherited` his spear after he passed away.</description>
<picture>3019.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="292" picture="68967.jpg">Nishi Rintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10718" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="12">6.19</rating>
<name>Tooya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An orphan boy and friend of Balsa, whom he regards as his elder sister. It is later discovered that he and Saya were saved by Balsa, and that is how they became acquainted. This may be the reason why Tooya claims that he would go "through fire and water for Balsa".</description>
<picture>31936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10719" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="17">4.36</rating>
<name>Saya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An orphan girl who is a friend of Balsa. Due to Balsa staying at their hut, she and Touya have to leave the city and end up following Balsa.</description>
<picture>31937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10720" type="appears in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="4">6.72</rating>
<name>Ni-no-Kisaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Second Empress. Mother to http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum], she was the one who requested http://anidb.net/ch8748 [Balsa] to become Chagum`s bodyguard.</description>
<picture>31954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10721" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="6">3.27</rating>
<name>Gakai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sagum`s tutor, later entrusted by Shuga with the responsibility of organizing the translations of the Secret Tome.</description>
<picture>31955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10722" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="18">6.63</rating>
<name>Shuga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum]`s tutor; the youngest master star diviner in history. He is amongst the only three people aware of the hunters that serve in the Emperor`s shadow. He investigates the real cause of the Drought Sign and Chagum`s supposed death in secret.</description>
<picture>31956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10723" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="8">5.70</rating>
<name>Mon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the initial pursuers sent to retrieve prince http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum] after http://anidb.net/ch8748 [Balsa] leaves with him. Head of the hunters.</description>
<picture>31959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10724" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="10">5.86</rating>
<name>Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the initial pursuers sent to retrieve prince http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum] after http://anidb.net/ch8748 [Balsa] leaves with him. After securing the prince, Jin attempts to kill him so that Chagum need not die by his own father`s hands; knowing though that this act of insubordination would mean Jin`s own death. He deems it a favour in return for the kindness that the prince showed him earlier in his life.</description>
<picture>31963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10725" type="appears in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="1">2.05</rating>
<name>Zen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the initial pursuers sent to retrieve prince http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum] after http://anidb.net/ch8748 [Balsa] leaves with him.</description>
<picture>31961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2503" picture="186211.jpg">Mochizuki Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10726" type="appears in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="1">5.80</rating>
<name>Yun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the initial pursuers sent to retrieve prince http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum] after http://anidb.net/ch8748 [Balsa] leaves with him.</description>
<picture>31962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10727" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="8">2.43</rating>
<name>Seidoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1416" picture="18579.jpg">Ishimori Takkou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10728" type="appears in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="4">8.33</rating>
<name>Sagum</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum]`s older brother. Cares deeply for http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum]. When http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum]`s belongings were ordered burned after http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum] was presumed dead, Sagum took over the task to protect http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum]`s things.
He dies from overwork in his responsibilities as Crown Prince before being able to see http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum] alive again.</description>
<picture>31966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7065">Kobayashi Yoshinari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10730" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="11">1.79</rating>
<name>Mikado</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Emperor. Due to the belief that http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum] was possessed and that the possession was the reason for the Drought Sign being seen, he ordered http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum] to be killed. The Emperor is the only one able to kill http://anidb.net/ch8750 [Chagum] due to fact that was how his ancestor ascended the throne (by killing a Water Spirit), and the belief that only the Emperor knows this method.</description>
<picture>31992.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10733" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<name>Tanda no Oji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch8751 [Tanda]`s uncle.</description>
<picture>32029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7040" picture="32030.jpg">Makishima Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10734" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<name>Yaasam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10735" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<name>Yaasam no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch10734 [Yaasam]`s father.</description>
<picture>32037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3102" picture="24178.jpg">Chou Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10736" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Karubo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10737" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Gyopusaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2233" picture="21784.jpg">Takewaka Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10738" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Seena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3697" picture="78864.jpg">Asagami Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10739" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Tandoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10764" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="2">5.69</rating>
<name>Hyok</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of hunters.</description>
<picture>32084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6995" picture="186184.jpg">Sasada Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10765" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<name>Rai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of hunters.</description>
<picture>32085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10766" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="1">8.40</rating>
<name>Sun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of hunters.</description>
<picture>32086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="606" picture="18011.jpg">Masuda Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10767" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<name>Taga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of hunters.</description>
<picture>32087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5034" picture="33312.jpg">Fukuhara Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10769" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<name>Souya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3300" picture="24699.jpg">Kitagawa Yonehiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10770" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="3">6.28</rating>
<name>Nimuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10771" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<name>Nimuka no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch10770 [Nimuka]`s mother.</description>
<picture>32097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2221" picture="83141.jpg">Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10773" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Ichi-no-Kisaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The First Empress.</description>
<picture>32100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2221" picture="83141.jpg">Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10777" type="appears in" update="2009-07-27">
<rating votes="2">5.45</rating>
<name>Karuna</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch8748 [Balsa]`s father. He was a physician of Kanbal`s king. Rogsam, the king`s ambitious younger brother, blackmailed him into using poison to assassinate the king. He was threatened to kill http://anidb.net/ch8748 [Balsa] if Karuna refused.</description>
<picture>32122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10778" type="appears in" update="2009-07-27">
<rating votes="1">5.80</rating>
<name>Taguru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A closest friend of http://anidb.net/ch8755 [Jiguro] amongst spears of king. He was told to kill the co-conspirators of the http://anidb.net/ch10777 [physician] who poisoned the king. His wife and child have been taken hostage, so he has no choice but to fight his friend.</description>
<picture>32123.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="63202" update="2006-09-17">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69338" update="2007-04-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="56">8.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女用心棒バルサ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Balsa, the Female Bodyguard</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Balsa, La Guardaespaldas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna Youjinbou Balsa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71816" update="2007-04-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="37">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃げる者 追う者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hunter and the Hunted</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Fugitivo y cazador</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nigeru Mono Ou Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71817" update="2014-04-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="42">9.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fight to the Death</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Combate a Muerte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71818" update="2014-04-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="31">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トロガイの文</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Torogai`s Writings</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La epistola de Torogai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Torogai no Fumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71819" update="2007-04-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="31">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘策, 青い手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Step, the Blue Hand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hisaku, Aoi Te</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71951" update="2007-04-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="29">8.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青霧に死す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Dies in the Blue Fog</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aogiri ni Shisu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71952" update="2007-04-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="30">5.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チャグムの決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chagum`s Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chagum no Ketsui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72543" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="30">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">刀鍛冶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Swordsmith</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katanakaji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73307" update="2007-09-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="26">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渇きのシュガ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thirsty Shuga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaki no Shuga</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73308" update="2011-10-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">土と英雄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hero and Soil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Do to Eiyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73695" update="2011-10-04">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花酒をタンダに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flower Wine for Tanda</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hana Shu o Tanda ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73696" update="2007-05-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="26">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏至祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Solstice Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Geshi Matsuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73702" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="74424" update="2007-06-06">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="32">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人でなく虎でなく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Neither Man nor Tiger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito de Naku, Tora de Naku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75096" update="2007-06-11">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">結び目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Knot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Musubime</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75382" update="2007-06-18">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="23">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夭折</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Premature Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78042" update="2007-06-28">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="21">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ただひたすらに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In All Earnestness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tada Hitasura ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78557" update="2007-07-01">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水車燃ゆ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Water-Wheel Burning</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suisha Moyu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79787" update="2007-07-09">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いにしえの村</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ancient Village</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inishie no Mura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80255" update="2007-07-17">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃亡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toubou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80491" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狩穴へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Hunter`s Cave</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kariana e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80916" update="2007-07-30">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="28">9.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジグロ・ムサ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jiguro Musa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jiguro Musa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81100" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="23">8.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目覚めの季</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Season of Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezame no Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81101" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="19">9.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シグ・サルアを追って</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chasing After Sig Salua</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shigu Sarua o Otte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81102" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="19">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の希望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Kibou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81103" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="20">8.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Banquet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81104" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="20">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Going on a Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90003" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
