<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="445" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-01-05</startdate>
<enddate>2003-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Stratos 4</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">스트라토스4</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">สตราโตส 4 ภาค ทีวี</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">stratos4</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Стратос 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">s4</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ストラトス・フォー</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Stratos 4</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Stratos 4</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1858" type="Sequel">Stratos 4 (2004)</anime>
<anime id="2857" type="Other">Sentou Yousei Shoujo Tasukete! Maeve-chan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="630" approval="18" total="23">Uchuu no Stellvia</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="177640">If you can tell what is a BAC-TSR2 without resorting to Google you may enjoy this series a bit like me. This series could be much better if it had any verisimilitude, even the minimal amount. The problem isn`t the fanservice girls, the problem is that they are militar jet pilots, schoolgirls and waitresses all at the same time! Strike Witches makes more sense.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.stratos4.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="758" type="Animation Work">Studio Fantasia</name>
<name id="758" type="Original Work">Studio Fantasia</name>
<name id="2320" type="Character Design">Yamauchi Noriyasu</name>
<name id="2836" type="Series Composition">Takayama Katsuhiko</name>
<name id="3052" type="Direction">Mori Takeshi</name>
<name id="2320" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamauchi Noriyasu</name>
<name id="4483" type="Music">Amano Masamichi</name>
</creators>
<description>The show centres on the adventures and friendships of four Bishojo girls with a backdrop of a huge sky and the universe beyond.
The year is 2xxx AD. Numerous comets have passed and detected in our solar system, and because of that, there are fears and unpredictable dangers that some of them may crashed upon the earth and will cause mass destruction on the planet.
Therefore, as a part of Cosmic Crisis Management, mankind built a comet impact "cemetery" above earth`s satellite orbit. This comet impact cemetery equipped with Space Shock Machines that will eliminate those comets before they can reach the earth. Those space shock machines are flown by female pilots, who also known as the Storm Troops, and are armed with special missiles to destroy incoming comets into small pieces. Those girls are soon to be known as Comet Blasters and are very popular among people on earth.
On earth, in various places, many comet impact cemeteries were also made as second line of defence, so that in the event of large comet fragments passed the Comet Blasters, it can be destroyed by the Meteor Sweeper who fired special missiles from earth. At the same time, these comet impact cemeteries on earth provide training grounds where young pilots are trained to gain qualification as future Comet Blasters.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1170">4.86</permanent>
<temporary count="1177">6.93</temporary>
<review count="3">7.38</review>
</ratings>
<picture>53090.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1969</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1903</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>421</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1143</identifier>
<identifier>dkibtw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.stratos4.jp</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Stratos_4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ストラトス・フォー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240377</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5790</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2776" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>parasite</name>
<description>Parasites are life forms that feed off other beings in some way. In anime, they are often aliens and usually intelligent. For shock value, and to avoid having to draw aliens all the time, their prey is preferably human; they may see humans as food, as puppets for mind control, or simply as temporary body hosts. In every case, the human is the victim of a "merging", which is not to be confused with the more "amicable" symbiosis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="20619" type="main character in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="14">7.97</rating>
<name>Nakamura Ayamo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A candidate pilot and also the daughter of a politician. Ayamo is fiery and hot-headed and eager to become a Comet Blaster and is fed up with Mikaze`s laziness.</description>
<picture>53095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="490" picture="17481.jpg">Kikuchi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20620" type="main character in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="19">7.78</rating>
<name>Doi Shizuha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A candidate pilot and also the daughter of a photographer. Studious and ambitious, Shizuha is the yes-woman of the group.</description>
<picture>53094.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20621" type="main character in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="19">7.63</rating>
<name>Honjou Mikaze</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A candidate pilot and the 16-year-old protagonist. Despite coming from an elite class pilot family, Mikaze initially had no interest in becoming a pilot and was an underachiever and a slacker. However, she learns later the importance of piloting.</description>
<picture>53096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20622" type="main character in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="14">6.11</rating>
<name>Kikuhara Karin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61075" type="appears in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Orbital Station</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>145306.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61076" type="appears in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Conveyor YB-60</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>145305.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61077" type="appears in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>TYPE-559MS</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>145304.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61078" type="appears in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Il-SX1</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>145303.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61079" type="appears in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>SAC-1B</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>145302.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61080" type="appears in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>SAC-0 (Stratos Zero)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>145301.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61081" type="appears in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Yak-28MST</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>145300.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61082" type="appears in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>MiG-31MS</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>145299.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61083" type="appears in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>TSR.2MS</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>145298.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61084" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Tsukino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61090" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Chris Kalman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61091" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Betty Busemann</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61092" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<rating votes="4">6.73</rating>
<name>Annette Kaley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61093" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Kubo Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61094" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Oozora Miharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2049" picture="228615.jpg">Soumi Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61096" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Mikuriya Alice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61097" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Mikuriya Ran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61098" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Mikuriya Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61099" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Sako Kouichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61100" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Mukai Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34819" picture="130320.jpg">Kimura Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61101" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Robert Reynolds</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61102" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Kisaragi Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61103" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Fujitani Kei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61104" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Iwasaki Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61108" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Ikeda Sora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145265.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61109" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Miyazawa Tsubasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145264.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1630" picture="1887.gif">Tasaka Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107073" type="appears in" update="2019-11-20">
<name>Inspector</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5224" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">INITIAL POINT</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Initial Point</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Initial Point</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5314" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FOX ONE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fox One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fox One</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5403" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DECISION HEIGHT</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decision Height</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Decision Height</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5606" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">GO AROUND</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go Around</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Go Around</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5623" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TALLY HO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tally Ho!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tally Ho!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6062" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">CHECKING SIX</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Checking Six</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Checking Six</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6256" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MACH SPEED</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mach Speed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mach Speed</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6363" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">GO GATE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go Gate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Go Gate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6364" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">VAPOR TRAIL</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vapor Trail</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Vapor Trail</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6674" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MISSION ABORT</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission Abort</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mission Abort</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7025" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TARGET MARGE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Target Merge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Target Marge</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7057" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ENGAGE!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Engage!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Engage!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7265" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FINAL APPROACH</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Approach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Final Approach</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68507" recap="true" update="2011-08-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Logbook</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">LOG BOOK</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88962" update="2008-03-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD extras Stratos goods for sale announcement</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121123" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121124" update="2012-01-19">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121138" update="2012-01-19">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136477" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
