<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="448" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-01-04</startdate>
<enddate>2003-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Lime-iro Senkitan: Meiji Nippon, Otome Sakimorisu.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lime-Colored History of War</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lime-Colored War Tales</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Raimuro Senkitan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Raimuiro Senkitan</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">LCWT</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">RS</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">らいむいろ戦奇譚 明治日本,乙女 防人ス.</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2119" type="Sequel">Lime-iro Senkitan: Nangoku Yume Roman</anime>
<anime id="2807" type="Sequel">Lime-iro Ryuukitan Cross: Koi, Oshiete Kudasai.</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.limeiro.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3054" type="Direction">Suzuki Iku</name>
<name id="4511" type="Character Design">Watanabe Mayumi</name>
<name id="985" type="Animation Work">Studio Hibari</name>
<name id="1022" type="Series Composition">Akahori Satoru</name>
<name id="116" type="Music">Oomori Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="1022" type="Original Work">Akahori Satoru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on an eroge by http://anidb.net/cr878 [élf].
It is 1904, the Russo-Japanese war has just started and the Japanese army is getting ready to attack Port Arthur by establishing a training camp for female pilots in Hokkaido. http://anidb.net/ch35091 [Umakai Shintarou], a former diplomat who has once lived in Russia, is chosen to supervise the training.
Although the girls — http://anidb.net/ch35088 [Sanada Momen], http://anidb.net/ch35090 [Honda Sarasa], http://anidb.net/ch35089 [Katou Asa], http://anidb.net/ch29009 [Fukushima Kinu], http://anidb.net/ch28988 [Kuroda Rinzu] and http://anidb.net/ch31992 [Ichijouji Sumi] — assigned to him overwhelm him, his sense of duty as a teacher brings him to guide these girls to complete their secret mission, although he does not even know what that secret mission is.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="906">3.31</permanent>
<temporary count="916">6.20</temporary>
<review count="3">4.82</review>
</ratings>
<picture>168260.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2151</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1097</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1142</identifier>
<identifier>ropdfz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.limeiro.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Lime-iro_Senkitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>らいむいろ戦奇譚</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>598</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239547</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5663</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1314</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1816" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-09">
<name>uniform -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>The "uniform" tag is to be split and removed. Please help by tagging the character with the appropriate kind of uniform (e.g. school uniform, maid dress, etc) and removing this tag from them, and by not adding this tag to any further characters. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2675" parentid="2831" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Russia</name>
<description>Russia, officially known as the Russian Federation, is a sovereign country in Eurasia. Russia is the largest country in the world by area, covering more than one-eighth of the Earth`s inhabited land area, and the ninth most populous. The European western part of the country is much more populated and urbanised than the eastern; about 77% of the population live in European Russia. Russia`s capital Moscow is one of the largest cities in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5915" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>French kiss</name>
<description>A kiss in which the tongue enters the partner`s mouth.</description>
<picurl>238326.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="28988" type="main character in" update="2011-08-01">
<rating votes="11">8.62</rating>
<name>Kuroda Rinzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8011" picture="32603.jpg">Aimoto Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29009" type="main character in" update="2011-08-01">
<rating votes="9">5.80</rating>
<name>Fukushima Kinu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="410" picture="228116.jpg">Aoki Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31987" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="9">3.90</rating>
<name>Soushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71124.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31988" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="9">3.90</rating>
<name>Oushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71125.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31989" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="12">4.41</rating>
<name>Koushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6856" picture="151113.jpg">Machii Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31991" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="16">7.12</rating>
<name>Kuki-sama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31992" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="13">8.19</rating>
<name>Ichijouji Sumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="628" picture="188442.jpg">Dodo Asako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31995" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Kaji Hyougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35088" type="main character in" update="2011-08-01">
<rating votes="9">7.41</rating>
<name>Sanada Momen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35089" type="main character in" update="2011-08-01">
<rating votes="9">6.69</rating>
<name>Katou Asa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4860" picture="211311.jpg">Sasajima Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35090" type="main character in" update="2011-08-01">
<rating votes="9">7.83</rating>
<name>Honda Sarasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8012" picture="32604.jpg">Otomiya Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35091" type="main character in" update="2011-08-01">
<rating votes="4">6.57</rating>
<name>Umakai Shintarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35092" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-01">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Date Masanosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35096" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-02">
<rating votes="8">5.91</rating>
<name>Rasha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76345.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2089" picture="151696.jpg">Morota Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35097" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-02">
<rating votes="8">3.66</rating>
<name>Saten</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76346.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35098" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-02">
<rating votes="3">5.53</rating>
<name>Sophia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76347.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2810" picture="45903.jpg">Yokote Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35099" type="appears in" update="2011-08-02">
<rating votes="2">7.60</rating>
<name>Veludo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76348.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2810" picture="45903.jpg">Yokote Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35100" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="2">2.19</rating>
<name>Grigori Ephimovich Rasputin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76349.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35101" type="appears in" update="2011-08-02">
<name>Yukimura</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76359.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35102" type="appears in" update="2011-08-02">
<name>Tadakatsu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76361.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35103" type="appears in" update="2011-08-02">
<name>Kiyomasa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76362.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35104" type="appears in" update="2011-08-02">
<name>Masanori</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76363.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35105" type="appears in" update="2011-08-02">
<name>Nagamasa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76364.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35108" type="appears in" update="2011-08-02">
<name>Antoinette Gandhi XIII</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35109" type="appears in" update="2011-08-02">
<name>Amanohara</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="35110" type="appears in" update="2011-08-02">
<name>Lime-tai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>76370.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35111" type="appears in" update="2011-08-02">
<name>Russia-gawa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>76371.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35119" type="appears in" update="2011-08-03">
<name>Pyotr</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5226" update="2006-08-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦艦の中の女学校</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The girl`s academy on the battleship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkan no Naka no Jogakkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5315" update="2006-08-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天乃原発進</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amanohara, weigh anchor!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amanohara Hasshin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5540" update="2006-08-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">軍人として, 教師として</title>
<title xml:lang="en">As A Soldier, And As A Teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gunjin toshite, Kyoushi toshite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5574" update="2006-08-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名探偵更紗!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Detective Sarasa!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meitantei Sarasa!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5668" update="2006-08-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう一つの故郷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Other Homeland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mouhitotsu no Kokyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5815" update="2006-08-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">静かなる休日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Peaceful Day Off</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shizuka Naru Kyuujitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5816" update="2006-08-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">千羽鶴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Thousand Paper Cranes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senbazuru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6138" update="2006-08-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大凶なんか怖くない!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m not afraid of bad luck!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daikyou Nanka Kowakunai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6139" update="2005-07-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">リトル・ステップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Step</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Little Step</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6407" update="2005-07-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">閉ざされた心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Closed Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tozasareta Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6410" update="2005-07-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいちゃんの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Onii-chan Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-chan no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6544" update="2005-07-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の授業</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Class</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Jugyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6938" update="2005-07-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝利の鐘よ 未来へ響け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Victory Bell, Echo To The Future!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouri no Kane yo Mirai e Hibike</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125842" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125843" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
