<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4486" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>51</episodecount>
<startdate>1991-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>1992-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Zettai Muteki Raijin Ou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Absolutely Invincible Raijin-Oh</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Raijin-Oh</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Eldran Series 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Zettai Muteki Raijin-Oh</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">raijin ou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">絶対無敵ライジンオー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Matchless Raijin-Oh</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4487" type="Sequel">Zettai Muteki Raijin Ou (1992)</anime>
<anime id="6317" type="Character">Kanzen Shouri Daiteiou</anime>
<anime id="3961" type="Character">Nekketsu Saikyou Gozaurer</anime>
<anime id="5816" type="Character">Genki Bakuhatsu Ganbaruger</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/works/list/detail.php?cid=95</url>
<creators>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="5273" type="Story Composition">Sonoda Hideki</name>
<name id="3580" type="Direction">Kawase Toshifumi</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
<name id="6389" type="Character Design">Takeuchi Akira</name>
</creators>
<description>Suddenly, an evil empire, Jaaku, raids the Earth. But the light appears from the Earth, and fights against Jaaku. It is Raijin Oh operated by Eldran. Eldran has protected the earth since the ancient ages. But he was injured during the fight, and Raijin Oh falls to the ground. On the other hand, Jaaku scatters their weapons, Aku Darmer, all over the world.
Meanwhile, in Yosho elementary school, they have extra lessons in the 3rd class of the 5th grade. Eldran leaves Raijin Medal to them and asks them to save the Earth for him, and then he disappeared. In this way, the Earth Defense Agency consisted of elementary students is founded.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="21">5.64</permanent>
<temporary count="23">6.80</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>187492.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2459</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1897</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2873</identifier>
<identifier>uamuxm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/works/list/detail.php?cid=95</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Zettai_Muteki_Raijin-Oh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>絶対無敵ライジンオー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3586</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89105</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>절대무적_라이징오</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>绝对无敌</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5638" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-25">
<name>military is useless</name>
<description>The regular military force per se or certain units thereof are way out of their league when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes (e.g. powerful aliens). Thus the regular military is completely useless. 
Often, only children (of all people) with special abilities and/or powered suits can defend Earth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="49938" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライジンオー見参!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raijin-Oh Arrives!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raijin Ou Kenzan!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49939" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくたち地球防衛組</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We are the Earth Defense Class</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi Chikyuu Boueigumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49940" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">テストなんて大迷惑!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Test is How Big an Annoyance!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Test Nante Dai Meiwaku!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49941" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お花畑を守りぬけ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect the Field of Flowers!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ohanabatake o Mamorinuke!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49942" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決めろ! 無敵の龍尾脚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decision! Unrivaled Dragon Tail</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimero! Muteki no Ryuubikyaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49943" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">交通戦争を生き残れ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Survive the Traffic War!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutsuu Sensou o Ikinokore!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49944" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">酔っぱらいにはご用心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taking Care of Drunkard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yopparai ni wa Goyoujin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49945" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友情の無敵合体!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Absolute Union of Friendship!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuujou no Muteki Gattai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49946" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">心のカビを吹き飛ばせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blowing Away Moldy Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro no Kabi o Fukitobase</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49947" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガソリンが消えた町</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Town Where Gasoline Vanished</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gasoline ga Kieta Machi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49948" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クッキーの悪夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cookie`s Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cookie no Akuma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49949" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プールはアツイドン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pool is Too Hot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pool wa Atsuidon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49952" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤ちゃんを取り戻せ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Back the Baby!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akachan o Torimodose!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49953" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! ベースボール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Match! Baseball</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Baseball</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49954" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マッハ9で飛べ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly at Mach 9!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mach 9 de Tobe!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49955" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特訓なんかはね返せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crash Course in Returning the Shot!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokkun nanka Hanekaese!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49956" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">先生は邪悪獣!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teacher is a Jaaku Beast!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensei wa Jaaku Juu!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49957" recap="true" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大公開!防衛組の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Presentation! Earth Defense Class` Secrets</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Koukai! Boueigumi no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49958" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">臨海学校は大騒ぎ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seaside School is in Chaos!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rinkai Gakkou wa Oosawagi!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49959" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリアが消えた!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maria Has Disappeared!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maria ga Kieta!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49960" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵はライジンオー!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Enemy is Raijin-Oh!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki wa Raijin Ou!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49961" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">発進! 無敵の戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departure! The Invincible Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hasshin! Muteki no Senshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49962" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出た! 超無敵合体!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come Forth! Absolutely Invincible Union!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deta! Chou Muteki Gattai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49963" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬猫パニック作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dog/Cat Panic Plan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu Neko Panic Sakusen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49964" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特ダネはもらった!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Getting the Scoop!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokudane wa Moratta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49965" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカ大決戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Great African Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa Dai Kessen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49966" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大地震をやっつけろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defeat the Earthquake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Jishin o Yattsukero</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49967" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖のダルマ勝負!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Garuma`s Competition of Fear!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu no Darma Shoubu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49968" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">出現! スーパー邪悪獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Appear! Super Jaaku Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsugen! Super Jaaku Juu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49969" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">邪悪獣はおともだち?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jaaku Beast is a Friend?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jaaku Juu wa Otomodachi?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49970" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘! チャンネル争い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fierce Battle! Channel War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitou! Channel Arasoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49971" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おばけ屋敷で大冒険!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adventure in the Haunted House</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Obake Yashiki de Dai Bouken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49972" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖!踊る邪悪獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Terror! Dancing Jaaku Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu! Odoru Jaaku Juu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49973" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1991-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スキーはサムイドン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Skiing is Too Cold</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ski wa Samuidon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49974" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えたコマンダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vanished Commander</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Commander</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49975" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">邪悪獣は正義の味方!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jaaku Beast is an Ally of Justice!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jaaku Juu wa Seigi no Mikata!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49976" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">落書きたちの反乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graffiti Revolt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakugaki-tachi no Hanran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49977" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超能力者・仁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Psychic Jin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Nouryokusha Hitoshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49978" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おめでたいのは困り物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Celebration is a Troubling Thing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omedetai no wa Komarimono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49979" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベルゼブ大接近</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Belzeb`s Great Approach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Belzeb Dai Sekkin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49980" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対無敵の大誘拐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kidnapping of the Absolutely Invincible</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Muteki no Dai Yuukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49981" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">学校の秘密を守れ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect the Secret of the School!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakkou no Himitsu o Mamore!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49982" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超巨大れいこ出現!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Giant Reiko Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Kyodai Reiko Shutsugen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49983" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミクロ大決戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Micro-Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Micro Dai Kessen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49984" recap="true" update="2018-02-13">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">発表! 防衛組大百科!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Broadcast! Earth Defense Class Facts!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Happyou! Boueigumi Dai Hyakka!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49985" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイダー地球人になる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taida Becomes an Earthling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taida Chikyuujin ni Naru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49986" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大人が子供で大騒ぎ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adult to Child Chaos!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otona ga Kodomo de Oosawagi!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49987" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">変身! ブラックタイダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Transformation! Black Taida</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henshin Black Taida</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49988" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">出現! ジャーク帝国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Appear! Jaaku Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsugen! Jaaku Teikoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49989" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-03-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">皇帝ワルーサを倒せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defeat Emperor Warza!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutei Warza o Taose!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49990" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕らの夢は絶対無敵!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Dream is Absolutely Invincible!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokura no Yume wa Zettai Muteki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175969" update="2016-03-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175970" update="2016-03-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198503" update="2018-04-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャスト&amp;スタッフインタビュ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast &amp; Staff Interview</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cast &amp; Staff Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198504" update="2018-04-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">映像特典</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Karaoke</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eizou Tokuten</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
