<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4502" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-07-10</startdate>
<enddate>2006-07-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hoshizora Kiseki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Starry Sky Miracle</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Чудното звездно небе</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Чудо зоряного неба</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">星空奇迹</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">星空キセキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hoshizora Kiseki</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Чудо звёздного неба</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.cwfilms.jp/hoshizora/</url>
<creators>
<name id="8383" type="Character Design">Matsubara Toshikazu</name>
<name id="8383" type="Original Plan">Matsubara Toshikazu</name>
<name id="8383" type="Direction">Matsubara Toshikazu</name>
<name id="3529" type="Character Design">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="3529" type="Direction">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="1236" type="Work">CoMix Wave</name>
<name id="26263" type="Music">Double Oats</name>
</creators>
<description>Kozue, a member of an astronomical club, is a girl who dreams of the starry sky and of a summer romance. During one summer break, she sets out on a journey with a shining fragment of a fallen meteor hanging from her wrist and with a distant feeling that someone calling her. On her trip, she catches a glance of a boy with sad eyes. Later that evening she meets him in an isolated astronomical observatory,and feels an attraction to him, as they spend time talking about the stars. Ginga is a boy who has lived his life in a bubble as part of a governmental program to contact an orbital satellite and feels very alone in his structured and isolated life. Under the innumerable stars in the sky, a night of friendship and miracles begin...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1052">3.22</permanent>
<temporary count="1059">5.95</temporary>
<review count="1">8.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10878.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6681</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1220</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3748</identifier>
<identifier>mprkhv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.cwfilms.jp/hoshizora/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hoshizora_Kiseki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>星空キセキ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>966</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>325090</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8391</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4524" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-23">
<name>stars</name>
<description>Heavenly bodies that twinkle and sparkle in the night sky; sometimes beautifully and serenely, sometimes ominously. 
In some way, the plot is related to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4706" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-14">
<name>astronomy</name>
<description>Astronomy is the study of celestial objects (such as stars, galaxies, planets, moons, asteroids, comets and nebulae) and processes (such as supernovae explosions, gamma ray bursts, and cosmic microwave background radiation), the physics, chemistry, and evolution of such objects and processes, and more generally all phenomena that originate outside the atmosphere of Earth.
Astronomy is the oldest of the natural sciences. The early civilizations in recorded history, such as the Babylonians, Greeks, Indians, Egyptians, Nubians, Iranians, Chinese, and Maya performed methodical observations of the night sky. Historically, astronomy has included disciplines as diverse as astrometry, celestial navigation, observational astronomy and the making of calendars, but professional astronomy is nowadays often considered to be synonymous with astrophysics.
During the 20th century, the field of professional astronomy split into observational and theoretical branches. Observational astronomy is focused on acquiring data from observations of astronomical objects, which is then analyzed using basic principles of physics. Theoretical astronomy is oriented toward the development of computer or analytical models to describe astronomical objects and phenomena. The two fields complement each other, with theoretical astronomy seeking to explain the observational results and observations being used to confirm theoretical results.
Astronomy is one of the few sciences where amateurs can still play an active role, especially in the discovery and observation of transient phenomena. Amateur astronomers have made and contributed to many important astronomical discoveries, such as finding new comets.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="38692" type="main character in" update="2011-11-14">
<name>Ginga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77111.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9360" picture="171916.jpg">Chikiri Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38693" type="main character in" update="2011-11-14">
<rating votes="1">5.58</rating>
<name>Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77112.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10414" picture="38409.jpg">Hosono Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38694" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-14">
<name>Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kozue`s friend.</description>
<picture>77110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="613" picture="155849.jpg">Mizuno Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38695" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-14">
<name>Mitsuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77114.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4456" picture="43242.jpg">Sawada Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38696" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-14">
<name>Kanbu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of the project.</description>
<picture>77113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="50278" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51065" update="2010-02-27">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2006-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
