<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="451" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-06-21</startdate>
<enddate>1995-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fushigi no Kuni no Miyuki-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Миюки в Стране Чудес</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">不思議の国の美幸ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Miyuki-chan in Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Miyuki-chan w krainie czarów</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2733" type="Alternative Setting">Tsubasa Chronicle</anime>
<anime id="841" type="Character">Clamp Gakuen Tanteidan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/1997-1994/works_ova_fushiginokuni.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="747" type="Original Work">Clamp</name>
<name id="898" type="Work">Animate Film</name>
<name id="10665" type="Work">Ootake Masahiro</name>
<name id="6176" type="Character Design">Aoki Tetsurou</name>
<name id="6461" type="Music">Honda Toshiyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr747 [Clamp]`s manga adaptation of Alice in Wonderland.
Schoolgirl http://anidb.net/ch16405 [Miyuki] chases a skateboarding bunny-girl into a Wonderland of beautiful women.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="765">3.16</permanent>
<temporary count="771">5.63</temporary>
<review count="2">6.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>204866.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1496</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649</identifier>
<identifier>bqiksi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/1997-1994/works_ova_fushiginokuni.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Miyuki-chan_in_Wonderland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>不思議の国の美幸ちゃん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1583</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88260</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1817</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2756" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>board games</name>
<description>People here play a board game. It can vary from chess and Go, to Monopoly, to Dungeons and Dragons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2917" parentid="2756" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>chess</name>
<description>Chess is a game for two players. It is played on a square board, made of 64 smaller squares, with eight squares on each side. Each player starts with sixteen pieces (eight pawns, two each of knights, bishops, and rooks, and one king and queen). One player`s pieces are a light color, he is called "White", and the other player`s pieces are a dark color, he is called "Black".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3457" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-17">
<name>Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland</name>
<description>Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland (often shortened to Alice in Wonderland,) is an 1865 novel written by English author Charles Lutwidge Dodgson under the pseudonym Lewis Carroll. It tells of a girl named Alice falling through a rabbit hole into a fantasy world populated by peculiar, anthropomorphic creatures. The tale plays with logic, giving the story lasting popularity with adults as well as with children. It is considered to be one of the best examples of the literary nonsense genre. Its narrative course and structure, characters and imagery have been enormously influential in both popular culture and literature, especially in the fantasy genre.
The anime or an episode features important elements of the novel. This could mean that the main character is portrayed as Alice (with another name), accompanied by somebody portraying the white rabbit (possibly as a human). While the world can be a Wonderland, it does not have to be.</description>
<picurl>169452.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4517" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>inter-dimensional schoolgirl</name>
<description>One, or more, schoolgirls cross through time, space or some dimension using a space-warp-magic-portal-wormhole-singularity-thing to save one, or more, worlds, or planets.
A major twist could be that the schoolgirl might originate from that very magic-futuristic world, bearing one great secret legendary power to defeat one big bad legendary foe. The return back home is the leitmotiv of the whole series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16405" type="main character in" update="2010-04-04">
<rating votes="3">6.19</rating>
<name>Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Follows a bunny girl on a skateboard into a hole and insanity ensues...</description>
<picture>45724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1662" picture="25819.jpg">Kouda Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16406" type="appears in" update="2010-04-04">
<rating votes="3">6.30</rating>
<name>Bunny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Draws Miyuki down the "rabbit hole".</description>
<picture>45725.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="492" picture="17483.jpg">Nagashima Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16407" type="appears in" update="2010-05-04">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Tobira no Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Draws Miyuki into her chest, the door to Wonderland</description>
<picture>45726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2142" picture="170565.jpg">Shiina Hekiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16440" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-05">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Cho Li</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ally to To Li, attempts to attack Miyuki, we presume to take her clothes.</description>
<picture>45782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="492" picture="17483.jpg">Nagashima Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16441" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>To Li</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ally to Cho Li. They attack Miyuki when she passes through the door. She wears blue, while Cho Li wears red.</description>
<picture>45783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16442" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-05">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Boushiya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tries to get Miyuki to sit down and have some tea, while her henchman snoop around under her skirt.</description>
<picture>45785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16443" type="appears in" update="2010-04-05">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>March Hare</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Appears with Mad Hatter.</description>
<picture>45786.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16444" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Dormouse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Assistant to the Mad Hatter. Looks up Miyuki`s skirt when she finally accepts the tea.</description>
<picture>45787.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16445" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-05">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Cheshire Neko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cheshire ignores Miyuki`s frantic questions when she is lost in the woods and instead attempts to seduce her.</description>
<picture>45788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16446" type="appears in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Trump Card Girls</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>These girls work for the Queen of Hearts, and are painting her roses red, though they all secretly want to be punished for having white roses.</description>
<picture>45789.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16447" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Rose Girls</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The roses getting painted. Everything is female in this series.</description>
<picture>45790.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16448" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Joou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A dominatrix Queen of Hearts who punishes her servants severely if they don`t grow white roses. Upon discovering Miyuki, she demands that she call her Queen and lick her boots. She also chases her with her whip out of Wonderland.</description>
<picture>45791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16449" type="appears in" update="2010-04-05">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Jabberwocky</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sits atop the sword at the entrance to Mirrorland, and carries Miyuki to a world where the ground is above her and the sky is beneath her.</description>
<picture>45793.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16450" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-05">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Is at first angry at Miyuki when she falls out of the sky onto her, but then decides that Miyuki is a cute girl, and proceeds to jump on her face, claiming to have a nasty scratch on her inner thigh.</description>
<picture>45794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16602" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuri-san seems to a bit more mature than her counterpart Sumire-chan, but is first to decide that Miyuki is a pretty girl. Invites her to "play".</description>
<picture>46136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="483" picture="27541.jpg">Tange Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16603" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Butterfly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tiny humanoid butterfly, who does not try to seduce Miyuki. Does not understand Japanese when Miyuki tries to ask her where she is, and is blown away by the wind.</description>
<picture>46137.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16606" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Humpty Dumpty</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Controls the chess game.</description>
<picture>46138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16607" type="appears in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Chess Pieces</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>They slap each other when they take each other`s spots, and the loser automatically loses her clothes.</description>
<picture>46140.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="7542" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1995-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議の国の美幸ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miyuki-chan in Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushigi no Kuni no Miyuki-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14903" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">1.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鏡の国の美幸ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miyuki-chan in Mirrorland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagami no Kuni no Miyuki-chan</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
