<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4528" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>22</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2007-03-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sumomo mo Momo mo: Chijou Saikyou no Yome</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Sumomomo Momomo: The Strongest Bride on Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">地上最强的新娘</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">su(mo)+</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sumo^6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sumomomo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sumomomo momomo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">momomo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">すもももももも ~地上最強のヨメ~</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4821" approval="31" total="51">Seto no Hanayome</anime>
<anime id="5277" approval="7" total="15">Kamen no Maid Guy</anime>
<anime id="13434" approval="2" total="11">Hinamatsuri (2018)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="533215">i never thought i could really be sad when it went to finish.... and it`s made of 22 episodes!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="101072">is better that the rattings shows</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-sumomo.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="985" type="Animation Work">Studio Hibari</name>
<name id="14333" type="Character Design">Amisaki Ryouko</name>
<name id="14017" type="Music">4-Ever</name>
<name id="3719" type="Series Composition">Inoue Toshiki</name>
<name id="3684" type="Direction">Nakanishi Nobuaki</name>
<name id="14333" type="Chief Animation Direction">Amisaki Ryouko</name>
<name id="14282" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kanou Aya</name>
<name id="14270" type="Original Work">Ootaka Shinobu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr14270 [Ootaka Shinobu], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23601 [Young Gangan].
http://anidb.net/ch11491 [Inuzuka Koushi] is a smart high school student who aims to become a public prosecutor. Unfortunately for Koushi, he was born into a martial arts family whose head (i.e. his father) only knows one language: violence. When Koushi was still a baby, his father made a pact with his biggest rival to marry Koushi to his opponent-turned-friend`s daughter. The union of the two blood lines is supposed to bring forth Earth`s strongest martial arts clan.
Now, Koushi is in high school, oblivious to the marriage arranged for him at birth, when http://anidb.net/ch11490 [Kusuryuu Momoko] shows up: a sugar bomb, airhead, young-looking martial arts artist and Koushi`s self-proclaimed bride (the strongest on Earth, no less). Her wish for sexual intercourse meets with Koushi`s square refusal as he has absolutely no desire to get it on with someone who looks like she could be his little sister, not to mention that he does not have the foggiest idea who she actually is.
Meanwhile, a war has broken out between the martial arts families. For Koushi, this means that numerous fighters are out to challenge him. As if that were not bad enough, he also has a fight a phobia due to a traumatic incident that took place in his childhood. Now it is up to Momoko and her superhuman fighting skills to protect her "husband". Will the two sweethearts survive the trials and tribulations ahead of them?
— written by Kotonoha</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2453">5.05</permanent>
<temporary count="2488">7.18</temporary>
<review count="2">6.74</review>
</ratings>
<picture>154138.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6555</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1568</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3419</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3744</identifier>
<identifier>hsslup</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-sumomo.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sumomomo_Momomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>すもももももも_地上最強のヨメ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>960</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326172</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8574</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>스모모모모모모_~지상최강의_신부~</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>地上最強新娘</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="997" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>association football</name>
<description>Football is a sport that involves kicking a ball in order to score a goal, while the other team tries to stop you by kicking the ball in the other direction to score a goal of their own. In the United States, this sport is known as soccer; the inappropriately titled "American" football (which in fact is played with the egg-shaped "ball" being carried around) is some kind of rugby for babies.</description>
<picurl>40031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1559" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>narcissistic</name>
<description>The term narcissism refers to the personality trait of egotism, which includes the set of character traits concerned with self-image ego. The terms narcissism, narcissistic, and narcissist are often used as pejoratives, denoting vanity, conceit, egotism or simple selfishness. Applied to a social group, it is sometimes used to denote elitism or an indifference to the plight of others.
In short. One who shows extreme love and admiration for oneself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2259" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-30">
<name>naked apron</name>
<description>A character wearing nothing but an apron appears in the show.</description>
<picurl>162045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2670" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>school festival - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>THIS TAG NEEDS TO BE SPLIT:
into http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=6119&amp;reltb=eptb [school culture festival]
and http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=2665&amp;reltb=eptb [school sports festival]
The obligatory school festival (or cultural fair) with cosplay cafe, haunted house, theatre performance, and food booths cannot be missing in any school setting.
For good measure there may also be an athletics or sports festival in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2780" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>indirect kiss</name>
<description>Comedy element: Especially in a school setting the character who has fallen for a fellow student, but has not yet confessed his/her love, will be desperate for any sign of "closeness".
The indirect kiss: Anything the adored person touches with his/her lips — e.g. a used glass of lemonade, some half-eaten food, a half-emptied can of soda — the love struck will want to touch with her/his own lips.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3043" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-05-16">
<name>scary dad</name>
<description>Comedy element: The father of one of the usually female characters, appears to be a very menacing figure. He can be huge, often with facial scaring, and may be connected with the yakuza.
Think Nogizaka Gentou or Seto Gouzaburou.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3101" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-22">
<name>lottery wheel</name>
<description>One of the protagonists plays the lottery wheel in some shopping mall and — as fate will have it — wins a prize, e.g. a visit to the local hot springs or water park. Thus adding an unexpected plot twist to the story (and some ecchi potential).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4462" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>barefoot</name>
<description>This character never seems to wear any shoes — possibly a martial artist that prefers to stay in close contact with the ground, or a girl from the country now living in the city.
Alas, under more dire circumstances this can also be a sign of real poverty.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11490" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="10">5.03</rating>
<name>Kuzuryuu Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momoko is a strange and hyperactive, barefoot (but she starts to wear shoes to school after Koushi buys her a pair) young girl who is also a martial artist in a special form of martial arts that only members of the twelve Zodiac Masters of Japan can learn. She is associated with the dragon of the Chinese zodiac. She wants to become Koushi`s bride in order to produce a strong son with him, as her father told her that since she is a female, she is currently unable to master her family`s martial arts techniques effectively. Momoko shares a strange relationship with Koushi—its early stages have been compared to that of a dog and it`s master in the series itself. Momoko is very adamant about getting married to Koushi, and often tries to do the best she can to please him in any way. She always refers to Koushi ending his name with the term "-dono" because she has huge respect for him. Her martial arts skill is very incredible for a girl at her age which is very useful to protect Koushi from the assassins. She also has much stronger heart and sense of determination than Koushi. Although he does not see or admit to it, Koushi always appears to be pathetic for he always has to depend on Momoko to defend him against his enemies. For Koushi`s sake, Momoko will do anything even sacrifice herself for him because she loves him too much and always believes in Koushi. A running gag throughout the series is if she is experiencing extreme emotions, she will change into a super deformed form.</description>
<picture>1222.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2291" picture="23193.jpg">Kano Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11491" type="main character in" update="2009-09-01">
<rating votes="3">3.16</rating>
<name>Inuzuka Koushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20493" type="main character in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="8">6.90</rating>
<name>Miyamoto Iroha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyamoto Iroha is a young girl of fifteen and a member of the family of Zodiac Masters associated with the snake. The Miyamoto group was once a feared yakuza gang, but its power, repute and membership dwindled under Iroha`s father; his kind nature did not inspire hardened criminals to remain loyal. Iroha, along with her subordinate Hanzou with whom she travels, are the first to attempt the assassination of Koushi. Iroha wants to restore the reputation her family used to have as the most fearful of the twelve Zodiac Masters by killing Koushi, but is hindered by Momoko. Eventually, Iroha develops a crush on Koushi and resolves to find a new path for the Miyamoto family, after Momoko praises her for her fortitude in battle and laments that Iroha should follow the path of an assassin. Iroha eventually develops a close friendship with Momoko and supports her to get closer to Koushi. She even honestly wishes for their success. Iroha has attempted to save money for the resurrection of the clan, but is often troubled by Hanzou, who spends the money selfishly and by the landlady, an old woman who manages to terrify them whenever she demands their rent.</description>
<picture>52900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="184" picture="23381.jpg">Miyazaki Ui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20494" type="main character in" update="2017-04-24">
<rating votes="4">9.77</rating>
<name>Nakajima Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanae is a female high school student who is also one of Koushi`s friends. She is also his class` representative. Unknown to everyone, however, she changes into a heroine known as Tenchuu Senshi Uma Kamen, literally meaning "Divine Punishment Warrior Horse Mask", the identity she uses to fight as a superhero. She is apparently also the granddaughter of Iroha`s and Hanzou`s landlady. Both she and her grandmother are masters associated with the horse of the zodiac. As the chosen protector of the Inuzuka heir, Sanae has been given her tribe`s special outfit to wear, which increases its wearer`s power. Alas, the outfit closely resembles a bondage costume and is most effective when less of it is worn; when the wearer only has certain pieces of the costume equipped, their power is highly focused in the parts covered. In the Nakajima family, kicks are the central part of their combat style, so the costume is most effective for Sanae when she wears nothing but the boots. Needless to say, Sanae finds the costume embarrassing enough when wearing all of it.</description>
<picture>52901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20495" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-24">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Koganei Tenka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tenka is from the tiger family of the twelve Zodiac Masters and initially comes to assassinate Koushi. As he is from the tiger family, he carries a lot of traits with his personality that are akin to that of a feline such as being aquaphobic, and liking to play with round objects. He always carries around with him a soccer ball which he nicknamed "Becky" which seems to talk to him. (Although bystanders have commented that he is using ventriloquism.) It is interesting to note that Bekki has spoken to Tenka since early childhood, her voice maturing just as he matured. Tenka has a crush on Momoko based on a time when they met as children, when he defeated her during a training match and they agreed to meet again. Unfortunately for Tenka, while he assumed they would meet and marry once Momoko had grown stronger, she intended to meet and have a death match. Tenka later returns to warn Momoko of the fact that his relatives are coming to attack her and Koushi and takes their side during the battle. At the end of the anime, relations between Tenka and the main cast are much more friendly than initially.</description>
<picture>52902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20496" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-24">
<rating votes="2">7.37</rating>
<name>Hanzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanzou is seventeen and Iroha`s subordinate in the plot to kill Koushi. Since Iroha saved his life one day, he has followed her orders closely. The two of them share a relationship like Koushi and Momoko in that it could be likened to a dog and its master, although Iroha appreciates Hanzou from the start; he is the only member of her family`s once feared yakuza legion that has remained at her side. This is because he admires her greatly and considers her example an inspiration to improve himself. It is also quite likely that he has become romantically infatuated with Iroha. Unfortunately for him, Iroha states publicly that she considers him to be like a brother to her and considers the idea of a romantic relationship between them impossible.</description>
<picture>52903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20498" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="3">8.52</rating>
<name>Kameda Inaho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inaho is an anime-only character, a representative of the Kameda family, which once contested the Nakajima family for the right to be the protector of the Inuzuka family. The Kameda family is associated with turtles, which do not appear in the Chinese zodiac. In order to gain ascendancy over the twelve families, Inaho studies law and gains a teacher`s license in a bid to get close to Koushi as his school teacher and marry him—despite having a dislike for law and considering becoming a teacher a lot of hard work. Like Sanae Nakajima, she has an alter ego, hers named Kame Kamen (Turtle Mask), with an equally exposing outfit which features several large pieces of armor plating, like a turtle`s shell. She goes so far as to try and drive off Momoko and kidnap Koushi after drugging him because she could not seduce him, but in the end relinquishes her efforts in the face of Sanae`s dedication. She admits to having developed genuine feelings for Koushi. Unfortunately for her, he did not reciprocate, considering a relationship between a student and teacher to be unethical.
Inaho seems to be the first of a new initiative versus Koushi, since she is the first of several women who have sought him out to marry him and gain power over the twelve families, rather than assassinate him.</description>
<picture>52905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20499" type="appears in" update="2017-04-24">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Koganei Tenchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest of the Tiger tribe, and Tenka`s only true brother. He initially comes to kill Koushi after learning of his brother`s failure to do so, and is angry at his brother for supposedly abandoning Tenchi after realizing the he could become more powerful than he is, but instead becomes a protagonist towards the end of the series.</description>
<picture>52906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2091" picture="151645.jpg">Ishikawa Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20500" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-24">
<rating votes="3">5.45</rating>
<name>Koganei Tenten</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only sister out of the Tiger clan. She is the one who initially poisons Koshi, forcing him to come to their village to seek out the antidote. She is always wearing a fake smile, and is also the one who destroyed the Miyamoto clan from being the most powerful clan. She is secretly in love with Hanzo, though never reveals this in the series. She also shares a deep hatred for Iroha, who apparently "stole" Hanzo away from her.</description>
<picture>52907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20501" type="appears in" update="2017-04-24">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Koganei Tenga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4423" picture="26687.jpg">Okuda Keijin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20502" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Koganei Tenrei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the brothers of the Tiger clan. He uses cueballs and a pool stick to attack his enemies, even using such techniques as bouncing cueballs on the ground off each other to hit from behind. He is the first one that Koushi and friends must fight to retrieve his part of the antidote to the poison that Tenten inflicts upon Koushi.</description>
<picture>52909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20503" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Saigou Katsuyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saigou is a large, muscular young man who attends the same school as Koushi and the rest of the main cast. He has a very threatening demeanor, communicating mostly in grunts and gestures and continuously wears sunglasses. He is the admired leader of a trio of hoodlums from Koushi`s class and apparently frequently gets into fights. Appearances are deceiving, however; Saigou is quite fond of kittens, of which he has several, and apparently reads romantic stories for enjoyment. When he first meets Alice Uzuki, he defends her against a large group of assassins without any concern for his own safety. Later, he takes a hit from Alice`s guitar string weapon to protect Koushi from harm. He falls deeply in love with Alice and seeks help from Momoko and the other main cast to find a way to deepen their relationship. In the end, he allows Alice to go so she can pursue her dreams and be safe, speaking out loud for the first time to simply wish Alice "good luck", rather than demanding she stay for his sake. Saigou seems to be very friendly to the main casts, especially Koushi, as shown at the ending credits of the last episode, the three hoodlums came with Saigou to threaten Koushi but the three hoodlums flinched when Koushi greeted and waved his hand at Saigou and Saigou waved back.</description>
<picture>52910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4908" picture="28313.jpg">Kawano Taketoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20504" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="2">5.66</rating>
<name>Uzuki Alice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alice is another anime-only character, and is a member of the Uzuki clan, which is associated with the rabbit of the Chinese Zodiac; she has a unique `bunny ear` hairstyle when she dons her combat gear. While the Uzuki clan is heavily involved with assassinations and Alice is considered one of their best, she breaks away from her family and goes on the run, aspiring to becoming a successful musician. Eventually, Alice meets and befriends Saigou, leaving her open to blackmail from her own clan. She receives the order to either kill Koushi or be responsible for Saigou`s death. After nearly succeeding in the deed, Alice is stopped by Saigou, who tells her - through interpreter Momoko - that her hands were made to create music, not shed blood. Thanks to the other young martial artists` intervention, Alice finally manages to leave her clan behind and goes to France to study music.</description>
<picture>52911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8238" picture="186683.jpg">Mi-Ko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20505" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-24">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Inuzuka Unken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Unken is a martial arts master and the father of Koushi. He wants his son to follow in his footsteps, but is unable to persuade him to train in the martial arts. He heads the dog family of the Zodiac Masters of Japan. He and Sendayu are both friends and rivals. An old school photo shows that, although he now has a rather odd face, he was once the spitting image of his son. This has caused Koushi some concern for the future.</description>
<picture>63748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20506" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-04">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Kuzuryuu Sendayu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sendayu is a martial arts master and the father of Momoko. He told Momoko to find the strongest warrior and marry him, eventually bearing the strongest child, since Momoko cannot master her family`s techniques as she is female.</description>
<picture>60383.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20507" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-24">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Nakajima Kimie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9679" picture="203641.jpg">Komiya Kazue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20508" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Tomoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="20509" type="appears in" update="2017-04-24">
<rating votes="2">5.66</rating>
<name>Ayatsuji Kinu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60387.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20510" type="appears in" update="2013-05-04">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Miyazawa Rumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60385.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20511" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Nakajima Hikaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60386.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20512" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Kimogari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60384.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22177" type="appears in" update="2010-10-08">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Yuuki Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="63221" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地上最強の許婚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Fiancee on Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chijou Saikyou no Iinazuke</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63942" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天然爆熱少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Naturally Exploding Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tennen Baku Netsu Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64027" update="2008-04-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">15 Second Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64127" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">動物園でつかまえて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Caught at the Zoo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doubutsuen de Tsukamaete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64128" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仁義なき暗殺計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Humanity and Justice Is Not an Assassination Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jingi naki Ansatsu Keikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64129" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! もも子VSいろは</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash! Momoko vs. Iroha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Momoko VS Iroha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64130" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虎の刺客, 現る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assassination of the Tiger, Reality!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tora no Shikaku, Arawaru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65280" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見えない絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonds that Cannot Be Seen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mienai Kizuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65281" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐を呼ぶ後輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Kouhai That Calls the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi o Yobu Kouhai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65282" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲恋のヒーロー女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heroine`s Disappointing Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiren no Hero Onna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65696" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">早苗の許嫁(フィアンセ)現る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sanae`s Fiance Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanae no Fiance Arawaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65713" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天誅戦士ウマ仮面, 参上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heaven`s Punishment Warrior Horse Mask, Arrives</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenchuu Senshi Uma Kamen, Sanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65714" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風邪の日, 半蔵の場合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day of a Cold, Hanzou`s Situation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze no Hi, Hanzou no Baai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66506" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライバル対決! ウマとカメ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confrontation of Rivals! The Horse and the Tortoise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rival Taiketsu! Uma to Kame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66907" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お化け屋敷の恋騒動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Chaos of Love in the Haunted House</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Obake Yashiki no Koi Soudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66908" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">西郷の恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Love of Saigou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigou no Koi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67022" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Parody Episode 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67344" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">倦怠期の壊し方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Way to Break Fatigue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kentaiki no Kowashikata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67345" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! 虎の兄弟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash! The Tiger Siblings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Tora no Kyoudai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67346" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤミ鍋で歓迎会!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcoming Party at Yaminabe!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yaminabe de Kangeikai!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67347" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家政婦が来た!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Maid Has Come!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaseifu ga Kita!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67935" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命を共に...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Together with Fate...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei o Tomo ni...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68465" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの思い......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Respective Thoughts...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Omoi...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68466" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつもの日々へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Usual Days</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsumo no Hibi e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82424" update="2012-05-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉独占ラブ合戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Episode 23 Hot Spring Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsen Dokusen Love Kassen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82425" update="2012-05-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらわれた孝士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Episode 24 Kidnapped Koushi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sarawareta Koushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125920" update="2010-12-07">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125921" update="2010-12-07">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125922" update="2010-12-07">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125923" update="2010-12-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125924" update="2010-12-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
