<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4529" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2007-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mamoru-kun ni Megami no Shukufuku o!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mamoru-kun was Blessed by a Goddess!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Богиня, благослови Мамору-куна!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Megadere</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mamoru-kun ni Megami no Shukufuku wo!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">把女神祝福赐予护君</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">m-kun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mamoru-kun</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">護くんに女神の祝福を!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Venus to Mamoru</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9496" approval="5" total="7">Witch Craft Works</anime>
<anime id="88" approval="1" total="4">Koutetsu Tenshi Kurumi</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="420400">A cute enjoyable show</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kadokawa-pictures.jp/official/mamoru/</url>
<creators>
<name id="788" type="Animation Work">Zexcs</name>
<name id="122" type="Series Composition">Okada Mari</name>
<name id="4797" type="Direction">Kawasaki Itsurou</name>
<name id="4638" type="Music">Agematsu Noriyasu</name>
<name id="8506" type="Original Work">Iwata Hiroki</name>
<name id="8890" type="Character Design">Takashina Yuka</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr8506 [Iwata Hiroki] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr3431 [Satou Toshiyuki].
A strange power called Beatrice responds to the will of certain people and is capable of doing many wondrous and dangerous things. And http://anidb.net/ch4716 [Yoshimura Mamoru] has been accepted to a high school that specialises in teaching the use of this magic power.
On his way to school, Mamoru notices a pretty second-year student standing under the cherry trees. After a few words with her, she suddenly blushes and asks him to go out with her! — And so http://anidb.net/ch4717 [Takasu Ayako] becomes Mamoru`s girlfriend. She is a year older than him, taller, very beautiful, the committee leader for school discipline, a genius at using her Beatrice powers and the terror of the school. Nobody would ever believe Mamoru if he tried to tell them that she is really a very nice and shy girl.
In his first class, Mamoru is surprised that everybody is staring at him — as it turns out this is due to the rumour that Ayako, the Angel of Death, actually confessed to him! And then suddenly, he is summoned to the student council chambers and offered a position with Ayako on her student committee. It is indeed going to be a very busy school year for Mamoru.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1075">5.15</permanent>
<temporary count="1096">7.19</temporary>
<review count="1">3.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>13101.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6803</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1588</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3784</identifier>
<identifier>hbepat</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kadokawa-pictures.jp/official/mamoru/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mamoru-kun_ni_Megami_no_Shukufuku_o!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>護くんに女神の祝福を!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>963</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326181</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8566</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1894" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-04">
<name>shota</name>
<description>Shotacon, sometimes shortened to shota, is a Japanese slang portmanteau of the phrase Shoutarou complex and describes an attraction to young boys, or an individual with such an attraction. Outside Japan, the term is less common and most often refers to a genre of manga and anime wherein pre-pubescent or pubescent male characters are depicted in a suggestive or erotic manner.
In a general sense, this is the same as http://anidb.net/t2566 [loli], just replace young girls with young boys.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>35399.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2670" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>school festival - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>THIS TAG NEEDS TO BE SPLIT:
into http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=6119&amp;reltb=eptb [school culture festival]
and http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=2665&amp;reltb=eptb [school sports festival]
The obligatory school festival (or cultural fair) with cosplay cafe, haunted house, theatre performance, and food booths cannot be missing in any school setting.
For good measure there may also be an athletics or sports festival in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2781" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>first kiss</name>
<description>The first kiss plays a role in this anime. Especially for the female cast this can be quite an important moment, so that stealing ones first kiss is serious for them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2811" parentid="2831" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Germany</name>
<description>Germany, officially the Federal Republic of Germany, is a federal parliamentary republic in central-western Europe. It includes 16 constituent states, and has a largely temperate seasonal climate. Germany is the most populous member state of the European Union. Germany`s capital and largest metropolis is Berlin, while its largest conurbation is the Ruhr, with its main centres of Dortmund and Essen.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214345.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2873" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>Valentine`s Day</name>
<description>Valentine`s Day is a festive day celebrated every February 14.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China, Valentine`s Day is one month before http://anidb.net/t3147 [White Day], a celebration unique to those countries.
In the rest of the world:
On Valentine`s Day, both males and females will express their feelings of affection towards their loved ones, by exchanging gifts (such as cards, candies, and chocolates), going on dates, and other signs and actions of affection. Some people also take the opportunity to confess and propose for marriage. In Western countries, it is generally expected of the male to offer gifts to the significant other.
In many countries, friends and co-workers also exchange small gifts to show their friendship towards each other.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China:
On Valentine`s Day, many women feel obliged to give chocolates to all male co-workers, except when the day falls on a Sunday, a holiday. This is known as giri choco (義理チョコ, "obligation chocolate"), with unpopular co-workers receiving only chougiri choco (超義理チョコ, "ultra-obligatory chocolate") cheap chocolate.
This contrasts with honmei choco (本命チョコ, "love chocolate"), chocolate given to a loved one.
Friends, especially girls, may exchange chocolate referred to as tomo choco (友チョコ, "friend chocolate").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>160891.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2909" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>karaoke</name>
<description>Obligatory national pastime for students in any anime with school setting. Amateur singing to subtitled music videos.
The word itself is a compound of the Japanese words for "empty orchestra".</description>
<picurl>160894.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3408" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>skiing</name>
<description>Skiing is a recreational activity and competitive sport in which the participant uses skis to glide on snow.
Popular school excursion destination in winter is a ski resort, a town or village in the mountains where students do skiing, snowboarding and other winter sports.</description>
<picurl>161690.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5725" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-15">
<name>purikura</name>
<description>A standard on a date in a school setting, to remember the moment with the "loved one".
In Japan, purikura (プリクラ) refers to a photo sticker booth or the product of such a photo booth. The name is a shortened form of the registered trademark Purinto Kurabu (プリント倶楽部). The term derives from the English print club.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4716" type="main character in" update="2009-03-09">
<rating votes="7">3.07</rating>
<name>Yoshimura Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very short boy with a good smile. He is a 16 year old high school student, who just transferred to a new and prestigious school due to his high intellect. On his first day at school, he not only becomes a member of the student council, but also the boyfriend of fellow student council member, Ayako Takasu, who confessed her love for him earlier that day. He often comes off as a soft spoken character who is unsure of himself as to why Ayako would like him. He later learns that he too has the power to use Beatrice. Mamoru can`t often say no to the student council and becomes like a dog to them.</description>
<picture>20835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="188" picture="1804.gif">Kimura Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4717" type="main character in" update="2009-03-09">
<rating votes="10">5.64</rating>
<name>Takasu Ayako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very strong high school girl and girlfriend to Mamoru. She is very well-endowed when it comes to the power of Beatrice, and is considered one of the most powerful Beatrice users in the world, which is why she is sometimes targeted by assassins. Usually, Ayako is a very serious girl, who has been known to never smile around others, however, whenever around Mamoru, she can`t help but blush and smile a bit, as she becomes much more shy, and stutters often as well. Ayako lives with a caretaker alone in her grandfather`s mansion.</description>
<picture>20836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4718" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-09">
<rating votes="4">5.86</rating>
<name>Sudou Maya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The student council president, who has a strong character, which complements his status. He often does things that irritate Ayako to the point of earning a heavy punch from her.</description>
<picture>20837.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4719" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-09">
<rating votes="6">4.87</rating>
<name>Emelenzia Beatrix Rudiger</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Beatrice user, and a genius who entered into a university at the age of twelve. She was an orphan until the Rudiger family acknowledged her potential. She now aims to be strong enough to support her older brother, Johan, whom she has the utmost respect for. Emelenzia also admires Ayako since she was able to stand toe-to-toe with her brother in battle. She has a crush on Mamoru and tries to seduce him after she transfers.</description>
<picture>20838.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4720" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-09">
<rating votes="6">6.41</rating>
<name>Sudou Shione</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The vice-president of the student council, and Maya`s younger sister. She often has a very extravagant hairstyle, which changes everyday, that even her own brother calls "complicated". Everyone became so used to her wacky hairstyles that they could not recognise her when she had her hair down, though Maya was overjoyed to realize that he had such a cute little sister.</description>
<picture>20839.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4721" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-09">
<rating votes="4">7.23</rating>
<name>Fujita Mitsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The public relations officer of the student council. She likes to take pictures all the time, often taking pictures of Ayako, then selling them for outrageous prices in order to make a profit. Beside pictures of Ayako, Mitsuki is often seen taking pictures of the student council after they are hurt by Ayako.</description>
<picture>20840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21992" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-10">
<rating votes="4">5.42</rating>
<name>Yoshimura Itsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoshimura Itsumi is Mamoru`s younger sister.</description>
<picture>65447.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21993" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kikukawa Soushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65448.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21994" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-10">
<rating votes="3">4.87</rating>
<name>Maruyama Yuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maruyama Yuuka is the science officer of the student council. She is very shy and soft spoken, she owns a pet dog named Aru.</description>
<picture>65445.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21995" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-10">
<rating votes="3">5.77</rating>
<name>Hase Anna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hase Anna is the secretary of the student council. She seems to be the most "normal" of all the student council officers.</description>
<picture>65443.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1886" picture="21014.jpg">Inokuchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21996" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-10">
<rating votes="3">5.77</rating>
<name>Kirishima Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirishima Youko is the treasurer of the student council. She is very level-headed and confident and is the tallest among the girls.</description>
<picture>65444.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21997" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-10">
<rating votes="3">3.52</rating>
<name>Yagi Kousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yagi Kousuke is the executive committee member of the student council. He is very tall and muscular, well versed in using weapons, and has a major quirk of speaking a lot of English.</description>
<picture>65446.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2071" picture="74324.jpg">Oohata Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21999" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Johan Dieter Rudiger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Johan Dieter Rudiger is a German university student who is called the Prussian Devil and is considered to be one of the most powerful Beatrice users in the world. Despite his battle with Ayako resulting in a draw, Ayako was the one who ended up being gravely injured while Johan barely had a scratch on him. Although, because Ayako was capable of fighting against him on equal footing, he aims to have Ayako as his bride as he considers no one else worthy of her, especially Mamoru. Besides his outstanding Beatrice control, Johan is also very intelligent and is on an expedition with Ayako`s uncle researching the origins of Beatrice.</description>
<picture>55629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22000" type="appears in" update="2017-10-10">
<rating votes="3">5.96</rating>
<name>Yoshimura Shizue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoshimura Shizue is the mother of Mamoru and Itsumi.</description>
<picture>65449.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1881" picture="20979.jpg">Kobayashi Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22001" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="4">1.09</rating>
<name>Abiko Tsuneo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Abiko Tsuneo is a student in Mamoru`s school who is Ayako`s stalker enthusiast. He tends to be a very loud and imposing person, who would stop at nothing to be close to Ayako, whom he holds in very high regard.</description>
<picture>130802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2065" picture="228616.jpg">Kimura Taku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22006" type="appears in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Watanabe Takayuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Watanabe Takayuki is Mamoru`s classmate.</description>
<picture>55643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22007" type="appears in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Takasu Naoyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takasu Naoyuki is Ayako`s grandfather.</description>
<picture>55642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22008" type="appears in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Takasu Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22011" type="appears in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="3">3.87</rating>
<name>Akane Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1431" picture="25110.jpg">Kosuge Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22012" type="appears in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="3">5.05</rating>
<name>Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="63230" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋するビアトリス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loving Beatrice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi Suru Beatrice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63231" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アストラル・ファイア奪還作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Astral Fire Recovery Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Astral Fire Dakkan Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63232" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青春のかくれんぼ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adolescent Hide-and-Seek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seishun no Kakurenbo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63233" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私だけの王子様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Prince</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi dake no Ouji-sama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64107" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こころを重ねて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart to Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro o Kasanete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64108" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷の少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl of the Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koori no Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64109" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたに捧げる...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Devoting myself to you...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata ni Sasageru...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64110" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">湯煙パニック!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steam Panic!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukemuri Panic!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64111" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいちゃんといっしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Together with Oniichan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-chan to Issho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64112" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めざせ! ジョシコウセイ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Target! School Girl!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezase! Joshikousei!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64828" update="2006-10-31">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吉村護ろめろめ作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoshimura Mamoru Dovey-Lovey Operation!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoshimura Mamoru Romerome Sakusen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64829" update="2006-10-31">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビアトリス・クリスマス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beatrice Christmas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beatrice Christmas</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65369" update="2006-11-27">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔王あらわる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Devil appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maou Arawaru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65370" update="2006-11-27">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絢子さんの恋人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayako-san`s lover</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayako-san no Koibito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65371" update="2007-01-31">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界一えくせれんとな髪の毛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World`s most excellent Hair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekaiichi Excellent na Kaminoke</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67094" update="2007-01-31">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">参上, 暴れ総理!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter Rioting President!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanjou, Abare Souri!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67095" update="2007-01-31">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">南の島の注意報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Storm Warning for the Southern Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minami no Shima no Chuuihou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67096" update="2007-01-31">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の中で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Middle of the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Naka de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67097" update="2007-01-31">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">火花散る散るバレンタイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sparks scattering on Valentine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hibana Chiruchiru Valentine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67098" update="2007-01-31">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビアトリス消失!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beatrice disappears!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beatrice Shoushitsu!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67099" update="2007-01-31">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠くへ行っちゃ, やだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I don`t want you to go far away</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tooku e Iccha, Ya Da</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67100" update="2007-01-31">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">原初への帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return to the Origin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gensho e no Kikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67101" update="2007-01-31">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">無敵な二人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Invincible Pair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Muteki na Futari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67102" update="2007-01-31">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">護くんに女神の祝福を!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Goddess` Blessing to Mamoru-kun!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamoru-kun ni Megami no Shukufuku o!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68081" update="2007-03-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122692" update="2010-09-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122693" update="2010-09-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146085" update="2012-12-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">EP 24 Special Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
