<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4530" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-01-01</startdate>
<enddate>2007-01-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Strike Witches</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Штурмовые ведьмы</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">机械化少女</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ストライクウィッチーズ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5970" type="Parent Story">Strike Witches (2008)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9227" approval="31" total="48">Girls und Panzer</anime>
<anime id="10161" approval="5" total="7">Kantai Collection: KanColle</anime>
<anime id="14156" approval="0" total="3">Watashi ni Tenshi ga Maiorita!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="461772">Fan service is really great in this one. Nice settings. Character types for everyone. I really enjoyed this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="556547">cute girls, fan service, ok story, nice settings. 
Enjoy.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://s-witch.cute.or.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
</creators>
<description>* Concept OVA for what became the http://anidb.net/a5970 [Strike Witches (2008)] TV series.
A faceless alien invasion brings mankind to it knees, since conventional weaponry is ineffective. In order to take arms against them, humanity develops a new anti-Neuroi weapon called the Striker Unit. These devices are piloted by young female magic-wielders, commonly known as the Strike Witches.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1177">2.90</permanent>
<temporary count="1192">5.82</temporary>
<review count="1">2.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10936.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6653</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1862</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3794</identifier>
<identifier>tlkzkd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://s-witch.cute.or.jp</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Strike_Witches</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ストライクウィッチーズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10410</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3131</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1994" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-25">
<name>flying</name>
<description>This character has wings, natural or artificial, which enable the character to take flight. Or is in command of some form of levitation (e.g. a witch using a broom to fly).
Not to be confused with "flying planes" or "flying helicopters".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2968" parentid="4831" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-05">
<name>faceless alien invasion</name>
<description>Uncommunicative, faceless aliens suddenly invade Earth from outer space or a parallel world thus causing a war with humans.
If the humans are lucky, the invasion may go off without a war that would cause untold destruction and death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4115" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-08-03">
<name>mecha musume</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4606" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>slide show animation</name>
<description>The entire anime or parts of it show sequences of still images. Sometimes used in low budged animations for action scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="98" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="142">7.61</rating>
<name>Francesca Lucchini</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joining the 501st from the Duchy of Romagna, Francesca is the youngest soldier of the unit at a mere twelve years. Her rank is that of a Warrant officer and her unit affiliation was with Romania`s Regia Aeronautica 4th Air Unit. Francesca is often childish and self-indulgent, shirking training and other duties in order to have fun around the base or nap. However, in battle she displays a true talent and passion for flying. Also displayed as having the ears and tail of a black leopard. Her best friend is Shirley, as the two are often seen together.</description>
<picture>130734.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-03">
<rating votes="112">8.04</rating>
<name>Charlotte E. Yeager</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sixteen year old girl hailing from the United States of Liberion with the rank of Flight Lieutenant. Magnanimous in character, tall and buxom in appearance, Charlotte ("Shirley" to her friends) is a thrill-seeker who is fascinated by speed. Like a speedy hare, she gains the ears and tail of a rabbit when equipped with her Striker.</description>
<picture>65913.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="104" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-03">
<rating votes="132">6.08</rating>
<name>Perrine-H. Clostermann</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Perrine is a wealthy and proper fifteen year old Gallian girl who looks down on some of the less-refined habits of her peers. The emotional scars left by the Neuroi`s conquest of her homeland cause her numerous problems. She often refuses to work as part of a team, and develops a dislike for the upstart newcomer Yoshika due to her attachment to Mio, which eventually develops into full-blown jealousy. When wearing her Striker Unit, she gains the dark ears and tail of a Chartreux. Perrine holds the rank of Flying Officer and her original unit was the Armée de l`Air 802nd Flying Corps.</description>
<picture>65912.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-13">
<rating votes="101">6.04</rating>
<name>Lynette Bishop</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fifteen years old, Lynette is the only Witch in the 501st who is native to the Britannia Federation. The middle child of eight siblings, Lynette developed very domestic and practical habits from helping to take care of them. Similarly domestic is the Scottish Fold, from which her Striker-equipped animal features are based. Plagued by occasional clumsiness and sometimes overlooked, she nevertheless strives to do her best. After she meets Yoshika, the two eventually become best friends. Holds the rank of Sergeant and her affiliation is the Royal Air Force 610th Fighter Squadron.</description>
<picture>130692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="106">6.63</rating>
<name>Sakamoto Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The first Strike Witch and sub-commander of the unit, with the commissioned rank of Squadron Leader and official rank of Major. Mio is also the oldest witch at nineteen (later, twenty) years old and, like Yoshika, comes from Fuso. She is seemingly the toughest and most mature of the Witches, being an experienced veteran of the early fighting against the Neuroi. She knew Yoshika`s father while he was first designing the Striker Unit and was the first person to pilot one. Her usual task is to train new recruits, and in this role she becomes a very strict disciplinarian, appropriately gaining the ears and tail of a Doberman when equipped with her Striker. Otherwise she is quite friendly, if a little too forward at times, with a very distinct laugh. Under Mio`s eyepatch is a magic eye that grants her increased visual prowess and the ability to spot Neuroi cores when used.</description>
<picture>130735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="114" type="main character in" update="2013-01-13">
<rating votes="146">5.51</rating>
<name>Miyafuji Yoshika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character of the series, age fourteen and hailing from the Fuso Empire. A typical young girl who comes from a family of clinicians who use their magic powers to heal people. Yoshika gains the features of a mame-shiba when using said power. Her father designed the Striker Units the Strike Witches use to fight. However, because her father died in the war she is vehemently against fighting when Mio Sakamoto appears to recruit her. Only after entering combat for the first time, helping to defend the Fuso fleet heading to Britannia from a Neuroi attack, does she decide to join the 501st. Now she holds the rank of Sergeant.</description>
<picture>130695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="123" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="116">6.50</rating>
<name>Minna-Dietlinde Wilcke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The ranking officer of the 501st Joint Fighter Wing at eighteen years old, Minna has a sisterly air that shows her concern for those under her command. Whether in or out of battle, her first priority is the safety of her subordinates. Her more gentle demeanor means that she often acts as the "good cop" to Mio`s "bad cop" when it comes to discipline. She also has a talent for singing, wanting to become a professional before she joined the war effort. However, she gave up that dream when her lover was killed in battle. Because of this, she is afraid of losing anybody else, which leads her to eventually give an order that prohibits the male workers on the base from having unauthorized contact with the witches. Alluding to her namesake, Minna gains wolf features when equipped for combat. She has the power of clairvoyance used to analyze situations such as enemy muster, hidden spies and identify targets.</description>
<picture>130693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="149" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-03">
<rating votes="107">7.37</rating>
<name>Gertrud Barkhorn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eighteen year old Witch from Karlsland; a Flight Lieutenant formerly of the Luftwaffe JG 52. Quiet, efficient, and private, Gertrud (known as "Trude" to her friends) tends to support her comrades from the shadows. Her naturally calm attitude grants her great battlefield stamina, allowing her to rack up an impressive shot-down tally. A long-time acquaintance of Minna and Erica, she is often seen supporting the former in her leadership tasks and chastising the latter for her sloppiness. She has a younger sister named Chris who was badly injured during the invasion of her country and vaguely resembles Yoshika. Her magical power grants her the most physical strength of all the Witches to the extent where she can lift a steel girder many times her size. In flight she gains the features of a German Wirehaired Pointer.</description>
<picture>65911.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="155" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="114">7.61</rating>
<name>Erica Hartmann</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karlsland`s sixteen year old "ultra ace" of the Luftwaffe JG 52 with more than 200 confirmed victories and the rank of Flying Officer. While extremely efficient and strategic in battle, Erica is surprisingly sloppy with her belongings and often neglects cleaning tasks. The type of person who is only serious when the situation calls for it. Her special technique is an offensive barrel roll named Sturm. With her Striker Unit equipped, Erica gains Dachshund features.</description>
<picture>130732.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="156" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="197">7.91</rating>
<name>Eila Ilmatar Juutilainen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eila Ilmatar Juutilainen is the fifteen year old top ace of the Suomus Air Force 24th Unit with the rank of Pilot Officer (although the three roses on her collar would indicate the rank of captain). Eila`s hobby is fortune-telling with tarot cards, although the accuracy of her predictions is questionable at best. In battle however, she literally has the magical power of seeing into the future, allowing her to evade incoming attacks with ease. Somewhat mischievous, like the black fox whose features she gains in flight. She is particularly affectionate towards Sanya and will become cold to anyone who comes too close to her, this usually being Yoshika. In combat her weapons of choice are the MG42 and Suomi M1931 submachine gun. Eila`s Striker Unit is based on the Messerschmitt Bf-109G-2 and she is based on the ace Eino Ilmari Juutilainen.</description>
<picture>193261.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="159" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="217">8.40</rating>
<name>Sanya V. Litvyak</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanya V. Litvyak is the single Witch out of the Orussia Empire at thirteen years old. Preferring to stay indoors during the day, Sanya has been described as "nocturnal." At times she is literally asleep on her feet, counting on Eila to move her around. Despite this somewhat limiting her contact with the other members of the 501st, her low profile makes her ideal for night missions and sneak attacks. Also helping her in this duty is her magical specialty, the ability to read signals such as radio waves that are invisible to the naked eye, giving her a highly advanced spatial awareness. Gains the ears and tail of a black cat with her Striker Unit equipped. Sanya`s rank is Flying Officer and her original unit affiliation is the Orussia Imperial Army 586th Fighter Regiment. Her Striker Unit design is based on the MiG60 (a fictional warbird combining features of the MiG-1, MiG-3, and Yakovlev Yak-1) and her pilot archetype is http://anidb.net/ch85347 [Lydia Litvyak].</description>
<picture>130691.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19414" type="appears in" update="2010-07-08">
<rating votes="3">5.25</rating>
<name>Rengougun Dai 501 Tougou Sentou Koukuu Dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>50828.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="64819" update="2006-10-30">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66774" update="2008-09-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66816" update="2008-09-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<rating votes="5">2.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PREMIUM1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
