<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4557" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2007-06-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Major (2007)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">メジャー 第3シリーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Мейжър С3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Major 3rd Season</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Major S3</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">棒球大联盟 第3季</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">major3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">メジャー (2007)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">메이저 3기</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5316" type="Sequel">Major (2008)</anime>
<anime id="3423" type="Prequel">Major (2005)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="152878">You gotta see this anime it rox ^^</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www3.nhk.or.jp/anime/major/</url>
<creators>
<name id="734" type="Work">Shogakukan Productions</name>
<name id="985" type="Animation Work">Studio Hibari</name>
<name id="1050" type="Work">NHK</name>
<name id="1649" type="Character Design">Oonuki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="2164" type="Character Design">Usami Kouichi</name>
<name id="2847" type="Series Composition">Tsuchiya Michihiro</name>
<name id="654" type="Direction">Kasai Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="7764" type="Direction">Fukushima Toshinori</name>
<name id="6883" type="Music">Asakura Noriyuki</name>
<name id="4412" type="Original Work">Mitsuda Takuya</name>
</creators>
<description>After leaving Kaido, Gorou wanted to go back to Mifune in order to challenge the Kaido players, but once he got there he saw that the team has been improving greatly on their own efforts. Not wanting to disorganize the team he dropped his plan on enrolling back to Mifune and turned his eyes to Edawara High, but his enrollment was rejected due to interference of Kaido Asst. Director Egashira.
Gorou finally avoided Egashira`s interference and went to Seishuu High which did not have a baseball club yet. Gorou decided that he himself will put up a team consisting of the very few boys of Seishuu High (previously an all-girls high school). Will Gorou succeed in establishing a team? If so, will the team be able to make it to Koshien? Will they face Kaido?
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1873">8.19</permanent>
<temporary count="1902">8.37</temporary>
<review count="1">7.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221786.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4115</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1842</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3825</identifier>
<identifier>urhiok</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www6.nhk.or.jp/anime/program/detail.html?i=major3</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>メジャー_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>965</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326640</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6996</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-08">
<name>ambitious</name>
<description>having a strong desire for success or achievement; wanting power, money, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2384" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-22">
<name>prodigy</name>
<description>Character is very good at everything he/she does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2067" type="main character in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="242">8.03</rating>
<name>Shigeno Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The story`s main character, Goro Honda is a young talented baseball player. His love of the game stems from his father who played for the Yokohama Marine Stars. Wanting nothing more than to follow in his father`s footsteps, he strives to become a professional ball player. Thriving on the challenge of the mound, he puts everything into the competition. He makes friends easily, as people are drawn to his personality and his excitement of the game. After Momoko and Hideki married his name was changed to Goro Shigeno. He initially pitched right handed, but blew out his shoulder in senior little league. In junior high school and high school, he pitches left, but continues to bat right. While he never made it to Koshien, his excellent match against the Kaido High School earned him the attention of many professional baseball team`s scouts. However, he went to America and joined a Triple A team, the Memphis Bats. During the Baseball World Cup, he replaced the injured pitcher Noro, and played as an excellent closer. He used to only use the pitch gyroballs ("rising fastball"), though beginning with the Baseball World Cup, he has successfully added gyrofork ("forkball") to his repertoire.</description>
<picture>16889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2072" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-09">
<rating votes="99">8.32</rating>
<name>Shigeno Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2074" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-09">
<rating votes="44">2.91</rating>
<name>Satou Toshiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2077" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-10">
<rating votes="34">6.46</rating>
<name>Shigeno Hideki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2380.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="144" picture="16904.jpg">Sakuya Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2107" type="appears in" update="2009-01-10">
<rating votes="49">9.07</rating>
<name>Joe Gibson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="156" picture="227713.jpg">Ochiai Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2110" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-10">
<rating votes="6">5.25</rating>
<name>Komori Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13070" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-17">
<rating votes="66">7.70</rating>
<name>Shimizu Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaoru is in Goro`s class in elementary school and eventually begins to play little league baseball on the Mifune Dolphins Little League after an argument with Goro where she sees his passion for the game. In Junior High School she switches to softball and becomes captain of the Mifune East Junior High team. Initially she plans to follow Goro, whom she has a crush on, to Kaido High School. However, she changes her mind after she discovers Kaido does not have a softball team and after Goro tells her to follow her love of softball. After high school, she attended Kyowa University. During the winter break of her freshman year, Goro confesses to Kaoru and they are going out.</description>
<picture>38892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="137" picture="214428.jpg">Sasamoto Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13071" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="17">3.25</rating>
<name>Shimizu Taiga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brother to Kaoru Shimizu. First seen back in Season 1 where he asked his sister if baseball was fun? Returned again in Season 3 as a new member of Seishuu Baseball Team where he played as a shortstop. With his excellent skill and speed, he helped Goro in challenging Kaido. Besides that, he also helped to take over the mound when Goro was injured by Egashira during their practice game with Kaido. Later on he became the captain of the Seishuu Baseball Team to challenge Kaido once again with his new teammates.</description>
<picture>153313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13072" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="4">5.25</rating>
<name>Shigeno Shingo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153308.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10500" picture="38508.jpg">Iwamura Kotomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13076" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="3">5.25</rating>
<name>Yamada Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teacher and baseball coach at Seishuu High School.</description>
<picture>153316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13078" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="3">5.25</rating>
<name>Fujii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the first to agree on entering in the baseball club, wich Goro created in Seishuu, after being beaten in a one on one toss and hit game. He always makes mistakes during the games and he is always fired up when it`s his time to hit, but always misses.</description>
<picture>153315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13079" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="3">5.25</rating>
<name>Tashiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13087" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-08">
<rating votes="9">7.99</rating>
<name>Mayumura Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced in season 2, he is initially asked to teach Goro a lesson by Kaido`s recruiter for rejecting Kaido during a middle school game between Kaido Unified, and East Mifune. This beating makes him the instant rival of Goro, even though he admires him for his confidence and straight forward attitude. His personality is very direct and to the point, often times coming off as cold. He appears to be in complete control of his emotions at all times, including when facing established and more experienced players. His pre-game ritual of sitting in a bathroom stall while listening to music is seen by others as getting him in the right frame of mind to pitch, but in actuality he does it because he is anxious and helps him focus his anxiety. His goals are to achieve all possible individual achievements in Japanese Baseball before moving onto the Majors.</description>
<picture>38915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14035" type="appears in" update="2010-01-12">
<rating votes="17">7.44</rating>
<name>Kawase Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41345.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9364" picture="34580.jpg">Endou Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14037" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="3">3.43</rating>
<name>Kashimoto Shuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="66435" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゼロからのスタート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Start from Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zero kara no Start</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66436" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい仲間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Nakama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66437" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父から子へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Father to Son</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi Kara Ko e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66438" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無謀な賭け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reckless Gamble</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mubou na Kake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67338" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺たちのグラウンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Ground</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore-tachi no Ground</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67339" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの選択</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Each One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Sentaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67340" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突然の訪問者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Abrupt Visitor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsuzen no Houmonsha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67341" update="2007-05-07">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">江頭の陰謀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Egashira Conspiracy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Egashira no Inbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67342" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エース不在</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ace Absence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ace Fuzai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67754" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝染する闘志</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Contagious Fighting Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densensuru Toushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67755" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">手負いのエース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wounded Ace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teoi no Ace</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67756" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三船戦開始!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Against Mifune, Start!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mifune-sen Kaishi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71855" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">意地vs意地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Willpower vs. Willpower</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iji vs Iji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71856" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白熱! 三船戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Climax! Mifune Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakunetsu! Mifunesen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72051" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フルスイング!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Full Swing!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Full Swing!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72052" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">意外な再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unexpected Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Igai na Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72490" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">投手戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pitching Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toushusen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72491" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラストスパート!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Spurt!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last Spurt!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72492" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">王者への挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge to the Top</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ouja e no Chousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72493" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">隙なし! マニュアル野球</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Openings! Manual Baseball</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sukinashi! Manual Yakyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72494" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寿也の秘策</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toshiya`s Secret Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toshiya no Hisaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73491" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真っ向勝負</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Head to Head Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makkou Shoubu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73492" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギリギリの戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Close Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giri Giri no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="74989" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">策謀の結末</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of the Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakubou no Ketsumatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="74990" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傷だらけのエース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ace Full of Injuries</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizudarake no Ace</title>
</episode>
<episode id="74991" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の舞台へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Towards Your Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Butai e</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
