<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4568" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-02-11</startdate>
<enddate>2007-03-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Byousoku 5 Centimeter</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">5 cm per second</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Byosoku 5 centimeter ~a chain of short stories about their distance~</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">5 Zentimeter pro Sekunde</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">5 cm al secondo</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">5 centimetri al secondo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Пять сантиметров в секунду</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">5 cm na sekundę</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="synonym">5 centimeter i sekunden</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">5 سنتيمترات في الثانية</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="synonym">5 εκατοστά το δευτερόλεπτο</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">5 ס"מ בשנייה</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">5 centimetrai per sekundę</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Saniyede 5 Santimetre</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">5 centimetri pe secundă</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">5 Cm Một Giây</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">5 centimét một giây</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">5 сантиметра в секунда</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Пет сантиметра на секунда</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Byousoku Go Senchimeetoru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Byosoku Go Senchimetoru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Byousoku Go Senchime-toru</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">5 сантиметрів за секунду</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">5 сантиметрів на секунду</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">5cm/s</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">5cm per Second</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">5cm</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">秒速5センチメートル</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">5 Centimeters per Second</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">5 Centimeters per second</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">5 Centimètres par seconde</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">5 cm per second</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">5 centímetros por segundo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">5 сантиметров в секунду</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">초속 5 센티미터</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">5 centymetrów na sekundę</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">5 centimetrů za sekundu</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="official">5 centimeter per seconde</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Másodpercenként 5 centiméter</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">5 sentimeetrit sekundis</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">秒速5厘米</title>
<title xml:lang="mn" type="official">Секундэд таван сантиметр</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="469" approval="153" total="162">Kumo no Mukou, Yakusoku no Basho</anime>
<anime id="104" approval="143" total="150">Hoshi no Koe</anime>
<anime id="9589" approval="72" total="81">Kotonoha no Niwa</anime>
<anime id="7348" approval="24" total="28">Meguriau Sekai</anime>
<anime id="13846" approval="11" total="16">Shikioriori</anime>
<anime id="4151" approval="3" total="12">Toki o Kakeru Shoujo</anime>
<anime id="8181" approval="2" total="15">Ano Hi Mita Hana no Namae o Bokutachi wa Mada Shiranai.</anime>
<anime id="11835" approval="2" total="6">Tabi Machi Late Show: Awaiting My Journey</anime>
<anime id="13038" approval="1" total="7">Itsudatte Bokura no Koi wa 10 Centi Datta.</anime>
<anime id="12605" approval="1" total="6">Uchiage Hanabi, Shita kara Miru ka? Yoko kara Miru ka?</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="65">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="510613">It`s anime is such a Heart-Breaking for me :(, every time i think about it, it makes me wanna cry</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="52807">for thouse who defenetly love beyond the clouds this one is not better then beyond the clouds on my opinion but its perfect!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="258331">beautiful sad things.&lt;br /&gt;watch in the night, with a girlfriend.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="108726">Real gr8, also really heartaching. If you liked Voices of  Distant Past, this would qualify as the genre... &lt;br /&gt;I see this theme appear more and more in anime, and I get the feeling Ill have to get to live in Japan very soon before my youth ends and I will not be able to live these feelings ever again. Am I turning emo? lol :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="266058">Smooth work, lots of eye candies, good storyline with a nice theme song. If it doesn`t touch your heart (even just a tiny bit), then you`re not human.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="257594">One of the great anime and best of Makoto  Shinkai I`ve ever seen! Very touchy!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="270712">Awesome Movie</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="284604">It a slice of life from the perspective individuals from different time periods of their life. It encompasses their worries dreams and wishes, while the story continues marching onward.

Very interesting and feels quite a bit like real life in that sometimes interactions one goes through may not end in the one would wish.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="5807">Well worth spending some time on.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="296475">Very touching, a really beautiful story. Brought back very sweet memories, and a sense of longing for things that never came to be...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="139195">For romantics...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="323986">Technically very good!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="299448">very nice story</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="516692">first anime from makoto shinkai and immediately make me be his fan, really great artwork (like painting), recommended to watch this</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="484425">The animation in 5 Centimeters Per Second was breathtakingly beautiful.  The level of detail that went into every frame was astounding.  The story was sweet and moving.

My one disappointment was that the last vignette didn`t work nearly as well as the first two.  I`m guessing the studio ran out of time or money, which lead to a decision to turn the third episode into a montage-music video.

I suppose one could argue that the last episode was demonstrating the "speed of life," or something like that, but the story in episode three left me wanting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="321649">A very moving, relate-able story with superb animation.  A must watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="97041">A visually stunning movie that tugs at your heartstrings.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="237158">Simply crystal-clear and detailed art in every aspect. Interconnected short stories. Touching.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="354280">Some of the most beautiful animation available, with a wonderfully bittersweet story.  An excellent choice.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="65644">I have yet to see such a tremendous work of art in Japanese animation. You MUST see the 1080P version, its nothing but pure art, the attention to details is exquisite, the story has to be one of the saddest but most beautiful you might come across, but its message and meaning is remarkable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You MUST see it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="481845">When I watched this movie, suddenly some lines of the song `So close` came to my mind.
`A life goes by. Romantic dreams must die. So I bid my goodbye and never knew...`
OMG! What am I saying?! I want to say that this is definitely a must see. xD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="408065">Absolutely must see ! 1080 recommended</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="232143">Graphical whoring with moody, slow-paced flow. If you wish to be stunned with beautiful scenery and enjoy the moment, this is a MUST SEE. (Other works of Makoto Shinkai also highly recommended.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best in 1080p, as it really is not just an upscale. Unlike most 1080p, 5cm/s not only sharpens line-art but also adds detail to small things (snow drop, starts, horizon, clouds, every small object).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="427215">Don`t miss your chance- this is excellent.  Keep in mind however, it is sad.  If possible, watch in 1080p.  The animation is breathtaking, and especially amazing considering how short the number of Key Animators and Artists there are.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="206351">Sad like Hoshi no Koe was, but it is beautifully and flawlessly animated. Pretty much every shot looks like it could be a wallpaper. That`s the level of detail that went into this. An absolute masterpiece concerning distances, heartbreak, and regrets.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="198490">... very impressive creation, for those in love in special</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="114582">Must see. Animes like Byousoku 5 Senchimeetoru are more focused on the relationships between characters, their feelings and emotions, you must go into their lives, if not, you`re going to think something`s missing. The animation and visual art used on this help you very well with that matter.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="488006">Very sad with a meaningful message. I had to rewatch it to fully understand it, and suddenly felt a little better. 
A must see for anyone.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="122200">Simply beautiful in HD and a masterpiece. Do not forget the tissues when sitting down to watch this...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="221060">a lovely piece of work, animation and story-wise.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="145292">nice animation! nice anime!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="536175">the best movie I`ve seen so far</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="556696">Definitely something worth watching.  It tells us that no matter how much we want something, there are always going to be hindrances along the way. But then, these hindrances would also show us how to move on; to let go but to never forget the people that had been important to us.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="281330">Very nice love story,and great visual.MUST SEE !! :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="571562">Beautiful movie. A must see for every romance/drama fan.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="814391">Very, very beautiful, but sad story.

Definitely must-see one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="399845">A movie that entails realism to it, a movie that has a full of depth for the allotted time it`s given. A movie where each person will get a different theme of the movie. Truly a movie a must see for both fans of romance or non-romance a like.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://5cm.yahoo.co.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="445" type="Work">Shinkai Makoto</name>
<name id="445" type="Original Work">Shinkai Makoto</name>
<name id="1810" type="Character Design">Nishimura Takayo</name>
<name id="445" type="Direction">Shinkai Makoto</name>
<name id="3546" type="Music">Tenmon</name>
<name id="10345" type="Work">CoMix Wave Films</name>
</creators>
<description>This is the story of two close friends, http://anidb.net/ch4062 [Toono Takaki] and http://anidb.net/ch4063 [Shinohara Akari], who became separated by space and time:
Part 1 — The Chosen Cherry Blossoms (26 min.): Because of family relocation, Shinohara Akari had to leave Tokyo after graduating from elementary school. The strong feelings between Takaki and Akari keep them in contact, but they worry that they may not meet again. Then, one day, Takaki learns that his family will move from Tokyo to an island in the far south of Japan, so he decides to use this last chance to visit Akari by train...
Part 2 — Cosmonaut (21 min.): Years have passed, and Takaki still writes emails meant for Akari, only to never send them to her. Meanwhile http://anidb.net/ch7782 [Sumita Kanae], his classmate, has feelings for Takaki, but she does not have the courage to confess her love to him...
Part 3 — 5 Centimetres per Second (16 min., mostly a music clip): Takaki is working as computer programmer now, occasionally remembering his former life — and love. And one day, at a railroad crossing, he suddenly passes by a woman who looks familiar to him...
— written by DD of Mikomi, edited</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9331">8.10</permanent>
<temporary count="9470">8.25</temporary>
<review count="15">8.93</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221335.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6696</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1689</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3821</identifier>
<identifier>fkfpzq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.cwfilms.jp/5cm/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5_Centimeters_Per_Second</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>秒速5センチメートル</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1924</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326527</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8685</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>초속_5센티미터</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>秒速5公分</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5-centimeters-per-second</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9904</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2402" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-09">
<name>archery</name>
<description>Archery is the art, practice, or skill of shooting arrows with the use of a bow, from Latin arcus. A person who participates in archery is typically known as an archer.
While archery has been historically used for hunting, both for food and later, in a use that survives to this day, also as a sport, through most of pre-gunpowder human history its main use was for combat; archers were extremely important in warfare, in open field and siege alike, due to their ability to massively kill enemy armies with literal rains of arrows and to set things aflame with burning arrowheads. Proper easy of burning arrowheads could destroy the morale of an invading infantry division or set the entire defending fortress on fire, while non-burning arrowheads could destroy a large portion of the enemy infantry before it could even enter melee combat. Such was the destruction ability of archers that horse archers were the backbone of the both the Hun and Mongol hordes; the former brought terror to and helped the eventual demise of the Roman Empire, while the latter conquered such a large portion of Eurasia that historians coined the term Pax Mongolica (paralleling the Pax Romana) to describe their empire that at its apex spanned from modern-day Poland to the Middle East to Southern China, Korea and the southern parts of Russia.
With the discovery of gunpowder and the invention of firearms, archery was quickly rendered obsolete in warfare. Early firearms were not good in comparison to good archers, with drawbacks such as a vastly inferior rate of fire and high susceptibility to wet weather; nevertheless, they had longer effective range and, most importantly, required almost no practice to use properly in comparison to the many years that it took to train an archer; indeed, a popular saying used to go that "to make a good archer, one must start with his grandfather". Nevertheless, in the Far East archery is to this day considered an important subject in the studies of martial arts, and some Japanese schools have archery dojos ran by archery clubs. Additionally, archery saw an 18th century reemergence as a recreational activity in the West, becoming relevant as an elite class sport, specially for hunting but also at non-living targets, and eventually also becoming an Olympic competition.</description>
<picurl>145640.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3804" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-04-08">
<name>beauty in simplicity</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3869" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>mono no aware</name>
<description>Literally "the pathos of things", also translated as "an empathy toward things," or "a sensitivity of ephemera"; a Japanese term used to describe the awareness of the transience of things and a gentle sadness (or wistfulness) at their passing.
Also frequently been translated as "the `ahh-ness` of things".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3974" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>star-crossed lovers</name>
<description>Two lovers — usually teenagers — destined to be kept apart no matter how hard they struggle to be together. It may be fate or just feuding families, or even something as mundane as a few hundred miles, but something will always be in their way. Often, the two can only be together in death. The phrase is astrological in origin, stemming from the belief that the positions of the stars ruled over people`s fates. To describe a relationship as "star-crossed" is to say that it is "thwarted by a malign star", or that the stars are working against the relationship. Shakespeare`s Romeo and Juliet is the most famous example of this archetype but it dates back at least as far as the ancient Greeks.
"From forth the fatal loins of these two foes, / a pair of star-cross`d lovers, take their life."
- Romeo and Juliet, prologue</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5213" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-04">
<name>the effects of time and distance on human relationships</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5409" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-22">
<name>longing</name>
<description>One or more characters yearn for some person or some place.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5561" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-08-16">
<name>lonely atmosphere</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4062" type="main character in" update="2012-01-21">
<rating votes="26">6.86</rating>
<name>Toono Takaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takaki is the central character of the film. Because of his parents` jobs, he is forced to move a lot. He and Akari become close friends, but begin to drift apart when Akari moves away and they end up attending different junior high schools. In the second arc, he is shown to be an apt kyuudou practitioner and a member of his school`s kyuudou club.</description>
<picture>20016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2077" picture="21427.jpg">Mizuhashi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4063" type="main character in" update="2012-01-21">
<rating votes="25">5.40</rating>
<name>Shinohara Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takaki`s best friend and supposed love interest in elementary school. Like Takaki, she and her family moves a lot. After elementary school, she moves to Iwafune. Apparently she suggests living with her aunt in Tokyo in order to stay with Takaki, but her parents disallow her from going on her own.</description>
<picture>20017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2079" picture="21440.jpg">Onoue Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7782" type="main character in" update="2012-01-21">
<rating votes="29">7.54</rating>
<name>Sumita Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate of Takaki in high school. She has been in love with Takaki since he began attending her junior high school, but cannot express her feelings to him. Kanae loves to surf and rides a scooter to school. Her older sister is a teacher at her high school.</description>
<picture>29048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="93" picture="142975.jpg">Hanamura Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100593" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-26">
<name>Mizuno Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="613" picture="155849.jpg">Mizuno Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="51955" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="9">8.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52019" update="2018-07-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2007-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="77">9.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜花抄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cherry Blossom</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Essence de fleurs de cerisier</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Отрывок о цветущей сакуре</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Opowieść o płatkach wiśni</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oukashou</title>
<summary>Upon graduating from elementary school, Takaki Tono and his close friend Akari Shinohara drifted apart. Akari moved to Tochigi Prefecture due to her parents` jobs, while Takaki attended a junior high in Tokyo. The two kept in contact by writing letters, but despite the special feelings that existed between them, the only thing that persisted was time. When Takaki became aware that his family would move to Kagoshima, he decided to go see Akari since they would be too far apart to visit each other after he moved. However, when the day came, a severe snowstorm delayed Takaki`s trip, and it would be hours before he reached Iwafune, where they promised to meet.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>732501</identifier>
<identifier>5-centimeters-per-second</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="65249" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67613" update="2014-03-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="48">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コスモナウト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cosmonaut</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cosmonaute</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Космонавт</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Kosmonauta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cosmonaut</title>
<summary>Takaki is now in the third year of senior high in Tanegashima, where the Tanegashima Space Center is located. Kanae Sumita, a classmate of Takaki, has special feelings for Takaki, but she does not have the courage to express her love to him. She later observes that Takaki is always staring off into the distance, as if searching for something far far away.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>732501</identifier>
<identifier>5-centimeters-per-second</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="67614" update="2018-07-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="46">6.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秒速5センチメートル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">5 Centimeters per Second</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">5 centimètres par seconde</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Пять сантиметров в секунду</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">5 centymetrów na sekundę</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Byousoku 5 Centimeter</title>
<summary>It is now 2008, and all three characters have gone their separate ways. Takaki is now a computer programmer in Tokyo, and Akari is preparing to get married. One day, Takaki goes out and sees the face of a familiar-looking woman at a railroad-crossing. Puzzled by the encounter, he tries to look back, but a train comes and cuts off his view.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>732501</identifier>
<identifier>5-centimeters-per-second</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75373" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="12">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">One More Time, One More Chance</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Jeszcze raz, kolejna szansa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81124" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Storyboard of "The Chosen Cherry Blossoms"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81125" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Storyboard of "Cosmonaut"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81126" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Storyboard of "5 Centimeters per Second"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81127" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Shinkai Makoto interview</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wywiad z Makoto Shinkaiem</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81128" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Mizuhashi Kenji interview</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wywiad z Kenjim Mizuhashim</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81129" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoshimi Kondo interview</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wywiad z Kondō Yoshimi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81130" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Satomi Hanamura interview</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wywiad z Satomi Hanamurą</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81131" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayaka Onoue interview</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wywiad z Ayaką Onue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81132" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Photo Montage (Making Of)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
