<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4575" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>27</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-01</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Heaven-Piercing Gurren Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Гуррен-Лаганн: на прорыв!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Гуррен Лаганн - прочь из этого мира</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="synonym">Pokořitel nebes Gurren-Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gurren-Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Ґуррен Лаґанн</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">天元突破 红莲之眼</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ttgl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gurren</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gurren Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ttgl tv</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="short">天元</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">天元突破 グレンラガン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gurren Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Gurren Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Gurren Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Sfondamento dei Cieli Gurren Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Гуррен-Лаганн</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">천원돌파 그렌라간</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">อภินิหารหุ่นทะลวงสวรรค์ กุเร็นลากันน์</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Небесен пробив Гурен Лаган</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Gurren Lagann</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">天元突破 红莲螺岩</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Gurren Lagann</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8918" type="Side Story">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann: Ore no Gurren wa Pikka Pika!!</anime>
<anime id="5783" type="Summary">Gekijouban Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann: Gurren Hen</anime>
<anime id="6325" type="Summary">Gekijouban Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann: Lagann Hen</anime>
<anime id="6082" type="Other">Gurren Lagann Parallel Works</anime>
<anime id="6609" type="Other">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann Kirameki Youko Box: Pieces of Sweet Stars</anime>
<anime id="7485" type="Other">Gurren Lagann Parallel Works 2</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9875" approval="252" total="266">Kill la Kill</anime>
<anime id="2120" approval="117" total="124">Top o Nerae 2! Diebuster</anime>
<anime id="185" approval="56" total="85">Top o Nerae! Gunbuster</anime>
<anime id="4527" approval="30" total="40">Top o Nerae 2! Gekijouban</anime>
<anime id="117" approval="22" total="52">Furi Kuri</anime>
<anime id="4526" approval="21" total="26">Top o Nerae! Gunbuster (2006)</anime>
<anime id="1170" approval="20" total="44">Dead Leaves</anime>
<anime id="6467" approval="16" total="33">Needless</anime>
<anime id="1838" approval="13" total="18">Shin Getter Robo</anime>
<anime id="6255" approval="7" total="18">Basquash!</anime>
<anime id="177" approval="5" total="20">VanDread</anime>
<anime id="7591" approval="5" total="20">Star Driver: Kagayaki no Takuto</anime>
<anime id="13259" approval="5" total="16">Darling in the Franxx</anime>
<anime id="10784" approval="4" total="10">The Rolling Girls</anime>
<anime id="9556" approval="3" total="26">Suisei no Gargantia</anime>
<anime id="4861" approval="3" total="13">Bokura no</anime>
<anime id="2826" approval="2" total="14">Koukyoushihen: Eureka Seven</anime>
<anime id="11164" approval="2" total="12">Drifters</anime>
<anime id="640" approval="2" total="9">Scrapped Princess</anime>
<anime id="13261" approval="2" total="5">Promare</anime>
<anime id="11123" approval="1" total="14">One Punch Man</anime>
<anime id="70" approval="1" total="10">Abenobashi Mahou Shoutengai</anime>
<anime id="10243" approval="1" total="6">Nobunaga the Fool</anime>
<anime id="9992" approval="1" total="5">Kyousougiga (2013)</anime>
<anime id="10897" approval="1" total="4">Yoru no Yatterman</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="165">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="540649">BEYOND EPICNESS!!! MUST WATCH!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="258936">funny, lots of action, some emotional parts and a cool plot ....love it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="6082">Like the best mecha anime i`v seen.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="72649">So awesome it HURTS</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="357617">This is a good fun cartoon!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="179096">EPIC</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="246107">something missing from 2000`s anime show? go watch this, and feel 70 and 80`s badass show</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372933">Great!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="307364">Very action oriented, but with a great sci-fi story! Galaxy-sized robots are never to be missed!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="112300">This is one hell of an anime, very good story line and one of the best coming of age animes i ever watched, totally recomended...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="246165">Every episode is getting better and better</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="18468">This is hands down the best anime you will EVER see. Epic is the only word needed to describe it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="341051">I wouldnt call it an epic but it is for sure something to watch. Only if kamina featured in all the episodes it would have been amazing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="145123">Just too Much!!!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="334612">Not over embellishing, fav anime of my life thus far.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="289891">This anime will make you laugh from the beginning to an end! If you are in a bad mood, or feeling down watch this anime. It so wacky it will crack you up! Highly recommended!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="159558">Great story, great character, definitely a must watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="34249">PIERCE THE HEAVENS WITH YOUR DRILL!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="254176">You have to watch this .</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="139657">best in year 2007</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="337547">pure awesome</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="547345">Weel, it IS overhyped... my experiece suffered a bit from that, but it is still quite good.
It`s funny, light hearted, engaging and well-paced.
Has some of the most awesome fights in all the mecha animes I`ve ever seen. EVER
Dominated by the Rule of Awesome from start to finish (the flashier, the better), though sometimes, pushes it a bit too far...
Despite that, it`s definently a must-see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="261686">It takes every possible mecha/shounen cliche and creates something completely original.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="181048">PURE AWESOME!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="281802">BEST ANIME EVER!!!!!!!!!! :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="346533">Very good anime, Character development and emotions portrayed though the anime are absolutely stunning.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="175892">Great anime, definitly deserves the score it has received. Great story, lot`s of action and sometimes a bit of humour</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="297941">This anime is going so deliciously over the top, and they`re doing a great job of that. Best mecha anime I`ve ever seen so far.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="510860">Good story that`s unique and not like other mecha anime shows. Imho a little overrated but definetly a show that didn`t disappoint. Felt the progression of the story &amp; characters flowed very nicely and very emotional at times.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="221392">excelent anime! 1000/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="219874">AWESOME AWESOME</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="290278">Awesome series, a must watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="283829">Trigun, FullMetalPanic, VanDread and friggin Powerrangers all blended into a gripping story</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="67247">This is a prime example of exactly how awesome and epic (EPIC!!!) anime can be. Just watch it and be amazed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="584375">Really good anime, I enjoyed the series - I`d recommend this to anyone who wants to watch an entertaining and joyful seires</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="1294">GAINAX, awesome animation, drills, GAR, EPIC, the whole lineup known from FLCL, Gunbuster/Diebuster, Dead Leaves.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="185992">There needs to be a word beyond epic because thats what this is. This series has ridiculously intense over the top fighting paired with a colorful cast. Its a grandiose tale of overcoming the odds no matter how impossible it may seem. It has amazing comicbook-like sequences thanks to its unique art direction and presentation. The music orchestrated for this show magnificently captures the soul and essence of what is Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann. You might want to strap yourself down because youll be blown away in what this series will deliver.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="296701">Epitome of how manly and epic an anime can be.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="610626">Epic!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="319919">Epic is a little word for this Masterpiece</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="599448">Try to imagine the most action-based mecha anime you have ever seen... Now add 3 tons of testosterone and throw away the filter for "wtf" factor. That`s a clue to what this is. Not to be missed!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="387097">I skipped it more than once &amp; then watched it unwillingly.

I WAS STUPID, this show is the embodiment of epicness.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="167701">This is a Masterpiece.
Just watch it.
Evangelion
Cowboy Beebop
Ghost in the shell
Trigun
Those are masterpieces
Gurren Lagan is one of them.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="276125">What can I say that hasn`t already been said? Start to finish, TTGL oozes amazing at a grandiose scale, and goes from being super-serious to totally nonsensical. One of my top ten all-time must-watch series, it`s truly hard to hate it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="184076">Only one word: masterpiece!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="622725">This one is a nice anime, but sadly i dont like exaggeration, and this one is exagerated, but overall is a nice watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="209879">Willpower, the anime. This could have been one of the best anime I have ever seen if it weren`t for the last third of the show. The first 15 episodes are just pure action that is so overblown, nonsensical and whacky that it`s easy to enjoy its pure fun and not to question anything.

Unfortunately the following episodes are too slow-paced and too drawn-out, making them predictable and coming around as too serious. Luckily the last few episodes get back into the groove.

Nevertheless a really great show that anyone watching anime should have seen.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="42439">epic!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="153611">Great anime and lives up to the high expectations I gave it. Good Music, good detail, great story</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="228325">Kolla på den här, detta är utan tvivel den bästa Super Robot serien som nånsin gjorts.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="204204">Awesome Anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="60703">The anime series is just full of awesome!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="276267">A truely amazing anime, certainly one  of my favorites, i wish it never ended...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="158248">watch it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="210694">One of those very few anime that leaves an unfadable footprint in the history of animation. It is absolutely a must-see, even if you don`t like mecha, or the visual style in wich it was conceived. You will not regret it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="57909">Awesome storyline/ character development / and lots of action  best ending everrrrr</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="283337">Watch it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="170338">see type!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="273014">This is an Instant Classic, so good in many ways.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="347296">Epic</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="244394">One word  : Awesome</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="329142">a masterpiece, must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="212664">Definitely one of the best out there! I loved the whole story line!

Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann, Nuff` said!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="112286">Truly manly tears. Just epic.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="257215">A mixture of everything action, story, sci fi, tragedy and comedy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="237158">ABSOLUTELY best story expanse I have ever seen. Realistic guide for mastering universe :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="399240">it`s gurren lagann - what do you want?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="77085">My favorite anime EVER!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="391443">droolworthy animation and masterful storytelling spiraled together, taking "epic" to the extreme on every level. people will be talking about it for decades.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="396363">One of the best anime ever made.&lt;br /&gt;DO THE IMPOSSIBLE&lt;br /&gt;SEE THE INVISIBLE&lt;br /&gt;ROW! ROW!&lt;br /&gt;FIGHT THE POWER!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="275599">This series and Code Geass are the best when it comes to epicnessss! Purely overwhelming apocalyptic epic scenarios + Insanely awesome epic comedy = 200% epicness. 200% epicness + Biggest Breathtaking, most Humongous Galaxy size Mecha of pure (epiccingness) = Epicness Infinity</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="142767">Must See almost the best series in 2007</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="231997">All anime elements in one box. Best of all :). Epic, nice characters, inteligent story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="115911">A must SEE anime!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="291829">Great action, amazing character development and a fitting story ... I don`t know what more to tell you to make you watch it xD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="31431">Freakin` awesome anime. Starts out weird, but keep watching and it will be your new favorite.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="117857">This is one of the manliest manly Animes ever. If you are a man you are required to watch this!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="298465">Must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="498834">This is like a Michael Bay movie on crack the fight scenes are over the top it has a great story, awesome characters, great animation, Amazing OST and a lot of symbolism. Even if you don`t like mecha anime at least try it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="207137">This anime is more than epic, so watch it, even if you don`t like the mecha genre!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="387032">can`t be described in words , you must definitly watch it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="468351">The most manly anime ever. watch it as a right of passage. perhaps not one for the furries though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="444838">Right from the first ten minutes you know you`ll be for one hell of a ride. The storyline is extemely dynamic, covers many different genres in its path, from action/adventure to shounen/combat to sci-fi/space opera. Its nonsense and surrealism actually never goes stale thanks to the continued genre shifts.
Just because of this from now on I will trust Gainax.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="473733">People are talking this as overrated.... But who the heck cares about them.
I seek more in anime and this gives me ALL of them....
Epicness, a detailed story, great action and fights, things beyond logic and best of all boobs that all man wants.
Some would say that "This is childish and lame"... I hardly think that it is childish because there bloodshed in this whole series.
Want for something different and PURE EPICNESS? This is your choice.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="491368">This is the first review I write for basically anything. I had to write, because it REALLY good. Not a masterpiece like Gode Geass, but still exciting, with a good development-themed plot. Do NOT drop at episode 8, by the way. TOttaly worth it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="513817">All I can say is Holy Sh*t... This anime made me cry for the first time in a long time. There were sad parts, epic parts, funny parts, and just that jaw dropping awesomeness. I had no idea that the show that was a little odd in the beginning would leave my eyes full of tears at the end and laughing. Just watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="97500">This is the kind of series that only come every few years or so, it is a fantasic story of epic poportions. Every episode eceeds your expectations.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="239740">For any anime fan! Even for those who don`t like mechas, if you want to watch something epic the thats it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="382602">Best friggin super robot show ever. 
Epic action, epic manly tears, epic awesomeness. 
Those who think it`s overrated can go back to their generic superpower shounen for 10 yos or their fanservice boob-harems for no lifers.
[b]If you call yourself an anime fan and you haven`t watched this, DO IT NOW![/b]</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gurren-lagann.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="718" type="Animation Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="3078" type="Character Design">Nishigori Atsushi</name>
<name id="1568" type="Series Composition">Nakashima Kazuki</name>
<name id="155" type="Direction">Imaishi Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="1414" type="Music">Iwasaki Taku</name>
</creators>
<description>In the distant future, people build their homes and raise domestic animals in subterranean caverns called "pits". This way of life has persisted for hundreds of years, and yet, the people are still powerless against the earthquakes and cave-ins which occasionally devastate their villages. Jeeha is one such village...
One day, while digging tunnels to expand Jeeha`s edges, a boy named http://anidb.net/ch469 [Simon] happens to find a small, shiny drill. Meanwhile, http://anidb.net/ch468 [Kamina] — Simon`s soon-to-be "bro" — insists that there is another land above the village and tries to break through the ceiling in order to leave the cavern. He fails; however, an earthquake suddenly occurs, the ceiling collapses, and a gigantic robot — a "Ganmen" — crashes to the cave floor!
Kamina is now certain that there is a world above their tiny pit-village. Encouraged, he begins to fight recklessly against the robot, until he encounters another person who has arrived from the land above. She is a beautiful girl by the name of http://anidb.net/ch470 [Youko], who has come from a neighbouring village with a rifle in hand. She has been hunting the robot, but her shots only seem to irritate it. Desperately trying to escape its attacks, Simon brings Kamina and Youko to what he had previously found: a mysterious robot with a head for a body.
And so begins the "epic" adventure...
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="12096">8.72</permanent>
<temporary count="12411">8.62</temporary>
<review count="29">8.61</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221630.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6698</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3352</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2001</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3824</identifier>
<identifier>iajrht</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gurren-lagann.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gurren_Lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>天元突破グレンラガン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1000</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326669</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8880</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9950</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B001IIR3G2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1221" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-28">
<name>scooter</name>
<description>A scooter is a type of motorcycle with a step-through frame and a platform for the rider`s feet.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>218044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-08">
<name>ambitious</name>
<description>having a strong desire for success or achievement; wanting power, money, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1386" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-11">
<name>reckless</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1393" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-08">
<name>drill</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1438" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-18">
<name>ruthless</name>
<description>This character will stop at nothing to achieve their goals and will be unbound by any constraints</description>
<picurl>214979.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3313" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>evolution</name>
<description>Evolution is change in the heritable characteristics of biological populations over successive generations. Evolutionary processes give rise to biodiversity at every level of biological organisation, including the levels of species, individual organisms, and molecules.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64170.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3696" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-28">
<name>off-model animation</name>
<description>Anime shows tend to most often run on an already tight budget; some have even tighter ones. Thus, over the years it became a norm to invest more time and money into the first and last episode, leaving many episodes in the middle to stand severe budget restrictions. This sometimes results in episodes which particularly stand out due to the drop in artwork or animation quality; bar some basic framework, they often have little in common with the rest of the series.
One clue to upcoming off-model animation is the noticeable addition of many Korean names in the production credits, as farming out more animation to Korean artists is a nearly universal indicator of a production company trying to save money in all possible ways.
This effect is often called yashigani, after the infamous http://anidb.net/e4682 [fourth episode] of http://anidb.net/a403 [Lost Universe], Yashigani Hoburu. Another prominent term describing the same effect is "QUALITY animation", with capital letters meant to show contrast to actual quality. http://anidb.net/a4531 [Yoake Mae yori Ruriiro na: Crescent Love] is another legendarily terrible offender: the TV airing of its http://anidb.net/e63752 [third episode] had a perfectly spherical ball in place of what should be a cabbage; the "cabbage" was so egregious that it became closely associated with the anime itself, to a point the show would henceforth be nicknamed "Cabbage Love" among Western viewers.
One should not confuse the yashigani effect with art shifts that stem from guest staff, changes in main staff, intentional art shifts, and similar effects. Another effect one shouldn`t confuse this one with is the so-called DVD/BD enhancement, which is when a studio scrambles to meet the deadline for a TV airing and airs a half-finished episode but eventually fixes it for a disk release; for example, http://anidb.net/cr792 [Shaft] is particularly infamous for its disk enhancements, to a point it has become known as "Shafting", and they prominently feature intentionally weird character models, but they don`t often leave bad artwork on the disk release. Additionally, it should also not be confused with intentional lack of detail on background plane characters; this effect is instead when even the foreground has art quality shifting over time due to the aforementioned budget restrictions.</description>
<picurl>29532.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3852" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>Bright slap</name>
<description>"You hit me! Not even my father ever hit me!" 
You are the commander of a spaceship, leader of a faction or a team and your best mecha pilot stops fighting and grows increasingly hysterical and angsty, while the enemy could strike you at any time. What are you going to do? 
You slap or punch him, preferably in the face, and back to his senses while delivering a heroic speech that would turn any wimp into a man of destiny.
Named after Bright Noa of Mobile Suit Gundam, a prominent user of this for-sure method.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3874" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>bridge bunnies</name>
<description>A term and English nickname describing the attractive girls who manage the various functions aboard a ship`s/starship`s bridge area. 
Although it originated in reference to characters from Macross, it does not exist among Japanese fans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4330" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-09">
<name>quantum mechanics</name>
<description>Quantum mechanics (or physics) is a set of principles that describe the physical world (everything that is material) in terms of atoms and subatomic particles (e.g. electrons, photons, neutrons, quarks) and the relations between them. (See wikipedia for detailed info).
The story or plot used in this anime is directly related with one or more of this principles; mainly the simultaneous wave-like and particle-like behavior of all matter and radiation, or the "Heisenberg uncertainty principle" (one can never know both the location and the speed of a particle with all certainty).
Sometimes just some terms of quantum mechanics are used in the anime, like "Schrödinger`s cat" or "synchrotron radiation", to make the story more "real".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4417" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>existentialism</name>
<description>Most commonly defines the rejection of a god and any transcendent will that dictates how humans should live. It rejects any "created" meaning of life and the world, stating a leap of faith is required to live an authentic life. In this existentialism, belief in a god is often considered a form of Bad Faith.
In length, the Absurd contains ideas that there is no meaning in the world beyond what meaning it`s given. Meaninglessness also encompasses amorality or "unfairness" of the world. This contrasts with "karmic" ways of thinking in which "bad things don`t happen to good people"; there is no such thing as a good person or a bad thing; what happens happens, and it may just as well happen to a good person as to a bad person. This contrasts daily experience where most things appear meaningful, and where good people receive a "reward" for goodness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4558" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-12">
<name>long time span</name>
<description>The anime spans a much longer than usual (for that genre) period of time, typically several years (possibly decades or even centuries).
Example: In a school setting this could mean the character development is followed from school through college right into working life and the founding of a family with children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4566" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-08">
<name>transforming weapons</name>
<description>This anime features transforming weapons, this can either be cars or household appliances that transform into weapons, such as transformers or weapons that themselves transform into bigger badder shapes to deal more and more damage.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6901" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-23">
<name>underground</name>
<description>Some or all of the action occurs underground, in caves, mines, sewers, subways or underground cities.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7086" parentid="2846" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>soft science fiction</name>
<description>Soft science fiction is a type of science fiction in which the science presented is scientifically inaccurate or unimportant to the story, in contrast to http://anidb.net/t4667 [hard science fiction]. Its elements generally present themselves via artistic licence.
This is not to be confused with social science fiction, confusingly also called "soft science fiction", which is science fiction concerned with the "soft sciences" (social sciences), as opposed to the "hard sciences" (natural sciences).</description>
<picurl>222752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="39" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-02">
<rating votes="1228">7.83</rating>
<name>Souryuu Asuka Langley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuka is only one quarter Japanese, which accounts for her Japanese name but European appearance. Asuka is a native of Germany, having been raised there, though her nationality is technically American. Asuka`s native language is German, and in both the series and the manga she tends to curse in German. She is a child prodigy and has earned a university degree in an unspecified field as a teenager; she also speaks fluent Japanese, but has trouble reading and writing kanji. She is characterized by her fiery red hair and equally fiery temper. Asuka is very proud of being an Eva pilot, and near-constantly wears her A10 nerve clips in her hair, because she wants everyone around her to know that she is a pilot.</description>
<picture>14311.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="310" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-07-28">
<rating votes="1632">8.12</rating>
<name>Ayanami Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayanami Rei is the "First Children" of the Marduk Report and the pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6996 [EVA-00]. Shrouded in mystery, she is socially withdrawn and rarely shows emotion. Seemingly completely devoted to her duty as an EVA pilot, her only apparent human relationship being with http://anidb.net/ch5009 [Nerv] commander http://anidb.net/ch5000 [Ikari Gendou].
Rei comes to know http://anidb.net/ch309 [Ikari Shinji], and after some initial mistrust they come to better understand each other, revealing more of Rei`s emotional side and helping Shinji trust others again.
Rei`s body was created at Nerv in an attempt to bring back Gendou`s wife http://anidb.net/ch9620 [Ikari Yui], who was stuck inside http://anidb.net/ch8704 [EVA-01]. Soulless clones of her are kept hidden in the deepest levels of NERV, to be used both as replacement bodies for Rei should she die and as "cores" of the Dummy Plugs. Gendou, plans to make Rei help him control Instrumentality to reunite him with his wife.</description>
<picture>59479.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="468" type="main character in" update="2016-10-26">
<rating votes="1619">8.82</rating>
<name>Kamina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamina is a young man from Jeeha village who dreams of leaving the village and go to the surface, which he saw as a child. He`s very passionate about his goals, expressing his wishes through energetic speeches, which seem to affect all those who hear them.
As the leader of the "Gurren Brigade", he convinces Simon to aid him in his plan to drill through the roof of the village and get to the world above, but the plan fails and he is imprisoned. After defeating an invading Gunmen, he leaves the village with Simon and Yoko, in the cockpit of a tiny but powerful Gunmen Simon unearths and Kamina names "Lagann".
Kamina is extremely impulsive, and sometimes acts with little regard for his life. His plans are rarely well thought-out, often relying solely on brute strength and determination to win, but for some strange reason or another, they seem to work most of the time. It is revealed that Kamina`s impulsive confidence is mostly a show to give Simon the courage to act. He believes that in reality, all he can do is give Simon the motivation to "reach the heavens"; he couldn`t do it himself.</description>
<picture>14764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="469" type="main character in" update="2016-10-26">
<rating votes="660">7.68</rating>
<name>Simon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Simon is a fourteen year-old digger from Jeeha village. Although he is initially looked down upon because of it, Simon excels at drilling through the ground, and the drill quickly becomes his trademark symbol. One day, he finds a mysterious drill-shaped item, which is later revealed to be the "Core Drill", for a head-shaped Gunmen he also finds buried in the soil. With the help of the small Gunmen, Kamina, and Yoko, he fights off a much larger Gunmen that falls into the village. In the process of defeating the invader, they reach the surface world. Prior to the time-skip, Simon is mostly depicted as merely following Kamina`s lead and often acting as a counter-balance to Kamina`s impulsiveness. An unfortunate accident forces Simon to mature and take up a leadership role within Team Dai-Gurren.</description>
<picture>14766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="470" type="main character in" update="2020-01-16">
<rating votes="1477">8.55</rating>
<name>Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl from Jeeha`s neighbouring village of Littner, who had been chasing the Gunmen which entered Jeeha village. She wields an extensive arsenal of firearms and has previous experience fighting Gunmen. She uses her marksmanship from afar to assist Kamina and Simon, while they pilot their respective Gunmen.</description>
<picture>14767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="471" type="main character in" update="2008-12-10">
<rating votes="530">6.69</rating>
<name>Nia Teppelin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nia is a mysterious young girl found by Simon sleeping in a capsule in the middle of a dump site. She has had no prior contact with humans except her father. She is very curious, pure and innocent, because of a sheltered childhood in a peaceful environment away from all the battles occurring in the outside world, and because she had only recently gained sentience. During her travels with Team Dai-Gurren, she discovers the harsh realities of the world and has a very close relationship with Simon throughout the story.</description>
<picture>14768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="472" type="main character in" update="2009-12-29">
<rating votes="224">1.74</rating>
<name>Rossiu Adai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy from another underground village, Adai, in which the people worship the Gunmen as gods. A modest but intelligent person, he`s often seen looking after the young Gimmy and Darry. When the twins are chosen to leave the village, he decides to go with them, thus the trio joins Team Gurren. Before he leaves, the village elder gives him a book that seems to withhold some secrets from humanity`s past, with the task to find someone able to read it, as no one in his village can decipher its content. After Kamina`s death, Rossiu temporarily begins piloting Gurren in his place, though initially has trouble, due to Simon`s breakdown</description>
<picture>14771.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="508" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="184">6.95</rating>
<name>Kittan Bachika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kittan Bachika is the oldest of the Black Siblings. During his first encounter with Team Gurren, he mistakenly confuses Kamina for a Beastman. This is reconciled, when it is discovered that Kamina is piloting the Gunmen, Gurren. Shortly after, the two teams (the Black Siblings and Team Gurren) come into contact with the sixteen-headed enemy Gunmen, whom the Black Siblings had crossed paths with earlier. After the eventual defeat of the enemy Gunmen, the two teams part ways.</description>
<picture>14807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="514" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="102">3.22</rating>
<name>Kinon Bachika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinon is the second oldest of Kittan`s younger sisters. After Team Dai-Gurren`s capture of Dai-Gunzan, she takes up a position within its control tower, monitoring the radar. She seems to be the calmest and smartest member of the Black Siblings.</description>
<picture>14812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1491" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="20">8.29</rating>
<name>Gurren Lagann</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Later in the series the land-bound Gurren Lagann merges with another unnamed enemy Gunmen and gains a permanent set of wings.</description>
<picture>16014.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1492" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="27">8.10</rating>
<name>Gurren</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Gurren, originally named the "Gunzar" as mentioned by other Beastmen in the manga, is initially an above-average sized Beastmen-piloted mecha, which attacked Litner Village the morning after Team Gurren`s arrival early in the series. The mech is subsequently captured, rebuilt, stylised and named by its eventual pilot, Kamina, who had the Gurren`s original swords converted into massive sunglasses similar to his own that could be used as a blade or boomerang in combat. Being of typical Gunmen proportions, the Gurren is capable to fight without the Lagann`s power. While its individual power was initially not on the same level as advanced Gunmen/pilot pairs, such as Viral and his Enki, Kamina eventually became experienced enough to hold his own against multiple enemies.
After Kamina`s death, the Gurren was mainly piloted by Rossiu and one-time pilots until the aftermath of the battle of Tepplin, pilotless until Viral becomes the Gurren`s offical pilot during the battle against the AntiSpirals. Gurren (紅蓮) means "Crimson Lotus". As a homage to it, a white Gunzar unit is seen during the battle of Tepplin, sporting a pair of pistols rather than blades.</description>
<picture>16033.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1493" type="appears in" update="2017-10-08">
<rating votes="42">8.50</rating>
<name>Lagann</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Lagann is Simon`s personal Gunmen which he finds in the first episode while digging tunnels in his village. It received its name, Lagann (羅顔), meaning "enveloping face", from Kamina and draws power from the Core Drill, a small golden drill Simon uses similar to an ignition key. Unlike any other Gunmen in the series, the Lagann sports a unique cockpit and stands just short of an average human adult as opposed to the others which are all mostly the sizes of small buildings or larger. This physical handicap, in tandem with the usually average level of fighting spirit supplied to it by Simon, puts the Lagann at a considerable disadvantage in single combat against enemy Gunmen. However, when Simon is driven to give his best during combat the Lagann`s power increases exponentially, giving it the unique ability to generate drills from nearly any part of its frame. Lagann`s other and most notable power is the "Lagann Impact", its trademark ability to combine with other machines by piercing them with its drills. It`s through this ability that the titular Gurren Lagann is created, along with the other more large-scale mechas in the series.</description>
<picture>16032.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1502" type="appears in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="3">7.00</rating>
<name>Arc-Gurren Lagann</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>When Simon uses the Gurren Lagan to merge into the Arc-Gurren, he converts the Dai-Gun into a Dai-Gunman called the Arc-Gurren Lagann, powered up by one of the Gurren Lagann`s Giga Drills similar to how the Lagann is powered by Simon`s Core Drill. The power of this Gunmen isn`t fully displayed in the series, but it has the ability to rip the fabric of space-time itself through its sheer brute force on its debut. The Arc-Gurren Lagann is usually used exclusively by Simon and Viral, in the Gurren-Lagann. It can form massive drills or fight with punches.</description>
<picture>16028.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1503" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-19">
<rating votes="299">8.29</rating>
<name>Viral</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Viral is a member of the Human Eradication Army, who regards Kamina as a strong rival. Though being among the more humanoid of the Beastmen, his DNA contains aspects of shark and feline genetics. He pilots Enkidudu, which mainly utilizes swords and a powerful laser. He is extremely loyal to Lordgenome and the four supreme generals, and he does his best to serve them. After Kamina`s death, he continues to fight Gurren-Lagann, thinking that Kamina is still alive, and he is shocked once he learns the truth. He is given the gift of immortality by Lordgenome, so that he could spread his legacy. After the fall of the empire, he resurfaces and causes an uproar with his Gunmen, calling Simon out to fight him. He is later taken into custody, and pilots Gurren during the battle against the Anti-Spirals. Viral thus becomes a `reformed villain` of sorts. It is also shown that his deepest desire is to get married and have children, but cannot do so as Beastmen lack the spiral energy necessary for reproduction. In the epilogue, he becomes the captain of the Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren and an emissary for Earth.</description>
<picture>16029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1504" type="appears in" update="2017-10-08">
<rating votes="3">6.10</rating>
<name>Arc-Gurren</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Named Arc-Gurren by Rossiu, this is one of Lordgenome`s Gunmen battleships, a Dai-Gun, which his armies used when he was a Spiral Warrior in events prior to the series. Enormous in size, it is initially used to gather hundreds of thousands of animals and people onto it as possible to escape world-destroying events later in the series. It uses Spiral Energy to run and only recognizes Lordgenome as its operator. It is capable of going into space for at least a year, and contains an array of large-scale defensive systems and weaponry.</description>
<picture>16030.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1506" type="appears in" update="2017-10-08">
<rating votes="5">9.15</rating>
<name>Chouginga Gurren Lagann</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>During the final battle with the Anti-Spirals, when dealing with larger Ashtanga, Simon channeled enough massive Spiral Energy, with aid from the spiral energy of those before Team Dai-Gurren to battle the Anti-Spiral, to merge the Arc-Gurren Lagann with the battleship and transform it into a humanoid shape, the Ultra Spiral Dreadnought Gunman Super Galaxy Gurren Lagann; this is similar to the method that created the Arc-Gurren Lagann.</description>
<picture>16034.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1510" type="appears in" update="2017-10-08">
<rating votes="22">8.80</rating>
<name>Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>By combining his own Spiral Energy with his comrades`, Simon created the ultimate entity, the titular Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann in the final battle against the Anti-Spirals. Not actually a mecha at all, it is a mass of materialized Spiral Energy on the scale of a galaxy. Though being similar to the Gurren Lagann, its design is overall very different from other mecha in the series, its armor being made up of red skulls bound together by Spiral Energy that burns continuously from its core, giving it the appearance of Team Dai-Gurren`s emblem.
It has been confirmed in the data books that the Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann is 10 million light years (94,607,304,725,808,000,000,000 metres) in height.</description>
<picture>16043.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1540" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="13">5.73</rating>
<name>King Kittan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The King Kittan is the Gunman piloted by Kittan. Inspired by Kamina`s hijacking of an enemy Gunmen, Kittan and some others seized Gunmen for their own use to fight against the Beastmen. The King Kittan is a gold-colored star-shaped mecha with a menacing face, able to use its body as a weapon.</description>
<picture>16076.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1541" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="93">5.91</rating>
<name>Darry Aday</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darry Aday is a girl from Aday Village, who used to be cared for by Rossiu. She is Gimmy`s twin sister and has a good bond with him. As a young girl, she was shy and quiet and used to cling to a plush doll, which she carried with her at all times. After the timeskip, however, she is much more confident and has left her old personality behind. As a Grapearl pilot, she is careful, calm and perceptive, and puts more thought and planning into her actions than Gimmy.</description>
<picture>16077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1543" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="79">3.78</rating>
<name>Gimmy Aday</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gimmy Aday is a boy from Aday Village, who used to be cared for by Rossiu. When new children were born into the village, the population exceeded its limit of 50, which mandated that two people be removed and sent to the surface. Since Gimmy and Darry had no parents, the village elder chose them to leave the village, however, Rossiu decided to go with them. The pair of twins have a very good bond with each other, and were often left to their own devices around Dai-Gurren, except when they were with older girls, such as Yoko or Nia. After the timeskip, Gimmy and Darry become important Grapearl pilots, often fighting together. Gimmy tends to be more impulsive and reckless, which sometimes puts the duo in trouble.</description>
<picture>16078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1544" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="88">6.20</rating>
<name>Kiyal Bachika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest of the Black Siblings.</description>
<picture>16079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1545" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="74">5.94</rating>
<name>Kiyoh Littner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The oldest of Kittan`s younger sisters.</description>
<picture>16080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1546" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="35">5.25</rating>
<name>Dayakka Littner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dayakka Littner is the former leader of Littner Village, abandoning his post, when most of Littner joined Team Dai-Gurren. His Gunmen is the Dayakkaiser, but after the seizure of Dai-Gunzan, he acted as the captain of Dai-Gurren during battles, while Kiyoh piloted the Dayakkaiser in his stead.</description>
<picture>16081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1548" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="7">7.06</rating>
<name>Dai-Gurren</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Originally called the Dai-Gunzan while under the command of Thymilph, one of Lordgenome`s four generals, it`s essentially a walking battleship many times larger than conventional Gunmen, with numerous heavy artillery gun turrets and heavy armour. The arms attached to the control tower serves as the hangar bay launchers for its housed Gunmen. After its capture by Team Dai-Gurren, it is renamed the "Dai-Gurren" (although still referred to by its original name by the Beastmen) by Kamina and remodelled to accommodate the Brigade members, sporting a red color scheme and a different tower on the head as the original was destroyed when Simon took control of it using Lagann.</description>
<picture>16085.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1549" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="3">1.92</rating>
<name>Dayakkaiser</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Dayakkaiser is the Gunman initially piloted by Dayakka, but it was transferred over to Kiyoh after he became the captain of the Dai-Gurren. Along with the other human-piloted Gunmen, this was also seized from the Beastmen Empire. It has a cannon mounted on top of its head, which fires explosive solid rounds.</description>
<picture>16086.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1550" type="appears in" update="2017-10-08">
<rating votes="7">6.70</rating>
<name>Chouginga Dai-Gurren</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren, christened by Simon, is another colossal battleship-type Gunmen akin to the Arc-Gurren. It first appeared in the prologue of the first episode, before being formally introduced near the end of the third part of the series. During http://anidb.net/ch1561 [Lordgenome]`s era, the battleship was named the Cathedral Terra.</description>
<picture>16087.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1551" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="59">3.63</rating>
<name>Adiane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Adiane the Elegant is the second of the Spiral King`s Four Supreme Generals, and the only female general among their number. She is good friends with her fellow General, Thymilph, though Guame jokes that they had a closer relationship. She implies this friendship was strong because both Guame and General Cytomander treat her as an inferior because of her gender, while Thymilph respected her as a warrior.</description>
<picture>16090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1552" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="27">3.04</rating>
<name>Guame</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guame the Immoveable is one of the Spiral King`s Four Supreme Generals, who specialises in ground combat. His appearance is like that of a crocodile and armadillo and the oldest of the four generals, revealed in the parallel works to be originally an animal-like figure seen by Lordgenome`s side as a parallel to Boota, living as long as or almost as long as the Spiral King has.</description>
<picture>16092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="480" picture="232940.jpg">Kawakubo Kiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1556" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="22">2.88</rating>
<name>Cytomander</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cytomander the Swift is one of the Spiral King`s Four Supreme Generals and the commander of Teppelin`s aerial forces and owner of the flying battleship, the Dai-Gunten.</description>
<picture>16096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1558" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="15">3.16</rating>
<name>Thymilph</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Thymilph the Crasher is the first of the Spiral King`s Four Supreme Generals introduced in the story, representing the classical element of fire. He is Viral`s initial superior officer and the commander of the Human Eradication Army Eastern Branch, which he monitors from the deck of the land battleship, the Dai-Gunzan. He is good friends with Adiane, though Guame insinuates a closer relationship.</description>
<picture>16098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="287" picture="73062.jpg">Yanada Kiyoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1561" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="83">7.58</rating>
<name>Lordgenome</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A seemingly cruel and ruthless tyrant who employs legions of creatures known as Beastmen to systemically eradicate all human-kind on the planet surface, commanding his armies from a gigantic funnel-shaped castle called Teppelin.</description>
<picture>16099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="481" picture="127294.jpg">Ikeda Narushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1580" type="main character in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="212">5.63</rating>
<name>Leeron Littner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leeron Littner, or simply "Ron", is the village mechanic of Littner, who is able to repair and scavenge the various Gunmen he and his group encounter. Quite knowledgeable, and very flamboyant, Leeron was the first one to join Kamina, Simon, and Yoko on their quest to defeat the Beastmen. He has become the main technician for Team Dai-Gurren, as well as being in charge of coordination and communication between the Gunmen during battle from Dai-Gurren. His ability to learn and adapt is incredibly great, seeing as he once mentioned that he didn`t even know how to read before becoming a mechanic.</description>
<picture>16119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1583" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="30">8.74</rating>
<name>Dai-Gurren-Dan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>2304.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="1585" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="4">5.89</rating>
<name>Enki</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Enki is Viral`s personal Gunman, modelled after an armoured samurai. The Enki is the product of significant innovation in Gunmen technology, and sports a number of advances that eclipse lesser models in performance, and is the first model seen to support solid-based ammunition. Unlike stout Gunmen, such as the Gurren, that have bulky limbs that can only be used in wide swings, the Enki is more segmented and has multiple joints that allow it to perform complex actions, such as throws, kicks, and various martial arts techniques. The Enki`s arm and thigh plates conceal rows of hidden gun turrets that fire large steel projectiles (kunai). There are pop-up compartments in the shoulders that can fire a single volley of rockets, and the entire chest plate can open to reveal a number of launchers that deliver an explosive payload of missiles. The Enki possesses a wrist mounted concave blast-shield, and a helmet with a large black ring atop of it, that is actually the charging focus for a medium-range particle beam cannon.
Its helmet becomes the possession of Simon and Kamina, as they stole it when they first combined to make the Gurren-Lagann.</description>
<picture>16123.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1586" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="4">4.54</rating>
<name>Enkidu</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Later, the helmet-less Enki has been redeployed as the degraded "Enkidu" and sports a new sickle-like weapon, which is affixed to its head. When wielded, it provides an alternative to the dual swords the Enki usually resorts to in melee combat. Furthermore, it is also capable of shelling from afar by physically launching munitions from the same point on its head, once the sickle has been removed.</description>
<picture>16124.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1587" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="5">5.52</rating>
<name>Enkidudu</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>During the Invasion of Teppelin, Viral`s Gunmen remodified into the "Enkidudu", replacing the sickle crest for an extra pair of arms, meaning the Gunmen can now fight with four blades.
When the new form fights the Gurren-Lagann, however, it is swiftly defeated, despite its upgrade. After the timeskip, the Enkidudu is shown fighting the Grapearl unit, in order to protect a group of humans who decided to continue living underground. However, the damaged Enkidudu is unable to hold its own against the advanced Grapearls and is ultimately defeated, shutting down as Viral thanked his mecha for lasting this long for his grudge. The fate of the Enkidudu is never known, but is likely scrapped like the other Gunmen.</description>
<picture>16125.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1618" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">6.53</rating>
<name>Shuzack</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Shuzack currently serves as the personal Gunman of Cytomander. Whereas the Sayrune was best-suited for underwater combat, the Shuzack is more adapted to aerial superiority, sporting a compact flight engine and a massive winged design. Additionally, its multi-jointed frame allows for both arms to both extend and retract in close-quarter situations. Its torso also holds a deadly buzzsaw.
The Shuzack is destroyed, along with its pilot, when it got in the way of the Dai-Gurren ramming into the Dai-Gunten. Like the custom Gunman of the other Generals, the Shuzack can also transform.
However the full extent of its abilities are unknown, as the Shuzack was immediately destroyed following it`s transformation.</description>
<picture>16149.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1619" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="3">3.73</rating>
<name>Gember</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The custom Gunmen Gember first appeared in action on the deck of the Dai-Gurren as its owner, Guame, had retreated to it, to personally perform his public warning execution of the captured members of Team Dai-Gurren. It is the second Gunman to feature a transformation. It has the appearance of being rather broad and bulky starfish in its regular mech state and is somewhat insect like with its antennae, which can ensnare enemies. Its second form is a large face-like apparition and is also insect-like with sharp needles that resemble legs. The controls of the Gember differ from normal Gunmen to accommodate its user, as Guame is placed into a sphere-like crevice with a pair of mechanical hands aiding him. The only known attack of the Gember was its Gember Press, wherein the foe is caught in a hold and crushed by the needles that are released from its arms.
The time of the Gember was short lived, as it was destroyed by the Gurren-Lagann`s Giga Drill Break. However, its pilot ejected himself before his Gunman got obliterated.</description>
<picture>16147.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1620" type="appears in" update="2008-12-27">
<rating votes="2">7.50</rating>
<name>Sayrune</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Sayrune is currently commissioned as Adiane`s personal Gunman and was first seen deployed from the flagship, Dai-Gunkai, while pursuing the stolen Dai-Gunzan. It is one of the few Gunman seen thus far in the series to feature two unique configurations: its default winged humanoid appearance, as well as an alternate scorpion-shaped layout. While in its winged state, the Sayrune seems to rely mostly on a range of energy whips and tendrils to mount any sort of attack, whereas its scorpion form is endowed with massive pincer claws and a stinger. The Sayrune can also use its wings to form a double-edged weapon called the Bloody Clamper.
The Sayrune was destroyed, along with its pilot, when it was shot by the Dai-Gurren`s cannons at point blank range, after Adiane`s failed attempt to take Nia as a hostage.</description>
<picture>16148.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1621" type="appears in" update="2008-12-27">
<rating votes="2">6.53</rating>
<name>Byakou</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Byakou is Thymilph`s personal Gunman. It is stored within the Dai-Gunzan`s hangar bays and first saw deployment during Team Dai-Gurren`s second attack on the mobile Gunman fortress. Equipped with a polearm called the Alkaid Glaive, it is capable of emitting a powerful energy beam attack from the tip of the weapon, Condemnn Blaze. The Byakou was especially deadly in single combat and proved to be even more lethal, when paired with the Enki in pummeling the lone Gurren. Unlike personal Gunman units fielded by the other Generals, the Byakou was never shown to have a distinct alternate configuration.
The Byakou was the first victim of the Gurren-Lagann`s multi-stage Giga Drill Break attack, which completely obliterated both the Gunmen and its pilot. It was also the last enemy defeated by Kamina, who was heavily wounded and died shortly after.</description>
<picture>16146.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1623" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">6.53</rating>
<name>Lazengann</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Meaning "Spiral Face", the Lazengann is Lord Genome`s personal Gunman, using his consorts as batteries. It is very similar to the Gurren-Lagann and has the same abilities that the Lagann can use (by extension, it also proves immune to being controlled by the Lagann Impact attack). However, it is much stronger and can use more powerful drill techniques, as well as defend against the Gurren-Lagann`s techniques with ease.
In the end, it took the Lagann on its own to severely damage the Lazengann. The mecha was later recreated as part of the Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann, used in the desperation move Lazengann Overload to convert itself and the energy from the Grand Zamboa`s Infinity Big Bang Storm into pure Spiral Energy, taking the form of a gigantic drill with Lord Genome`s head on the tip that is ingested by the Tengen Toppa`s abdominal mouth.</description>
<picture>16150.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1644" type="appears in" update="2008-12-27">
<rating votes="3">4.82</rating>
<name>Dai-Gunzan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Essentially a walking battleship many times larger than conventional Gunmen, with numerous heavy artillery gun turrets and heavy armour. The arms attached to the control tower serves as the hangar bay launchers for its housed Gunmen. After its capture by Team Dai-Gurren, it is renamed the "Dai-Gurren" (although still referred to by its original name by the Beastmen) by Kamina and remodelled to accommodate the Brigade members.</description>
<picture>16179.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1681" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="27">8.10</rating>
<name>Lordgenome Head</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seven years later, Rossiu recovered Lordgenome`s brain and regrows the likeness of Lordgenome`s head from a tissue sample collected from the Spiral King`s corpse. This is done because Lordgenome`s memories could not be accessed directly from a normal computer, so a special "Bio-Computer" had to be built to allow Lordgenome to relay his memories personally to the curious. Once activated, the bemused Bio-Computer explains the existence of the Anti-Spirals to Rossiu, and later serves as a power source for Arc Gurren when the Mugan have overrun Kamina City. The Bio-Computer`s information later proves invaluable, helping to prevent the moon drop and provide the means to reach the Anti-Spiral`s pocket dimension.
However, though programmed without a personality, Lordgenome eventually regains self-awareness and assumes the identity of the man he used to be, joining as navigator of the newly recommissioned Chouginga Gurren just to finally come face to face with the Anti Spiral. Once Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann is formed, Lordgenome uses the Super Spiral Space`s power to temporary recreate his body to serve as one of the thirteen key pilots. He then later detaches Lazengann Overload to block the Grand Zamboa`s Infinity Big Bang Storm and wilfully sacrifices himself to convert the massive attack and himself into a galaxy-sized drill of Spiral Energy that Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann absorbs to ensure Lordgenome`s intent of paving a path for the spiral beings of future generations.</description>
<picture>16222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="481" picture="127294.jpg">Ikeda Narushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1682" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="42">8.60</rating>
<name>Gurren Lagann</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Gurren Lagann, the titular mech of the series, is piloted jointly by two pilots for most of the story, with the Lagann portion always operated by the series` main protagonist Simon and the Gurren piloted by Kamina initially and then various other characters after his death. The mech was originally formed as a hotblooded response from Kamina to the Enki`s initial two-headed configuration.</description>
<picture>16226.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1813" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="2">5.52</rating>
<name>Dekabutsu</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A Dai-Gunmen originating from the capital city, Teppelin. It is extremely bulky, and has a very uncomplicated humanoid shape.
Extremely powerful, it was able to stop the Gurren-Lagann`s drilling power. On one arm it has a hand, whilst the other has a giant hammer, and it can deploy a vast amount of Gunmen. Like the Arc-Gurren-Lagann, it was designed to be piloted by a normal-sized Gunmen - in this instance, the Lazengann, with Lord Genome`s throne directly above it. It was stopped upon the defeat of the Spiral King, automatically shutting down and collapsed. After the seven-year timeskip, it is the capitol building for Kamina City. Half of its head was destroyed when the Anti-Spirals attacked. In Parallel Works 8, it is shown to be able to dock with Super Galaxy Gurren-Lagann in the same way as the Arc Gurren-Lagann did. Also, the tower on top of Dekatbutsu`s head was where the Lazengann docks with it. It can be assumed that, after Lazengann docked with Dekabutsu, the tower was constructed around it. The tower also provides a unique interface, allowing Lordgenome to control the entire Space Gunman without needing to be inside Lazengann. The Dekabutsu itself seems to project energy to all allied gunman, as normally beastmen piloted gunman are unable to function during the night (which they did during the battle of Tepplin) and the fact that all beastmen gunman shut down right after Lordgenome`s defeat.</description>
<picture>16404.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1814" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="3">3.73</rating>
<name>Dai-Gunkai</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Dai-Gunkai, rivalling the Dai-Gunzan in terms of sheer bulk and apparently much lengthier, is an aquatic serpentine Gunmen fortress, which served as Adiane`s flagship. Little is known about its abilities, other than its obvious aptitude for sea travel. While it seems to only be able to travel in a body of water, the Dai-Gunkai`s first appearance was marked by a sudden deluge over the battlefield (suggesting that it may have the ability to either divert or even create large volumes of water).
The only appearance of the Dai-Gunkai in combat was in episode 12, when it ambushed the Dai-Gurren, while it was crossing the ocean on its march to the Helix Empire`s capital. Its main weaponry consisted of torpedoes guided by dolphin Beastmen and two massive pincers, which it used on its attempt to drag the Dai-Gurren to the bottom of the ocean. After bringing the Dai-Gurren back to the surface, the Gurren-Lagann obliterated the Dai-Gunkai completely, but Viral, who was commanding the ship at that time, managed to survive.</description>
<picture>16405.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1815" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="2">6.53</rating>
<name>Dai-Gunten</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A fortress-type Gunmen, the flying Dai-Gunten is Cytomander`s flagship. The Dai-Gunten made its début during Cytomander`s campaign against the Dai-Gurren, acting primarily as a carrier to launch multiple waves of small aerial Gunmen bombers.
As the battle wore on, Simon and Yoko`s Gurren-Lagann and Viral`s Enkidu found their way deep below its decks and ended up dealing severe internal damage to the ship. Having lost altitude in the process, the Dai-Gunten was eventually damaged by a series of powerful kicks delivered by the Dai-Gurren, which had launched itself into the air using a cliff face. In the process, Team Dai-Gurren managed to snatch one of the enemy airship`s two Levia-Spheres for themselves, and used it to safely float back to the ground, while the Dai-Gunten managed to retreat using the remaining one.
A month after the first confrontation, the Dai-Gunten returns in the following episode along Guame`s flagship, the Dai-Gundo, as Teppelin`s last line of defence against Team Dai-Gurren`s invasion. Its forces managed to trap the Gurren-Lagann, after the rest of the Dai-Gurren`s gunman forces were forced to retreat and protect it against Guame`s offensive, and when the Shuzack was about to finish it, Simon and Rossiu were saved by some unexpected allies who entered the battlefield to aid them. In the end, the Dai-Gunten is sunk once run through by the flying Dai-Gurren. Pieces of its wreckage fell on the Dai-Gundo, provoking a massive explosion, but was unable to damage the heavily armoured flagship.</description>
<picture>16406.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1816" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="3">3.19</rating>
<name>Dai-Gundo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This fortress-type Gunmen is Guame`s flagship. Its carapace is extraordinarily resilient, as evidenced by its survival of the aerial carrier gunman Dai-Ganten`s impact. It is propelled by many legs on its underside, and can travel at a decent clip. It later combines its strengths with Teppelin to form a whirling tornado of energy that destroys anything that comes in contact and disrupts communications and navigation.
The Gurren-Lagann destroyed the Dai-Gundo from beneath the surface of the earth, piercing its armour and reversing its spinning, violating its union with Teppelin and dissipating its energy storm before lancing it clean through, causing it to explode. The Dai-Gundo`s means of locomotion was later adopted by the humans for the various vehicles they use (cars literally ran on legs, not wheels).</description>
<picture>16407.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1817" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<name>Kiyalunga</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Kiyalunga, named for and piloted by Kittan`s sister Kiyal, has the ability to transform into a lance and shield for use by the King Kittan, with Kittan referring to the formation as the King Kittan Deluxe. A homage to this Gunman is seen when Kittan piloted the Space King Kittan, where wielded weapons that resembles the Kiyalunga`s lance and shield transformation.</description>
<picture>16408.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1818" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="6">7.00</rating>
<name>Space King Kittan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Space King Kittan, an Dai-Gunman piloted by King Kittan, was created by Leite later in the series.
But was destroyed in a failed attempt to save the Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren from the Anti-Spirals` Galactic Death Spiral by destroying its core. However, before exploding, the normal-sized King Kittan ejected and through Kittan awakening his Spiral Power and the usage of its own variant of Gurren Lagann`s Giga Drill Break attack, it achieved its mission before getting destroyed too along with its pilot.</description>
<picture>16410.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1819" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="2">5.52</rating>
<name>Space Dayakkaiser</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Among the Space Gunmen manufactured by Leite, Space Dayakkaiser in particular was equipped with many new weapons, such as arm-based rocket launchers and an exceedingly powerful cannon.
Notably it is the only Gunmen (other than the Gurren Lagann) to survive the final battle with the Anti-Spirals.</description>
<picture>16411.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1820" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="2">9.44</rating>
<name>Grand Zamboa</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Grand Zamboa is the mecha piloted by the Anti-Spiral.
Created to fight the newly formed Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann on even grounds, beat Team Dai-Gurren at its own game and put an end to the fight once and for all. Its styling is similar to the Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann, with the Anti-Spiral home world as its core on its forehead and an extra pair of arms, located on its shoulders, which it used to catch the galaxies as well as execute its Infinity Big-Bang Storm attack, crushing to two galaxies together to produce a blast equal to a Big Bang to instantly vaporise the target. Though the attack was intended to annihilate Team Dai-Gurren, the manoeuvre backfired when Lordgenome used the Lazengann to take the blast, converting it and himself into Spiral Energy for the Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann. It was ultimately destroyed when Simon and Nia managed to pierce its pilot`s body with the Lagann`s drill, using the Lagann Impact.
Notably, the Grand Zamboa`s arms were in fact able to transform into drills, normally a symbol of Spiral Beings - however, when they are shown stationary, the drills in fact have entirely straight lines from base to tip.</description>
<picture>16412.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1821" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="31">8.03</rating>
<name>Koko-jii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Old Coco is a mysterious, silent old man who leads Team Gurren to the hot springs resort in episode six.
Although he tricks the group into entering the Beastmen`s trap, he helps Kamina later on by letting him onto the Beastmen Gunmen. He then gets caught up with Team Dai-Gurren, and now follows it around, although nobody seems to notice him. He seems to be incredibly hard to notice, to the point of saving Nia in episode eleven, and disappearing again before anyone realises he is gone. The timeskip reveals that he is in fact a Beastmen who was in charge of taking care of Nia, and continued to do so after she was no longer the princess of Teppelin.</description>
<picture>16413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1822" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="55">7.20</rating>
<name>Messenger Nia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>For most of the third arc, Nia serves as the messenger from the Anti-Spirals to the humans, during the Earth`s Human Extermination System.
After the Anti-Spiral data awakens within her and converts her into an Anti-Spiral virtual lifeform, becoming an emotionless and serious person, the exact opposite of how Nia was beforehand. As the messenger, she wears a dark skin-tight suit, covered with a green line pattern resembling something like a circuit board, and the previously red irises of her eyes have become black.
After becoming a messenger on the birth of the 1 millionth human, she possesses the power to travel between spatial dimensions, jump between positions instantly and intercept most methods of communication. She appears before Simon several times over the course of the arc, to repeatly tell him that all efforts against the Human Extermination System is futile while increasing the odds against mankind. But it was when she is the only thing keeping the Gurren Lagann from the "moon"`s control system, Simon points out to her that all her actions and appearances before him were in fact the act of her true feelings of her former self, who urges Simon to keep fighting, allowing Nia to have the strength to return to her former self while ending the Human Extermination. However, she is transported back to the Anti-Spiral homeworld so the data on Team Dai Gurren can be extracted from her for analysis, resulting in the rescue attempt that begins the fourth and final arc.</description>
<picture>16414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1823" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="69">2.61</rating>
<name>Anti-Spiral</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Anti-Spiral is the ultimate villain of Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann, and the central antagonistic presence for the final two story arcs. He first appears as a disembodied voice in episode twenty four, but is formally introduced in episode twenty six. His physical form is a chaos of arbitrary human concepts fluctuating on a black silhouette, with cartoonish gestures and exaggerated expressions.
Anti-Spiral is both the leader and collective mental manifestation of the "Anti-Spiral Race" after they seal themselves away to purge their race of Spiral energy. The highly advanced technology bequeaths onto him extensive, almost supernatural powers, which manifest in the form of red energy. With these abilities he is able to manipulate physical and chemical laws (going as far as altering probability), which he does regularly both offensively and as a form of intimidation. The Anti-Spiral is the nemesis of Lordgenome, being responsible for Lordgenome`s madness after explaining the nature of Spiral Nemesis to him.
Beyond what is known of the Anti-Spirals, little is known of the Anti-Spiral personally. He has the mannerisms of a scientist, suggesting he had a hand in both the creation of Anti-Spiral technology and the decision to undergo the millennia-long battle against the Milky Way`s spiral beings. The Anti-Spiral is very proud and holds deep contempt for spiral beings, specifically Simon, frustrated him that across all of time, spiral beings still resist limiting their populations and continue to defy the resolution of his race and their ideology.</description>
<picture>16415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="482" picture="17466.jpg">Kamikawa Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1824" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-25">
<rating votes="20">7.16</rating>
<name>Leite Jokin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leite Jokin is the chief engineer of Team Dai-Gurren and Leeron`s direct subordinate. She is a skilled and ingenious mechanic, an ideal work partner for the naturally gifted Leeron. Her central duties revolve around maintaining Dai-Gurren`s spiral engine, which appears less technologically sophisticated in Fortress-class Gunmen thus requiring additional fuel beyond spiral energy. Her personal trademarks are her lab coat and a cigarette she holds in her mouth.
In Part III, Leite`s role in the story is expanded from a virtual background character to an important member of the supporting cast. She is married to Makken, who she affectionately calls "Oto-chan" or "Daddy", and the two have three children. Leite and Makken operate a small business servicing mechanical equipment and automotive vehicles, though on occasion they get contracts to develop weapons from the New Government. She and Makken have great faith in Simon and his capacity as a decision maker; their loyalty to him urges them to resist Rossiu by rebuilding the scrapped Gunmen of Team Dai-Gurren, refitting them with spiral weaponry capable of damaging Mugann. Leite also refits Gurren Lagann`s power pack to allow it to reach escape velocity, but opts out of the Battle of Earth to stay with her children on the surface [5]. When Team Dai-Gurren is reformed, she assumes her old post as engineer of the gang`s flagship, the Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren. She eventually ends up as one of the fourteen pilots of Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann, battling Grand Zamboa to both avenge Makken`s death at the hands of Anti-Spiral Kantai and for the freedom of the entire galaxy.</description>
<picture>29961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1825" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="9">6.21</rating>
<name>Makken Jokin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makken is a fairly silent man who is an important part of Team Dai-Gurren, but has rarely spoken or gotten much screen time whatsoever. He has his own Gunmen, Moshogun, which is based on an ancient samurai.
After the timeskip, Makken is married to Leite with three children. Sadly, he is killed in the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, after sacrificing himself to stop a large Anti-Spiral missile from destroying the Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren.
In the epilogue, a memorial site, in the form of a sword, is seen in his honour right alongside Kamina and the other members of Team Dai-Gurren.</description>
<picture>27556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34821" picture="73716.jpg">Kaminaga Reo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1826" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="10">5.57</rating>
<name>Zorthy Kanai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zorthy Kanai appears at the end of episode seven as a new addition to Team Dai-Gurren. His most recognisable quality is his smoking habit, which is unique to every other character in the series. The name of his Gunmen is the Sozoshin.
Zorthy is killed during the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals.</description>
<picture>27550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12665" picture="227715.jpg">Kawakami Takafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1827" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="14">6.08</rating>
<name>Iraak Coega</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iraak Coega is a member of Team Dai-Gurren. He pilots a Gunmen that serves Youko as a mobile rifle platform. Together, they assaulted Dai-Gunzan with the rest of the Team Gurren. The name of his Gunmen is Ainzer.
Iraak is killed during the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, after he and Kid attempted to avenge Zorthy.</description>
<picture>27555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1828" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="11">6.88</rating>
<name>Kid Coega</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kid Coega is another new member of Team Dai-Gurren. His Gunmen utilises two pistols to attack enemies, the Kid Knuckle.
Kid is killed during the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, when he and Iraak attempt to avenge Zorthy`s death.</description>
<picture>27552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1829" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="13">4.42</rating>
<name>Jorgun Bakusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jorgun Bakusa and Balinbow Bakusa are the towering, twin brothers of Team Dai-Gurren, piloting the two-faced Gunmen, Twin Boukun. The two are always hyped and normally speak in manly grunts and monosyllabic phrases. They sport differently coloured sunglasses, which can be used to tell one brother from the other — Jorgun wears red shades, while Balinbow sports blue ones. After the timeskip, the two were appointed Directors of the Public Affairs Department, in which they were responsible for the human population count.
Jorgun and Balinbow are killed in the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, after saving Gimmy and Darry`s lives.</description>
<picture>16421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1830" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="31">1.92</rating>
<name>Balinbow Bakusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jorgun Bakusa and Balinbow Bakusa are the towering, twin brothers of Team Dai-Gurren, piloting the two-faced Gunmen, Twin Boukun. The two are always hyped and normally speak in manly grunts and monosyllabic phrases. They sport differently coloured sunglasses, which can be used to tell one brother from the other — Jorgun wears red shades, while Balinbow sports blue ones. After the timeskip, the two were appointed Directors of the Public Affairs Department, in which they were responsible for the human population count.
Jorgun and Balinbow are killed in the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, after saving Gimmy and Darry`s lives.</description>
<picture>16420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5410" picture="222917.jpg">Douzaka Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1831" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="70">3.44</rating>
<name>Attenborough Cortitch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Attenborough Cortitch is a hyperactive, impulsive, trigger-happy man, who is the gunner of Dai-Gurren`s control team. He tends to fire at enemies or move Dai-Gurren without warning. After the timeskip, he joins Leeron`s science team and still appears to have his hyperactive nature. After Team Dai-Gurren moved to Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren, he assumed the same position he had before at the weapons control. Curiously, this trait became one of Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann`s attacks. He randomly showed up in the series one day, later it was confirmed that he sneaked into some bozo`s luggage, and that is how he joined Team Dai Gurren.</description>
<picture>16423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1832" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="9">5.80</rating>
<name>Tetsukan Littner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tetsukan Littner is a member of the control team for Dai-Gurren. He is in charge of monitoring the condition of the ship. After the timeskip, he becomes a part of Leeron`s science team. Also due to being attracted to the fast-food restaurants that were built in the new city he became obese.</description>
<picture>27871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1833" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="14">5.84</rating>
<name>Gabal Docker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gabal Docker is Team Dai-Gurren`s helmsman, in charge of Dai-Gurren`s steering and manoeuvring.</description>
<picture>16422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1834" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="11">5.48</rating>
<name>Cybela Kuto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cybela Kuto is mainly seen at a computer, where she can communicate with Grapearls or do analysis tasks. Later, she joins Team Dai-Gurren, assuming a position at Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren`s bridge.</description>
<picture>16419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1835" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="8">3.97</rating>
<name>Guinble Kaito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guinble Kaito, along with Kinon, seems to be one of the more important members of Rossiu`s intelligence team. He and Kinon often accompany Rossiu, and stayed with him on Earth to watch out for the city while the rest of Team Dai-Gurren headed into space for their final battle against the Anti-Spirals.</description>
<picture>16418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1837" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-06-06">
<rating votes="43">5.91</rating>
<name>Amano Kazumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24550.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2134" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-03">
<rating votes="154">7.99</rating>
<name>Boota</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The unofficial mascot of Team Dai-Gurren, Boota is a small pig-mole from Giha village, whom Simon keeps as a pet. Boota is characterized by his sunglasses and star pattern surrounding his tail. No matter how many years pass, Boota`s physical appearance does not change much. Although he can`t talk, he can understand humans, and even has near-human intelligence. His favorite spots to stay are between Youko`s breasts or on Simon`s shoulder.</description>
<picture>16989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6474" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="12">4.17</rating>
<name>Aki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The neighborhood cross-dresser. A life-long resident of the Abenobashi Shopping Arcade, he is quite knowledgeable about the history of the area and its people.
He appeared in http://anidb.net/a4575 [Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann] as a Hot Spring Inn Manager (okami).</description>
<picture>137587.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6594" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="225">8.43</rating>
<name>Andou Mahoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mahoro is an android created by VESPER to fight an alien invasion by Saint in the 1980s. She is immensely powerful and fast, and is considered to be a formidable opponent by her enemies.
Being an android, she has a limited life span. At the beginning of the story, she has just 398 days to live, and is given the choice to do anything she wants by VESPER. She chooses to become a maid for Suguru Misato: his father was her superior commander, and she was forced to kill both him and an alien when the alien took him hostage.
Mahoro has a very sunny disposition and is friendly to just about everyone — she becomes a welcome regular at the market and becomes famous at Suguru`s school for working for him. She also quickly becomes an excellent cook, able to emulate and recreate dishes from the best restaurants. She is also quite devoted to Suguru, with feelings for him reminiscent of both doting mother and shy girlfriend.</description>
<picture>28703.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9221" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-06-02">
<rating votes="111">8.78</rating>
<name>Nono</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hailing from a rural community in the Martian countryside, Nono is a simple and clumsy girl with a big dream: she wants to be a space pilot. And not just any space pilot, but one to rival "Nonoriri". Of course, dreaming of being a pilot and actually becoming one are two entirely different things, as she soon finds out upon reaching the city. Even after landing a somewhat dead-end job as a waitress in one of the city`s bars, Nono stubbornly holds on to her ideals, despite the chiding of her boss and the bar`s regular patrons. Her persistence pays off, however, when she encounters a real space pilot in the person of Lal`C Melk Mark, member of the elite Fraternity and current pilot of Buster Machine Dix-Neuf. It is through Lal`C (whom she impulsively dubs her onee-sama, or big sister) that Nono finally finds the means to make her dreams a reality.
Possessing a bubbly personality and a near-endless supply of optimism, Nono seems to be a normal, if clumsy, country girl. However, Nono is anything but normal; in fact, she isn`t even human, but an android, who can`t quite remember the reason why she was built (though much of her past is revealed later in the series). She idolizes Lal`C, despite the fact that the latter seems to regard her with mild annoyance, and will do anything to please her.
Nono has trace recorded history of http://anidb.net/ch1836 [Takaya Noriko] and http://anidb.net/ch1837 [Amano Kazumi] (The pilots of Buster Machines 1 and 2) in her memory. The very person she Idolizes and wants to become is Takaya Noriko. Due to her damaged memory, Nono cannot remember Noriko`s actual name and thus pronounces it Nonoriri.</description>
<picture>2277.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="9225" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-11-15">
<rating votes="36">7.51</rating>
<name>Lal`C Mellk Mal</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The current holder of the top kill score among Topless pilots, Lal`C, along with fellow pilots Nicola and Tycho, is part of the so-called "Idol" group (pilots with exceptionally high kill rates). She is also the current pilot of Buster Machine Dix-Neuf, the oldest buster machine still in operation. Nicknamed "princess" ("hime") by her teammates, Lal`C is outwardly cool and self-confident - traits that draw Nono`s admiration for her, much to her initial annoyance. It is Lal`C who helps induct Nono (with some indirect assistance from Nicola) into the Fraternity as an "auxiliary member", despite the fact that Nono manifests none of the traits associated with being a Topless.
While initially bothered by Nono`s hero-worship of her, Lal`C gradually gets used to her company, to the point where she can talk about things she wouldn`t normally tell anyone. She senses some potential in Nono, and admires the girl`s never-give-up attitude a little (though she might act otherwise), but doubts if guts and perseverance alone can make the girl`s dreams come true.</description>
<picture>2278.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="12879" type="appears in" update="2010-04-10">
<rating votes="13">6.45</rating>
<name>Tsuuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Viral`s wife in the universe created by the Anti-Spiral`s Alternate Space Labyrinth for him.
Since his deepest desire was it to have a family but he was unable to because of his lack of spiral energy, his wish manifisted in this universe almost trapping him and the rest of Dai-Gurren-Dan.</description>
<picture>46106.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12880" type="appears in" update="2010-04-10">
<rating votes="4">4.54</rating>
<name>Memu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Viral`s daughter in the universe created by the Anti-Spiral`s Alternate Space Labyrinth for him.
Since his deepest desire was it to have a family but he was unable to because of his lack of spiral energy, his wish manifisted in this universe almost trapping him and the rest of Dai-Gurren-Dan.</description>
<picture>46107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16594" type="appears in" update="2010-04-10">
<rating votes="5">5.09</rating>
<name>Boota (Ningen Gata)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Temporary humanoid form, which appeared when Boota`s spiral energy resonated with http://anidb.net/ch1681 [Lorgenome`s].
Curiously, his "human form" appears in the prologue of the first episode. The glasses Boota has in his humanoid form are the same glasses Nono have in her http://anidb.net/ch9222 [Buster Machine No. 7 form] in the anime http://anidb.net/a2120 [Diebuster].</description>
<picture>46108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41145" type="appears in" update="2012-02-07">
<name>Sonchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayor of Giha village.</description>
<picture>81176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41146" type="appears in" update="2012-02-07">
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<name>Kamina no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamina`s father.</description>
<picture>81177.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41147" type="appears in" update="2012-02-07">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Gyuuzakku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Former juujin rider of Gurren.</description>
<picture>81178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41148" type="appears in" update="2012-02-07">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Ukomu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man who has three newly born children.</description>
<picture>81186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41149" type="appears in" update="2012-02-07">
<rating votes="2">5.93</rating>
<name>Magin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Headmaster of Adai village.</description>
<picture>81187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41262" type="appears in" update="2012-02-11">
<name>Kunba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kunba is a boy from Youko`s class.</description>
<picture>81425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="603" picture="223012.jpg">Jou Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41263" type="appears in" update="2012-02-11">
<rating votes="1">2.91</rating>
<name>Nakim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakim is a boy from Youko`s class.</description>
<picture>81427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2766" picture="181834.jpg">Mamiya Kurumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41264" type="appears in" update="2012-02-11">
<rating votes="1">1.93</rating>
<name>Maosha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maosha is a girl from Youko`s class.</description>
<picture>81428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41325" type="appears in" update="2012-02-13">
<rating votes="1">9.93</rating>
<name>Grapal (Gimmy Ki)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Gimmy`s Grapal.</description>
<picture>81534.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41326" type="appears in" update="2012-02-13">
<rating votes="2">5.35</rating>
<name>Grapal (Darry Ki)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Darry`s Grapal.</description>
<picture>81533.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="44258" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-06-06">
<rating votes="17">6.13</rating>
<name>Jung Freud</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87122.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="69171" update="2007-03-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69172" update="2007-03-29">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69679" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="70">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お前のドリルで天を突け!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pierce the Heavens with Your Drill!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Durchbrich den Himmel mit deinem Bohrer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Transpercer les cieux avec ta vrille !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Trapassa i cieli con la tua trivella</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Пронзи своим буром небеса!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omae no Drill de Ten o Tsuke!!</title>
<summary>Living underground in Giha Village, Simon and Kamina dream of a life on the surface. When their home is invaded from above, it is up to them to activate the mysterious mecha Lagann and save their village.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624247</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="69680" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="49">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺が乗るって言ってんだ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Said I`d Ride It</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ich sagte, ich werde dieses Ding steuern</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J`ai dit que c`est moi qui le piloterai !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ho detto che lo piloterò io</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">А я сказал — оседлаю!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ga Norutte Itten Da!!</title>
<summary>Now that they`ve made it to the surface, Simon and Kamina must join together with Yoko and her village to defeat the Beastmen pursuing them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624249</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="69681" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="52">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">頭が2つたぁナマイキな!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Two-Faced Son of a Bitch!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Was glaubst du, wer du bist mit deinen zwei Gesichtern?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Arrogant à deux tête !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Due Belle Facce Toste</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ты кто такой, с двумя рожами?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kao ga Futatsutaa Namaiki na!!</title>
<summary>Kamina and Simon must work together to defeat a dangerous new Beastman threat.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624251</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="69682" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="61">2.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">顔が多けりゃ偉いのか!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Does Having So Many Faces Make You Great?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auch mit vielen Gesichtern bist du kein starker Typ</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est pas le nombre de têtes qui compte !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Tante Facce Non Ti Rendono Migliore</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Если много рож — уже крутой?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kao ga Ookerya Erai no ka!?</title>
<summary>Team Gurren must work together with the eccentric Black Syblings to take down a Beastman foe on empty stomachs.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624511</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="72310" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="39">4.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺にはさっぱり判らねえ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Don`t Understand It at All!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ich versteh das überhaupt nicht!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sérieux, je pige que dalle a tout ça !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Proprio Non Riesco a Capire!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мне этого не понять!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ni wa Sappari Wakaranee!</title>
<summary>Team Gurren must find their way out of a strange underground village where they worship Gunmen as divine beings.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624513</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="72629" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="43">5.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">てめえら全員湯あたりしやがれ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All of You Bastards Put Us in Hot Water!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Es gibt ein paar Dinge, die ich unbedingt sehen muß!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Quel Che Voglio Vedere lo Voglio Vedere</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Всё скрытое должно быть открыто!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Temeera Zen`in Yuatari Shiyagare!!</title>
<summary>Continuing to the Gunmen rallying point, Team Gurren finds themselves on a strange hot springs getaway.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624515</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="72630" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="37">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それはお前がやるんだよ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`ll Be the One To Do That!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Du wirst es machen!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cette fois, c`est toi qui va te charger du boulot</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Di Questo Te ne Occuperai Tu!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Это сделаешь... ты!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Omae ga Yarunda yo!!</title>
<summary>Thymilph, one of the Four Divine Generals of the mysterious Spiral King, arrives to support Viral`s Enki, with the massive mobile Gunmen fortress, the Dai-Ganzan. Kamina and Simon pilot the Gurren-Lagann against seemingly overwhelming odds.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624867</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73552" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="63">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あばよ, ダチ公</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell Comrades!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Später, Kumpel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu mon frère</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Addio, Amici Miei</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Счастливо, братцы!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abayo, Dachikou</title>
<summary>Having temporarily stalled Viral and Thymilph in the last skirmish, the Team Gurren and their newly arrived allies join forces as "Team Dai-Gurren" and launch a decisive strike against the regrouping Gunmen force.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624869</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73553" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="32">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒトっていったい何ですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Just What Exactly Is a Human?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Was genau ist ein Mensch?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Qu`est-ce exactement un homme ?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Che Cosa Significa la Parola "Persona"?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Что значит «человек»?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitotte Ittai Nandesuka?</title>
<summary>Team Dai-Gurren is still mourning on Kamina`s death. Simon notices a Gunman throw a capsule into a deep valley. He inspects it and is able to open it, and inside is a human girl named Nia, but their introduction is cut short when an enemy Gunman appears.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624871</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73714" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="28">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニキっていったい誰ですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who Really Was Your Big Brother?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wer ist dieser Bruder?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`était quoi comme genre de type, ton frangin ?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Chi era la persona che chiami "fratello"?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">«Братан» — это кто?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anikitte Ittai Dare Desuka?</title>
<summary>Having been temporarily spared by Adiane, another of the Four Divine Generals, Team Dai-Gurren uses the reprieve to reassess their situation. Nia learns of Kamina`s significance in Simon`s erratic behavior and offers him some stinging, yet honest advice, which draws the ire of an untrusting Yoko. With tension building within the Team, the crew scrambles to stand by Nia`s side when Adiane returns to complete her stalled attack.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>625263</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="74421" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="39">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シモン, 手をどけて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Simon, Please Remove Your Hand</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Simon, Hände Weg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retire ta main, Simon !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Simon, togli le mani</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Симон, убери руки!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Simon, Te o Dokete</title>
<summary>Team Dai-Gurren falls into a trap set by the third member of the Four Divine Generals, Guame. The Team is taken captive and stored underground to await execution. While digging an escape path, Simon finally understands Kamina`s last words to him and after having a discussion with Guame, Nia finds out the reason why she was thrown away.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>625265</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="74425" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="27">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヨーコさん, お願いがあります</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Youko-san, I Have Something to Ask of You</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Yoko, tust du mir einen Gefallen?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mademoiselle Yoko, j`ai une faveur à vous demander</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Yoko, mi faresti un favore?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ёко, сделайте одолжение!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youko-san, Onegai ga Arimasu</title>
<summary>On their way to Teppelin, the Beastmen`s capital city, Team Dai-Gurren stumbles upon a vast ocean and must wait for modifications on the Dai-Gurren to be completed before crossing it. While the rest of the group play at the beach, Yoko starts to feel uneasy about Nia and all the attention she gets from them. After preparations are complete, Team Dai-Gurren begins their sea cruise, oblivious to the fact that an ambush is underway by Adiane and Viral.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>625267</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="74426" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="27">8.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みなさん, たーんと召しあがれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everybody, Eat to Your Heart`s Content</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aufessen, alle Mann!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bon appétit à tous !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ragazzi, mangiate a volontà!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Господа, налетайте на еду!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minasan, Taanto Meshiagare</title>
<summary>Trying to do her part in Team Dai-Gurren, Nia decides to become a cook, but just before the crew have a taste of her dishes, Cytomander, the fourth member of the Divine Generals, launches an aerial attack on the Dai-Gurren. Simon leads the counter-attack on the Gurren-Lagann, this time accompanied by Yoko, who replaces a sick Rossiu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>625615</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75112" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="28">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">皆さん, ごきげんよう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Are You, Everyone?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gut getroffen, Leute</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ravie de faire votre connaissance</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Salve, ragazzi</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Приветствую, друзья!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mina-san, Gokigenyou</title>
<summary>At last, Team Dai-Gurren arrives at the outskirts of Teppelin, but before aiming to the city, they must face a combined full-scale attack of Cytomander and Guame`s forces.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>625617</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75113" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="40">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私は明日へ向かいます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Head Towards Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ich werde in die Zukunft aufbrechen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je vais affronter mon avenir</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Io andrò incontro al domani!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Я пойду навстречу новому дню</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi wa Ashita e Mukaimasu</title>
<summary>The last of the Divine Generals fall, and the city of Teppelin collapses, revealing a Gunman of gigantic proportions. Simon and Nia struggle to pass through it in order to confront her father, the Spiral King himself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>625619</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="79637" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="29">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聞かせてもらうぞ この世界の謎を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Make You Tell the Truth of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verrat mir die Geheimnisse dieser Welt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Expliquez-moi les énigmes de ce monde</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Svelami i segreti di questo mondo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Поведай мне секреты этого мира</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikasete Morauzo Kono Sekai no Nazo o</title>
<summary>After the Anti-Spirals` first attack and Nia`s astonishing announcement, Simon looks desperately for her, while Rossiu finally completes his secret project.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>626279</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="79638" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="31">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたは何も分かってない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Understand Nothing</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Du weißt überhaupt nichts</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vous n`avez rien compris ou quoi ?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Tu non capisci proprio nulla!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ты не понимаешь абсолютно ничего</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata wa Nani mo Wakattenai</title>
<summary>During the following seven years, a new civilization rises and prospers under Simon`s leadership. However, these peaceful times come to end when the threat mentioned in Lordgenome`s last words starts to reveal itself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>626277</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="79639" recap="true" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="35">2.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">総集片</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summary Episode</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zusammenfassung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Polysynthèse complète</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Episodio riassuntivo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Меганарезка!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushuuhen</title>
<summary>A recap of the story`s events, as of episode 15.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>626275</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80303" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="29">8.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生き残るんだ どんな手段を使っても</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Must Survive. No Matter What It Takes!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wir werden überleben, koste es, was es wolle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nous devons survivre, peu importe les moyens à employer</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Noi tutti sopravviveremo, con ogni mezzo!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мы должны спастись во что бы то ни стало</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikinokorunda Donna Shudan o Tsukatte mo</title>
<summary>To soothe the public opinion, Rossiu overthrows Simon and puts him under arrest. But when the Anti-Spirals launch a large-scale attack on Kamina City, he is left with no option but to let Simon engage the enemy using the Gurren-Lagann, not before resorting to extremes to put him under his control.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>626629</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80949" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="28">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神はどこまで僕らをためす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh God, To How Far Will You Test Us?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wie lange will Gott uns noch prüfen?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dieu, jusqu`où irez-vous pour nous tester ?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fino a che punto Dio ci metterà alla prova?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Сколько ещё нас ждёт Господних испытаний?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami wa Doko made Bokura o Tamesu</title>
<summary>As Simon arrives in prison, he unexpectedly meets Viral, who comments on how far he has fallen. Meanwhile, the truth about Rossiu`s emergency plan and the consequences for those left behind on Earth are revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>626631</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80950" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="30">8.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたは生き残るべき人だ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Must Survive</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Du bist jemand, der überleben sollte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vous devriez être la dernière personne à survivre !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Tu sei tra le persone che devono sopravvivere</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Вы — человек, который обязан выжить</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata wa Ikinokorubeki Hito Da</title>
<summary>One year earlier, Yoko starts working as a schoolteacher on an island until she learns of the situation at Teppelin and returns to break Simon free. Once again reunited, Simon and the members of Team Dai-Gurren launch themselves into space to protect the Arc-Gurren from the enemy forces, now accompanied by Viral as co-pilot of the Gurren-Lagann.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>626633</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80951" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="33">9.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それが僕の最後の義務だ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And to Space</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Dies ist mein letzter Dienst</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est ma dernière responsabilité</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Questo è il mio ultimo dovere</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Это мой последний долг</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore ga Boku no Saigo no Gimu Da</title>
<summary>The Gurren-Lagann and the Arc-Gurren join together to form the massive Arc-Gurren-Lagann and stop the Human Annihilation System.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627525</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81106" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="28">8.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">行くぞ 最後の戦いだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go, The Final Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vorwärts, dies ist die finale Schlacht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En route pour le combat final</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Andiamo! Questa è l`ultima battaglia!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Вперёд, навстречу главной победе!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikuzo Saigo no Takakai Da</title>
<summary>The members of Team Dai-Gurren make their preparations for the imminent war against the Anti-Spirals, but Rossiu is missing. However, when Kinon tells Simon about what he really intends to do, both start to look desperately for him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627527</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81107" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="33">8.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忘れるものか この一分一秒を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Will Never Forget, This Minute and Second</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ich vergesse niemals diese Minute, diese Sekunde</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je n`oublierai jamais cette minute, cette seconde !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Non potrò mai dimenticare questo preciso momento!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Это мгновение будет со мной всегда!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wasureru Mono ka Kono Ippun Ichibyou o</title>
<summary>Guided by Simon and Nia`s feelings for each other, Team Dai-Gurren break through dimensions in search for the Anti-Spirals` homeworld. But after falling into the enemy`s trap, they end up losing some of their most precious members, due to its vicious offensive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627529</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82568" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="41">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お前の遺志は受け取った</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Accept Your Dying Wish!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ich akzeptiere deinen letzten Wunsch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Que ta dernière volonté soit respectée !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sarò io a compiere le tue ultime volontà!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Я исполню твою последнюю волю!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omae no Ishi wa Uketotta!</title>
<summary>Team Dai-Gurren struggles to escape from the ocean of despair created by the Anti-Spirals without success, until history repeats itself, as another irreplaceable member of the Team sacrifices himself to save the others.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>628017</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82986" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="40">9.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">行くぜ ダチ公</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go, Comrades!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vorwärts, Kumpel!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En avant camarades !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Andiamo, compagni!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Идём, братцы!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikuze Dachikou</title>
<summary>After finally transforming their flagship into the Super Galactic Gurren-Lagann, Simon and his friends successfully fight back against the enemy. When their enemy starts to use their own memories and desires against them, Kamina reappears to help.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>628019</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="83002" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="56">9.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天の光はすべて星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All the Lights in the Sky are Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Lichter im Himmel sind Sterne</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La piste des étoiles</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Tutte le luci in cielo sono stelle</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Все эти огни в небе — звёзды...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ten no Hikari wa Subete Hoshi</title>
<summary>At last, Simon and Nia are reunited, and by combining the power of its members, Team Dai-Gurren creates the galaxy-sized Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann, and engage the Anti-Spiral threat in a decisive battle to determine the fate of the universe.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>628021</identifier>
<identifier>gurren-lagann</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85239" update="2018-07-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85240" update="2018-07-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85241" update="2018-07-28">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85242" update="2018-07-28">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85243" update="2018-07-28">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85244" update="2018-07-28">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88846" update="2018-12-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見てえものは見てえんだ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll See What I Wanna See!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans la vie, y`a des occases qu`un mec peut pas rater !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Всё скрытое должно быть открыто!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitee Mono wa Miteenda!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118280" update="2015-01-01">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136398" update="2012-06-19">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227549" update="2020-03-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>23</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
