<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4576" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>18</episodecount>
<startdate>1989-04-15</startdate>
<enddate>1989-09-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ranma 1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-unk" type="synonym">Ranma ½</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Ранма 1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ranma</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">らんま1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ranma 1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Ranma 1/2 (Teil 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ranma 1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Ranma 1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Ranma 1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">란마 1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">ينبوع الأحلام</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Ranma 1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Ranma 1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">ראנמה 1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">亂馬1/2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">乱马1/2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="193" type="Sequel">Ranma 1/2 Nettou Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="377" approval="40" total="44">Urusei Yatsura</anime>
<anime id="288" approval="4" total="7">Maison Ikkoku</anime>
<anime id="806" approval="3" total="5">Yawara! A Fashionable Judo Girl</anime>
<anime id="5625" approval="2" total="8">To Love-Ru: Trouble</anime>
<anime id="144" approval="2" total="5">Inuyasha</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="403846">The first season was awesome! 10/10. But at following seasons it gets kinda boring and old due to the lack of character development. Anyway, first season was amazing and must see for every comedy fan.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="401067">Ranma 1/2 is mild anime, this is specially good for those who are new to anime, it has humor, a funny and interesting setup, good character design with a taste of martial arts. totally recommended. the first season is more interesting than the rest, probably because the whole thing is still new for the viewer, but never the less you can watch an episode now and then and it will always be interesting.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="1419" type="Character Design">Nakajima Atsuko</name>
<name id="818" type="Original Work">Takahashi Rumiko</name>
<name id="4229" type="Direction">Shibayama Tsutomu</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="500" type="Direction">Mochizuki Tomomi</name>
<name id="3719" type="Series Composition">Inoue Toshiki</name>
<name id="4243" type="Series Composition">Urasawa Yoshio</name>
<name id="970" type="Work">Kitty Film</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="7090" type="Music">Mori Hideharu</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7247 [Saotome Ranma] and his father, http://anidb.net/ch7339 [Genma], fell into cursed springs during a journey to China. As a result, whenever Ranma comes into contact with cold water, he turns into a girl; when the same thing happens to Genma, he becomes a panda. Wheneven that happens, they stay in their alternative form until the process is reversed by hot water. And if that wasn`t bad enough, Ranma has a bigger problem to deal with: his father and http://anidb.net/ch7371 [Tendou Souun] decide to marry Ranma to the youngest daughter of the Tendou household, http://anidb.net/ch7338 [Akane], so that the two can eventually take over her family`s dojo. Meanwhile, the youngsters are less than thrilled about this forced engagement...
Note: Ranma 1/2 was canceled due to poor ratings, and was taken off the air to be retooled. It was relaunched as http://anidb.net/a193 [Ranma 1/2 Nettou Hen] with some changes in staff. Furthermore, the US release shuffled the episodes around to bring it more in line with the manga.
Note 2: The aired timeline differs from the timeline that was originally intended for this and http://anidb.net/a193 [Ranma 1/2 Nettou Hen]. The intended order for the episodes to be viewed is: http://anidb.net/a4576 [Ranma 1/2] 1-13, http://anidb.net/a193 [Ranma 1/2 Nettou Hen] 7-9, http://anidb.net/a4576 [Ranma 1/2] 14-18, http://anidb.net/a193 [Ranma 1/2 Nettou Hen] 1-6, http://anidb.net/a193 [Ranma 1/2 Nettou Hen] 10-End</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2657">6.99</permanent>
<temporary count="2683">7.67</temporary>
<review count="2">8.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>4937.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>64</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>210</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.viz.com/anime/streaming/ranma</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>らんま1/2#.E3.82.89.E3.82.93.E3.81.BE1.2F2.EF.BC.88.E7.AC.AC1.E6.9C.9F.EF.BC.89</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3033</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89161</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1449</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="659" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-17">
<name>dojo</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1783" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>immature</name>
<description>Marked by or indicating a lack of maturity</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3550" parentid="6021" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-05">
<name>sex change</name>
<description>Someone in this anime has his/her body changed to the opposite gender.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4722" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>omiai</name>
<description>One character promised to marry another one, either by free will (read: love), or due to external interference e.g. by parental "guidance".
This can be a comedy element, especially if both parties are less than thrilled by the prospect of marriage. There is also potential for embarrassment-related humour concerning the emotional interaction between the newly weds.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7247" type="main character in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="295">8.00</rating>
<name>Saotome Ranma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranma, the only son of Genma and Nodoka Saotome, was taken from his home by his father when approximately 2 years old, to begin a 13-14-year training trip to perfect his skills in the martial arts.
Later, near the end of the trip, Genma took Ranma to a training ground in China named Jusenkyo that few people used, due to the springs being cursed. Falling into them would transform a person into whatever first fell in. Not knowing this, and not having the patience to listen to a warning from the local guide, Genma attempted to train with Ranma atop the bamboo poles which jutted up out of the pools. When Ranma knocked Genma into Shonmaoniichuan/"Spring of `Drowned` Panda", he was surprised to watch a panda emerge from the pond and leap onto one of the poles. Genma, now cursed, was able to hit a surprised Ranma into Nyannichuan, or the "Spring of `Drowned` Girl". Thus he turns into a female version of his original form when splashed with cold water, which is only temporarily reversible through contact with hot water.</description>
<picture>30262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7338" type="main character in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="272">6.21</rating>
<name>Tendou Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7339" type="main character in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="79">3.53</rating>
<name>Saotome Genma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7371" type="main character in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="55">3.83</rating>
<name>Tendou Souun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3383" picture="24325.jpg">Oobayashi Ryuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7372" type="main character in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="122">6.55</rating>
<name>Tendou Nabiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7373" type="main character in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="127">8.31</rating>
<name>Tendou Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7449" type="main character in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="404">8.31</rating>
<name>Saotome Ranma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He turns into a female version of his original form when splashed with cold water, which is only (temporarily) reversible through contact with hot water.</description>
<picture>26086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7456" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="83">4.38</rating>
<name>Kunou Tatewaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7457" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="81">2.90</rating>
<name>Kunou Kodachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2055" picture="21393.jpg">Shimazu Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7458" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="10">5.59</rating>
<name>Ono Toufuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26158.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3270" picture="30153.jpg">Mitsuya Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7459" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="139">6.68</rating>
<name>Hibiki Ryouga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7460" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-29">
<rating votes="212">8.41</rating>
<name>Shampoo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7491" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-28">
<rating votes="58">5.91</rating>
<name>P-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryouga turns into a piglet when he gets into contact with cold water.</description>
<picture>26142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7651" type="appears in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="12">4.41</rating>
<name>Jusenkyou Guide</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7662" type="main character in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="90">6.34</rating>
<name>Saotome Genma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Genma turns into a panda when he gets into contact with cold water.</description>
<picture>26530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12938" type="appears in" update="2009-11-13">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Zen-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38686.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12939" type="appears in" update="2009-11-13">
<rating votes="2">4.43</rating>
<name>Atsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38687.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12940" type="appears in" update="2009-11-13">
<rating votes="4">2.08</rating>
<name>Baa-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38688.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12941" type="appears in" update="2009-11-13">
<rating votes="4">3.18</rating>
<name>Bess</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38689.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12998" type="appears in" update="2009-11-13">
<rating votes="2">2.33</rating>
<name>Ono Kin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1828" picture="20727.jpg">Oota Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="51999" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">中国から来たあいつ! ちょっとヘン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strange Stranger from China</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein ungewöhnliches Mädchen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un bien étrange garçon</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Che strani tipi sono arrivati dalla Cina...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-other">Here`s Ranma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chuugoku kara Kita Aitsu! Chotto Hen!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52000" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遊びじゃないのよ学校は</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Is No Place for Horsing Around</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Sprung ins kalte Wasser</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Premier pour l`école</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La scuola non è un parco di divertimenti!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asobi ja Nai no yo Gakkou wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52001" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いきなり愛の嵐 ちょっと待ってョ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Sudden Storm of Love... Hey, Wait a Minute!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebe liegt in der Luft</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Coup de foudre ou coup de guerre</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una tempesta d`amore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikinari Ai no Arashi: Chotto Matte yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52002" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乱馬とらんま? 誤解がとまらない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ranma and... Ranma? If It`s Not One Thing, It`s Another</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verwirrter Kuno</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Julian s`interroge</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ranma e Ranma: Le incomprensioni continuano</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ranma to Ranma? Gokai ga Tomaranai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52003" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">骨まで愛して? あかね恋の複雑骨折</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Me to the Bone! The Compound Fracture of Akane`s Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein tolles Versprechen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adeline et Ranma sont en froid</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ami tutto di me?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hone made Aishite? Akane Koi no Fukuzatsu Kossetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52004" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あかねの失恋 だってしょうがないじゃない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akane`s Lost Love... These Things Happen, You Know</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gebrochene Herzen und verstauchte Hälse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chagrin d`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Cuore infranto per Akane</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akane no Shitsuren: Datte Shou ga Nai ja Nai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52005" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">登場! 永遠の迷い子・良牙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter Ryoga, the Eternal "Lost Boy"</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Planlos!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Roland, ou celui qui ne trouve jamais son chemin</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ryoga, l`eterno disperso</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Entre Ryoga! O Eterno Garoto Perdido</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toujou! Eien no Mayoigo Ryouga</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52006" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学校は戦場だ! 対決乱馬VS良牙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Is a Battlefield! Ranma vs. Ryoga</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine haarige Sache</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ranma contre Roland</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ranma contro Ryoga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakkou wa Senjou Da! Taiketsu Ranma Tai Ryouga</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52007" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙女白書・髪は女のいのちなの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Confessions! A Girl`s Hair Is Her Life!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ryogas Verwandlung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La nouvelle coiffure d`Adeline</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un brutto taglio di capelli</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome Hakusho: Kami wa Onna no Inochi na no</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52008" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピーピーPちゃん ろくなもんじゃねェ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">P-P-P-chan! He`s Good for Nothin`</title>
<title xml:lang="de">So ein kleines Ferkel!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le petit cochon malicieux</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Non te ne va bene una, Pi-Chan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">P-P-P-chan: Rokuna Mon Janee</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52009" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乱馬を激愛! 新体操のスケバン登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ranma Meets Love Head-On! Enter the Delinquent Juvenile Gymnast!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die schwarze Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le coup de foudre</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un amore per Ranma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ranma o Gekiai! Shintaisou no Sukeban Toujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52010" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女の恋は戦争よ! 格闘新体操でいざ勝負</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Woman`s Love Is War! The Martial Arts Rhythmic Gymnastics Challenge!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kampf um Ranma</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La rose noire aime bien piquer</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il giorno del torneo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna no Koi wa Sensou yo! Kakutou Shintaisou de Iza Shoubu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52011" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スケバンの目に涙? ルール無用の格闘新体操決着</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Tear in a Girl-Delinquent`s Eye? The End of the Martial Arts Rhythmic Gymnastics Challenge</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Kampf mit allen Mitteln</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La revanche</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Le lacrime di Kodachi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sukeban no Me ni Namida? Rule Muyou no Kakutou Shintaisou Kecchaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52012" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">骨盤占い! らんまは日本一のお嫁さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pelvic Fortune-Telling? Ranma Is the No. One Bride in Japan</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine Braut für Dr. Tofu</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`heureuse élue</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una fidanzata per il dottor Tofu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotsuban Uranai! Ranma wa Nippon`ichi no Oyome-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52013" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激烈少女シャンプー登場! ワタシ命あずけます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter Shampoo, the Gung-Ho Girl! I Put My Life in Your Hands</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Amazone Shampoo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Disparais ou épouse-moi !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`arrivo di Shampoo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekiretsu Shoujo Shampoo Toujou! Watashi Inochi Azukemasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52014" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャンプーの反撃 必殺指圧拳は身も心も奪う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shampoo`s Revenge! The Shiatsu Technique That Steals Heart and Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kopfwäsche mit Folgen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La revanche de Bambou</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La rivincita di Shampoo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shampoo no Hangeki: Hissatsu Shiatsuken wa Mi mo Kokoro mo Ubau</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52015" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乱馬大好き! さよならはいわないで!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Love You, Ranma! Please Don`t Say Goodbye</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Her mit dem Shampoo!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les adieux de Bambou</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ranma, ti amo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ranma Daisuki! Sayonara wa Iwanaide!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52016" recap="true" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレは男だ! らんま中国へ帰る?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am a Man! Ranma`s Going Back to China!?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zurück nach China</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ranma et la Chine</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ranma torna in Cina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore wa Otoko Da! Ranma Chuugoku e Kaeru?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102695" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1989-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102696" update="2013-07-09">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1989-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102697" update="2013-07-09">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1989-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102698" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1989-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
