<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="458" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2003-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mahou Tsukai ni Taisetsu na Koto</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Somedays Dreamers</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Нечто важное для мага [ТВ-1]</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mahoutsukai ni Taisetsu na Koto</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Важливе для чарівника</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">MTK</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Yume Mahou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mtntnk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mttk</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">魔法遣いに大切なこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Someday`s Dreamers</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">حالمو في يوم ما</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">魔法使的條件</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5830" type="Same Setting">Mahou Tsukai ni Taisetsu na Koto: Natsu no Sora</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11469" approval="5" total="7">Flying Witch</anime>
<anime id="5975" approval="4" total="10">Toaru Majutsu no Index</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="456964">peaceful and beautiful life of the beginner magician`s.

very good to cure hurting heart, with peaceful ost .

and the ed "the indigo - under the blue sky" is awsome</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="208300">Very beautiful, care-free anime. Recommended watch if you like fuwa fuwa marshmellows.
8.5/10</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.jcstaff.co.jp/sho-sai/maho-shokai/maho-story.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="105" type="Character Design">Chiba Michinori</name>
<name id="8464" type="Original Work">Yamada Norie</name>
<name id="8463" type="Original Work">Yoshizuki Kumichi</name>
<name id="4138" type="Direction">Shimoda Masami</name>
<name id="4666" type="Music">Haketa Takefumi</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="923" type="Animation Work">View Works</name>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="8464" type="Original Plan">Yamada Norie</name>
<name id="7159" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawashima Keiko</name>
</creators>
<description>Based in the present day Tokyo, there exist people known as Mahou Tsukai (people who use magic or "Mages"). But, even though there`s magic around, there`s not much difference from the world we live in.
http://anidb.net/ch19558 [Kikuchi Yume] is a 17 year old 2nd year senior high school student. So that she can officially become a Mage, Yume makes use of her summer break and leaves for the capital from Tooya in the Iwate prefecture. It`s the first time she`s been to Tokyo. First time she`s been to a boarding house. And she was thinking that it`ll be an all girl`s place too but in fact, the manager`s a charming male. Caught in a mix of anxiety and great anticipation, Yume`s training in magic begins.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1874">5.82</permanent>
<temporary count="1880">7.25</temporary>
<review count="8">8.47</review>
</ratings>
<picture>222405.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1372</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>273</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1132</identifier>
<identifier>ixuwcv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jcstaff.co.jp/sho-sai/maho-shokai/maho-story.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Someday's_Dreamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>魔法遣いに大切なこと#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E7.AC.AC1.E4.BD.9C</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239954</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5713</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/101</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2003/mahotai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8265</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="569" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-18">
<name>clumsy</name>
<description>A clumsy person is one lacking in coordination, and as such prone to often having accidents such as tripping, bumping into objects, or dropping things. In female characters, this is often thought of as endearing.</description>
<picurl>63355.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2461" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>domestic cat</name>
<description>The cat (Felis catus or Felis silvestris catus), also known as the domestic cat to distinguish it from other felines and felids, is a small, usually furry, domesticated, and carnivorous mammal. Cats are valued by humans for companionship and their ability to hunt vermin and household pests, and are often kept as indoor pets, in which case they are also called housecats; they have been associated with humans for at least 9,500 years and are currently the most popular pet in the world, being found almost everywhere on Earth.
Cats are similar in anatomy to the other felids, with light, strong and flexible bodies, excellent hearing, sense of smell, and near darkness eyesight, quick reflexes, sharp retractable claws, and teeth adapted to killing small prey. They are skilled predators and hunt over 1,000 species for food. Despite being solitary hunters, cats are a social species, with communication means that include pheromones, body language and a variety of vocalizations, such as meowing, purring, trilling, hissing, growling and grunting.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>41283.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3135" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>hero complex</name>
<description>A hero complex is a state of mind in which an individual believes they need to save or assist others, uphold morals, serve justice, or perform other such supposedly hero-like acts, often at any cost. That is a common trait among vigilantes. Those with a hero complex may feel personally accountable for any failure at those self-assigned duties. Their main concern is performing their supposedly heroic deeds; any questions others might raise about such actions are all secondary concerns at best. Such questions can include, but are not limited to: who is to be saved; what are they to be saved from; why are they being saved; whether or not the other person needs or wants to be saved at all; whether or not others share in the sense of morals and justice being upheld; how people feel about the so-called heroic actions; whether people feel like those actions are being forced down their throats; what negative effects can arise from such actions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3931" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-27">
<name>magical realism</name>
<description>Magical realism is fiction that portrays magical or unreal elements as a natural part in an otherwise realistic or mundane environment, in particular when a highly detailed, realistic setting is invaded by something too strange to believe. Magical realism is often associated with Latin American literature, particularly authors including Gabriel García Márquez and Isabel Allende.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="19549" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Zennosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19550" type="main character in" update="2012-03-14">
<rating votes="4">5.07</rating>
<name>Angela Charon Brooks</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19551" type="appears in" update="2012-03-14">
<name>Katou Gou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4917" picture="10660.gif">Iida Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19552" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-14">
<rating votes="1">5.70</rating>
<name>Furusaki Rikiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19553" type="main character in" update="2012-03-14">
<rating votes="2">6.68</rating>
<name>Oyamada Masami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19554" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Sachiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19555" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Kikuchi Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="568" picture="65531.jpg">Sakuma Kumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19556" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<name>Kikuchi Etsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153306.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5073" picture="33047.jpg">Sasaki Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19557" type="appears in" update="2017-01-03">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Kikuchi Haru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153307.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19558" type="main character in" update="2010-07-13">
<rating votes="7">5.45</rating>
<name>Kikuchi Yume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kikuchi Yume, a girl who can use magic, goes to Tokyo to be an apprentice mage to the handsome Masami Oyamada (a professional mage). In Tokyo, Yume learns about magic, helping people, and various other things on her way to being a mage. but she soon also finds out that even just magic alone isnt enough to make someone truly happy...</description>
<picture>12214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15650" picture="44736.jpg">Miyazaki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19559" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Kikuchi Isaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19560" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-14">
<rating votes="1">5.70</rating>
<name>Endou Kouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42412" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-14">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Iwashita Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42413" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-14">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Ginpun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74236" type="appears in" update="2015-03-31">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Iwanaga Junko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>171168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="62" picture="16663.jpg">Kurumado Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5291" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夕焼けと鉄骨・前篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunset &amp; a Steel Frame: Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuyake to Tekkotsu: Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5486" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夕焼けと鉄骨・後篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunset &amp; a Steel Frame: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuyake to Tekkotsu: Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5570" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最高のニュース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Greatest News</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikou no News</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5636" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の夜と魔法遣い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Summer Night &amp; a Mage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Yoru to Mahou Tsukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5783" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エプロンとシャンパン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Apron &amp; Champagne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Apron to Champagne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6016" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法遣いになりたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Become a Mage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou Tsukai ni Naritai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6082" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法遣いになれなかった魔法遣い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Mage Who Couldn`t Become a Mage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou Tsukai ni Narenakatta Mahou Tsukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6207" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋のバカヂカラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enormous Power in the Name of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Bakajikara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6365" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユメと少女と夏の種</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yume, the Girl &amp; a Seed of Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume to Shoujo to Natsu no Tane</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6444" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法の行方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magic`s Whereabouts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou no Yukue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6558" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">折れてしまった虹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Broken Rainbow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orete Shimatta Niji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6559" update="2011-08-06">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法遣いに大切なこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Things Important to a Mage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou Tsukai ni Taisetsu na Koto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15210" update="2011-05-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2003-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Under the Blue Sky Video Clip</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40883" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46540" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150195" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV3 15s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150196" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2 15s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150197" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1 15s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154836" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宮﨑あおいインタビュー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Miyazaki Aoi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miyazaki Aoi Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154837" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">中野正貴 フォトセッション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Photo Session</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154838" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154839" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154840" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宫崎あおいコメント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Comments from Miyazaki Aoi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miyazaki Aoi Comment</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154842" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Single and OST CMs</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
