<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4583" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-01-05</startdate>
<enddate>2007-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kyoushirou to Towa no Sora</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">京四郎と永遠の空</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kyoushirou and the Eternal Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kyoshiro and the Eternal Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kyoshiro to Towa no Sora</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">京四郎和永远的天空</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kttns</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">京四郎と永遠(とわ)の空</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shattered Angels</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">쿄시로와 영원의 하늘</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ศึกนางฟ้าเหนือมนุษย์</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2142" type="Character">Kannazuki no Miko</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="543946">Not a big deal , u get bored after the 1st episode</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kyoshiro-sora.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="794" type="Animation Work">TNK</name>
<name id="3656" type="Series Composition">Uetake Sumio</name>
<name id="6517" type="Original Work">Kaishaku</name>
<name id="6445" type="Direction">Yanagisawa Tetsuya</name>
<name id="6242" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujii Maki</name>
<name id="4441" type="Music">Kubota Mina</name>
<name id="6242" type="Character Design">Fujii Maki</name>
</creators>
<description>Ten years have passed since the most serious crisis of mankind occurred. The story takes place in the huge academic city — Academia — symbol of the recovery.
The main character, http://anidb.net/ch4508 [Shiratori Kuu], is a high school girl, who enjoys school life, but thinks her routine life is empty. She sometimes has a recurring dream though, a dream in which she encounters a prince. And while all the students are preparing for the school festival, the prince from her dream appears in reality. And just like in her dream, the prince — http://anidb.net/ch4509 [Ayanokouji Kyoushirou] — asks her: "Come with me..."
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="862">2.95</permanent>
<temporary count="880">6.06</temporary>
<review count="3">5.44</review>
</ratings>
<picture>11750.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6809</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2911</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1810</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3813</identifier>
<identifier>qwhvph</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kyoshiro-sora.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shattered_Angels</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>京四郎と永遠の空</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>985</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326162</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8738</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>京四郎與永遠的空</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4508" type="main character in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="10">3.84</rating>
<name>Shiratori Kuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuu is quite the normal high school girl who feels as if she is drifting through her existence and she always describes herself as being "empty". She never misses a chance to give letters to the mysterious prince in her dreams and frequently talks to him in her thoughts. In reality she is an introverted girl, believing that she lacks good qualities. She appears to be easily overwhelmed by situations that deviate from her previous experiences and expectations.
Her original name is Cielo, meaning sky, who is the original Absolute Angel researched by Kazuya and his grandfather. During the incident ten years prior to the main story, Cielo is split into four pieces, Murakumo, Batraz, Claíomh Solais and Megingjord. In addition, Megingjord is separated into two pieces. Kuu is the original body, while Valteishia is the soul; this explains Kuu`s initial feelings that she is lacking something inside.</description>
<picture>20596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4509" type="main character in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="5">4.76</rating>
<name>Ayanokouji Kyoushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyoshiro is instantly likened by Kuu to the prince in her dreams when he transfers to Kuu`s school from the legendary Joutou Academy. He is a refined gentleman, adept in horseback riding, and has a tendency to play the violin while deep in thought. Kyoshiro is the youngest of the four children in his family. He supports the Central Student Government and has also stated his intention to recover and destroy all of the Absolute Angels, following what he believes to be the wishes of his deceased brother, Kazuya.</description>
<picture>20597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4510" type="main character in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="8">6.12</rating>
<name>Setsuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also known as "Setsuna of the Moment of Dreams," is the Absolute Angel Claíomh Solais (Kurau Sorasu). She fights alongside Kyoshiro as his partner. Setsuna treasures a ribbon bow with bells, which is given to her by Kyoshiro and tied to the right side of her headdress. Rarely expressing any emotion, she is physically beautiful and can carry out every household chore flawlessly, leading Kuu to call her a "princess". Setsuna acts solely based on Kyoshiro`s orders and wishes, not her own will, and has a habit of saying, "Would you prefer that, Kyoshiro?" She begins to grow jealous of Kyoshiro and Kuu`s closeness, but she holds back her feelings so as to not trouble Kyoshiro.</description>
<picture>20598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4511" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-25">
<rating votes="11">8.16</rating>
<name>Kaon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also known as "Kaon of the Lunar Spiral," is the Absolute Angel Murakumo (a reference to the mecha/deity Ame no Murakamo from Kannazuki no Miko.) A student from the Higashigetsu Fuuma Witch Academy, she stages attacks on Kuu and her friends by order of Mika, although she does not seem to feed on the energy of innocent bystanders as Tarlotte does. Himiko usually appears with her. Despite the fact that she is Mika`s sword, she harbours a deep affection for Himiko, although she initially denies that their relationship is of a romantic nature.</description>
<picture>20599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4512" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-25">
<rating votes="6">5.78</rating>
<name>Himiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Himiko adheres closely to Kaon and is one of Mika`s many lovers, although the relationship is not romantic; rather, Himiko is Mika`s subordinate in all things, with Mika using her as she sees fit. Himiko has even mentioned that her name was `assigned` to her by Mika. She is based on the character Himeko Kurusugawa from Kannazuki no Miko and has been said to be Himeko`s reincarnation. She certainly initially seems to display Himeko`s lack of self-confidence and strong emotional bond with Chikane`s counterpart, Kaon.</description>
<picture>20600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4513" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="5">2.71</rating>
<name>Ayanokouji Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The ruler of the Higashigetsu Fuuma Witch Academy, who is setting forth the domination of all the female students through her right hand, Kaon. She displays signs of jealousy fueled by possessiveness when observing Himiko providing Kaon with energy, and apparently has a vindictive streak, as she punishes those of her subordinates who fail her.</description>
<picture>20601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4514" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="5">5.00</rating>
<name>Tarlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also known as "Tarlotte of the Aligned Planets," is the Absolute Angel Batraz (Badorasu). Her anger lays waste to all who stand before her, but she has a childish personality and mind to go with her childish body. Tarlotte frequently has trouble finding the right words to express herself.</description>
<picture>20602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="427" picture="47184.jpg">Mochizuki Hisayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4515" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="4">3.40</rating>
<name>Ayanokouji Soujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second eldest child of the Ayanokouji family. He is a muscular, heavily scarred man who can stop Kyoshiro`s sword swings and endure Tarlotte`s beatings. Whatever is said or done to Tarlotte by anyone, often it is Soujirou who endures the wrath of her anger.</description>
<picture>20603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1926" picture="156610.jpg">Kishi Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4516" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="2">3.09</rating>
<name>Oogami Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jin, as the shield of order in the city of Academia, is the leader of the Seventh Public Morality Enforcement Squad.</description>
<picture>20604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4517" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="4">4.22</rating>
<name>Satou Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kozue has been Kuu`s best friend since they were little and always keeps her in mind.</description>
<picture>20605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4518" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="4">3.66</rating>
<name>Valteishia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Valteishia, referring to herself as "Valteishia of the Sun and Solitude," commands the Absolute Angel Megingjord. She has experienced death and reincarnation many times and is now using her fourth body. Valteishia is the current companion of Kazuya and his loyal follower.</description>
<picture>20606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4519" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="3">1.32</rating>
<name>Ayanokouji Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The eldest son of the Ayanokouji family and a genius, who was involved in the experiments to create Absolute Angels alongside his grandfather. Kyoshiro believes that he sacrificed himself in an attempt to quell the great catastrophe of ten years prior to the main time line of the story. Soujirou, however, has stated that for all his positive traits, Kazuya was a fool. Mika has added to this that Kazuya was as ruthless as a demon behind his eternal smile and tendency to always be victorious in any challenge. Kyoshiro looks up to him and makes every effort to emulate him, something his brother Soujirou has advised him against and which arouses Mika`s hatred for him.</description>
<picture>20607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4520" type="appears in" update="2009-05-15">
<name>Claiomh Solais</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>20608.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4521" type="appears in" update="2009-05-15">
<name>Murakumo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>20609.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4522" type="appears in" update="2009-05-15">
<name>Batraz</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>20610.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4523" type="appears in" update="2009-05-15">
<name>Megingjord</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>20611.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4524" type="appears in" update="2009-05-15">
<name>Bastille</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>20612.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="64276" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠[とわ]の空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eternal Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ท้องฟ้าที่ไม่สิ้นสุด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Towa no Sora</title>
<summary>Kuu can’t help but think that Kyoshiro, the new student in her class, looks familiar. Just after she realizes he looks like a prince from her dreams, she finds the boy coming to her rescue!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="65531" update="2006-12-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66038" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三華月百夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Three Gorgeous Months, a Hundred Nights</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สามจันทร์นวลร้อยราตรี</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikazuki Byakuya</title>
<summary>Kuu is only just beginning to reflect on the chaos that unfolded at school when she is abducted by an unfamiliar girl who knows important information about the Absolute Angels.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="66689" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞い踊る螺旋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dancing Spiral</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เกลียวจักรเริงระบำ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maiodoru Rasen</title>
<summary>Kuu tries very hard to truly understand Setsuna, even as battle plans are put in place to deal with the looming threat of Batraz. Meanwhile, Kyoshiro offers Kuu a chance to see his former academy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="66690" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋蛍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fireflies of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="th">หิ่งห้อยแห่งรัก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koibotaru</title>
<summary>Though there is little she can do to help, Kuu does her best to tend to wounded Kyoshiro. Her efforts are rewarded when Kyoshiro shares an important story from his past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="66691" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">くちづけ洗礼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Baptismal Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="th">จูบทดสอบ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuchizuke Senrei</title>
<summary>Shocking revelations spell out Kuu’s fate after she finds her relaxing shopping trip with Kyoshiro interrupted by a kidnapping attempt!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="67319" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆめはて十字路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crossroads at the Ends of Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สี่แยกสุดปลายฝัน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume Hate Juujiro</title>
<summary>Kuu discovers the truth of her role in the world of the Absolute Angels and accepts the consequences of uniting with Kaon. But before action can be taken, a battle erupts.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="67391" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彷徨いの哀歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Elegy for the Wandering</title>
<title xml:lang="th">บทกวีไว้อาลัยที่ไร้จุดหมาย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samayoi no Aika</title>
<summary>Safe for now and pondering the direction of her life as an Absolute Angel, Kuu takes steps to release the powers within her. Meanwhile, Kyoshiro’s feelings for the girl lead to a conflicted heart.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="67392" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">刻(とき)の目覚め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moment`s Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การตื่นขึ้นของห้วงแห่งนิรันดร</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki no Mezame</title>
<summary>After Kyoshiro saves Kuu from a tragic fate, he proclaims his love to her and vows to make things right with Setsuna. Unfortunately, Setsuna is already in turmoil after overhearing Kyoshiro’s confessions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="67393" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙女見果てぬ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maiden Unfulfilled</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สาวน้อยไม่สมประกอบ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome Mihatenu</title>
<summary>Kazuya’s presence could spell disaster. After reappearing, he takes harsh action against anyone who dares stand in his way of claiming the power of the Absolute Angels.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="68021" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使の牢獄[バスティーユ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bastille</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คุกนางฟ้า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bastille</title>
<summary>After Tarlotte is captured, Kazuya moves forward with his plan. All five Absolute Angels are his - and the Bastille could soon be unleashed. Kyoshiro must act quickly to rescue Kuu and the others.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="68346" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使回廊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Angel`s Corridor</title>
<title xml:lang="th">โรงละครนางฟ้า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi Kairou</title>
<summary>Kazuya’s goal is at hand! With Bastille reborn, the situation looks bleak - unless the Absolute Angels can once more take control of their own fates.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="68373" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eternal Kuu</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คูผู้เป็นนิรันดร์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Kuu</title>
<summary>Kazuya is defeated but victory did not come without loss for the Absolute Angels. Kyoshiro must say goodbye to Kuu -if only for now.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="79360" update="2009-12-18">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2007-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逢瀬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tryst</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ouse</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80239" update="2009-12-18">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白鳥くう観察日誌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kuu Shiratori Observation Diary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiratori Kuu Kansatsu Nisshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80961" update="2009-12-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2007-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンゲージ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Engage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Engage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81238" update="2009-12-18">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2007-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot-Spring Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsen Tenshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86574" update="2009-12-18">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2007-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遥かなる空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Distant Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Harukanaru Sora</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86575" update="2009-12-18">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真・京四郎と永遠の空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Real Kyoushirou to Towa no Sora</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Kyoushirou to Towa no Sora</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119223" update="2011-09-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119224" update="2011-09-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
