<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4601" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-08-08</startdate>
<enddate>2006-10-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hanoka</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">HANOKA~葉ノ香~</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.rams.jp/hanoka/</url>
<creators>
<name id="23366" type="Work">Fanworks</name>
<name id="1487" type="Work">RAMS</name>
<name id="16388" type="Original Work">Morino Aruji</name>
<name id="16388" type="Direction">Morino Aruji</name>
<name id="16494" type="Music">Fujimoto Jun</name>
</creators>
<description>The story takes place on a planet Tokinea where human beings and Star Races have been fighting. The story revolves around a girl who was made as Demon God, an ultimate weapon against human beings, and a boy who is a partner of the girl.
Source: AnimeNfo
Note: This anime is the first full-fledged TV anime made with Flash.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="344">1.63</permanent>
<temporary count="349">4.27</temporary>
<review count="2">2.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>11105.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6786</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1993</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1812</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3805</identifier>
<identifier>wgoovd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hanoka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>HANOKA〜葉ノ香〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1012</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>325649</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8580</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="355" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-30">
<name>wings</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4200" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>flash animation</name>
<description>Made in Adobe Flash (formerly known as Macromedia Flash), a software package for rich multimedia and Web animations and applications. Very popular on amateur fanproductions (like the ones found in places such as YouTube)
Sadly, Flash has also earned a bad reputation among the animation purists because it leads to cheap low-quality animation jobs, since anyone with a hint of creativity and a "idea" on its head can easily learn how to produce an animated feature in Flash... and sell it to the masses.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="47014" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-19">
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<name>Kokutou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91172.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47015" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-19">
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<name>Kaori Harusaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="77" picture="30668.jpg">Oumi Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47016" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-19">
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<name>Mika Kisaragi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47017" type="main character in" update="2012-07-19">
<rating votes="1">3.49</rating>
<name>Yuuri Kaminoza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47018" type="main character in" update="2012-07-19">
<rating votes="1">3.49</rating>
<name>Hanoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="313" picture="158104.jpg">Nogawa Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47019" type="appears in" update="2012-07-19">
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<name>Kongo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91177.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11101" picture="40055.jpg">Namekawa Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47021" type="appears in" update="2012-07-19">
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<name>Barz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91179.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="57781" update="2006-09-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2006-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦の地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battlefield</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61846" update="2006-08-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Devil</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61900" update="2006-09-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beginning Of A Journey</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62002" update="2006-08-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">希望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desire</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62151" update="2006-09-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">静寂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calmness</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64513" update="2006-10-28">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">名前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Name</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65165" update="2006-11-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2006-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Foe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ada</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65258" recap="true" update="2007-01-10">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>9</length>
<rating votes="2">1.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7.5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65259" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2006-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seperation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65260" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2006-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Persons</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65261" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2006-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sky</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65262" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">破滅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Destruction</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65263" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2006-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星の王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King of the Stars</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
