<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4645" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-02-09</startdate>
<enddate>2007-12-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Okane ga Nai!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">お金がないっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">No Money!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9906" approval="2" total="3">Love Stage!!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2"/>
<url>http://www.anime-nomoney.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1152" type="Unknown Relation">Happinet Pictures</name>
<name id="5516" type="Character Design">Yamamoto Sawako</name>
<name id="6546" type="Direction">Sokuza Makoto</name>
<name id="25146" type="Original Work">Shinozaki Hitoyo</name>
<name id="32365" type="Animation Work">Lyrics</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch11230 [Ayase Yukiya] is a university student. His cousin Ishii Tetsuo betrays and sells him in an auction to settle his heavy debts. Ayase is bought by http://anidb.net/ch11229 [Kanou Somuku] for 120 million yen.
Kanou does this because he remembers Ayase from 4 years ago, when Ayase, a stranger, helped him. Now Kanou wants to keep Ayase close to himself, and uses the debt of 120 million yen to force Ayase to live with him. As Ayase is still a student and does not have a job, he is forced to sell his body to Kanou for 500,000 yen each time they have sex.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="500">3.87</permanent>
<temporary count="516">6.37</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>6884.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7071</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2148</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>30262</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3942</identifier>
<identifier>gumpyp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.anime-nomoney.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>No_Money</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>お金がないっ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5196</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326356</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8746</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5804" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-19">
<name>piledriver</name>
<description>As you can see, the characters shirts were torn from a fight as they were previously wrestling. They seem to wrestle a lot in the show and most of the time you just see them doing the choke hold wrong and giving each other piledrivers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11229" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">6.55</rating>
<name>Kanou Somuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A twenty-six year-old businessman who runs a financial firm in Shinjuku. He was saved by Ayase`s kindness around four years ago, therefore saved Ayase when he was being auctioned off by buying him for 120 million Yen. In order to protect Ayase, he forced the 120 million yen debt (plus a hefty interest of 10% every 10 days) on Ayase as a means to keep Ayase with him, and pays 500,000 Yen to Ayase each time they have sex.
He has a hard time trying to express his feelings towards Ayase due to his gruff, no-nonsense exterior, and particularly Ayase`s naïveté and reluctance to accept a relationship between two guys. Domineering, possessive and jealous, Kanou forbids anyone to come close to Ayase without his permission and lets him go outside only begrudgingly. He is not above bullying or even manhandling Ayase if he happens to hurt his feelings. Nevertherless, Kanou is mostly kind and considerate towards Ayase and expresses his passionate affection without restraint.
Realizing that he has started off on the wrong foot by raping Ayase after the auction, he tries to make it up to him by doing various things with mixed results (i.e: solving Testuo`s debt, and in the manga: buying Ayase new clothes, allowing him to attend summer classes, allowing Ayase to work).
In the released artbook, an interview with him shows that his motto is "perseverance brings success" and that he washes his right shoulder first when bathing.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>33333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11230" type="main character in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="3">5.33</rating>
<name>Ayase Yukiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayase Yukiya is the eighteen year-old boy who was betrayed by his own cousin, Tetsuo, and was auctioned off to settle Tetsuo`s debt. He was bought by Kanou for the price of 120 million Yen, and had to pay off the debt by having sex with Kanou for 500,000 Yen each time.
He had lost his parents in a young age and had a lonely childhood. Gentle and very naive, he has a hard time expressing himself to people and not very good at socializing. He tends to keep to himself and to act aloof towards people but Kanou has forced himself into his life. He also has a knack for getting in trouble mostly because he does not realize that men tend to feel a very strong sexual attraction to him when he`s around.
He is confused about his relationship with Kanou and often feels guilty that he is involved with another guy. In the manga, he is currently trying to change his personality to be a bit more outgoing and more sociable. Gaining Kanou`s permission, he is currently working part-time as a kitchen helper in Someya`s store.
In the released artbook, an interview with him shows that his motto is "you can go far little by little" and that he washes his left arm first when bathing.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>33336.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31375" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-20">
<name>Kuba Misao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31376" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-20">
<name>Kuba Homare</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31377" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-20">
<name>Someya Kaoruko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="68767" update="2007-04-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2007-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71657" update="2007-04-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73721" update="2007-05-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">綾瀬日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayase Diary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayase Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82813" update="2007-09-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2007-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86096" update="2007-12-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2007-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191741" update="2017-10-15">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">綾瀬日記 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayase Diary 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayase Nikki 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191742" update="2017-10-15">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">綾瀬日記 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayase Diary 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayase Nikki 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191743" update="2017-10-15">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">綾瀬日記 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayase Diary 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayase Nikki 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208546" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208547" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
