<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="466" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>1999-09-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gokudou-kun Man`yuuki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Jester the Adventurer</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Путешественник Гокудо</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gokudo-kun Manyuki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gokudo-kun Mannyu-ki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gokudou-kun Manyuuki</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="short">Гокудо</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gokudo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gkm</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゴクドーくん漫遊記</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gokudo</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Jester: El Aventurero</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="39" approval="37" total="39">Slayers</anime>
<anime id="3468" approval="5" total="10">Gintama</anime>
<anime id="392" approval="1" total="2">Hikyou Tanken Fam &amp; Ihrlie</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="89596">Very funny anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="253095">Good (and fresh!) comedy, spiced with various crazy elements like body or gender swaps or silly versions of folklore motives.
The story also benefits from the womanly touch of the author; thanks to it Gokudo averts many pitfalls of shounen genre and provides blends of comedy that a more ordinary show could not.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="472606">Solid entertainment ... gr8 characters and comedy ...</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.geneon-ent.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/gokudo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="838" type="Unknown Relation">Pioneer LDC</name>
<name id="950" type="Unknown Relation">SoftX</name>
<name id="1136" type="Animation Work">Trans Arts</name>
<name id="3688" type="Series Composition">Tomioka Atsuhiro</name>
<name id="4401" type="Direction">Sugishima Kunihisa</name>
<name id="10225" type="Original Work">Nakamura Usagi</name>
<name id="6473" type="Character Design">Shimogasa Miho</name>
<name id="6473" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shimogasa Miho</name>
<name id="45584" type="Music">Akimoto Naoya</name>
</creators>
<description>It all starts when http://anidb.net/ch25158 [Gokudou] steals a pouch from a fortune teller, thinking that it contains a gem. Instead, it turns out to be a rock, from which emerges Djinn. The genie grants Gokudou the standard three wishes, but our anti-hero does not think heavily about his wishes. Gokudou does get his wishes, though not exactly in the fashion that he expected. The best thing he gets out of his wishes is Honou no Maken, a magical sword that enables its owner to perform fire attacks and it can be summoned from anywhere in the world.
Even with an enchanted sword, Gokudou does not get much respect. He gets turned into a woman by Djinn, who is also a shapeshifter. He is followed by http://anidb.net/ch45121 [Rubette La Lette], a potential love interest who is more interested in adventure, karaoke and outperforming Gokudou. He gets whacked on the head a lot, especially by the fortune teller who reappears throughout the series just to plague Gokudou it seems. Later he is joined by another sidekick, a former evil magician named Prince, who is more handsome and a better womaniser than Gokudou.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="794">6.50</permanent>
<temporary count="806">7.49</temporary>
<review count="2">6.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>76343.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>250</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2409</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>185</identifier>
<identifier>nmqsay</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nbcuni.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/gokudo/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゴクドーくん漫遊記</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5124</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>250</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90315</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1032" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-10">
<name>fishing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4113" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-20">
<name>body exchange</name>
<description>Two or more characters swap bodies (or, equally, swap minds).
When this plot is done, usually the voices also switch as narrative cheat to help viewers keep track of who`s who. More subtly, it`s just the eyes. More serious/action-oriented shows might not do this. The Flip often involves characters of different ages, genders, races, or social classes. Another variation is a protagonist and antagonist switching, which usually involves each trying to undermine the other`s organization while simultaneously trying to switch back. If one or both of the characters have superpowers or other special abilities, they`ll have a lot of trouble figuring their new powers out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9115" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="60">3.32</rating>
<name>Ten</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lum`s infant cousin. He is often called "Ten-chan" by Lum and many of the other main female characters, the male characters often call him by his full-name "Jariten" ("Jari" means something like "brat" in Japanese). He comes to earth after flying in a spaceship inside a peach (a reference to the Japanese folktale of Momotaro) to live with Lum in the Moroboshi household when his Oni powers first manifest. He appeared much earlier in the anime (making his debut in Episode Two) than in the Manga. Ten has a single horn on his head, can breathe fire, flies very slowly, and wears tiger striped diaper. He and Ataru utterly loathe each other and often fight. Ten`s character design and relationship to the series` male lead is somewhat similar to that of Shippo from Inuyasha (though there is much more acrimony between Ten and Ataru than between Shippo and Inuyasha).
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28603.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25158" type="main character in" update="2010-11-18">
<rating votes="9">7.69</rating>
<name>Gokudou Yuccot Kikansky</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Unlike most main characters, he is closer to a villain than a hero. He doesn`t hesitate to abuse the needs of people, sell out his friends to save himself, run away from any dangers, or ditch others who helped him if he doesn`t have any more interest in them. His life starts to change when he finds a magical Genie named Djinn who will to grant him three wishes. As most people would benefit from having three wishes, in his case it leads him to a lot of trouble, and it doesn`t take long before he tries to escape from Djinn, as well as every other person he meets.</description>
<picture>59487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45121" type="main character in" update="2012-05-24">
<rating votes="10">5.69</rating>
<name>Rubette La Lette</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88337.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5216" picture="29203.jpg">Yoshida Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5611" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スフィンクスにワケわかんねー謎を出される のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Riddle of Sphinx</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Una esfinge pide cosas imposibles.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sphinx ni Wake Wakannee Nazo o Dasareru no Koto</title>
<summary>Gokudo comes across a wisecracking unicorn, a sphinx, and a little demon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763867</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5612" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">のるかそるか!? 国王レースに出ちゃうぞ! のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The King`s Race: Ready or Not, Here I Come!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Camina o revienta, empieza la carrera por el reino.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Noru ka Soru ka!? Kokuou Race ni Dechau zo! no Koto</title>
<summary>Gokudo signs up for the `King`s Race`, having no idea what he is getting himself into.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763863</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5613" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレ様の最後の願いを聞いてくれ! のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Please, Grant My Last Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Escucha el último de mis deseos.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oresama no Saigo no Negai o Kiite Kure! no Koto</title>
<summary>Our heroes converge on the throne room after contending with a hall of enchanted mirrors and Gokudo`s abortive attempt to throw in with their enemies.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763859</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5614" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おマヌケな飛び入りさわやか乱入 のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sappy Sidekick, Bracing Appearance</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Irrumpen los secundarios, ¡qué cara más dura!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omanuke na Tobiiri Sawayaka Rannyuu no Koto</title>
<summary>Trapped in the Magic King`s castle, we meet Rubette, Asuga, and Mora. While searching for some way out, they run across Seigi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763855</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5615" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いきなり美少女にばけちゃうオレなのよのこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suddenly, I`m a Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Me Convierto En Una Tia Buena</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikinari Bishoujo ni Bakechau Ore na no yo no Koto</title>
<summary>My name is Jester. I am a master swordsman and I love adventure. An old fortune-telling woman tells me that the King wants to kill me. I steal her purse and open it. There is only a stone inside. It is not an ordinary stone though. A giant spirit named Jin comes out of the stone. He transforms me into a young lady before I can even ask why. I am captured and thrown into a jail in a castle. "What is going on?" 
Source: enoki-films.co.jp</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763853</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6052" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう女なんかぜってー信用しねぇ! のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Let Women Fool You</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Nunca más confiare en las mujeres.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Onna nanka Zettee Shin`you Shinee! no Koto</title>
<summary>Summoning Princess Coco to help him solve the riddle of the Sphinx, it soon becomes obvious that she knows more than she`s letting on.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763875</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6122" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第三の男の正体にオレたちゃブッとんだ! のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shocking Truth of the Third Man!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Se nos revela la identidad del tercer hombre.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daisan no Otoko no Shoutai ni Oretacha Buttonda! no Koto</title>
<summary>Gokudo manages to chance upon the sacred relic, but is more than a little intimidated when he discovers it`s guarded by a huge dragon!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763877</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6123" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">薔薇の君プリンスあやかしの微笑み乱れ咲き のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rose Prince, the Charming, Winning Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El príncipe de las rosas, una sonrisa muy sospechosa.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bara no Kimi Prince Ayakashi no Hohoemi Midarezaki no Koto</title>
<summary>Prince Niari, who`s defining trait is his womanizing nature, kidnaps the three princesses.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763883</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6128" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレがあいつでこいつがどいつで大混乱 のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Identity Crisis! I Am You but Who Are You?</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Si yo soy ese, ¿Quién es aquel?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ga Aitsu de Koitsu ga Doitsu de Daikonran no Koto</title>
<summary>Gokudo and the others enjoy some short lived rest and relaxation on Demon Island.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763907</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6129" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絵にも描けない龍宮城に来てみれば のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When in the Unimaginable Ryuga Castle...</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Tienes que venir al palacio del rey Dragón.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">E ni mo Kakenai Ryuuguujou ni Kite Mireba no Koto</title>
<summary>Frustrated at having come out of his desert race with no more than a dusty old box, Gokudo pops it open and is instantly turned into an old man.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763887</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6130" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">驚天動地! イナホ国の明日はどっちだ!? のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">World-Shattering World! Which Way Is the Future of Inaho!?</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Extraordinario, ¿Cual será el destino de Inaho?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoutendouchi! Inaho-koku no Asu wa Docchi Da!? no Koto</title>
<summary>The capital city of Inaho burns as Indra and the Dragon God battle one another while searching for Gokudo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763901</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6131" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホトケと魔族のなんだか根の深そーな因縁 のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Destiny of the Hotoke and Magic Gods</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La profunda razón de la enemistad entre budas y demonios.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hotoke to Mazoku no Nandaka Ne no Fukasoo na Innen no Koto</title>
<summary>Hoping to find the magic sphere, the gang find Niari who has been transformed into a merman!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763895</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6132" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お天気激変! 爆裂太陽娘にふりまわされる のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stormy Weather! The Selfish Sun-Goddess Explodes</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Un brusco cambio de clima, aparece la diosa del Sol.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otenki Gekihen! Bakuretsu Taiyou Musume ni Furimawasareru no Koto</title>
<summary>Gokudo and the others set off after the Sun Goddess.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763891</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6202" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレ猿のまったくとんでもない正体は? のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The True Identity of Me, I`ll Be a Monkey`s Uncle!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¿Cual es la increíble identidad de mi yo mono?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore Saru no Mattaku Tondemonai Shoutai wa? no Koto</title>
<summary>Using pop star Gokudo as bait, the gang manages to infiltrate the secret monkey encampment ruled by Gokuu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763923</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6203" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魅惑のチンゲンツァイシスターズ!登場 のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Trembling Debut of the Bok Choy Sisters!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La presentación de las hermanas Chingentzai.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miwaku no Chingentsuai Sisters! Toujou no Koto</title>
<summary>Gokudo goes on stage and causes a complete ruckus and the audience rushes forward for autographs, leaving them no choice but to fight their way out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763919</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6204" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変わり果てたオレの体は何でそーなるの!? のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Me, Myself &amp; Monkey!?</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¿Que ha sido de mi pobre cuerpo?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawarihateta Ore no Karada wa Nande Soo Naru no!? no Koto</title>
<summary>Everyone attempts to get back into their correct bodies with the help of others.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763915</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6268" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お医者さんゴッコで宝玉大接近! のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Play Doctor! Here Comes the Magic Sphere!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Te puedes acercar mucho a la joya sagrada, jugando a los médicos.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oisha-san-gokko de Hougyoku Daisekkin! no Koto</title>
<summary>Gokudo and the others are hypnotized by Ah and Ng, and Lady Nano is abducted!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763899</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6282" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おそるべき妖怪姉妹涙の再会! のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Temptation of the Deadly Gorgeous Sisters!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Las hermanas demonio, un encuentro entre lágrimas.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osorubeki Youkai Shimai Namida no Saikai! no Koto</title>
<summary>Rubette has accidentally turned herself into cannot speak, and she`s having no luck communicating her plight to Gokudo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763911</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6295" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みつめ愛・しのび愛・からみ愛 のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World Is Full of Loving and Shoving!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Un amor encontrado, un amor callado, un amor liado.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsumeai, Shinobiai, Karamiai no Koto</title>
<summary>Gokudo and the others are still suffering from the body switching, and they meet Nanya, royal servant of Queen West.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763927</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6297" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この子誰の子パンダの子?青い卵の謎 のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who`s That Baby? Whose Baby? Mystery of the Blue Egg</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¿Quién es? ¿Qué pasa con ese bebé?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Ko Dare no Ko Panda no Ko? Aoi Tamago no Nazo no Koto</title>
<summary>The magical talking panda returns, and gives birth to the demon lord Gokuu!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763931</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6298" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三蔵法師登場!オレたちの幸せ探し のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monk Sanzo Appears! What Is Happiness?</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Caos, ¡Confusión! Gracias, Sanzo.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanzou Houshi Toujou! Oretachi no Shiawase Sagashi no Koto</title>
<summary>The heroes find Sanzo, who tries to convince them that he can put their souls back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763935</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6328" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弥勒覚醒! 幸せっていったいナニ? のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Awakening of Miroku! Where Is Happiness?</title>
<title xml:lang="es">A ver, ¿Qué es la felicidad?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miroku Kakusei! Shiawase tte Ittai Nani? no Koto</title>
<summary>Sanzo engages in a full-blown philosophical debate with Miroku over the latter`s purpose.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763939</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6330" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三蔵の逆襲! とにかくオレを元に戻してくれ! のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sanzo Counterattacks! Please Gimme Back My Body!!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Ya va siendo hora de recuperar mi cuerpo.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanzou no Gyakushuu! Tonikaku Ore o Moto ni Modoshite Kure! no Koto</title>
<summary>Nanya needs a human form and tries to kill Gokudo in Rubette`s body.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763943</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6331" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めざめよ命の泉!オレ様大復活!! のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Back the Spring of Life! I Shall Return</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La fuente de la vida, un autenticó renacer.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezameyo Inochi no Izumi! Oresama Daifukkatsu!! no Koto</title>
<summary>Team Gokudo make a beeline for the country of Yanu to find the Spring the Life, which allegedly should be able to age Gokudo back to his previous self.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763947</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6332" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢見るオレ様!起きてビックラ のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Am I Dreaming? Surprise at Sunrise!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¿Esto es un sueño o la realidad?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yumemiru Oresama! Okite Bikkura no Koto</title>
<summary>Rubette and Gokudo are fighting for their own souls and control of their own bodies.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763951</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6333" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あばよ! 誰にも文句はいわせねーぜ! のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">See Ya, Everybody! Nobody Can Stop Me Now!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Me llamo Jester Euborn Libertein.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abayo! Dare ni mo Monku wa Iwasenee ze! no Koto</title>
<summary>Gokudo, Rubette, and Niari try to defeat their adversary so they can set out on new adventures.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763953</identifier>
<identifier>gokudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86589" update="2008-01-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117557" update="2010-04-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136039" update="2012-01-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
