<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4661" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-09-02</startdate>
<enddate>1996-08-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mama wa Poyopoyosaurus ga Osuki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">ママぽよ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ママはぽよぽよザウルスがお好き</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">BB保你大</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="19004">Great series especially for family with small children!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nippon-animation.co.jp/na/mamapoyo/index.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="3654" type="Direction">Suzuki Takayoshi</name>
<name id="7694" type="Music">Maruyama Kazunori</name>
<name id="8458" type="Original Work">Aonuma Takako</name>
<name id="16324" type="Character Design">Miura Tatsuo</name>
</creators>
<description>This is the story of a young couple who struggle with their children.
Miki is the mother of two kids, Hyoga and Jura. Hyoga is a 4-year-old boy and Jura is a 2-year-old girl. Miki writes children`s books at home. Miki wants to be a gentle and kind mother, but it is difficult to be patient with the kids. Her husband Gendai tries to be as cooperative as he can and helps her to attend to the kids. But sometimes he only makes her even angrier.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9">5.87</permanent>
<temporary count="9">6.22</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>78513.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1949</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4782</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1031</identifier>
<identifier>rxbuoi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nippon-animation.co.jp/work/1722/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mama_Loves_the_Poyopoyo-Saurus</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ママはぽよぽよザウルスがお好き</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88995</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1295</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1283" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-24">
<name>tsukkomi</name>
<description>A tsukkomi is a comedy duo stock character in a traditional Japanese slapstick stand-up comedy style known as manzai. Tsukkomi characters are the smart, reasonable, and down-to-earth half of the unit; their simple-minded counterparts are the http://anidb.net/t1399 [boke] characters. As a result of their boke counterparts` simple mistakes and gross exaggerations, tsukkomi berate and abuse them both verbally and physically; a very common example of tsukkomi physical abuse is a paper fan slap, which is generally accompanied by a sound effect. Their approximate equivalent in Western culture is the comedy role of straight man.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="60023" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かけひきママ 子供押しつけあいバトル / 反省ママ 今日から叱らないお母さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60024" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">痛快ママ 男の子は痛いッ! / 実感ママ 女の子はワガママ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60025" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">追跡ママ さすらいのヒョウガ / 宝くじママ ダーリンは当たりかハズレか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60026" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幼稚園ママ 朝のドタバタ必勝法 / ワイルドパパ ダーリン流育児法</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60027" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">策略ママ デパートホリデー入門 / 置き去りママ ジジババの家にお泊まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60028" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プッツンママ 二歳児ジュラの主張 / 感激ママ タリラリヒョウガの運動会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60029" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">うんざりママ オモチャ減らし大作戦 / くたくたママ ジュラと地獄の旅巡り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60030" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レフェリーママ 兄妹ゲンカの裁き方 / こだわりママ ジュラ, パーマをかける</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60031" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロフェッショナルママ 子連れ遊園地マニュアル / 迷走ママ ヒョウガの早期教育</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60032" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぐったりママ 毎日が関所破り / ぶきっちょパパ ダーリンの抜けてる育児</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60033" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パニックママ ジュラの発熱大騒動 / ずぼらママ ダブルでやってきた七五三</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60034" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">しつけママ ジュラのおしゃぶり物語 / 親ばかママ ヒョウガのおたのしみ会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60035" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どきどきママ ダーリンの実家へ行く / しみじみパパ 暴かれるダーリンの宝物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60036" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">うっかりパパ ジュラの荷造りに御用心 / 手抜きママ おべんと作りなんか大嫌い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60037" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">深刻ママ 悩めるヒョウガの人間関係 / 気配りママ ジュラのお誕生パーティー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60038" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どたばたママ X\`マスプレゼント大作戦 / ハッスルパパ サンタクロース大作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60039" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">困ったママ ダーリンvsジュラ / はらはらママ ヒョウガの寒げいこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60040" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ため息ママ 夜ふかしヒョウガの大みそか / 泣き虫ママ 死なないでジャック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60041" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">辛抱ママ ジュラは只今反抗期 / 心配ママ 初めてのお留守番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60042" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">反省パパ これがダーリンの叱り方 / おろおろママ ヒョウガの家出騒ぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60043" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">見栄張りママ 冷や汗スケートホリデー / 風邪引きママ 病は母を強くする</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60044" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">張り切りパパ ダーリン鬼になる / お手上げママ おばあちゃんの子育て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60045" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">失敗パパ 冷や汗バレンタイン / 複雑ママ 涙の本命チョコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60046" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤っ恥ママ ヒョウガのTV出演 / 赤っ恥ママ ヒョウガのTV出演 その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60047" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おのろけママ ダーリンとデート / うろたえママ ドタバタ妊娠騒動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60048" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わざありママ 親子ゲンカでひな祭り / ズタボロママ ヒョウガの参観会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60049" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あたふたママ ご両親がやってくる / 汗タラママ 迷子の迷子のおじいちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 27</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60050" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひらめきママ 料理はアイデア勝負 / 熱血パパ ヒョウガの自転車特訓</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 28</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60051" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お答えママ どっちの子が好き? / 気合ママ ジュラの入園面接</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 29</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60052" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ど忘れママ ヒョウガの誕生日 / 貧乏くじママ うららか釣り堀日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60053" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">びっくりママ ジュラの入園式 / 冷や汗ママ だんまりジュラの参観日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60054" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶきっちょママ 恐怖の手作りグッズ / 決断ママ 管理人さんの大災難</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60055" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩ママ たくやくんチの柔道[やわらみち] / どっきりママ ジュラは悩めるお年頃?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 33</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60056" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">入れこみママ ジュラのバレエ教室 / カルガモパパ 追跡・ヒョウガの遠足</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 34</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60057" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恥かきママ ジュラのうそ物語 / むりやりパパ 泳げ!こいのぼりッ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 35</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60058" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">まゆつばママ ダーリンの禁煙宣言 / 感動ママ 母の日ふたたび</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 36</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60059" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">出張パパ ヒョウガの二日天下 / のんきママ ジュラvsれいら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 37</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60060" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お手伝いママ ぎっくり腰でSOS / 猫かぶりママ 本当[ホント]はみ~んな怒りんぼ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 38</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60061" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">でまかせママ ヒョウガ悩める季節 / へとへとママ 傘をたずねて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 39</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60062" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">目撃パパ 保与田家魔の月曜日 / 胸キュンママ ジュラのバレエ発表会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 40</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60063" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わくわくパパ 父の日に栄光あれ / のめりこみママ めざめよ, 天才画家!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 41</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60064" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">やきもきママ ジュラのお流れ遠足 / 気遣いママ ふるさとを捨てた義父[ちち]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 42</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60065" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">探偵ママ ヒョウガの秘密 / ミーハーママ 無敵レンジャー大ピンチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 43</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60066" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バタバタママ 七夕の夜は大騒ぎ / ちゃっかりママ 母親だって遊びたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 44</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60067" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">げんなりママ お姉ちゃんが欲しい / 不可解ママ ヒョウガ, 目覚める</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 45</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60068" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">へたばりママ 恐怖の夏休み / なりきりパパ 納涼肝試し大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 46</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60069" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">意地っぱりパパ 縁日でいざ勝負!! / しぶしぶママ 新車なんて見てるだけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 47</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60070" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バカンスママ いち君チのお別荘 / 面食らいママ ジュラの三角関係</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 48</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Vacance Mama: Ichi-kun Chi no Obessou / Menkurai Mama: Jura no Sankakukankei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60071" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">言い聞かせママ ジュラ我慢の一日 / いきなりパパ ダーリンのUターン願望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 49</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60072" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほのぼのママ 意地でも花火見物だ / 爆発パパ 甘い誘惑, ゲームの味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 50</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60073" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とばっちりママ 爆睡ママと海水浴 / イライラママ おじいちゃんの子守り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 51</title>
</episode>
<episode id="60074" update="2006-08-15">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛情ママ おねしょはナイショ / バイバイママ 太君のお引っ越し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 52</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139967" update="2012-06-01">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139968" update="2012-06-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139969" update="2012-06-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
