<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4680" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-11-26</startdate>
<enddate>2001-05-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dotto Koni-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドッとKONIちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Koni-chan</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="4134" type="Series Composition">Amiya Masaharu</name>
<name id="3963" type="Direction">Watanabe Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="6116" type="Animation Character Design">Yoneda Mitsuhiro</name>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="6116" type="Character Design">Yoneda Mitsuhiro</name>
<name id="739" type="Work">Genco</name>
<name id="2341" type="Music">Masuda Toshio</name>
</creators>
<description>Koni (whose character is based on the famous Sumo-wrestler) and his gang have lots of crazy and incoherent adventures in their town. From fighting with their Lovely-Teacher and dealing with Samurai fish, to confirming if The Armored-Guy`s wife has an affair and saving the world, Koni, High, Moro, Nari and Afro, the Afro-dog, do the craziest and funniest things to have fun.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="27">6.74</permanent>
<temporary count="27">7.14</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>203931.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1738</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1684</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234366</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4294</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="63844" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">WearetheKONIちゃん / スクールウォーズ? / 忍びこむのだ~っ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">WearetheKoni-chan / School Wars? / Shinobikomu no Da!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63845" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">正しい証明写真の撮り方 / @KONIちゃんの家! / フィギュア王!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tadashii Shoumei Shashin no Torikata / Koni-chan no Ie! / Figure-ou!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63846" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">つりつりパニック / 立ち読み大作戦! / 聖騎士KONI伝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuritsuri Panic / Tachiyomi Daisakusen! / Hijiri Kishi Koni Den</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63847" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一日支店長~激闘編~ / 高度でコードな女の子 / 暗黒街のKONI</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichinichi Shitenchou: Gekitou Hen / Koudo de Code na Onnanoko / Ankokugai no Koni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63848" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特訓サムサム(寒む寒む)アップ!? / 魔法のイカ少女スルメちゃん / KONIちゃん地獄遍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokkun Samusamu Up!? / Mahou no Ika Shoujo Surume-chan / Koni-chan Jigoku Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63849" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あけましてさようなら!? / さようならKONIちゃん!? / あけましてこんにちは</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akemashite Sayounara!? / Sayounara Koni-chan!? / Akemashite Konnichiwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63850" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">丸いのが好き! / リストラ男は闇将軍 / 最近のジョージはわりと元気?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marui no ga Suki! / Restaurant Otoko wa Yami Shougun / Saikin no Jouji wa Wari to Genki?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63851" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃え尽きるまで... / KONIちゃんの休日 / タクシードライバーのゆううつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moetsukiru made... / Koni-chan no Kyuujitsu / Taxi Driver no Yuuutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63852" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちぇんじ・ちぇんじ・ちぇんじ / 悲劇のオオオカミ男 / 戦え!KONIレンジャー750!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Change Change Change / Higeki no Ookami Otoko / Tatakae! Koni Ranger 750!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63853" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の温泉卵 / 祖師ヶ谷大蔵電子倶楽部の野望 / 週刊少年KONI</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Onsen Tamago / Soshigaya Tani Ookura Denshi Club no Yabou / Shuukan Shounen Koni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63854" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鎧妻 真昼の裏切り / 七つの海のサバ侍 / ロケットマンの熱い冬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoroi Tsuma Mahiru no Uragiri / Nanatsu no Umi no Saba Samurai / Rocket Man no Atsui Fuyu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63855" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンコとカエル / 祖師ヶ谷大蔵電子倶楽部ふたたび / KONIちゃんのさいゆーき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anko to Kaeru / Soshigaya Tani Ookura Denshi Club Futatabi / Koni-chan no Saiyuuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63856" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">麺達KONIちゃん / さようならHIGHちゃん / 君の名は!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">mentachi Koni-chan / Sayounara High-chan / Kimi no Na wa!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63857" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トレカ大作戦!? / 超高度でコードレスな女の子 / 教科書が教えないおとぎ話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toreka Daisakusen!? / Choukoudo de Cordless na Onnanoko / Kyoukasho ga Oshienai Otogibanashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63858" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月に向かって打て! / 初恋!?初濃いHIGHちゃん!? / 忍び...忍んで...忍者蕎麦!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki ni Mukatte Ute! / Hatsukoi!? Hatsukoi High-chan!? / Shinobi... Shinon de... Ninja Soba!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63859" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">KONIちゃんがころんだ / 第一次ダイエット作戦 / お絵かきなのダ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koni-chan ga Koronda / Daiichiji Diet Sakusen / Oekaki na no Da</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63860" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ド根性KONIちゃん! / 鯖対関鯖 / ふしぎなおともだち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokonjou Koni-chan! / Sabatai Sekisaba / Fushigi na Otomodachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63861" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と青春の準優勝 / ドッと三匹が行く! / 好きとか嫌いとか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Seishun no Jun Yuushou / Dotto Sanbiki ga Iku! / Suki to ka Kirai to ka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63862" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドッとKONIさん大登場! / 篠龍見参!撮影現場は大騒ぎ!! / KONIちゃん徹底攻略</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dotto Koni-san Daitoujou! / Shino Ryuukenzan! Satsuei Genba wa Oosawagi!! / Koni-chan Tettei Kouryaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63863" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">教えて, 秘密のパーティ! / KONIぐるみ, 大変身!! / ドッとカルタ その壱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshiete, Himitsu no Party! / Koni Gurumi, Daihenshin!! / Dotto Karuta Sono Ichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63864" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">心霊写真がほしい! / オールナイト・ドッとKONI / ドッとカルタ その弐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinrei Shashin ga Hoshii! / Alnight Dot Koni / Dotto Karuta Sono Ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63865" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケリ, ケリ, カンケリ / 思い出は永遠に さよならスルメちゃん / 本当はよーしゃなくきびしいイソップ童話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keri, Keri, Kankeri / Omoide wa Eien ni Sayonara Surume-chan / Hontou wa Youshanaku Kibishii Isop Douwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63866" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">言葉は大切に....の巻. なんだよ, 巻って? / 嗚呼, 鎧家族! / リングに燃えろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotoba wa Taisetsu ni... no Maki. Nanda yo, Makitte? / Aa, Yoroi Kazoku! / Ring ni Moero!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63867" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">資格は世界を救う! / ラブリー先生ハッピーウェディング!! / ドッとKONIちゃん キャラクター大図鑑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikaku wa Sekai o Sukuu! / Lovely-sensei Happy Wedding!! / Dotto Koni-chan Character Oozu Akira</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63868" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">KONIちゃん像に花束を / 高度でコードな大暴走 / 疾走!! 毒々マシンKONIレース!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koni-chan Zou ni Hanataba o / Koudo de Code na Daibousou / Shissou!! Dokuge Machine Koni Race!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63869" update="2006-10-05">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドッとお宝鑑定団 / 史上最大のゲスト登場!? / だってキャラだもん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dotto Otakara Kanteidan / Shijou Saidai no Guest Toujou!? / Datta Chara Da Mon!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
