<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4691" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>23</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-01-12</startdate>
<enddate>2007-06-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nodame Cantabile</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Нодамэ Кантабиле</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">จังหวะรัก หัวใจดนตรี</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">วุ่นรักนักดนตรี</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Нодаме Кантабіле</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="short">โนดาเมะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">NC1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">NC</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Nodame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">noda</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">のだめカンタービレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Nodame Cantabile</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">노다메 칸타빌레</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Nodame Cantabile</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Nodame Cantabile</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Nodame Cantabile</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Nodame Cantabile</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Нодаме Кантабиле</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">交响情人梦</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Nodame Cantabile</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5941" type="Sequel">Nodame Cantabile: Paris Hen</anime>
<anime id="12392" type="Other">Channel 5.5 3rd Season</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2835" approval="113" total="153">Hachimitsu to Clover</anime>
<anime id="10539" approval="54" total="69">Shigatsu wa Kimi no Uso</anime>
<anime id="8870" approval="46" total="73">Sakamichi no Apollon: Kids on the Slope</anime>
<anime id="4935" approval="23" total="34">Piano no Mori</anime>
<anime id="5678" approval="19" total="38">Itazura na Kiss</anime>
<anime id="895" approval="5" total="29">Planetes</anime>
<anime id="5855" approval="3" total="11">Fuyu no Sonata</anime>
<anime id="13537" approval="2" total="4">Piano no Mori (2018)</anime>
<anime id="9153" approval="1" total="9">Sakura-sou no Pet na Kanojo</anime>
<anime id="15013" approval="1" total="2">Arte</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="64">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="526796">It`s not bad at all, but I would recommend it only to people who already have a special interest in classical music. If you don`t love classical music, I think it`s safe to say there are better animes to spend your time with out there.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="270309">It`s a very good anime with plenty of humor and character developing. A must watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="152042">Slice of life, comedy and romance, a little tragedy as well and of course lots of classical music. Highly recommended if you liked Honey&amp;Clover (also other way around) or GTO. ^^&lt;br /&gt;Not recommended for people who value animation much over anything else.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="1">If you`re not allergic to school/music animes, then this one is a must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="7263">great!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="251414">Seriously best anime of 2007</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="334337">I went into this expecting more of a romantic comedy but the, much more emphasized, coming of age aspect is very appreciable too.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="206351">Great comedy, great music, and well-paced. Try this even if you don`t listen to classical music. There are some great, very likeable personalities in this show, even among the less important characters. It`s hilarious, yet the main characters do face some struggles, too.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="242315">best musical anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="681637">This good anime a solid 8/10 but it`s disappointing is so long i feel that what lets it down in the end from being a masterpiece.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="177593">Most fun I had watching/listening to an anime in a long time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="171530">One of the best animes I`ve ever seen!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="284709">Just a copy of my comment of the series, but it looks better to have some text than just nothing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I were really suspicious of this series, and have kept it on the shelf for a long time thinking it would be mediocre at best. I mean, classical music? Conducting? Orchestra? How good could that be? But I`m glad I decided to watch it finally. It`s absolutely hilarious and awesome. Alot different than I had expected.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For once there`s actually good animation on their instruments. Usually they just move randomly on their instruments and not at all to the music. But in this anime it`s really well timed and probably even the correct notes. It`s just the way it should be</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="120720">Great music-centric anime with Romance and Comedy sprinkled in for good measure. Goes for it`s sequel as well.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="570845">Breathtaking. After watching the final season, I can say with confidence that I will never see an anime like this again. Probably one of the least heard about and most underrated masterpieces of anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="254003">One of the best anime i`ve seen.&lt;br /&gt;Recommeneded for everyone! Great music, nice picture, wonderful story!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="82840">I`m really love this anime, Funny, good story, amazing music (even for does who don`t like classic music), It was a great time spent seeing this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I WANT MORE of Nodame</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="257875">Great anime, one of my favorites. If you are an anime fan this is one you DON"T want to miss.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="20281">one of the best i have ever seen</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="594938">MASTERPIECE! &amp; one of my most favorite anime ever, don`t even think about it watch it NOW! I guarantee you will laugh a lot &amp; even cry a bit at times but most of all you are going to have a really, really, really good time watching this, so good that the experience is going to be unforgettable.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="180244">A superb series.  It`s a music series that can appeal to more than just music lovers.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="292426">Type thing says it all</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="65644">The dynamic between the two main characters is basically unique! It has tons of awkward moments for both characters (mainly Nodame), and the music is just perfect!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="208034">The best anime I have ever watched</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="224473">i couldn`t even imagine that classical music can be so cool!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="614621">I watched all the episodes in 3 days... A MUST SEE.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="546492">Definitely must see. Good story, well defined characters, great pieces of music. Don`t skip on this one</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="163070">One of the best series I`ve ever watched. I laughed like a maniac, I yelled at my monitor like an idiot, and I cried like a baby... If you`ve already seen it then make sure you watch the live action as well, it is equally amazing!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="427701">Original characters and great music. Might not think there`s much to watch in a music anime but you`re very very wrong. Great Anime!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="247340">The best dramatic slice-of-life anime I have seen.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://nodame-anime.com/season1/</url>
<creators>
<name id="558" type="Original Work">Ninomiya Tomoko</name>
<name id="654" type="Direction">Kasai Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="739" type="Work">Genco</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="748" type="Work">Kodansha</name>
<name id="805" type="Work">Dentsu</name>
<name id="1142" type="Work">Sony Music Entertainment</name>
<name id="1237" type="Work">Asmik Ace Entertainment</name>
<name id="1273" type="Work">Sky Perfect Well Think</name>
<name id="2187" type="Character Design">Shimamura Hidekazu</name>
<name id="3501" type="Series Composition">Konparu Tomoko</name>
<name id="23403" type="Music">Nodame Orchestra</name>
<name id="4906" type="Music">Matsutani Suguru</name>
<name id="38408" type="Music">Toukyou-to Koukyou Gakudan</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the awarded shoujo manga by http://anidb.net/cr558 [Ninomiya Tomoko].
http://anidb.net/ch2128 [Chiaki Shin`ichi] is the top piano student at his university and an excellent violinist, but Chiaki doesn`t care about playing these instruments as much as he dreams of someday being a conductor. Chiaki, however, has several deeply rooted fears about traveling, and so finds himself trapped in Japan. Because he`s trapped, Chiaki starts to question exactly how far he can possibly go in music, especially when he`s passed over again and again for others he thinks are less worthy of musical scholarship and fame.
Recently dumped by his girlfriend for a sausage looking fellow, passed over for a chance to go overseas, removed from his star spot in the piano competition because he walked out on his piano instructor, Chiaki is at his limit. This is when he meets http://anidb.net/ch2106 [Nodame], or Noda Megumi. Nodame is a free — if filthy — spirit who reminds Chiaki that music can be fun. She reminds him what drew him to be a conductor in the first place and, in learning how to deal with Nodame, Chiaki learns how to deal with others. Chiaki begins to realize what is possible for him, even on the tiny island of Japan.
For Nodame, Chiaki is everything she isn`t. Clean, neat, dedicated, studious and inherently arrogant about his accomplishments and capabilities, Chiaki constantly bullies her into being more serious about life. He sees potential in her and her abilities as a pianist that she doesn`t care about. Nodame loves Chiaki and wants to be with him, but, because she`s not serious about her piano studies nor her personal hygiene, Chiaki denies her affections again and again.
But Chiaki and Nodame complete each other in ways no other can, a musical complement that neither of them can completely escape entirely. Watching them grow as people and musicians, and even as a couple, is an interesting ride.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7381">8.98</permanent>
<temporary count="7507">8.79</temporary>
<review count="12">8.21</review>
</ratings>
<picture>84035.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7010</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5656</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1698</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3965</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3850</identifier>
<identifier>hdrqem</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://nodame-anime.com/season1/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nodame_Cantabile</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>のだめカンタービレ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1025</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326415</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8684</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/nodame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2419" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-10-17">
<name>glutton</name>
<description>A character (who quite often is anything but fat) eats enough for an entire football team, usually devastating the whole table — and perhaps entire restaurants — with their insatiable hunger. Often combined with a speed-eating technique that makes food seem to vanish spontaneously from the plate.</description>
<picurl>239821.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3758" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-28">
<name>concert</name>
<description>The main characters play one or more live music performances during the show. This mostly happens for anime with the main focus on music.</description>
<picurl>169133.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3848" parentid="6348" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-02">
<name>preview in ed</name>
<description>For some reason the director decided to show the preview during the ending sequence.
In some cases the preview might be after the ending animation, but still during the ending theme.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4344" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-26">
<name>motivational anime</name>
<description>The anime motivates doing something which is shown in the show (for example club activity, sports, choosing a job, a hobby etc).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6348" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2015-02-19">
<name>old animetags - OP ED</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2106" type="main character in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="532">9.02</rating>
<name>Noda Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noda is, at the start of the series, a twenty-year-old free-spirited second-year music student. She is depicted as a complete slob: her cooking and cleaning skills are atrocious to the point of having mushrooms growing on her clothes. However she is an incredibly talented pianist who primarily plays by ear, in a cantabile style. In love with Chiaki, she follows him around constantly, claiming to be his wife, and leans on him to help her get through sticky situations. She sometimes compulsively needs to play the piano, neglecting everything in order to do it. She also seems to enjoy childish manga and movies. She is constantly hungry, and is fed dinners by Chiaki; she also steals many lunches from her fellow friend, Maki.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>139560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2128" type="main character in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="278">8.54</rating>
<name>Chiaki Shin`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiaki is twenty-one years old and a 3rd-year piano student at Momogaoka Music Academy at the start of the series. He is an accomplished pianist and violinist, but is also known to be a perfectionist and highly critical of himself and others. He comes from a distinguished and well-off family, and is a fairly good cook. He seems to think that most "poor" people (such as Sakura Saku) are like the little match girl. While he dreams of studying abroad and becoming a famous conductor like his mentor, Sebastiano Viella, he must overcome his fear of flying and the sea to do so. He is dismayed to discover that this freakish but talented girl, Nodame, lives in the apartment next door to him,. However, he develops a sort of empathy with Nodame as he discovers her hidden potential to be a great pianist, and he begins to transcend his perfectionism and begins to enjoy his music and the music of others.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>139562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2468" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-25">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Sebastiano Viella</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>World renowned conductor and Chiaki`s mentor. Stresemann is rather adverse towards Viella and initially extended his dislike of the conductor to Chiaki. Viella has considered Chiaki as his apprentice since the boy was twelve and is a surrogate father figure to Chiaki.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>2605.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2502" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="66">7.51</rating>
<name>Franz von Stresemann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stresemann is a highly respected and internationally famous conductor who comes to Momogaoka Music Academy as a guest instructor. In love with the Academy`s director, he comes as a favor and is immediately pegged as an oddball lecher. Perverted, demanding, and not at all dignified, Stresemann seems to be the opposite of what is expected from a man of his reputation. He, however, immediately takes to Nodame, and even accepts Chiaki as his one and only apprentice after repeatedly rejecting his application to enroll in his conducting classes. His wild behavior constantly gets Chiaki in trouble, but he also teaches him how to feel and express music in a way that only he can. He often takes his orchestra out for mixers or group dates, and goes to night clubs and host clubs (especially Club One More Kiss) instead of attending the rehearsals he is supposed to conduct. He also gets drunk easily, forcing Chiaki to take over for him as assistant conductor.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>2603.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="544" picture="238510.jpg">Ogawa Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2517" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="40">6.53</rating>
<name>Mine Ryuutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mine Ryuutarou is 2nd-year violin student at Momogaoka academy, Mine is something of a prima donna whose violin technique is seen by himself to be deeply personal but by others to be simply sloppy. He is a member of the academy`s S-Orchestra and the R☆S Orchestra. His father, http://anidb.net/ch2774 [Mine Tatsumi], owns a Chinese restaurant "Uraken" right next to the university.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>2617.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2518" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-23">
<rating votes="20">5.43</rating>
<name>Miki Kiyora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A prodigious violinist whom Chiaki meets at the Nina Lutz seminar and joins to form the R☆S Orchestra, Kiyora Miki studies abroad in Vienna and is a student of former Berlin Philharmonic Orchestra concertmaster, Kai Dowin.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>29822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2530" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="37">7.09</rating>
<name>Kuroki Yasunori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A talented oboe player who falls for Nodame at first sight (oblivious to her true nature) and performs the inaugural solo of the R☆S orchestra. Because he tends to be phlegmatic and quiet, many members of the R☆S orchestra think of him as "samurai-like".</description>
<picture>2604.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2531" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="25">3.57</rating>
<name>Okuyama Masumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A claustrophobic timpanist and an okama, 3rd-year studen Masumi has a crush on Chiaki and considers Nodame a rival and often bullies her and anyone else who tries to get close to Chiaki. Despite his idiosyncrasies, he excels on his percussion skills, earning him the title of "Queen of Percussion" and a place in the S and R☆S orchestras conducted by Chiaki.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>2616.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="408" picture="17255.jpg">Fujita Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2532" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-19">
<rating votes="5">4.68</rating>
<name>Tagaya Saiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiaki`s former girlfriend, Saiko is a rich songstress student who suffers heartbreak throughout the story. Despite pretending that she no longer cares for Chiaki, Saiko`s been in love with him all along. Later on, she realizes that Chiaki never truly cared for her - he loved her voice, and her voice alone.</description>
<picture>29607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2533" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="10">3.62</rating>
<name>Etou Kouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A piano teacher for the elites at Momogaoka Academy, Etou Sensei has been dubbed "the harisen teacher" because he always carries one during his classes and uses it to punish his students for their mistakes.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>25861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2560" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-21">
<rating votes="2">3.88</rating>
<name>Kikuchi Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A womanizing cello player and one of the founders of the R☆S Orchestra along Chiaki, Kiyora, and Kuroki. Easily recognizable by his crew cut and small glasses. He had been studying in Boston prior to the creation of the R☆S Orchestra, and at the end of that year, returned to Boston.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>29391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2561" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-21">
<rating votes="1">7.36</rating>
<name>Tanioka Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A piano teacher at Momogaoka, said to specialise in "drop-out" students. Chiaki is reassigned to Tanioka after his loud argument with Etou Kouzou in chapter 1. He discovers that Nodame is already a student of Tanioka`s, and one of the first assignments Tanioka assigns him is to perform a Mozart piano duet with Nodame, which also entails teaching her, and himself, the focus and discipline to play well with others.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>29606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2562" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Saku Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A double bass player and a member of the S-Orchestra. Short of height, Sakura is often mistaken to be an elementary student and with her instrument being larger than she is, people usually do not see her when she is carrying it on her back, believing it to be moving by itself.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2582" type="appears in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="24">5.96</rating>
<name>Charles Auclair</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Charles Auclair is a judge at the Maradona piano competition in which Nodame features as one of the contestants. He is quite taken with her performances and recommends her to apply for a place at the Paris conservatoire where he is a teacher.</description>
<picture>2593.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2594" type="appears in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="15">4.35</rating>
<name>Elise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elise is Stresemann`s jerky-chewing, hard-nosed agent, and business manager. Aided by her bodyguard Oliver she kidnapped Chiaki and forced him to sign with her agency too.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>2606.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2596" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Noda Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Youko is Nodame`s mother who moonlights as a dressmaker. She enjoys copying designer brands.</description>
<picture>30016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="580" picture="17973.jpg">Yuya Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2607" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Noda Tatsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nodame`s father and Fukuoka seaweed farmer. Noda Tatsuo also prides himself on being a Wadaiko (drum) performer at the local festival.</description>
<picture>30014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2608" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Noda Yoshitaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nodame`s brother and the brighter sibling of the Noda family, Yoshitaka is of an entrepreneurial bent and has an online store. He is university student.</description>
<picture>30015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2609" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Noda Kisaburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nodame`s paternal grandfather.</description>
<picture>30012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="587" picture="228627.jpg">Sonoe Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2610" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Noda Shizuyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nodame`s paternal grandmother.</description>
<picture>30013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="579" picture="25835.jpg">Uemura Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2620" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<rating votes="3">6.73</rating>
<name>Miyoshi Seiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seiko is Chiaki`s mother and a divorcee. She currently resides at her ancestral home with the Miyoshis and manages a foundation for disadvantaged students of the arts.</description>
<picture>2602.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2632" type="appears in" update="2010-01-18">
<rating votes="6">4.33</rating>
<name>Chiaki Masayuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A world famous pianist and Shin`ichi`s estranged father. Masayuki and Seiko, divorced each other when Shin`ichi was 12.
He primarily resides in Berlin.</description>
<picture>41641.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2633" type="appears in" update="2009-03-01">
<name>Miyoshi Takehiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shin`ichi`s maternal uncle and 2nd generation president of the Miyoshi corporation. He`s been taking care of Chiaki`s tuition and living expenses while at Momogaoka. But, in truth, he`d prefer it if Chiaki succeeds him in his business.</description>
<picture>2598.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2634" type="appears in" update="2009-03-01">
<name>Miyoshi Toshihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toshihiko is Shin`ichi`s cousin and used to idolise him when he was younger. He used to play the violin as well.</description>
<picture>2599.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2635" type="appears in" update="2010-05-01">
<rating votes="9">4.55</rating>
<name>Miyoshi Yuiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyoshi Yuiko is http://anidb.net/ch2128 [Chiaki]`s cousin and addresses him as Shin-niichama. While initially unimpressed with http://anidb.net/ch2106 [Nodame], they get along famously later on.</description>
<picture>2600.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2636" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<name>Miyoshi Seiichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiaki`s maternal grandfather and a musical mentor of sorts. Seiichirou passed away a few years back and the Miyoshi household has not been the same ever since.
He used to play the cello and frequently invited other musicians for impromptu concerts in his salon. He held Edward Elgar in high esteem.</description>
<picture>31670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="609" picture="1835.gif">Aomori Shin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2720" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-28">
<rating votes="5">5.55</rating>
<name>Suzuki Moe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suzuki Moe is a flautist and part of the S-Orchestra. Moe is the twin sister of http://anidb.net/ch2721 [Kaoru] and is distinguished by her permed hairstyle.</description>
<picture>30021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2721" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-26">
<rating votes="4">5.42</rating>
<name>Suzuki Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A clarinetist and part of the S-Orchestra. Kaoru is the twin sister of Moe and is distinguished by her straight hairstyle.</description>
<picture>30022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2746" type="appears in" update="2009-03-03">
<name>Nina Lutz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A renowned French pianist and instructor, Nina is also a friend of the Chiaki family. She conducts an annual seminar and festival where experts from around the world hold master classes for budding musicians in Japan.</description>
<picture>2615.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="653" picture="18181.jpg">Tsuda Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2755" type="appears in" update="2009-01-27">
<name>Momogaoka Conservatory</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Momogaoka conservatory is a prestigious institution situated in Tokyo. It includes the Momogaoka College of Music (桃ヶ丘音楽大学) and the Momogaoka Graduate School of Music (桃ヶ丘音楽大学大学院).</description>
</character>
<character id="2764" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-26">
<rating votes="1">9.00</rating>
<name>Momodaira Minako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The current director of the Momogaoka Conservatory, Mina was a virtuoso pianist when young, but had to retire due to an illness. She is good friends with Stresemann and Doone and invites them both to teach at her institution.</description>
<picture>30026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="494" picture="17485.jpg">Ichijou Miyuki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2765" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Momodaira Sayoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31754.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2766" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-23">
<rating votes="1">3.62</rating>
<name>Kai Duun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Berlin string quartet and a visiting instructor at the Momogaoka Conservatory. He is also Miki Kiyora`s teacher.</description>
<picture>29821.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2767" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-26">
<rating votes="2">6.28</rating>
<name>Sakuma Manabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A music critic for Classic Life magazine and an enthusiastic fan of Chiaki. His favourite composer is Rachmaninoff.</description>
<picture>30020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2768" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-24">
<rating votes="3">4.92</rating>
<name>Kawano Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The editor of Classic Life magazine and a fan of Chiaki ever since she saw him at the Nina Lutz festival.</description>
<picture>29844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2769" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-21">
<rating votes="1">1.70</rating>
<name>Ookawa Soutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A music critic for a national newspaper.</description>
<picture>30017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="688" picture="18295.jpg">Tanaka Kan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2770" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Segawa Yuuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A pianist and childhood acquaintance of Nodame`s. Segawa is also a competitor in the Maradona piano competition. He is always chaperoned by his overprotective mother.</description>
<picture>30029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2771" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-21">
<name>Tanaka Makiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A piano major and one of Nodame`s friends at Momogaoka.</description>
<picture>29609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="690" picture="187038.jpg">Higa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2772" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Suganuma Saya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saiko`s classmate and rival.</description>
<picture>30030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2773" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="5">4.69</rating>
<name>Etou Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harisen`s wife. Kaori and Kouzou host Nodame while she trains for the Maradona piano competition.</description>
<picture>29390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2774" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-23">
<rating votes="2">8.37</rating>
<name>Mine Tatsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The senior Mine is the owner of the Chinese restaurant `Uraken` and also one of the sponsors of the Rising Star Orchestra.</description>
<picture>29823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2777" type="appears in" update="2009-06-24">
<name>Takahashi Noriyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A world-class violinist who passes on an offer from the entertainment world to join the Rising Star Orchestra as its new concertmaster instead. He is enamoured with Chiaki.</description>
<picture>29845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2778" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-26">
<rating votes="4">2.17</rating>
<name>Kimura Tomohito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A violinist and a member of the Rising Star Orchestra. Kimura is good friends with Mine and prefer to communicate with each other via snail-mail.</description>
<picture>30023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4149" type="appears in" update="2009-07-23">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Oliver</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elise`s beefy assistant.</description>
<picture>2607.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10578" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Ookouchi Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="465" picture="56019.jpg">Kondou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10579" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="3">3.04</rating>
<name>Gorota</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Protagonist character of Puri Gorota (プリごろ太) anime.</description>
<picture>31582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="257" picture="17078.jpg">Kudou Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10580" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Puririn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A fairy from outer space.</description>
<picture>31584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10581" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Kazuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3833" picture="25459.jpg">Shibahara Chiyako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10582" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Riona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10583" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Michael</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="610" picture="18093.jpg">Ooyama Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10584" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Saku Hidemi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10585" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Kinjou Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A viola player and a member of the S-Orchestra</description>
<picture>31589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2355" picture="223496.jpg">Tachibana Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10586" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Odagiri Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Piano course professor. The one of http://anidb.net/ch10587 ["Professor Trio"]. Nickname: Onigiri (おにぎり).</description>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10587" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Kyouju Trio</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Professor Trio.</description>
<picture>31592.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10588" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Nakamura Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A violin professor and one of http://anidb.net/ch10587 [Professor Trio].</description>
<picture>31596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6849" picture="186209.jpg">Mori Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10589" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Kiyo Boskovich</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10592" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Yamamoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4032" picture="77662.jpg">Okamoto Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10593" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Tamaki Keiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A clarinetist and a member of S-Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2364" picture="151724.jpg">Furushima Kiyotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10594" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="1">1.34</rating>
<name>Hashimoto Youhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An oboist and a member of S-Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10595" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-21">
<rating votes="2">1.39</rating>
<name>Inoue Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cello player and a member of S-Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10613" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<name>Sakata Chiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyoshi family`s maid.
She was credited in anime as Chiyo-san (千代さん).</description>
<picture>31672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4900" picture="28280.jpg">Sasamori Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10614" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<name>Gert Fischer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hypnotherapy counselor from Germany.</description>
<picture>31673.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10646" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<name>Yuuji-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10647" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<name>S Orchestra</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>31689.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10648" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A viola player and a member of S orchestra.</description>
<picture>31693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10652" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Iwai Kazushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A double bass player and a member of S Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31771.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10659" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-21">
<rating votes="8">4.39</rating>
<name>Ishikawa Rena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nodame`s friend studying at piano course. She played a pianica at festival with disguised S Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10660" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<name>Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10661" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<name>Yukko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10663" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Hans</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="325" picture="223404.jpg">Akagi Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10664" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Rising Star Orchestra</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>31730.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10667" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Tsuboi Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10668" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<rating votes="3">2.34</rating>
<name>Matsuda Yukihisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10670" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Segawa Yurie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10671" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Katayama Tomoharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A horn player.</description>
<picture>31759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10672" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Aizawa Maiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A flute player and a member of Rising Star Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6916" picture="187044.jpg">Sekiyama Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10673" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Hanazakura-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66945" type="appears in" update="2014-04-21">
<name>Miho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="593" picture="17990.jpg">Honda Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="66708" update="2008-04-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="35">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66709" update="2007-03-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="28">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66710" update="2007-03-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="22">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66711" update="2007-03-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66744" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="20">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66745" update="2007-03-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66746" update="2007-03-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="19">9.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66747" update="2007-03-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="20">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66748" update="2007-03-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66749" update="2007-03-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66750" update="2007-03-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="28">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66751" update="2007-04-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66752" update="2007-04-04">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66753" update="2007-04-04">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66951" update="2007-04-04">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67335" update="2007-05-18">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67336" update="2007-04-04">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67413" update="2007-04-04">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68497" update="2007-04-04">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68498" update="2007-04-04">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68499" update="2007-04-04">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68500" update="2007-04-04">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68501" update="2007-08-11">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="27">9.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80128" update="2015-06-19">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="3">2.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Allegro Cantabile PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88248" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">のだめと千秋の海物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nodame and Chiaki`s Summer Tales</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nodame to Chiaki no Umi Monogatari</title>
<summary>Special lesson about their travel to Nagano.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="97426" update="2020-02-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97427" update="2020-02-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112409" update="2020-02-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2007-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリごろ太 宇宙の友情大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Puri Gorota</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Prigorota: Uchuu no Yuujou Daibouken</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Puri Gorota: La gran aventura espacial de gran amistad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129609" update="2020-02-18">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129610" update="2020-02-18">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Puri Gorota trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129611" update="2020-02-18">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Commercial 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129612" update="2020-02-18">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Commercial 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129613" update="2020-02-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129614" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227083" update="2020-02-22">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
