<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="477" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-01-05</startdate>
<enddate>2002-06-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Patapata Hikousen no Bouken</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Adventures of Patapata Aircraft</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Secret of Cerulean Sand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Patapata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SOCS</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">パタパタ飛行船の冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Le secret du sable bleu</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Il Segreto della sabbia</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">الطاقة الزرقاء</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="40" approval="14" total="15">Fushigi no Umi no Nadia</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="183578">Could`ve been a great Ghibliesque adventure - if much more effort had been put into writing, directing and animating this. It`s still decent and even enjoyable as it is, but people over ten will likely find their attention lapsing.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.telecom-anime.com/patapata/japanese/</url>
<creators>
<name id="900" type="Animation Work">Telecom Animation Film</name>
<name id="8928" type="Character Design">Hachizaki Kenji</name>
<name id="9557" type="Direction">Yano Yuuichirou</name>
<name id="5973" type="Original Work">Jules Verne</name>
<name id="7894" type="Story Composition">Takeuchi Kouji</name>
<name id="9557" type="Story Composition">Yano Yuuichirou</name>
<name id="32525" type="Story Composition">Furuya Keiichirou</name>
<name id="4051" type="Music">Ikeda Daisuke</name>
<name id="54820" type="Music">Nakagawa Toshio</name>
</creators>
<description>* Inspired by and loosely based on http://anidb.net/cr5973 [Jules Verne]`s stories: Facing the Flag and The City in the Sahara.
A young lady of the noble Buxton family, http://anidb.net/ch37498 [Jane], is a vivid and cheerful girl, whose long yearning dream is to fly into the clouds and beyond. Being surrounded by the love of her family members as well as that of the servants, Jane`s life was a relatively happy one. Her emotions, however, are in turmoil when a letter arrives informing that Jane`s eldest and beloved brother, http://anidb.net/ch37499 [George], who was participating on the expedition to the East, was executed. At the same time, Jane`s stepbrother, http://anidb.net/ch37494 [William], leaves the family due to the protracted feud with their father, who soon after is charged for embezzling.
Days pass by and one day, Jane receives an envelope sent anonymously. Inside, there is a tiny piece of cerulean stone and right in front of Jane`s eyes a mysterious phenomenon occurs... "Could this be the Floating Water George was searching for?" "And could this be a letter sent by George?" Jane wonders. Convinced of George`s survival, Jane decides to embark on a quest to the unknown land in the East to find her brothers.
An adventure begins that will lead her from the safety of her English manor house to the vast foreboding deserts of the Middle East and then to isolated mountain trails somewhere in the Caucasus. Chasing after various clues appearing only as hushed rumours and forgotten legends, Jane and her protective fellow travellers find themselves having to fight off a band of soldiers equipped with strange airships, who are seemingly intent on keeping the Cerulean Sand a secret from all outsiders.
Note: This series was a co-production between Japanese and Korean animation teams and was aired simultaneously in both countries.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="214">6.64</permanent>
<temporary count="214">7.23</temporary>
<review count="2">7.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>66084.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>309</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>708</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775</identifier>
<identifier>qdzmjw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.telecom-anime.com/?works=page06</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/search/index.php?pdt_no=119</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/english/search/index.php?pdt_no=189</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Secret_of_Cerulean_Sand</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>パタパタ飛行船の冒険</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2688</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>236611</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5059</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/786</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="17">
<externalentity>
<identifier>patapata</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="569" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-18">
<name>clumsy</name>
<description>A clumsy person is one lacking in coordination, and as such prone to often having accidents such as tripping, bumping into objects, or dropping things. In female characters, this is often thought of as endearing.</description>
<picurl>63355.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1492" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-21">
<name>mask</name>
<description>Masks are items normally worn on the face. Their uses range from medical (example: oxygen mask) to disguise (avoiding recognition). They can also be used for entertainment (for example, in theater or dance), and may even be forced upon someone as punishment. Masks have been in use since ancient times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2091" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>blimp</name>
<description>An blimp or dirigible balloon is a type of aerostat or lighter-than-air aircraft that can navigate through the air under its own power. Aerostats gain their lift from large gas bags filled with a lifting gas that is less dense than the surrounding air.</description>
<picurl>221611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2419" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-10-17">
<name>glutton</name>
<description>A character (who quite often is anything but fat) eats enough for an entire football team, usually devastating the whole table — and perhaps entire restaurants — with their insatiable hunger. Often combined with a speed-eating technique that makes food seem to vanish spontaneously from the plate.</description>
<picurl>239821.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2487" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>charismatic</name>
<description>Charisma is a compelling attractiveness or charm that can inspire devotion in others.&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2835" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Africa</name>
<description>The world`s second-largest continent and the birthplace of the human species, Africa is a place of a huge diversity, with deserts and savannas, with famine and precious stones, with cultural and economical riches of all kinds. Throughout history, Africa has been the cradle of empires and has been ruled by foreign powers, and as of the early 21st century sees swift changes and economic boom going side by side with inhuman levels of poverty.</description>
<picurl>126530.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3826" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-26">
<name>evil laugh</name>
<description>The thing all great evil villains do after saying/doing something evil.
Some notable examples of great evil villains with evil laughs: Dr. Evil, Dr. Horrible, The Joker, Lelouche, Light, and Mickey Mouse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6115" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-02">
<name>omimai</name>
<description>Visiting a sick person (as in a hospital or at home).
The protagonist or any other character caught a cold so his friends go visit him. In a school setting this is used as a plot device to allow fellow students to show their concern, and it is also a pertinent excuse to get out of school.</description>
<picurl>160896.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="37494" type="main character in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>William F Buxton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>William is Jane`s stepbrother.</description>
<picture>66128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37495" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>Edward Buxton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Edward is Jane`s father. He is charged for embezzling shortly after a dispute with William.</description>
<picture>66181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="385" picture="215702.jpg">Tsukada Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37496" type="main character in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>Sabri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sabri is an orphan who later helps Jane and joins their expedition.</description>
<picture>66182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30649" picture="82105.jpg">Mizuma Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37497" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>San Bellan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>San Bellan is a stubborn old butler, but he always assists and protects his young mistress.</description>
<picture>66206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="599" picture="226547.jpg">Naya Rokurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37498" type="main character in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Jane Buxton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jane dreams since her childhood of flying, in search of a trace of her long-deceased mother beyond the sky. In search of her brother who has vanished somewhere in the far away land in the East, she departs for a great journey.</description>
<picture>66050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2034" picture="83417.jpg">Kogure Ema</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37499" type="main character in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>George Buxton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>George is Jane`s older beloved brother. He is announced as being sentenced and shot a traitor while in search for a secret flying ship but an anonymously sent letter leads Jane to believe that he is still alive.</description>
<picture>66127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29981" picture="233420.jpg">Suzuki Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37500" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>Sky</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37501" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>Christophe Balzac</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Christophe Balzac is a real gentleman, but he seems to be hiding something from Jane.</description>
<picture>66209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37502" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>Marcenay</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37503" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>Moririre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5410" update="2003-01-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バクストン家の三兄妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Buxton`s Family`s 3 Brother and Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les héritiers Buxton</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5411" update="2003-01-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな亀裂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Little Crack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un léger malentendu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5412" update="2003-01-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">滲み出した黒い陰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Shadow That Permeates</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une ombre furtive dans la nuit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5413" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての航海</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le voyage en mer (1re partie)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5414" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">船乗りの勲章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Badge of a Sailor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le voyage en mer (2e partie)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5415" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バルザックさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mr. Barsac</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystérieux Monsieur Barsac</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5511" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい出会い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De nouvelles rencontres</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5512" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂漠へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To The Desert</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans le désert</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5513" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂嵐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sandstorm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tempête de sable</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5514" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私に出来ること</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Things I Can Do</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Que faire ?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5515" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">難破船と青い砂の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of the Shipwreck and the Cerulean Sand</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère de l’épave au sable bleu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5516" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">機械盗賊団~前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mechanical Bandit Band - Prologue</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`attaque des luges mécaniques (1re partie)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5517" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">機械盗賊団~後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mechanical Bandit Band - Epilogue</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`attaque des luges mécaniques (2e partie)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5518" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モリリレの正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Morilire`s True Character</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mais qui est donc Morilire ?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5519" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おたがいの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Each Other`s Secrets</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À chacun ses secrets</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5520" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジョージ ここに眠る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">George Rests Here</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La tombe de George</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5521" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Flight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le baptême de l`air</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5522" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネオシティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Neo City</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Neo City</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5523" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カマレ博士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Professor Camaret</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Professeur Kamale</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5524" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃亡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`évasion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5525" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">浮遊泉の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of the Floating Liquid</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret de l’Azurium</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5526" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">侵入</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Infiltration</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’heure de vérité</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5527" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une révélation surprenante</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5528" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帝国の崩壊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Collapse of an Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chute de l’Empire</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5529" update="2007-06-25">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛行機械プロミネンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flying Machine Prominence</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le vaisseau maudit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5530" update="2011-10-07">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジェーンより愛を込めて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Jane, With Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le temps des adieux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jane Yori Ai o Komete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90319" update="2008-04-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90320" update="2008-04-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
