<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4778" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>5</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-03-20</startdate>
<enddate>2007-04-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Keitai Shoujo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Cell Phone Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Garota do Celular</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Момичето с телефон</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">手机少女</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ケータイ少女</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.ktai-s.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="985" type="Animation Work">Studio Hibari</name>
<name id="4511" type="Character Design">Watanabe Mayumi</name>
<name id="6519" type="Direction">Yabuki Tsutomu</name>
<name id="29314" type="Original Work">G-mode</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch12741 [Aida Hiro] is in his second year of high school. All of his previous encounters with love went without reciprocation., but it`s not unheard of for a 17 year-old-boy attending an all boys` school not to have much love experience. Still, he cannot be happy, being both unable to whole-heartedly pursue the opposite sex and fulfill his romantic curiosity.
However, he is able to experience true romantic love when he encounters the Keitai Girl, http://anidb.net/ch12748 [Rin].
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="503">2.28</permanent>
<temporary count="509">5.35</temporary>
<review count="1">4.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>149409.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7480</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1725</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3879</identifier>
<identifier>ocxipf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ktai-s.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ケータイ少女</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1115</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327040</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8887</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1010</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="12741" type="main character in" update="2009-11-05">
<rating votes="1">2.54</rating>
<name>Aida Hiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38336.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12742" type="main character in" update="2009-11-05">
<name>Mishima Ichiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12743" type="main character in" update="2009-11-05">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Yamada Ayano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12744" type="main character in" update="2009-11-05">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Tomoe Sayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12745" type="main character in" update="2009-11-05">
<rating votes="2">6.55</rating>
<name>Gotou Miya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12746" type="main character in" update="2009-11-05">
<name>Fujimiya Momoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12747" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-05">
<name>Kotaka Keisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38343.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12748" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-05">
<name>Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38337.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="69001" update="2007-03-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2007-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">着信1 美島いちる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call 1: Mishima Ichiru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chakushin 1: Mishima Ichiru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69002" update="2007-03-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2007-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">着信2 巴沙代</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call 2: Tomoe Sayo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chakushin 2: Tomoe Sayo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69003" update="2007-03-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2007-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">着信3 後刀美弥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call 3: Gotou Miya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chakushin 3: Gotou Miya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69004" update="2007-03-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2007-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">着信4 藤宮桃香</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call 4: Fujimiya Momoka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chakushin 4: Fujimiya Momoka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69005" update="2007-03-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2007-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">着信5 山田綾乃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call 5: Yamada Ayano</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chakushin 5: Yamada Ayano</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73720" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<rating votes="2">2.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Epilogue (includes Call 2)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82966" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD summary special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82967" update="2007-09-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118662" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
