<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4792" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>2007-06-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shinkyoku Soukai Polyphonica</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Shinkyoku Sokai Polyphonica</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">神曲奏界</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="short">Полифоника</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Polyphonica</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="short">Поліфоніка</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">神曲奏界ポリフォニカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Polyphonica</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6224" type="Prequel">Shinkyoku Soukai Polyphonica: Crimson S</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/polyphonica/</url>
<creators>
<name id="961" type="Animation Work">Ginga Ya</name>
<name id="1785" type="Series Composition">Sakaki Ichirou</name>
<name id="1785" type="Original Work">Sakaki Ichirou</name>
<name id="2302" type="Music">Nanase Hikaru</name>
<name id="3849" type="Character Design">Horiuchi Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="4138" type="Direction">Shimoda Masami</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the light novel `Crimson` Polyphonica series by http://anidb.net/cr1785 [Sakaki Ichirou] which in turn is based on a visual novel by the same writer.
Human beings rely on the miracles of fairies, while the fairies that have materialized in this world survive on the music played by humans. The fairies` powers are directed by Dantists, who play special music and are widely respected.
Most fairies do not usually appear, but some have enough power to materialize in the shapes of human beings or animals to spend their time living in peace together with mankind.
http://anidb.net/ch4190 [Conticarte] and a new Dantist, http://anidb.net/ch4191 [Phoron], discover their love for each other living in Polyphonica, a continent where people and fairies live together in harmony.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="928">4.04</permanent>
<temporary count="942">6.50</temporary>
<review count="2">5.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>153500.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7479</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1727</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3987</identifier>
<identifier>asqyjg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/polyphonica/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shinkyoku_Sōkai_Polyphonica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>神曲奏界ポリフォニカ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1117</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327042</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8807</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1696</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>228</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/polyphonica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3664" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>futuristic motorcycle</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3696" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-28">
<name>off-model animation</name>
<description>Anime shows tend to most often run on an already tight budget; some have even tighter ones. Thus, over the years it became a norm to invest more time and money into the first and last episode, leaving many episodes in the middle to stand severe budget restrictions. This sometimes results in episodes which particularly stand out due to the drop in artwork or animation quality; bar some basic framework, they often have little in common with the rest of the series.
One clue to upcoming off-model animation is the noticeable addition of many Korean names in the production credits, as farming out more animation to Korean artists is a nearly universal indicator of a production company trying to save money in all possible ways.
This effect is often called yashigani, after the infamous http://anidb.net/e4682 [fourth episode] of http://anidb.net/a403 [Lost Universe], Yashigani Hoburu. Another prominent term describing the same effect is "QUALITY animation", with capital letters meant to show contrast to actual quality. http://anidb.net/a4531 [Yoake Mae yori Ruriiro na: Crescent Love] is another legendarily terrible offender: the TV airing of its http://anidb.net/e63752 [third episode] had a perfectly spherical ball in place of what should be a cabbage; the "cabbage" was so egregious that it became closely associated with the anime itself, to a point the show would henceforth be nicknamed "Cabbage Love" among Western viewers.
One should not confuse the yashigani effect with art shifts that stem from guest staff, changes in main staff, intentional art shifts, and similar effects. Another effect one shouldn`t confuse this one with is the so-called DVD/BD enhancement, which is when a studio scrambles to meet the deadline for a TV airing and airs a half-finished episode but eventually fixes it for a disk release; for example, http://anidb.net/cr792 [Shaft] is particularly infamous for its disk enhancements, to a point it has become known as "Shafting", and they prominently feature intentionally weird character models, but they don`t often leave bad artwork on the disk release. Additionally, it should also not be confused with intentional lack of detail on background plane characters; this effect is instead when even the foreground has art quality shifting over time due to the aforementioned budget restrictions.</description>
<picurl>29532.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4190" type="main character in" update="2015-09-04">
<rating votes="37">8.40</rating>
<name>Corticarte Apa Lagranges</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The spirit Tatara made a contract with. Corti, as Phoron calls her, is one of the eldest spirits in their world, having eight wings and called the Red Elder Spirit— as well as other titles such as Crimson Annihilator or Bloody Duchess. She is entranced by young Phoron`s singing voice and thus decides to make a pact with him so he will be hers only.
Most of the time, Corti has the appearance of a child. She has a selfish character and dislikes it when Phoron is being kind to other girls.</description>
<picture>177084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4191" type="main character in" update="2015-09-04">
<rating votes="11">4.87</rating>
<name>Tatara Phoron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main protagonist. Phoron is a Dantist working in the Tsuge Divine Music Player Office. Although he is the master of the Red spirit, Corticarte is the one in control. He plays an organ-like instrument that can transform into a motorbike. He also uses a backpack piano-like One-Man Orchestra in occasions where he cannot use his motorbike.</description>
<picture>20184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4192" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-04">
<rating votes="20">5.73</rating>
<name>Yugiri Perserte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Prinesca`s older twin sister. Her sole purpose for coming to the Tsuge Divine Music Player Office seems to be meeting with Phoron.</description>
<picture>20185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4193" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-04">
<rating votes="20">6.23</rating>
<name>Yugiri Prinesca</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Prinesca is Perserte`s younger twin sister. She also works at Tsuge Divine Music Player Office. Everyone in the office usually addresses her as Prine except Phoron.</description>
<picture>20186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4194" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-04">
<rating votes="23">5.09</rating>
<name>Tsuge Eufinley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The boss of the Tsuge Divine Music Player Office. She has a very strict character about jobs, and plays a violin-like instrument. She has a contract with two spirit, Yardio and Mashat, of whom the latter is seldom seen.</description>
<picture>20187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4195" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-04">
<rating votes="13">4.06</rating>
<name>Saiki Renbart</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Phoron`s friend and co-worker in Tsuge Divine Music Player Office. He plays a saxophone-like instrument, and is usually seen with small two-winged fairies. He has not made a contract with a spirit.</description>
<picture>20188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4196" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-04">
<rating votes="2">7.53</rating>
<name>Yardio Voda Munagoul</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eufinley`s covenant spirit. On the day they meet, Yardio quickly tried to make a covenant by kissing her, but received a punch in his face instead. He is a laid back character in contrast to the more serious Eufinley. He also likes to fight, and his power level is above most four winged spirits. Unlike Corti, Yardio is more blatant in showing that he likes Eufinley.</description>
<picture>20189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4197" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-02">
<rating votes="2">3.61</rating>
<name>Akatsuki Dirrane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious Dantist that first appeared in episode 3. He seems to have a great dislike for spirits, and especially hates Mailreit (his own spirit). He plays a piano-like instrument that is disguised as a suitcase.</description>
<picture>20190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4198" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-02">
<rating votes="3">4.65</rating>
<name>Mailreit</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mailreit is the spirit that made a contract with Akatsuki, though she doesn`t seem to be happy being with him. It is said that Mailreit has good underwater battle skills. Ever since Dirrane began hating her, she pretended to be able to feel his Commandia, even though their soul can`t connect and gives her a lack of power.</description>
<picture>20191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10023" type="appears in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Matia Machiya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Police captain of special department.
A silent girl with long black hair, black eyes, and a black cape. Although at first it seems she`s the Spirit, Matia is actually the Dantist, and a good one.
Her instrument is a blues harp. Although not as complicated as a One-Man Orchestra, it is similar to the instruments of the past which require higher technique to play Commandia with.</description>
<picture>30221.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10024" type="appears in" update="2009-06-28">
<name>Managariastinockle Lagu Edraikerius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Managa is Matia`s covenant spirit. He is described as big, wearing all black and eyes like a bear. When together with Matia, they look like father and daughter.
Managa is actually a gentle person. He is a three winged spirit, which is not natural, and his wings also look torn and battered. In the timeline of the White series, he looks younger and has six black wings colored in gold. As an old spirit, he and Corti had met, but when they meet again, they don`t recognize each other because their different forms. Managa is also the Black Beast which means he is meant to protect the black goddess.</description>
<picture>30224.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77217" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-04">
<rating votes="6">4.99</rating>
<name>Corticarte Apa Lagranges</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="68467" update="2017-02-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">第0話~プロローグ 「お前の歌――良かったぞ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 0: Prologue - Your Song Was Good</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 0 Wa: Prologue - Omae no Uta... Yokatta zo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71656" update="2007-04-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレリュード 紅の精霊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prelude: The Crimson Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Prelude: Aka no Seirei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71658" update="2007-04-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オペレッタ 見つめる精霊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operetta: The Watching Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Operetta: Mitsumeru Seirei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72016" update="2007-04-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポルカ 海の底の忘れ物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Polka: The Left-Behind Item on the Ocean Bed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Polka: Umi no Soko no Wasuremono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72173" update="2007-04-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダルセーニョ 始まりの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dal Segno: The Day It All Began</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dal Segno: Hajimari no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72400" update="2007-05-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アッファンナート 裏切りの絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Affannato: The Bond of Betrayal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Affannato: Uragiri no Kizuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72544" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スケルツォ 傍にいる理由</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scherzo: The Reason to Be Together</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Scherzo: Soba ni Iru Riyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72545" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴァイオレンツァ 黒い追跡者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Violenza: Black Pursuers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Violenza: Kuroi Tsuisekisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72546" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">セレナーデ 人と精霊の狭間に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Serenade: Between Human and Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Serenade: Hito to Seirei no Hazama ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72547" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラプソディ とある神曲楽士の話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rhapsody: The Tale of a Divine Song Player</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rhapsody: Toaru Shinkyoku Gakushi no Hanashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72548" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バラード 愛憎の決着</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ballad: What Comes After Hatred</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ballad: Aizou no Kecchaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72549" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レクイエム 歌う精霊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Requiem: The Singing Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Requiem: Utau Seirei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72550" update="2007-05-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シンフォニー 虹の楽曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Symphony: The Divine Song of the Rainbow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Symphony: Niji no Gakkyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80429" update="2010-06-30">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">NC OP&amp;ED</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87775" update="2017-02-04">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">9.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87776" update="2017-02-04">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">9.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87777" update="2017-02-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">9.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87778" update="2017-02-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
