<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="481" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>19</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-10-22</startdate>
<enddate>2001-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gakkou no Kaidan</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ghost Stories in School</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ghosts at School</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">School`s Ghost Story</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Школьные истории о привидениях</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">قصة شبح المدرسة</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="synonym">Bújj,bújj szellem</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">学校の怪談</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ghost Stories</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">학교괴담</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Histórias de Fantasmas</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Strašidelné historky</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Bújj, bújj szellem!</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Povestiri cu Fantome</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Historias de Fantasmas</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6785" approval="20" total="21">Kaidan Restaurant</anime>
<anime id="2100" approval="4" total="6">Jigoku Sensei Nube</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="144147">the english version of this show is one of the funniest things I`ve ever watched</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="449787">Not bad for ghost stories, but with so many predictable plots and ways to defeat monsters are too easy, it become less interesting after 6 episodes above. Overall, its still watchable and english dubs makes me laugh on it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="364222">The best English dub in history! Must watch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/title/kaidan/</url>
<creators>
<name id="5442" type="Series Composition">Hashimoto Hiroshi</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="842" type="Work">SPE Visual Works</name>
<name id="724" type="Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="4566" type="Direction">Abe Noriyuki</name>
<name id="2703" type="Music">Wada Kaoru</name>
<name id="6428" type="Character Design">Oonishi Masaya</name>
</creators>
<description>Satsuki Miyanoshita and her younger brother Keichiro moved from Tokyo to their mother`s hometown who died after a long illness. Not long after they moved in, they discovered that the old abandoned school building near their new school is haunted by demons and evil spirits. At first, they don`t seem want to get involved with it, not until their family cat, Kaya, is taken by a demon. In order to save the town, Satsuki and her younger brother Keichiro along with their new friends, Momoko, Reo and Hajime forms a team to fight those demons.
[i]Note: This anime was originally supposed to have a completely different episode 3 titled "Am I Pretty? Hairlip Girl" (あたし, きれい? 口裂け女). But due to protests from people with cleft lip and palate, the episode was not put on air and the studio quickly made a recap/summary episode of the two previous episodes for the broadcast day of 05.11.2000. The original episode 3 was never released to the public. Furthermore, the broadcast of episode 19 was skipped. It did eventually air on TV on 24.08.2001, but the producers had labelled it as a special, not part of the regular episode numbering.
Another recap/summary episode aired on 03.01.2001.[/i]</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="811">5.99</permanent>
<temporary count="819">7.09</temporary>
<review count="2">8.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>18618.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1736</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22055</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>30825</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1281</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>905</identifier>
<identifier>oecwhc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/title/kaidan/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ghost_Stories_(anime)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>学校の怪談_(テレビアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>933</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>163160</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4254" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-01-24">
<name>ghost hunting</name>
<description>Ghost Hunting is the process of investigating locations that are reported to be haunted by ghosts. Typically, a ghost hunting team will attempt to collect evidence claimed to be supportive of paranormal activity. Ghost hunters often utilize a variety of electronic equipment.
Traditional techniques such as conducting interviews and researching the history of a site are also employed. Some ghost hunters refer to themselves as a paranormal investigator.
While many groups claim to utilize scientific methods in their search for the ghosts, no scientific body has been able to confirm the existence of ghosts. Ghost hunting can be classified as a pseudoscience.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5781" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-01">
<name>exorcism</name>
<description>Eviction of demons or other spiritual entities from a person or place which they are believed to have possessed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="45295" type="main character in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="3">5.76</rating>
<name>Miyanoshita Satsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3425.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45297" type="main character in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="2">3.38</rating>
<name>Miyanoshita Keiichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3427.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2766" picture="181834.jpg">Mamiya Kurumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45299" type="main character in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="3">6.87</rating>
<name>Aoyama Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3428.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45300" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<name>Kakinoki Reo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3429.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2898" picture="228086.jpg">Tsumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45301" type="main character in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="6">7.15</rating>
<name>Koigakubo Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3430.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="568" picture="65531.jpg">Sakuma Kumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45302" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-26">
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<name>Amanojaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>It`s a demon who was sealed in body of cat named Kaya. He sometimes helps main characters. Especially he likes Keiichirou</description>
<picture>88562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45303" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="2">5.55</rating>
<name>Miyanoshita Kayako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45304" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>Miyanoshita Reiichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5650" picture="30095.jpg">Murozono Takehiro</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45305" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>Sakata-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45306" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Matsushima-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5322" picture="29436.jpg">Fukamizu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45307" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>Akagami Aogami</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="418" picture="17270.jpg">Hirose Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45309" type="appears in" update="2012-06-26">
<name>Toilet no Hanako-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45310" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Mary-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45311" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>Piano Obake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45312" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Da Vinci</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45314" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Datto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6826" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死者からの鎮魂歌[レクイエム]エリーゼ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dead Man`s Requiem - Fur Elise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shisha kara no Requiem Elise</title>
<summary>While in the old schoolhouse, Satsuki hears a haunting melody drifting through the halls. The only trouble is the lack of a pianist! It seems that if Satsuki hears the melody a total of four times, she`ll die. The gang saddles up to put the ghostly piano to sleep.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692601</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6827" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">開演!! 呪いの学芸会くたべ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raise the curtain!! Cursed school arts festival - Kutabe!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaien!! Noroi no Gakugeikai Kutabe</title>
<summary>The big play is coming up, but the boy in the lead role is scared. He makes a wish for the gymnasium to catch fire--and it does. Then, when the play moves to being held in the old schoolhouse, the boy wishes to be injured--and he is! It seems another ghost needs to be put to sleep, and soon, before Leo gets hurt. Or worse.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692599</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6828" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トイレから手首が... 赤紙青紙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Out of the toilet, a hand... Red paper, blue paper</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Nyughatatlan szellemek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toilet kara Tekubi ga... Akagami Aoshi</title>
<summary>Something is stinking up the town, and it isn`t just urban reconstruction! A ghost has invaded the school`s bathrooms, and it`s up to Satsuki and the gang to find out how to put it back to sleep. The old book left by Satsuki`s mom just might be the ticket.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692597</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="6829" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今夜霊達が蘇る!! 天の邪鬼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tonight, the spirits are revived! Amanojaku!</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Szellemek iskolája</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kon`ya Rei-tachi ga Yomigaeru!! Amanojaku</title>
<summary>Moving to a new town is tough on kids. Nothing is familiar, and with no friends, it can be scary. In Satsuki`s case, that last part isn`t helped any when she, her little brother, and three kids from school end up in the old schoolhouse, which just so happens to be haunted by ghosts!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692595</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="7230" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血塗られた体育祭 だっと!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A sports festival painted with blood... Datto!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chinurareta Taiikusai Datto!!</title>
<summary>The gang helps Keiichiro train for a sports festival at school. A mysterious boy shows up at the track, running alongside Keiichiro. Despite the bonding between the two, it seems the new boy isn`t quite alive--and he`s got a penchant for cutting off the feet of those who run!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692603</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8016" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">扉を裂く悪魔の手 惨劇の夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The demon`s hand bursts through the door... a night of tragedy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobira o Saku Akuma no Te Sangeki no Yoru</title>
<summary>Stories spread about something preying on children who are all alone, and the gang gets scared. Especially since their parents will be out for the night! A deadly ghost with a sickle in hand stalks Satsuki and her friends. Can the gang survive the night?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692605</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8671" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鏡に盗まれた魂!! うつしみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The soul-stealing mirror!! Utsushimi</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Atenţie la oglinzi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaami ni Nusumareta Tamashii!! Utsushimi</title>
<summary>People all over town begin acting strangely, but it isn`t their fault, as most of them have been replaced by mirror world clones of themselves! With Satsuki and Hajime the last two people in the town who haven`t been swapped, they`ll have to find a way to end this ghost, before they end up in the mirror!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692607</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11053" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄へと続く回廊 黄泉の鬼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Path Which Leads To Hell - Yomi Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Site-ul celor făra viaţă</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku e to Tsuzuku Kairou Yomi no Oni</title>
<summary>Leo is convinced that there`s a ghostly website out there on the internet, and is determined to find it. Unfortunately for him... he does! Trapped in the computer, the rest of the gang needs to figure out how to apply old fashioned exorcism to new technologies.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692609</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="23379" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜をさまよう死体 シロタビ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Corpse Stalker of the Night!</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Bulgăre de nea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoru o Samayou Shitai Shirotabi</title>
<summary>There`s a girl in Satsuki`s class who is a little off. She tends to the rabbits at the school, whom she says are her only friends. But if that`s weird, then it gets only stranger when a dead rabbit shows back up at the pen, alive and well.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692611</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="23380" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出口なきトンネル 穴まねき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Endless Tunnel</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Tunelul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deguchi Naki Tunnel Ana Maneki</title>
<summary>Hajime has a close encounter with a spooky cab, which the rest of the gang doesn`t believe. Even when they see it for themselves, it seems like a perfectly normal cab... that is, until the cab driver takes them to a life-draining tunnel!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692613</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="23381" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">話すメリー人形!! 恐怖の影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Talking Doll Meili</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Mary, păpuşa vorbitoare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanasu Meili Ningyou!! Kyoufu no Kage</title>
<summary>The gang finds a strange doll in the trash. Satsuki prevents Keiichiro from bringing the doll home, but it shows up regardless. And then, late at night, Satsuki gets a phone call from none other than the doll herself! With the doll stalking her relentlessly, how will she ever be rid of it?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692615</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29195" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死を告げる看護婦 母の想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nurse Who Tells Your Death - Mother`s Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">O asistentă care condamnă la moarte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi o Tsugeru Kangofu Haha no Omoi</title>
<summary>A strange nurse haunts Keiichiro, which triggers memories of the past. Not just for Satsuki and Keiichiro, who remember the death of their mother, but for Momoko as well, who happened to meet their mother just before she passed away. Is the cursed nurse here to take the siblings to join their mother?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692617</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29196" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人を飲み込む絵画 ダビンチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Picture that Swallows People - Da Vinci</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Tabloul care înghite oameni - Da Vinci</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito o Nomikomu Kaiga Da Vinci</title>
<summary>A ghostly painter with the ability to trap souls within his work has reawakened, and not even the other ghosts of the old schoolhouse want anything to do with him. Satsuki and the gang travel back in time in order to put the artist back to sleep, where they meet someone familiar.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692619</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29197" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人を喰らう団地!! 悪霊の巣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Apartment that Eats People!! Nest of Evil Spirits</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Sălaşul mâncătorilor de oameni - cuibul spiritelor malefice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito o Kurau Danchi!! Akuryou no Su</title>
<summary>Following an accident on the job, Satsuki`s father is injured, but Leo thinks ghosts are behind it. When the gang investigates the building Satsuki`s father worked at, they find that the building itself is alive, and eager to have guests stay... for all eternity!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692625</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29198" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">放送室の茜さん!! 死者の声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akane-san of the Broadcasting Room!! Voice of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Akane la radio. Vocea morţiilor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Housou Shitsu no Akane-san!! Shisha no Koe</title>
<summary>Satsuki is asked to perform the after school broadcast in the wake of the previous announcers having fallen ill under mysterious circumstances. The only problem is, it seems the ghost of a deceased broadcast club member has invaded the system, intent on killing anyone that might upstage her!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692629</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29199" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば天の邪鬼 逢魔降臨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Amanojaku - The Descent of Ohma</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Adio Amanojaku: Ohma, spiritul răzbunării</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Amanojaku Ouma Kourin</title>
<summary>The entire school is possessed and drawn into the old schoolhouse, all to lure Satsuki and the gang into a trap. Lord Ohma has awoken, and seeks vengence upon Satsuki for her family`s past attempts to seal him. In this final confrontation, who will emerge?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692633</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29200" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血染めの湖の恐怖!! 雪の亡霊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Terror at Bloodstain Lake!! Apparition in the Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Teama de lacul însângerat - Fantoma zăpezii</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chizome no Mizuumi no Kyoufu!! Setsu no Bourei</title>
<summary>The gang takes a trip to the mountains to stay at a resort run by Satsuki`s cousin Miyuki. However, upon arrival, a young girl tells them that Miyuki is dead. It seems that her ghost still haunts the frozen lake, turning it blood red. But this story might not be as simple as it seems...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692627</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29201" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">命を奪う心霊写真 魔の踏切</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Life-Taking Psychic Photo - Railway Crossing of Evil</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Fotografia care ia vieţi: calea ferată fatală</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inochi o Ubau Shinrei Shashin Ma no Fumikiri</title>
<summary>Convinced that a ghost is haunting a train crossing, Leo takes the gang out to try and catch the spirit in a photo. When one of those photos shows a strange hand on Momoko`s shoulder, things start getting bad, and a tale of revenge unfolds.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692621</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29202" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔のおまじない 闇の儀式</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Devil`s Spell - Rite of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Incantaţia diavolului - ritualul negru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma no Omajinai Yami no Gishiki</title>
<summary>Satsuki falls in with a bad crowd, or it might be better to say coven. Several girls at her school conspire to cast spells together, and she reluctantly joins in. But when one of them goes missing, and no one seems to remember the girl`s very existence, Satsuki knows this isn`t just any ordinary fad!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692623</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29203" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">首なし ライダー!! 死の呪い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Headless Rider!! Curse of Death</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Motociclistul fără cap! Blestemul morţilor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kubi Nashi Rider!! Shi no Noroi</title>
<summary>A headless rider terrorizes the town on the anniversary of what was his death, seeking to decapitate people like himself. When the ghost turns his headlights upon Satsuki, the gang needs to find a way to put him to sleep again, and quick!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692631</identifier>
<identifier>ghost-stories</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="68608" update="2007-03-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68609" update="2007-03-19">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68610" update="2007-03-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68611" update="2007-03-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137830" recap="true" update="2016-10-13">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お化け大集合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summary 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Obake Daishuugou</title>
<summary>A new year special where Momoko stars to remember some of the adventures, she has had with her friends.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137831" recap="true" update="2016-10-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別編!! 霊眠の恐怖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summary 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Hen!! Rei Nemuri no Kyoufu</title>
<summary>A new year special where Momoko stars to remember some of the adventures, she has had with her friends.</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
