<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="482" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-05-08</startdate>
<enddate>2001-12-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gakuen Senki Muryou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Record of School War Muryou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Muryo - the Record of School Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">School Battle Muryo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">shingu tv</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">学園戦記ムリョウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shingu: Secret of the Stellar Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Muryoh</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13965" approval="2" total="4">Planet With</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="651677">If you like SF stories that make you keep guessing what the next episode will be like, you must watch this one. I even re-watched it several times.

The artwork &amp; visual design might be below average - the alien spaceship &amp; robots are ugly, but the story is actually good and certainly not a cliche. This anime shows that a good story can be slow and have few fighting scenes, but still very enjoyable to watch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.muryou.gr.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3613" type="Original Work">Satou Tatsuo</name>
<name id="4479" type="Music">Oono Yuuji</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="3630" type="Character Design">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="3613" type="Series Composition">Satou Tatsuo</name>
<name id="3613" type="Direction">Satou Tatsuo</name>
<name id="3630" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
</creators>
<description>The year is 2070. Hajime, a curious and outgoing second-year class rep at Misumaru Middle School, leads what he thinks is a quiet and ordinary life in the town of Tenmo. But, one day, two events turn all of his conceptions about the world around him upside down: the appearance of a giant white mecha fighting off an apparent alien invasion, and the arrival of Muryou Subaru, a transfer student with a predilection for old-fashioned (for the time) school dress and remarkable talents for combat and use of telekinetic power. As Hajime soon discovers, Muryou isn`t the only person at Misumaru with special powers and responsibilities, either. How is it all connected to the alien Galactic Federation and the strange white giant called Shingu?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="394">7.11</permanent>
<temporary count="396">7.50</temporary>
<review count="2">5.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>148858.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1009</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1179</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>34892</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>169</identifier>
<identifier>ldwjci</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.muryou.gr.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.rightstuf.com/rssite/nozomiEntertainment/seriesSites/shingu/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shingu:_Secret_of_the_Stellar_Wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>学園戦記ムリョウ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>55</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234361</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4554</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1999" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-29">
<name>tomboy</name>
<description>A girl who acts and dresses like a boy and enjoys rough, noisy activities traditionally associated with boys.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>visiting alien superhero</name>
<description>Sometimes, the Earth does not have enough of its own Defenders of Justice. In such cases, a "Gastarbeiter" hero from a foreign planet or world has to appear to save the day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3738" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-05">
<name>aliens living on earth</name>
<description>There`s an alien or a hive of aliens blending into society near you!</description>
<picurl>70750.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="39362" type="main character in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="1">7.30</rating>
<name>Subaru Muryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The mysterious transfer student that came to Misumaru Middle School wearing a 20th century school uniform, something rarely seen in the year 2070. He`s always calm and laid-back, but at the same time, he has secret powers that he rarely reveals. Little is known about Muryou; in fact, the more that`s revealed about him, the more enigmatic he becomes. He seems to know something about the recent alien incidents, though, which makes Vice President http://anidb.net/ch39365 [Kyouichi] instantly suspicious.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>2841.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2899" picture="79024.jpg">Miyazaki Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39363" type="main character in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="1">7.30</rating>
<name>Murata Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The narrator of the story. He`s a middle-schooler, and the class rep for 2nd year homeroom C. After discovering that http://anidb.net/ch39362 [Muryou] and http://anidb.net/ch39365 [Kyouichi] have astonishing powers, he decides to keep track of all the strange events that start to unfold - but he soon finds himself more deeply involved than he bargained for. Hajime is very social, mature for his age, and adjusts well to even the most bizarre situations.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>2845.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39364" type="main character in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="4">6.89</rating>
<name>Moriyama Nayuta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The other Vice President at Misumaru Middle School; she`s an honor student who always goes by the rules. Daughter of the Shrine Priest at the local Tenmo Shrine, Nayuta is very serious, almost to a fault. She has trouble expressing her emotions, and doesn`t like the idea of depending on anyone else.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>2847.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39365" type="main character in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Moriguchi Kyouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misumaru Middle School`s passionate Student Vice President. He has a black belt in martial arts and a lightning-quick temper to match, but he`s also very loyal and will stand by his friends no matter what. There appears to be some kind of connection between Kyouichi and http://anidb.net/ch39368 [Harumi]; but at the moment, neither of them seems willing - or able - to acknowledge it. Despite all his harsh words, Kyouichi actually does have a soft side, and is hard not to like.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>2849.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39366" type="main character in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Tsumori Hachiyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hachiyou is the Student Government President. His personality is very calm and quiet, but with a certain commanding presence - whenever trouble appears, Hachiyou is quick to take charge. He`s a bit like a father figure for the group; with only a word from Hachiyou, even the hot-headed http://anidb.net/ch39364 [Nayuta] and http://anidb.net/ch39365 [Kyouichi] will calm down and follow his lead.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>2850.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39367" type="main character in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Morihata Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shun is the Student Government Secretary. He`s always cheerful, no matter what the situation; he`s also very sharp, and eloquent with his words. Perhaps that`s why he`s so incredibly popular amongst the students (especially the ladies)! Shun has a lot of responsibilities around the school; he`s often called on to be an announcer at events, and he`s a member of the Theatre Club - a natural match for his acting skills.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>2851.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39368" type="main character in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="3">6.14</rating>
<name>Mineo Harumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Treasurer of the Student Government. She`s quiet and demure, but also extremely resilient; she seems to deliberately avoid being in the spotlight, and usually hides her emotions. Harumi`s role in the mystery that surrounds the Shingu is unclear, but one thing is certain - despite appearances, Harumi is a skilled fighter, and she takes her duties very seriously.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>2853.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39369" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-07">
<rating votes="3">5.72</rating>
<name>Subaru Setsuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch39362 [Muryou]`s older sister. She`s a college student who lives in Tokyo, but she often comes to Lady http://anidb.net/ch39380 [Momoe]`s home to visit Muryou. In fact, it`s become a trademark of hers to stop by with all sorts of sweets from various parts of Japan. She`s got a cheerful disposition, and sometimes seems a bit scatterbrained. But like a lot of people in http://anidb.net/ch39363 [Hajime]`s life, there`s more to her meets the eye...
Setsuna has a lot of hidden qualities, but one thing`s for certain - she`s very good at looking after people.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>2858.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="321" picture="17158.jpg">Yamazaki Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39370" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-07">
<rating votes="2">4.11</rating>
<name>Murata Futaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch39363 [Hajime]`s younger sister. She`s a bubbly sixth grader who tends to fall in love with her brother`s friends. Always optimistic, energetic and curious, Futaba is never afraid to speak her mind. She and her brother fight like cats and dogs... but in truth, she loves her brother a lot.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>2862.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39371" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="3">5.72</rating>
<name>Murata Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch39363 [Hajime]`s mother. She has two children, http://anidb.net/ch39370 [Futaba] (an elementary-schooler) and, of course, Hajime (a middle schooler). She`s a young mother, and currently takes care of the kids and the house while her husband is away. Casual and easygoing, Kyoko`s pretty laid back when it comes to the kids doing their schoolwork, but she`s very strict about their manners. Kyoko is a woman of many skills; not only is she good at running the Murata household, but she plays a mean game of Bam Bam Sumo Tournament, too.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78059.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39372" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Murata Kazuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch39363 [Hajime]`s father. He`s kept quite busy with his work so he doesn`t get to spend much time at home. Kazuo is cheerful and easygoing, but he does have a certain mystique.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9546" picture="77661.jpg">Sakaguchi Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39373" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-07">
<name>Inagaki Hikaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hikaru is the Media Club President at Misumaru Middle School, so she`s always on the lookout for a big scoop. She and http://anidb.net/ch39367 [Shun] are like two peas in a pod - they`re constantly exchanging information and plotting various schemes together. Hikaru and Shun are also usually appointed as MCs for school events. Hikaru is very cheerful, and has the uncanny ability to find humor in any situation.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1677" picture="223670.jpg">Matsumoto Sachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39374" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-07">
<name>Narita Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The last (but not least!) of http://anidb.net/ch39363 [Hajime]`s trio of best friends. With his outrageous antics and unmistakable looks, Jirou definitely knows how to stand out in a crowd. In fact, he`s earned a reputation as something of a troublemaker...
Jirou loves commotion, and with all the recent ruckus over aliens, he`s made sure to keep up to date on every little event. After all, history is being made - and as the years go by and the stories become legend, he wants to be able to say he was there to see it all happen!
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39375" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Mikami Toshio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toshio is one of http://anidb.net/ch39363 [Hajime]`s best friends. He`s the computer genius of the group, and is a very accomplished hacker. (Don`t worry, he wouldn`t harm a fly - he only uses his skills to gather information about aliens.) He`s got something of a stubborn streak, but overall he`s very calm and aloof.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39376" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Kawamori Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another one of http://anidb.net/ch39363 [Hajime]`s best friends. Atsushi is friendly and easygoing; his personality is the balance between http://anidb.net/ch39375 [Toshio]`s quiet reserve and http://anidb.net/ch39374 [Jirou]`s loud, playful nature. Just like his buddies, Atsushi is big into science fiction, and is patiently waiting for the day when all his favorite stories will become a reality.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="338" picture="17174.jpg">Ono Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39377" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Isozaki Hiromi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiromi Isozaki, is the phys-ed instructor and teacher at Misumaru Middle School. She may seem unemotional at times, but she is very much attached to her students. No matter what happens, she always does her best to be calm and in control.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2986" picture="144766.jpg">Sasaki Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39378" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-07">
<name>Jirutoushu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He`s a Velunnian. While most aliens do their best to blend in, he`s happy-go-lucky persona has bubbled over into his appearance - you`ll always be able to spot his wavy curls and bright red Hawaiian shirt. He is a first class diplomat, and every once in a while, you can tell that there`s something hidden behind his cheerful smile...
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="338" picture="17174.jpg">Ono Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39379" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-07">
<name>Uennuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He`s a Lieutenant in the Zaiglian Space Force, a man in search of the truth; and to that end, he`s decided to blend in with the people of Earth. Just like other Zaiglians, he`s very pokerfaced... But at the same time, he`s also calm and collected, as any good Lieutenant should be. Though he`s not much of a talker, he`s always ready and willing to adapt to new situations.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13050" picture="171761.jpg">Shibuya Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39380" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Sanemori Momoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Head Mistress of the Sanemori family. She holds an important position among the people of Tenmo. Momoe seems to know the truth about many things - Tenmo, http://anidb.net/ch39364 [Nayuta], even http://anidb.net/ch39362 [Muryou] - so it`s no surprise that when important events take place, Momoe is there to guide the way with her wisdom.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39381" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-07">
<name>Myouken Kanata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This mysterious figure first appears during the big judo match between Mischu and Miyanomori. He`s there under the guise of a simple team helper, but there`s more to him than meets the eye. Kanata is quiet, but extremely confident - and he has every reason to be.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39382" type="appears in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Yamamoto Tadakazu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch39363 [Hajime]`s homeroom teacher. He has a very mellow personality and at first glance, he seems like an average, ordinary man. But Mr. Yamamoto has an important role in policing the area and he can pull off some surprising fighting techniques! Mr. Yamamoto is an easy-going, approachable guy, and he`s very popular amongst his students.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78071.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4711" picture="244962.jpg">Ishihara Bon</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39383" type="appears in" update="2011-12-07">
<name>Vuerosshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He`s Captain of the Zaiglian battleship Jilton. Most of the Zaiglians so far have been unemotional and mysterious... but quite to the contrary, he is commanding, well-spoken, and diplomatic.
Source: shingu.rightstuf.com</description>
<picture>78072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1998" picture="21301.jpg">Nagasako Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5847" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦記, 始まる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The War Record Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chronique de guerre commence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senki, Hajimaru</title>
<summary>Hajime wakes up to discover that aliens have appeared and there`s a mysterious new transfer student in his class! He`s not sure which revelation startles him more, but those aren`t the only surprises the day has in store.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691503</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37657" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムリョウのチカラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Muryou`s Power</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La force de Muryoh</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Muryou no Chikara</title>
<summary>What started as an argument turns into a brawl with psychic powers! This is Hajime`s first clue that things aren`t quite what they seem, and that the obvious answers aren`t always right. When Hajime asks Muryou about his secrets, what will the response be?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691505</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37661" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">その名は, シングウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Name Is Shingu</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Son nom est Shingû</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Na wa, Shingu</title>
<summary>A thief has broken into Misumaru Middle School! While the students were away at gym class, someone snuck in and stole a girl`s clothes? But odd as this "thief" may seem, he`s part of a dangerous plan. Hajime had better watch his back!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691507</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37678" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">動き出す, とき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Time to Move</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au moment où tout se met en marche</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ugokidasu, Toki</title>
<summary>Tenmo has secrets and when Hajime sets out to uncover them, the powers that be start to take interest. Muryou, meanwhile, continues to attract trouble like a magnet; the sports teams can`t get enough of him, and Nayuta can`t get away from him!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691509</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37687" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">見つめる, 目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gazing Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le regard implacable</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsumeru, Me</title>
<summary>Hajime`s eyes have been opened but even with all he`s learned, he`s still just a kid. While he continues to laugh, study, and have fun with his friends, Jiltosh tries to teach an alien spy a lesson or two. The results, however, are disastrous.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691511</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37786" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ささやかな, うたげ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Humble Feast</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le banquet calme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasayaka na, Utage</title>
<summary>Jiltosh, Weinul, and Lady Momoe are now all living under one roof; and by a small twist of fate, Hajime`s family might be stopping by! Meanwhile, Hachio and Hajime are trying to form a new Festival Club, but Nayuta is dead set against it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691517</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37787" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">連邦と連盟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Federation and Alliance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Association d`intérêts communs et fédération</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Renpou to Renmei</title>
<summary>It`s a day like any other in Tenmo - except that a gigantic spaceship is hovering in the sky. While most people are in a frenzied panic, the natives of Tenmo are strangely calm - until a second spaceship closes in and the two ships face-off!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691547</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37788" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かくれさと, ふるさと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Village Hometown</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vallée cachée, le lieu de naissance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakure Sato, Furusato</title>
<summary>Setsuna invites Hajime, Shun, and Nayuta to visit the mysterious Village of Falling Stars, but this little vacation isn`t going to be all fun and games.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691527</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37789" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">助っ人, 相まみえる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Helpers Meet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les alliés arrivent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suketto, Aimamieru</title>
<summary>The sports clubs have finally cornered Muryou! Will he finally agree to help them in their upcoming judo match against Misumaru`s school rival, Miyanomori? One match couldn`t really hurt, right?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691543</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37790" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨ののち, また雨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After the Rain, More Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La pluie durant la pluie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame no Nochi, mata Ame</title>
<summary>Before, the Zaiglians were always content to lurk around in shadows, but no longer. Jiltosh and the others now find themselves face-to-face with the largest squadron of Zaiglian soldiers ever to set foot in Tenmo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691519</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37791" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さだむるもの, ここに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Destined Ones Gather</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`instabilité est ici</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sadamuru Mono, Koko ni</title>
<summary>With the looming alien threat, school has been cancelled but that hasn`t stopped the students of Misumaru Middle School from making their own plans! It will be a day of revelation both for the people of Tenmo, and the world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691549</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37792" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おだやかに, 突然に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calmly, but Suddenly</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Calmement puis soudainement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Odayaka ni, Totsuzen ni</title>
<summary>Alien forces are on the move and, aside from keeping Setsuna up all night, they seem to have a darker purpose. With a new impending invasion, could it be time to ask for the Galactic Federation`s support?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691533</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37793" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">見上げる, その先</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gazing Beyond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce que nous voyons au bout du regard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miageru, Sono Saki</title>
<summary>There`s a mysterious new student in Tenmo. All that`s known about this newcomer is his name: Kanata. But while Momoe and the others try to dig up information on him, he`s busy tracking down Muryou! Is he a friend or a foe?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691545</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37794" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚人, めざめる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Empty Soul Awakens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le géant est ici</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyojin, Mezameru</title>
<summary>Nayuta is forced to take drastic action. As she pushes the power of the Shingu farther than ever before, the Shingu`s darkest secret will finally be revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691551</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37795" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">せっかちな, 呑気</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Impatient Optimism</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La soûlerie impatiente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekkachi na, Nonki</title>
<summary>It`s festival time at Futaba`s elementary school! The members of the Festival Club have been invited to participate and that means a fun change of pace for the weary middle school students.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691541</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37796" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦記は, つづく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Record Continue</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les chroniques de guerre continuent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senki wa, Tsuzuku</title>
<summary>The final conclusion to Shingu: The Secret of the Stellar wars!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691553</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37797" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕たちの, 夏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Notre été à nous</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi no, Natsu</title>
<summary>The evidence from the battle with Sanadon leads to some troubling discoveries for the Sanemori Clan. Of course, Jiltosh would rather everyone focus on a more important matter. The Zaiglians are returning home and that means a going-away party!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691529</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37798" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父, 帰る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Father`s Return</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour du père</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi, Kaeru</title>
<summary>Hajime`s father, Kazuo Murata, is finally getting a vacation to see his family! What is it, exactly, that he does again? But his appearance at home is overshadowed by a startling announcement on the early morning news.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691531</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37799" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強がりな, 友情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Despite Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tiens bon, amitié</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyogari na, Yuujou</title>
<summary>Nayuta`s been acting a little strange lately. Normally very confrontational, she seems to be backing off... what could be bothering her so much that her personality has changed 180 degrees?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691525</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37800" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ありがとう, 勇気</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thank You, Courage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Merci, courage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arigatou, Yuuki</title>
<summary>Using the dangerous technique of Astral Deviation, Nayuta`s spirit is sent into space along with the Shingu to fight. But with an invasion force closing in on the Chosen`s location on the ground, it`s up to Harumi to protect everyone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691523</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37801" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">だから, 明日のために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Et donc, pour nos lendemains</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dakara, Ashita no Tame ni</title>
<summary>Something big is coming. School has been cancelled, and the Student Government has been called into a secret meeting with the Sanemori Clan. Hajime is about to witness to one of the Shingu`s most powerful secrets.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691521</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37802" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おだやかな, 戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Peaceful Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combat paisible</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Odayaka na, Tatakai</title>
<summary>Kyoichi`s all fired up and ready to lead his Red Team to victory - but then again, Muryou and Nayuta are both on the White Team, and they`ve got a few tricks as well! In the midst of all the commotion, an outsider infiltrates the school grounds.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691513</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37803" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">君の, えがお</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ton sourire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no, Egao</title>
<summary>Questions are still fresh in everyone`s minds. What happened during the final event? Did any cameras catch the crucial moment? Who knew Kyoichi and Nayuta would go that far for a chance to win?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691515</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37804" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">うけついだ, 悲しみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inherited Sorrows</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un héritage de tristesse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uketsuida, Kanashimi</title>
<summary>The students stumble upon an old video containing a short film from 100 years ago! Is that a young Lady Momoe playing the lead? Then, a troubled Harumi must face Kyoichi and tell him the truth about what really happened 11 years ago.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691537</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37805" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">きよらなる, 拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Virtuous Fist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le poing pur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiyoranaru, Kobushi</title>
<summary>Aliens have appeared in Kyushu and they`re making short work of the Protectors! Will Harumi be strong enough to protect the Chosen by herself? And why isn`t Muryou around when he`s needed the most?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691539</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37806" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どさくさに, ゴメン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chaotic Apology</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J`en profite pour m`excuser</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dosakusa ni, Gomen</title>
<summary>Everyone is shocked to discover that Hajime`s father is involved with the Space Diplomacy talks - even Hajime! Nayuta takes a special interest in the Festival Club and she holds a meeting, but it’s cut short when an alien battleship appears!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691535</identifier>
<identifier>shingu-secret-of-the-stellar-wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39476" recap="true" update="2005-08-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">総集篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushuuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39477" update="2005-08-01">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園戦記ムリョウ特集 ムリョウFAN倶楽部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gakuen Senki Muryou Report: Muryou Fanclub</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuen Senki Muryou - Muryou Fan Club</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198456" update="2018-04-22">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>40</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">よりぬきムリョウさん Girls Selection ~学園戦記ムリョウ特別編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yorinuki Muryou-san Girls Selection: Gakuensenki Muryou Tokubetsu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219585" update="2019-08-21">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
