<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4829" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-02-15</startdate>
<enddate>2007-05-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Juusoukikou Dancougar Nova</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Juusoukikou Dancouga Nova</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Juusou Kikou Dancouga Nova</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Dancouga 2007</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shin Dancouga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Dancougar Nova</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Dancouga Nova</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">Dancouga</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">獣装機攻ダンクーガノヴァ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1692" type="Alternative Setting">Choujuu Kishin Dancougar</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/tv_series/w041.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="778" type="Animation Work">Ashi Productions</name>
<name id="153" type="Direction">Oobari Masami</name>
<name id="39089" type="Character Design">Kazz</name>
<name id="33669" type="Music">Yamahara Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="9730" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tokuda Yumenosuke</name>
<name id="5112" type="Story Composition">Shudou Takeshi</name>
<name id="4247" type="Story Composition">Mitsui Hideki</name>
</creators>
<description>In the 22nd century, there are no longer any world wide wars. Instead, small scale wars break out all over the Earth. Meanwhile, a large robot appears who protects the weak. It is called "Dancougar Nova". Some even call it God.
However, no one knows the reason for its existence - not even its pilots.
Then, another robot, beyond anyone`s expectations, reveals itself as the true enemy and begins its attack on the Earth.
Dancougar Nova retaliates against this enemy with a power that was kept secret until now.
Will Dancougar Nova be able to save the Earth? The prelude to this explosive confrontation rings out.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="329">3.54</permanent>
<temporary count="331">6.08</temporary>
<review count="4">4.91</review>
</ratings>
<picture>11700.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7306</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1991</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3919</identifier>
<identifier>vjhbof</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/tv_series/w041.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Jūsō_Kikō_Dancouga_Nova</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>獣装機攻ダンクーガノヴァ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1077</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326450</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8800</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4004" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>organic mecha</name>
<description>An organic mecha is a mecha that has organic tissue in its composition. The most prominent historical example is http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion].</description>
<picurl>224892.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="47521" type="main character in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="4">4.25</rating>
<name>Hidaka Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A red-haired, undefeated Formula-Zero One racing champion. She is the chief pilot of the Dancouga Nova and the pilot of the Nova Eagle. Aoi also models as a side job. As the pilot of Nova Eagle, she is also the primary pilot of Dancouga Nova. Shortly into the series, she decides to quit racing as she doesn`t feel she can balance it with piloting Dancouga, and becomes a model full-time.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="394" picture="17239.jpg">Ikezawa Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47522" type="main character in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="3">2.12</rating>
<name>Tachibana Kurara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blue-haired, Top-class Narcotics Investigator. She is the pilot of the Nova Liger. Kurara is experienced using hand-held firearms and is an expert in her profession. As a child, she and her mother were forced to witness her father beaten by thugs. Spurred on by her mother`s comments that there was no such thing as justice, Kurara became the top policewoman in the country, and cleaned up the corrupt narcotics division in a year and a half.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47523" type="main character in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Kamon Sakuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A brown-haired, homeless man. He is the pilot of the Nova Rhino. Sakuya doesn`t seem to care that he is unemployed and homeless. Instead, he enjoys living his life the way it is. Sakuya is the first to (unknowingly) use the original Dancouga`s catchphrase "Yatte yaruze!" ("Let`s do it!"), which catches on among the team before they even learn its origin. Later, he begins feeling inferior to the rest of the team as Nova Rhino`s only function in Dancouga is the pivot foot, and desires a super-strong special attack to make up for it.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47524" type="main character in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Johnny Burnette</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blonde salary man. He is the pilot of the Nova Elephant. Johnny was a promising white-collar worker. He enjoys cooking, and reads many men`s magazines, giving him a surprisingly wide and varied knowledge base. During their first mission, Seimii give him the nickname "Clark Kent", which he dislikes. Johnny is also the first to realize that the Dancouga teams seem to be selected based on the Japanese blood type theory of personality - each team consists of an A, a B, an O, and an AB.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="84" picture="16692.jpg">Tai Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47525" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="3">2.09</rating>
<name>Eida Rossa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is an Idol and love interest of Johnny Burnette. Later, it is revealed that she is the pilot of R-Daigun.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47526" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Tanaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The commander of the Dancouga team, Tanaka is shown to know more than he lets on, but seems to genuinely care for the team`s well-being. He gives the team their missions and answers their questions to the best of his ability - though all too often, the team is called into battle before he can give proper answers.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47527" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="3">3.66</rating>
<name>Isabelle Cronkite</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a Dancouga-obsessed reporter. She later became a supporter of Dancouga.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47528" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="3">4.74</rating>
<name>Seimii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The chief engineer in charge of Dancouga Nova, she has a flirty, playful personality and tells the team before each mission to look out for her "baby". Later, it is revealed that she often has brief, unfulfilling relationships, and focuses on Dancouga as it, unlike a man, can`t hurt her feelings. When Sakuya asked her for a private conversation shortly afterwards, she seemed surprised and interested - until it turned out that he only wanted to talk shop, annoying her greatly.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47529" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="3">3.66</rating>
<name>Ruu Riruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 15-year-old psychiatrist and member of the Dancouga team, she displays a surprising level of maturity for someone her age. However, she becomes easily annoyed if her name is mispronounced. She cares for the team`s mental health, and like Tanaka, tries to answer their questions as best she can.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47530" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>F.S.</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also named Fog Sweeper, This mysterious, long-haired man is the overall commander of the Dancouga Nova project. Initially, he only communicates with Tanaka, but the Dancouga team meets him at a party in episode 6, in which he reveals that Dancouga is modeled after a legendary Super Robot that protected Earth from an inhuman threat.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47531" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="3">4.74</rating>
<name>Vladimir</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3274" picture="24702.jpg">Yamamoto Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47532" type="appears in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Dancouga Nova</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Dancouga Nova is basically the unit developed for the Dancouga Nova Project. The Dancouga Nova is a combination of four separate machines, which are the Nova Eagle, Nova Rhino, Nova Liger, and the Nova Elephant. In which each of these mecha have three different transformations; Humanoid, Beast, and Vehicle types. Dancouga Nova`s Weaponry include the (Slash/Sever Space Sword), an atomic-vibration blade and the Dancouga Nova`s default weapon, the (Slash/Sever Space Cannon), which is an array of cannons that can be fired all at once and the Boost Nova Knuckle, which Dancouga Nova launches its right arm. The unit can only be piloted by Aoi through a direct motion tracing system.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91959.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47533" type="appears in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>R-Daigun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The fifth unit of Dancouga Nova Project developed alongside the 4 main machines. A red Mecha similar to the predecessor, the Black Wing, the unit has both Humanoid, Beast, and Vehicle types. It is also equipped with a stealth capability that allows it to disappear and prevents it from being detected. Its attack capabilities were just like Dancouga Nova and it is equipped with newer weapons like the Dan-Stinger a pair of machine guns with one in each wrist, the Dan-Blade and its twin lancer form Dan-Blade Twin used for close combat, the Absolute Hurricane which fires a jet of wind that can blow away certain enemies.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91958.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47534" type="appears in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Dancouga Nova God Beast Mode</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Dancouga Nova God Beast Mode is Dancouga Nova`s second mode when its Aggressive System is activated. This changes the unit`s color to gold and became a beast-like mecha due to the beast modes of all four machines.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91960.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47535" type="appears in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Dancouga Max God</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The combination between Dancouga Nova and R-Daigun, this is the final unit of the Dancouga Nova Project based on the Final Dancouga`s data. Due to the combination of both units, the Dancouga Max God is the strongest of all the Dragon`s Hive`s machines as well as giving it an improved flight capabilities. Its armaments are similar to Dancouga Nova but with more attacks.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>91961.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="67461" update="2007-02-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎のダンクーガ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Dancouga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Dancouga</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67462" update="2007-02-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超獣合神!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Bestial God Combination!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choujuu Gasshin!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67463" update="2007-02-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">導きの剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Leader`s Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michibiki no Tsurugi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67464" update="2007-02-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅いダンクーガ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Dancouga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Dancouga</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67465" update="2007-02-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘆きの魔壁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evil Wall of Sadness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nageki no Maheki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67466" update="2007-02-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未知の襲撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack of the Unknown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michi no Shuugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67467" update="2007-02-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突!! ダンクーガ対ダンクーガ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash!! Dancouga vs Dancouga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu!! Dancouga tai Dancouga</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72081" update="2007-04-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去からの脱出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape From The Past</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako kara no Dasshutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72082" update="2007-04-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神獣覚醒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Divine Beast Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjuu Kakusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72083" update="2007-04-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱情の暴走!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Passion Out Of Control!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Netsujou no Bousou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72084" update="2007-04-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">粉砕? 龍牙島!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Destroyed? Dragon Fang Island!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funsai? Ryuugatou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72085" update="2007-04-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来への飛翔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly High Into Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai e no Hishou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
