<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="484" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>113</episodecount>
<startdate>1978-09-14</startdate>
<enddate>1981-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ginga Tetsudou 999</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">قطار المجرة 999</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ginga Tetsudo 999</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">ge999</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">銀河鉄道999</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Galaxy Express 999</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Galaxy Express 999</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Galaxy Express 999</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Галактический экспресс 999</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">은하철도 999</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Avaruusjuna Galaxy Express 999</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1000" type="Sequel">Ginga Tetsudou Monogatari</anime>
<anime id="2410" type="Prequel">Space Symphony Maetel: Ginga Tetsudou 999 Gaiden</anime>
<anime id="3286" type="Prequel">Kasei Ryodan Dnasights Four-Nine</anime>
<anime id="13306" type="Alternative Setting">Ginga Tetsudou 999 (2002)</anime>
<anime id="2231" type="Alternative Setting">Ginga Tetsudou 999: Glass no Clair</anime>
<anime id="485" type="Alternative Setting">Ginga Tetsudou 999 (1979)</anime>
<anime id="7039" type="Side Story">Ginga Tetsudou 999: Diamond Ring no Kanata e</anime>
<anime id="4230" type="Summary">Ginga Tetsudou 999: Kimi wa Senshi no You ni Ikirareruka!!</anime>
<anime id="4315" type="Summary">Ginga Tetsudou 999: Eien no Tabibito Emeraldas</anime>
<anime id="4122" type="Summary">Ginga Tetsudou 999: Kimi wa Haha no You ni Aiseruka!!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5673" approval="12" total="22">Kaiba</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="195647">Philosophical sci-fi in a dystopian setting; Galaxy Express 999 easily can be considered one of the 70s/80s classics and definitely one of Matsumoto Leiji`s greatest works, together with other great works like Harlock, Queen Millennia or the Yamato series. Having aged well I generally recommend it (and other works of Matsumoto) to all fans of oldskool anime or sci-fi anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="481642">Like Kino no Tabi and Heldensagen vom Kosmosinsel, but wider in (metaphyiscal) scope, space and time and set in a world where there is even more chaos and which is so limitless – literally encompassing the known universe – that what gives people (a sense of) purpose can only be how they design their own life story. An epic adventure with a strong philosophical background (I`d even say overlay), what happens on the screen must not be taken at face value and one needs to step back and think on their own. Very enjoyable. Just great.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="594612">Contains the romantic sci-fi/fantasy setting that cannot be found in modern anime... I was surprised by the depth of the drama and characters. Metaphysical and Philosophical in nature makes it a slow series to watch but the analysis and great ending make it worth the while.

If you enjoy classic stories, this is for you.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/999/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1107" type="Original Work">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
<name id="4808" type="Music">Aoki Nozomi</name>
<name id="5122" type="Chief Designer">Urata Mataji</name>
<name id="4542" type="Chief Direction">Nishizawa Nobutaka</name>
<name id="737" type="Work">Toei</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
</creators>
<description>In the far far future, technology has advanced enough so that it no longer matters what a spaceship looks like. You can have a space express service with a ship that looks like a 19th century train. Imagine where you can go and what adventures you can have. We follow Tetsuro as he goes on these adventures.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="388">7.73</permanent>
<temporary count="394">7.53</temporary>
<review count="1">5.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>148977.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1361</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>29716</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1491</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>503</identifier>
<identifier>jnsgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/999/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Galaxy_Express_999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>銀河鉄道999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1167</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89458</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>259</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="201" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>bounty hunter</name>
<description>A bounty hunter is one who hunts and captures targets (be it people, animals, etc.) for monetary gain, preferably without killing/destroying their target. Despite being illegal in most of the world today, it is a legal profession in the United States and Philippines (a former commonwealth of the US), who are known as "bail enforcement agents".
If they are only and constantly hired to kill, they are likely an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="566" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-10">
<name>dinosaur</name>
<description>Dinosaurs are vertebrate animals that dominated terrestrial ecosystems for over 160 million years, first appearing approximately 230 million years ago. At the end of the Cretaceous Period, 66 million years ago, non-avian dinosaurs suffered a catastrophic extinction, which ended their dominance on land. Taxonomists consider modern birds to be the direct descendants of theropod dinosaurs.
Since the first dinosaur was recognized in the 19th century, mounted, fossilized dinosaur skeletons have become major attractions at museums around the world. Dinosaurs have become a part of world culture and remain consistently popular, especially among children. They have been featured in best-selling books and films such as Jurassic Park, and new discoveries are regularly covered by the media.
Source: Dinopedia</description>
<picurl>191115.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2764" parentid="2627" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>space colony</name>
<description>The human race (or possibly some alien race) has mastered space travel and founded at least one colony either in space, on a moon or another planet. This usually also includes colony-life episodes that not only show the technical staff of professionals (astronauts, scientists, etc.), but also their families (i.e. children).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2868" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-20">
<name>racism</name>
<description>Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of an ethnically different background based on the pseudo-scientific belief that biological differences between peoples form so-called "races" and that one`s own "race" is superior to another, possibly also holding that members of different "races" should be treated differently. Some definitions include only consciously malignant forms of discrimination, and some views include discriminatory behaviors and beliefs based on cultural, national, ethnic, caste, or religious stereotypes. In works of fiction, this may also include similar actions against other sentient species.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3097" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-29">
<name>underwater</name>
<description>Underwater is a term describing the realm below the surface of water where the water exists in a natural feature such as an ocean, sea, lake, pond, or river.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3145" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-14">
<name>impact event</name>
<description>An impact event is a collision between celestial objects causing measurable effects. Impact events have physical consequences and have been found to regularly occur in planetary systems, though the most frequent involve asteroids, comets or meteoroids and have minimal impact. When large objects impact terrestrial planets like the Earth, there can be significant physical and biospheric consequences, though atmospheres mitigate many surface impacts through atmospheric entry. Impact structures are dominant landforms on many celestial solid objects and present the strongest empirical evidence for their frequency and scale. In fiction, an impact event is a common way to end the world as we know it, either through the impact itself or through its aftermath, and it may happen either naturally or through human hands; this may include man-made objects, such as space debris and fictional space colonies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3269" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-11">
<name>genocide</name>
<description>The systematic killing of substantial numbers of people on the basis of ethnicity, religion, political opinion, social status, or other particularity.
Acts committed with intent to destroy, in whole or in part, a national, ethnic, racial or religious group.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3309" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-12">
<name>space pirates</name>
<description>Depending how you view the future, lawlessness will always be present in society. There`s always going to be a shadier, nastier way of doing business, and that will almost certainly follow humanity to the stars. Thus, sci-fi authors will include Expies of modern and historic (un)organized crime—be they space mafia, gangs, or—in our case—pirates.
It`s not as anachronistic as it might seem. After all, pirates themselves have made a Real Life comeback in Somalia, and it`s a lucrative enough "business" that it`s taken a multinational military response to fight back. Surely an established society in outer space with significant trade and commerce would suffer similar problems!
... Well, maybe. The major problem with space pirates preying on space commerce is that space is vast. The challenge of catching commercial shipping in open space is orders of magnitudes more difficult than catching them on the open seas. Sometimes, this is cleverly worked around and justified. Most of the time, however, it isn`t.
There are two kinds of Space Pirates in science fiction. The normal version are violent criminals with a spaceship, who attack other spaceships, just like present-day pirates. Once you have shipping between different solar systems/planets, pirates preying on said shipping are bound to show. Simple as that. Done this way, piracy actually makes sense, provided there`s an enabling factor. That could be anything from the technology of the setting creating trade lanes (via a Portal Network, predictable Faster Than Light Travel routes thanks to Negative Space Wedgies, or timed space flights between planets to reduce time spent between planets, as in Real Life), to using a variant of the method employed by modern pirates (say, smaller ships striking at commercial shipping in the orbit of a planet).
The other version does a Recycled In SPACE on every eighteenth century pirate cliche ever. Reasons for including this version will typically be along the lines of "Because Space Is An Ocean, it has to have Pirates" rather than making any meaningful attempt at justifying their existence. They have Cornish accents, beards, say "Arr!" a lot, have parrots (probably robot) and false limbs (probably cybernetic) and wear tricorn hats and eyepatches (or have cybernetic eyes). They may even have ships shaped like boats.
One of the best known space pirates is http://anidb.net/ch2087 [Captain Harlock] from the same named popular http://anidb.net/a725 [TV anime series].
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>41919.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3464" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-07">
<name>space western</name>
<description>Space Western is a subgenre of science fiction that transposes themes of American Western books and film to a backdrop of futuristic space frontiers; it is the complement of the science fiction Western, which transposes science fiction themes onto an American Western setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3815" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>human cannibalism</name>
<description>Cannibalism is the practice of an individual of a species eating parts or the whole of another individual of the same species; as such, human cannibalism is when a human eats the flesh, organs, or other parts of another human being.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3896" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-23">
<name>bloodless wounds</name>
<description>No matter what weapon is used in what way to attack, hurt or kill somebody, there won`t be blood. You may see ripped clothes and smoke coming from the deadly wounds, but that`s it.
So if you have an aversion towards the red liquid but still love some action going on - this is the anime for you!</description>
<picurl>39189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4113" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-20">
<name>body exchange</name>
<description>Two or more characters swap bodies (or, equally, swap minds).
When this plot is done, usually the voices also switch as narrative cheat to help viewers keep track of who`s who. More subtly, it`s just the eyes. More serious/action-oriented shows might not do this. The Flip often involves characters of different ages, genders, races, or social classes. Another variation is a protagonist and antagonist switching, which usually involves each trying to undermine the other`s organization while simultaneously trying to switch back. If one or both of the characters have superpowers or other special abilities, they`ll have a lot of trouble figuring their new powers out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4488" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-02">
<name>terraforming</name>
<description>Terraforming (literally, "Earth-shaping") of a planet, moon, or other body is the hypothetical process of deliberately modifying its atmosphere, temperature, surface topography or ecology to be similar to the biosphere of Earth, in order to make it habitable by humans.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2087" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-03">
<rating votes="318">9.03</rating>
<name>Captain Harlock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harlock is the archetypical romantic hero, a space pirate with an individualist philosophy of life. He is as noble as he is taciturn, rebellious, stoically fighting against totalitarian regimes, whether they be earthborn or alien. In his own words, he "fight(s) for no one`s sake... only for something deep in (his) heart".
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>2364.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3233" picture="171389.jpg">Inoue Makio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2493" type="main character in" update="2014-12-13">
<rating votes="434">8.57</rating>
<name>Maetel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of Queen Prometheum, ruler of a mechanised empire.</description>
<picture>38136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3703" picture="151656.jpg">Ikeda Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12667" type="main character in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="64">4.76</rating>
<name>Hoshino Tetsurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tetsuro Hoshino is a young boy who was born on Earth into poverty, and who wants nothing more than a machine body. He also wants revenge on Count Mecha, an evil man who was given a machine body and now hunts humans for sport, for killing his mother. As a street urchin, Tetsuro has no means to buy a machine body. However, he has heard that at the end of the Andromeda Galaxy, there exists a planet where such robot bodies are given away for free. All Tetsuro needs to do is get a pass on the Galaxy Express 999, the cosmic railway. And one day, Tetsuro meets the mysterious Maetel, who promises to give him her unlimited use pass for the Express on the condition that she be his travelling companion. Tetsuro happily agrees, and embarks with Maetel on an adventure across the stars. When Tetsuro starts out, he is every bit the whiny, immature, selfish child. However, the adventures he goes with Maetel on, the people he meets, and the sights he witnesses cause Tetsuro to slowly but truly grow into a strong, young man. Tetsuro also grows closer and closer to Maetel, and although the nature of their relationship might not be called romantic, they form a very strong bond of love. Though it is never explicitly stated, it is implied that Tetsuro is Captain Harlock`s son. The evidence for this includes Tetsuro`s mother saying that his father is alive but away for some reason, Captain Harlock`s mysterious attachment to Tetsuro, and simple physical resemblance.</description>
<picture>38140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12668" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="21">7.54</rating>
<name>Claire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The dining car waitress on the 999, Claire has a machine body made of clear crystal glass. Unlike others who gave up their humanity by choice, Claire was forced into this existence by her vain mother. She works on the 999 in order to save up enough money to buy back her human body, which is stored on Pluto.</description>
<picture>38141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4105" picture="39793.jpg">Kawashima Chiyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12669" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="66">5.55</rating>
<name>Shashou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main crew member of the Galaxy Express 999. He is an alien being with an invisible body; only his eyes can be seen while he is wearing his conductor uniform. The Conductor prefers to go `strictly by the book` and frequently cites the Galaxy Express rule book, but occasionally ends up bending the rules and getting into adventures with Tetsurou and Maetel.</description>
<picture>38142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3285" picture="193568.jpg">Kimotsuki Kaneta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12670" type="appears in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="149">8.45</rating>
<name>Emeraldas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emeraldas has been compared many times to Captain Harlock, and the two have some similarities. They also know each other from the days of the Voice of Free Arcadia, when she fought side by side with him and Tochirou, the man who is their common bond. After the Ilumidus resistance, Emeraldas became much like Harlock, sailing the sea of stars and delivering justice in her own unique way.
Emeraldas is one of the few people who know the route of Count Mecha`s Time Castle, and when her ship, the Queen Emereldas, appears next to the Galaxy Express, Tetsuro doesn`t hesitate to get her attention. Emeraldas would`ve killed Tetsuro if it weren`t for two things. First, Maetel (whom she also knows) is with him. Second, Tetsuro has Tochirou`s hat and laser. She listens and then tells Tetsuro where the Time Castle will next appear: Trader`s Fork, on the planet of Heavy Melder.
Some time after she leaves, she realizes something is happening on Heavy Melder, something that had to do with Tochirou. She arrives too late. Harlock tells her he`s already dead. She leaves but later receives a message. It`s from Tochirou, whose soul had been successfully integrated into the Arcadia. Learning that it was Tetsuro who had helped him, she realizes that she owes him a favor, and she proceeds to Andromeda, to repay the favor. She and Tetsuro will cross path a few more times.
Emeraldas is a very lonely soul, especially after the death of Tochirou. Her closest companion, like herself, is a wanderer. You see, the reason she and Maetel know each other...is because they`re sisters. Emeraldas also has a daughter, Mayu, but she rarely sees her.
Source: Absolute Anime</description>
<picture>38143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10386" picture="38265.jpg">Tajima Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12672" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="13">3.58</rating>
<name>Kikai Hakushaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12673" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="9">5.92</rating>
<name>Shadow</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9005" picture="2570.gif">Nobusawa Mieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12674" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="8">4.22</rating>
<name>Tetsurou no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3642" picture="25837.jpg">Tsuboi Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12678" type="appears in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="6">5.75</rating>
<name>Antares</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Antares is the leader of the bandits of Grape Valley on Titan and guardian to a large collection of children orphaned by the human-hunting Count Mecha. (In the TV series, he was simply stealing in order to care for his own children.) He hates the machine people, and technology in general. Antales tells Tetsuro to seek out the pirate Emeraldas if he wishes to find the location of Count Mecha`s Time Castle, and advises the youngster to shoot the Count without giving him a moment`s pity. His body still contains a large number of unexploded energy bullets, which go off at the most inconvenient moment, just as he is about to warn Tetsuro of an important secret regarding Maeter.
Source: Cornponeflicks.org</description>
<picture>38152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3302">Imanishi Masao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12679" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="9">7.70</rating>
<name>Arcadia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>38153.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12680" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="4">6.41</rating>
<name>Queen Emeraldas</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>38154.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12681" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="5">7.41</rating>
<name>999</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>38155.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66754" type="appears in" update="2014-04-17">
<name>Oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1814" picture="20690.jpg">Saikachi Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66755" type="appears in" update="2014-04-17">
<name>Geronimo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66756" type="appears in" update="2014-04-17">
<name>Fleme</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2890" picture="23182.jpg">Sugiyama Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66793" type="appears in" update="2014-04-18">
<name>Akuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154111.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9650" picture="51986.jpg">Tsuda Nobuyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66794" type="appears in" update="2014-04-18">
<name>Rouba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154112.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66795" type="appears in" update="2014-04-18">
<name>Titan-jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66811" type="appears in" update="2014-04-18">
<name>Police</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3285" picture="193568.jpg">Kimotsuki Kaneta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66824" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<name>Tetsurou no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21114" picture="39572.jpg">Yamada Shunji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68052" type="appears in" update="2014-06-21">
<name>Ishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5976" picture="40971.jpg">Hase Sanji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68053" type="appears in" update="2014-06-21">
<name>Binanshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68054" type="appears in" update="2014-06-21">
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2795" picture="23209.jpg">Yamaguchi Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68055" type="appears in" update="2014-06-21">
<name>Kodomo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3772">Nakano Seiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76855" type="appears in" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Clock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2275" picture="21922.jpg">Tokumaru Kan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76856" type="appears in" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Ryuuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6374" picture="30939.jpg">Kitahama Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76857" type="appears in" update="2015-08-16">
<name>444</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176380.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="76858" type="appears in" update="2015-08-23">
<name>333</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176630.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="76909" type="appears in" update="2015-08-18">
<name>Ramen-ya no Shujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3378" picture="24406.jpg">Katou Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76910" type="appears in" update="2015-08-18">
<name>Restaurant no Oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5976" picture="40971.jpg">Hase Sanji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76911" type="appears in" update="2015-08-18">
<name>Hanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176456.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25701" picture="71454.jpg">Kikuchi Kouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76912" type="appears in" update="2015-08-18">
<name>Hanako no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2247" picture="72125.jpg">Nakanishi Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76913" type="appears in" update="2015-08-18">
<name>Hanako no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2942" picture="23713.jpg">Tanonaka Isamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76969" type="appears in" update="2015-08-23">
<name>111</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176631.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="76970" type="appears in" update="2015-08-23">
<name>222</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176632.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="76971" type="appears in" update="2015-08-23">
<name>555</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176633.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="76972" type="appears in" update="2015-08-23">
<name>666</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176634.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="76973" type="appears in" update="2015-08-23">
<name>777</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176635.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="76974" type="appears in" update="2015-08-23">
<name>888</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176636.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77208" type="appears in" update="2015-09-03">
<name>Suruu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5637" picture="188452.jpg">Shiraishi Fuyumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77209" type="appears in" update="2015-09-03">
<name>Nuruu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21114" picture="39572.jpg">Yamada Shunji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77210" type="appears in" update="2015-09-03">
<name>Tsuruu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19200" picture="50076.jpg">Tsukase Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97972" type="appears in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="1">2.41</rating>
<name>Chromeria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Green eyes and red hair that is past waist length.
Lives on an industrial planet and is active as an activist against the planetary destruction.</description>
<picture>223765.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="14923" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出発(たびだち)のバラード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departure Ballad</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le départ</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La ballata della partenza</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi no Ballad</title>
<summary>On the road to Megalopolis, Tetsuro is encountered by Count Mecha and watches as his mother is killed. Ironically, he is rescued by a woman who looks remarkably like his mother, and they set off on a journey on the Galaxy Express 999. He begins his trek towards the planet where he`ll be able to receive a mechanical body.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512592</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15650" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">火星の赤い風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Winds of Mars</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le vent rouge de Mars</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il vento rosso di Marte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kasei no Akai Kaze</title>
<summary>The capital of Mars, Great Syrtis. It is a deserted planet with nothing but the blowing of the red winds. Tetsuro is attacked by Geronimo, who has long dreamt of boarding the 999, and has his pass stolen by him. Ultimately, he draws his gun on his lover, Fleme.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512594</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="20203" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイタンの眠れる戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Titan`s Sleeping Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`enlèvement de Marina</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un guerriero su Titano</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Titan no Nemureru Senshi</title>
<summary>Tetsuro is rescued from a ghost by Claire, a waitress they met. But in doing so, Claire is blasted into a million pieces. After finally arriving on Titan, one of Saturn`s satellites, they go outside and Maetel is abducted. When Tetsuro goes to rescue her, oddly, he is given a gun by an old woman...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512596</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="24607" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大盗賊アンタレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Bandit Antares</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Antalius</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Antalius il rapinatore dello spazio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daitouzoku Antares</title>
<summary>The great bandit Antares hijacks the 999 and takes Tetsuro and the gang hostage as he forces them to make an unplanned stop at his home. He takes a liking to the humans Maetel and Tetsuro and invites them into his home. But lurking in there is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512598</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="24611" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷いの星の影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadow of the Planet of Indecision</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une planète glaciale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoi no Hoshi no Kage</title>
<summary>Pluto, the resting place for the bodies of those who have replaced their human bodies with mechanical ones. Tetsuro is greeted by the ice graveyard`s caretaker, Shadow. She transforms herself to look like Tetsuro`s mother and lures him in. She attempts to kill him, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512600</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26624" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">彗星図書館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Comet Library</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Silence, on coupe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suisei Toshokan</title>
<summary>Tetsuro arrives at the nest of Comets, Comet Station, and is shocked at its lack of vertical scope. He`s falsely accused by a suspicious man while killing time in a bookstore and gets attacked. He goes to a doctor, but instead of receiving medical care, he tries to force Tetsuro into buying a mechanical body!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512602</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26625" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">重力の底の墓場 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Graveyard at the Bottom of Gravity: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`accident du Galaxy Express, partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juuryoku no Soko no Hakaba Zenpen</title>
<summary>The 999 spirals downward to the bottom of gravity. They enter into the 333, which had previously crashed in there, only to find that hundreds of years appear to have passed by! The woman who controls the passage of time, a witch named Ryuz, takes a liking to Tetsuro and drags him to her home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512604</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26626" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">重力の底の墓場 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Graveyard at the Bottom of Gravity: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`accident du Galaxy Express, partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juuryoku no Soko no Hakaba Kouhen</title>
<summary>Continuing the plot, we find out that Ryuz is a depressed woman who was betrayed by the man she loved while she was transforming her body for him. Tetsuro sympathizes with her, but tells her, "I want to decide my future for myself." Ryuz`s retort to those words is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512606</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26627" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トレーダー分岐点 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trader Junction: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Halte sur Tradar, partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trader Bunki Ten Zenpen</title>
<summary>Trader Junction, a crossroads for the Galaxy Railways. Surrounding the station are countless desolate travelers with nothing more to do but wait. Tetsuro offers to treat one of the travelers to food and drinks and gets mobbed by them all. He`s rescued by a women named Hanako, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512608</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26628" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トレーダー分岐点 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trader Junction: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Halte sur Tradar, partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trader Bunki Ten Kouhen</title>
<summary>Tetsuro foolishly falls asleep and is taken by Hanako aboard the train bound for Wildflower Station. He is introduced to Hanako`s elderly parents as her fiance. After seeing the delight on their faces, Tetsuro didn`t have the heart to say anything. Even the idea of throwing a wedding reception is brought up...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512610</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26629" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不定形惑星ヌルーバ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Formless Planet Nuruba</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète informe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futeikei Wakusei Nuruba</title>
<summary>On the planet without a form, Nuruba, Tetsuro and Maetel are ambushed by its citizens for their bodies and their clothes are stolen. They plan to dress up like Tetsuro and Maetel and board the 999. A livid Tetsuro lunges at them, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512612</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26631" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">化石の戦士 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fossilized Warrior: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le gardien des fossiles, partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaseki no Senshi Zenpen</title>
<summary>The 999 has to make an emergency stop at Fossilized Planet, a place petrified all the way to the tracks. Tetsuro is curious about the fossils and leaves the 999. Suspecting that Tetsuro has intent to steal he fossils, a warrior who guards the Fossilized Planet attacks him...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512614</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26632" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">化石の戦士 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fossilized Warrior: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le gardien des fossiles, partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaseki no Senshi Kouhen</title>
<summary>Tetsuro rescues the fossilized warrior from a gang of thieves. However, the warrior runs off with Tetsuro`s pass. He attempts to leave on the 999 along with the fossil of his lover, Lidya. Just as Tetsuro follows him, the petrifying gas appears once again!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512644</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26633" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">二重惑星のラーラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laala from the Double Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les planètes jumelles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nijuu Wakusei no Laala</title>
<summary>"Perfect Mechanization," a planet where all its inhabitants have taken on mechanical bodies. All its people look down upon flesh-and-blood humans. A female doctor named Laala purposely hits Tetsuro with her car. She attempted to switch bodies with him!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512646</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26634" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">水の国のベートーベン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Water Kingdom: Beethoven</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le musicien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizu no Kuni no Beethoven</title>
<summary>On the "Black Knight`s Planet," Tetsuro is invited to live together with the Black Knight. When Tetsuro refuses, he frantically throws his lance at him! Maetel jumps to the rescue but his his by the lance! Tetsuro stands up to the Black Knight to get revenge, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512648</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26635" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">蛍の街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Town of Fireflies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tout ce qui brille</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hotaru no Machi</title>
<summary>On the planet where people have the ability to glow, Tetsuro meets a struggling aspiring animation director named Fraiya. Tetsuro feels lousy after she rejects his offer to give her money. However, she invites him into her room and asks him to buy one of her animation storyboards.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512650</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26636" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">装甲惑星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Armored Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète blindée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soukou Wakusei</title>
<summary>On a planet where all living things are covered in hard armor, Maetel is hit by an armored bug and is seriously injured. Tetsuro leaves the train in search of a doctor, but there are only two people on the entire planet. Due to a misunderstanding, Tetsuro is attacked by one of them, Nutal!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512652</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26637" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">泥のメーテル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maetel of Mud</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`autre Marina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doro no Maetel</title>
<summary>In the "Mud Capitol," a city where the rain never stops, Tetsuro receives a phone call from a woman and is dragged out into the mud. There he encounters a poor woman named Maetel who lives within the mud. She invites Tetsuro to live together with him. He refuses, however, but when he tries to escape from her mud house...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512654</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26638" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ざんげの国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Kingdom of Atonement</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète du repentir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange no Kuni</title>
<summary>In "The Kingdom of Atonement," a town famous for its sanitation, the conductor is attacked by a mugger on his day off! Tetsuro and Maetel console him. However, the news of the event reaches the upset Cleanliness Committee. They attempt to erase any record of the event and begin pursuing Tetsuro and the gang.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512656</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26639" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロフェッショナル魂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Souls of Professionals</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les professionnels1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Professional Tamashi</title>
<summary>On Professional, the planet of memories, Tetsuro ignores Maetel`s advice, and makes eye contact with a professional hangman. They attempt to hang Tetsuro! He is saved by a professional gunman, only to be forced into a shooting duel!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512658</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26640" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">枯葉の墓標</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tombstone of Dead Leaves</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les feuilles mortes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kareha no Bohyou</title>
<summary>The inside of Ballera has become hollow. Tetsuro and Maetel are swimming around in the air when they`re attacked by some cowboys and it causes a big commotion. In the Tomb of Dead leaves, they encounter Mr. Moriki, a man made from a briar bush. But then, an electric mushroom causes the 999 to suddenly stop moving!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512660</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26641" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海賊船クィーン・エメラルダス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pirate Ship Queen Emeraldas</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La pirate de l`espace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaizokusen Queen Emeraldas</title>
<summary>The 999 is raided by the pirate ship Queen Emeraldas. They try to put up a fight, but realize quickly that it is all in vain, and are forced to stop on the Pirate Planet. There, the female pirate, Emeraldas, proposes a duel. Maetel loses and they set off to dispose of her body! However, the Emeraldas they faced was really a fake!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512662</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26642" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">原始惑星の女王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Queen of the Primitive Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La reine des indigènes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genshi Wakusei no Joou</title>
<summary>This world has been split up, due to a feud, into civilization and primeval society. On this primitive planet, the gang is attacked by the locals and Maetel is nominated Queen. Queen Maetel orders for Tetsuro to be thrown off a cliff, but it`s all part of Maetel`s plan...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512664</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26643" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">次元航海惑星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Planet of Dimensional Voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète interdimensionnelle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigen Koukai Wakusei</title>
<summary>The Planet of Dimension Voyage travels across the galaxy at the whim of its egotistical queen, Egoterina. The gang is attacked by Egoterina`s men, but she takes a liking to them and invites them over for dinner. However, the queen is unimpressed, to say the least, with Tetsuro`s manner of eating...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512666</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26644" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鋼鉄天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Steel Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rose-Marie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutetsu Tenshi</title>
<summary>Masspron, a world covered in factories. The hotel Tetsuro is staying in is burnt to the ground. Ironically, it was deliberately caused by a young girl named Chromeria, who is leading a rebellion to get people to learn to build things while also beautifying the planet. Tetsuro manages to save her from execution, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512668</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26645" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">白骨の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Skeleton`s Song</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le crime de Teddy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakkotsu no Uta</title>
<summary>Horohoro egg vendor who loses a piece of his body each time he is betrayed by his lover. He`s to the point where his chest is completely hollow with the exception of a few bones. After selling eggs to Tetsuro, he pins a crime on him as he attempts to shoot his former lover and hew new man.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512670</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26646" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪の都の鬼子母神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Goddess of Children and Easy Birth in the Snow Capital</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un beau geste</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki no To no Kishimojin</title>
<summary>On this planet where snow never ceases to fall, Maetel and a straggling Tetsuro encounter a starving girl named Yuki. She offers to take them into her house after they offer her a piece of a biscuit. There, however, the girl`s mother attempts to cut Tetsuro open. She`s thinking about using him for food...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512672</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26647" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かげろう星の文豪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Writer of the Mirage Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`écrivain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagerou Boshi no Bungou</title>
<summary>Tetsuro and the gang touch down on the supposedly uninhabited Mirage Planet. There, they encounter the great novelist, Shosetsu Yoi. Though he had given upall attachments to the world, he becomes attracted to Maetel. He decides to abandon Tetsuro on the planet and leave on the 999.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512674</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26648" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サケザン大陸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sakezan Continent</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Takezan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakezan Tairiku</title>
<summary>On the Jungle Planet, the gang is captured by the alcoholic ruler, Sakezan. Maetel is chained up and forced to drink. Along with Liza, the queen, Tetsuro escapes Sakezan`s lair and leaves Maetel behind. However, he returns again and faces Sakezan!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512676</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26649" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽霊世界のフィラメント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ghost World Filament</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des esprits éclairés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuurei Sekai no Filament</title>
<summary>The 999 stops on Filament, a planet filled with gas, due to interference from some ghosts. There, Tetsuro is kidnapped by a ghost parent-child duo. They are planning on using Tetsuro`s body to revive the ghost! But once they realize that he`s on a mission to get a mechanical body, they...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512678</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26650" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒髪星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fury Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète des tumultes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dohatsu Boshi</title>
<summary>On the Fury Planet, a land where everyone is quick to pick a fight, Tetsuro slams into a tofu vendor as an assassin who works for Duke Mech, a friend of Count Mecha, targets him. Tetsuro feels bad for the kind-mannered tofu vendor and offers to give him some gold coins. But when he goes to leave...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512680</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26651" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">停時空間のかじられ星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bitten Planet of Stopped Space-Time</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète rongée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toma Toki Kuukan no Kajirare Hoshi</title>
<summary>The gang encounters the space warrior Edmond inside of the 999. His hometown, "Sweet, Sweet Planet" is shaped like an apple that has hadbites taken out of it. Because the ground tastes very sweet and delicious, the government has sold the land and it`s taken on a very ugly appearance. Upset by this, Edmond tried to battle the government, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512682</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26652" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウラトレスのネジの山</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ulatres`s Screw Mountain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vis cassée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ulatres no Neji no Yama</title>
<summary>Ulatres, a planet that specializes in screws. There, a woman named Lasen takes a liking to Tetsuro and imprisons him in the hopes of them living together. Tetsuro escapes and Lasen gives chase. However, when she sees that Tetsuro will never give up, she takes a deep look at herself...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512684</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26653" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレーテッド・シティの魔女 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Witch of Plated City: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète dorée, partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Plated City no Majo Zenpen</title>
<summary>Plated City, a planet where people are considered poor if they aren`t plated in gold. There, Maetel has her suitcase stolen by Wheel Lock, a young boy who wants to get plated. However, his mother tells him not to, so he gives up. Wheel Lock then begins to tell them about his planet...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512616</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26654" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレーテッド・シティの魔女 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Witch of Plated City: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète dorée, partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Plated City no Majo Kouhen</title>
<summary>Wheel Lock`s mother is against the tradition of plating and is trying to form a resistance. As her dying wish, she asks Wheel Lock to continue the fight against gold plating. Tetsuro goes into the heart of it all, a magnetized, plated tower. But waiting inside is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512686</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26655" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大酋長サイクロプロス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Chief Cicropros</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un grand savant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daishuuchou Cicropros</title>
<summary>In a ghost colony where no one is supposed to live, Tetsuro and the gang meet Dr. Cicropros and a legion of his clones. Having failed at building the colony in the past, Cicropros is using his clones to see if the colony is safe or not.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512618</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51165" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミーくんの命の館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mii-kun`s Mansion of Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`arche de l`au-delà</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mii-kun no Inochi no Kan</title>
<summary>They say the planet named Mii-kun`s Mansion of Life is a flower and animal-filled planet where the souls of beloved pets of children are brought to rest. Tetsuro, mistakenly believing Maetel is being attacked, draws his gun on the animals, only to be stopped by a mysterious woman.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512688</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51166" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">卑怯者の長老帝国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Empire of the Cowardly Elder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikyousha no Chourou Teikoku</title>
<summary>The 999 is in really bad shape on the Planet of the Cowardly Elder! And it`s the doing of the cowardly president of the planet who trusts no one, Delmukade. His motive is Tetsuro`s body because he lacks the courage to adopt a mechanical body.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512620</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51167" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧の都のカスミ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kasumi of the Mist Capitol</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une faiblesse mortelle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiri no To no Kasumi</title>
<summary>The suitcase with Tetsuro and Maetel`s passes is stolen. However, the thief collapses while making their escape. It turns out the people on this planet have only one percent of a normal human`s physical strength. Even a gunshot from their guns barely stings. They easily get their suitcase back, but the passes are counterfeit!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512690</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51168" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">球状住宅団の大酋長 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Chief of the Spherical Housing Complex: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuujou Juutaku Dan no Daishuuchou Zenpen</title>
<summary>Maetel is abducted by the Chief as soon as they arrive at the Spherical Housing Complex, a complex of spherical houses. There are no men here who will oppose the Chief who dwells in a castle in the sky. On the way to rescue her, Tetsuro encounters a man who looks exactly like an older version of himself, Tetsugoro Hoshino.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512622</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51169" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">球状住宅団の大酋長 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Chief of the Spherical Housing Complex: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuujou Juutaku Dan no Daishuuchou Kouhen</title>
<summary>Within the Chief`s castle Tetsuro learns of some sort of secret and sees Maetel being subservient to the Chief. He tries to save her but is almost sent flying out into space. Tetsugoro, livid after finding out that his former lover was killed, plants a bomb on the Chief`s castle. Tetsuro has to save Maetel in the five minutes before the bomb detonates!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512692</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51170" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フィメールの思い出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Female`s Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Female no Omoide</title>
<summary>As they approach the station, the Face of Memories, a woman passenger named Female causes a disturbance on the train and derails the 999. However, it seems that she knew the Conductor when he was young. As if to anger the Conductor on purpose, she slaps Maetel. An angry Conductor takes a gravity control device that derailed the train...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512624</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51171" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐が丘のキラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kira of Storm Hill, Arashigaoka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashigaoka no Kira</title>
<summary>Tetsuro has his pass stolen on a planet where the wind never stops blowing. Tetsuro believes the thief to be a young man named Kira but Kira denies any wrongdoing. The next day, Kira shows up in front of Tetsuro, confused. He says he wanted to steal the pass so he could board the 999. But Kira`s father who should be crying, apologizing for his son, is actually...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512694</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51172" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワルキューレの空間騎行 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Space Ride of the Valkyries: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Valkyrie no Kuukan Kikou Zenpen</title>
<summary>At Deadwood Mountain, a young man named Prider arrived on a train in order to make money for his girlfriend Alice by music. Tetsuro feels bad for his girlfriend, but doesn`t say so. He gets angry at Prider, who never stops singing. While fighting, Tetsuro remembers how he got his pass from Maetel. Just then, the 999 is taken over by a horrible mother-and-daughter duo known as Valkyries.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512626</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51173" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワルキューレの空間騎行 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Space Ride of the Valkyries: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Valkyrie no Kuukan Kikou Kouhen</title>
<summary>Tetsuro, haven been taken aboard the Valkyrie`s mothership, tries to escape. Prider tries to defend Tetsuro and is stabbed by the Valkyries. The Valkyrie mother, whose anger stems from the fact her daughter was murdered by a human, squares off against the four of them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512696</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51174" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エルアラメインの歌声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">El Alamein`s Singing Voice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">El Alamein no Utagoe</title>
<summary>Maetel, Nanmi, and Tetsuro go down to an ancient battlefield. Fully automated tanks which activate when they detect the presence of life have been left behind there. After Nanmi is shot, Maetel suddenly points a gun at Tetsuro. What did Maetel have to do in order to survive this crisis?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512628</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51175" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">永久戦斗実験室 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Laboratory of Eternal War: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eikyuusen to Jikken Shitsu Zenpen</title>
<summary>On a planet where war is considered a tourist attraction, the 999 stops and the passengers eat dinner while watching people actually in battle. Tetsuro was eating when a soldier is killed and another soldier, Zeda, sees Tetsuro and goes after him, thinking Tetsuro enjoyed it. Tetsuro takes his gun from the 999 and goes to work with the man to clear the misunderstanding.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512698</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51176" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">永久戦斗実験室 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Laboratory of Eternal War: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eikyuusen to Jikken Shitsu Kouhen</title>
<summary>Zeda is convinced to join a rebel militia by a female soldier named Santana and they set off to not fight as a tourist attraction, but to do battle with the leader of the planet. They are betrayed by Brudas and the enemy is given their battle plan. Tetsuro gives this information to Zeda but the government is plotting an ambush...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512630</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51177" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">これからの星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Future Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Korekara no Hoshi</title>
<summary>Tetsuro and the gang go to a planet full of industrious people. A planet that, although poor, is brimming with vigor. The husband and wife who run the inn where they are staying at are also hard workers. They are warmly welcomed. However, Tetsuro and Maetel lose their passes and luggage when a typhoon hits. Tetsuro suspects the husband and wife who run the inn, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512700</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51178" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">亡霊トンネル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Tunnel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bourei Tunnel</title>
<summary>A woman named Eroze who controls the tunnels that don`t absorb any sound tries to destroy the 999. In order to save the 999 from destruction, Tetsuro goes with the woman. We then find out she`s actually an android who was built for schadenfreude. Tetsuro becomes enraged that she`d pull off so many horrible pranks including destroying the 999. Then at long last...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512632</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51179" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">透明海のアルテミス 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Artemis of the Transparent Sea: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toumei Umi no Artemis Zenpen</title>
<summary>An oddly shaped planet complete with giant life-forms appears in the 999`s path. Though they have the desire, the planet lacks the desire to move and the 999, unable to escape, sinks into the planet. In order to rescue the 999, the Galaxy Railways Administration decides to send out oscillation waves to destroy the planet. When that is supposed to happen, a transparent woman lands in a space ship.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512702</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51180" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">透明海のアルテミス 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Artemis of the Transparent Sea: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toumei Umi no Artemis Kouhen</title>
<summary>The transparent woman is named Artemis. She lives on the oddly shaped planet but left to get a mechanical body and now she wishes to reside on the planet. But, to pay back her debts, she is forced to perform backbreaking labor. In the end, she returned to rest with her mother. Tetsuro cries at her death...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512634</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51181" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鏡の星の鉄郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tetsuro on the Planet of Mirrors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagami no Hoshi no Tetsuo</title>
<summary>Maetel, mistakenly brings Manabu Sunayama, a boy with a pass for the 999 who looks identical to Tetsuro, back to the hotel. Sunyama and his siblings worked themselves to the bone to get a pass to board the 999. Manabu`s older brother lost his life in the process. But, the pass turns out to be a fake, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512704</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51182" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりなき夏の物語 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tale of the Endless Summer: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owari Naki Natsu no Monogatari Zenpen</title>
<summary>Tetsuro and Maetel are captured by a group of bug-humans named Insectors who rule the planet. They go to boil them to use as food for their children. But, the boiling point of water on the planet is low due to the planet`s environment, so they escape unscathed. However, the Insectors proceed to cover the 999 in a cocoon. They plan to use the 999 and its passengers as food for their children as they send them off to another planet with food.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512636</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51183" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりなき夏の物語 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tale of the Endless Summer: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owari Naki Natsu no Monogatari Kouhen</title>
<summary>Tetsuro is unable to shoot the Insector babies that hatch from their eggs. The 999 then takes off into space with the Insector babies on board. The babies eat the seats, floors, and everything in sight with an amazing appetite. Just when you think the humans are in danger, though...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512706</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51184" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">冷血帝国 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cold Blooded Empire: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reiketsu Teikoku Zenpen</title>
<summary>On the Dinosaur Planet, a dinosaur named Tiny asks Tetsuro to let him board the 999. Of course, the 999 isn`t built for dinosaur-sized passengers, no matter how "tiny" he may be. However, the locals are fearful of people from other planets and attack and capture them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512638</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51185" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">冷血帝国 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cold Blooded Empire: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reiketsu Teikoku Kouhen</title>
<summary>Tiny, learning of Tetsuro`s trouble from his girlfriend Rayde, asks her to give a message to him. Rayde rescues Tetsuro in Tiny`s place and forwards the message. Tiny`s message says "You`re awfully polite considering we`re friends." Tetsuro, unwilling to never see Tiny again, sets off to see him once again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512708</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51186" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">足音村の足音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Footsteps of Footstep Village</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashioto Mura no Ashioto</title>
<summary>On a planet rumored to have ghosts, Tetsuro encounters a ghost made of water. After being asked by that ghost, Yayoi, Tetsuro digs up the spot underneath a tree. Maetel, worried about Tetsuro, drives Yayoi the ghost away. But inside of the package is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512640</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51187" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">なまけものの鏡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Idle One`s Mirror</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namakemono no Kagami</title>
<summary>The Lazy Man`s Mirror is a planet where everything has been made to be automatic and men have nothing to do. They`ve gotten obese enough to literally make their houses explode. A woman named Sabrina realizes that she doesn`t want to be on this planet anymore and asks Tetsuro to help her board the 999. But, the Galaxy Railways` policies dictate that a pass is required to board...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527966</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51188" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大四畳半惑星の幻想 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet of a Pint Size Room: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiyojouhan Wakusei no Gensou Zenpen</title>
<summary>They arrive on the Future Planet, a planet where the existence of the 999 is kept secret. There, Tetsuro`s pass is stolen by a young boy named Taro who dreams of traveling in space. Tetsuro and Maetel search for a place to stay and end up at a cheap hostel where they meet an aspiring comic-artist named Futoshi Adachi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512710</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51343" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大四畳半惑星の幻想 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet of a Pint Size Room: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiyojouhan Wakusei no Gensou Kouhen</title>
<summary>Without even food to eat, Tetsuro begins to work. But, they won`t reissue his pass so unless he gets it back he will be unable to board the 999. So Tetsuro and Maetel decide to wait at the station to get their passes back. There, Taro shows up, but he`s suddenly not sure if he truly wants to board the 999...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512642</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51344" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜のない街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">City Without Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoru no Nai Machi</title>
<summary>Under the "Perfect Sleep" law, you are not allowed to go out at night on the planet Town without Night. There, Tetsuro gets into a scuffle with a group of men hoping to get a shot of the kind monster Heron, and the police are called. He`s taken in by the police and it looks like he won`t make it back in time to board the 999. Then, Heron appears once again...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512712</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51345" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤミヤミの姉妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pitch Dark Sisters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yamiyami no Shimai</title>
<summary>Tetsuro is asked by a woman to kill her sister Lelan who is trying to launch an artificial sun on planet Dark-Dark, a place enveloped in the dark of night. Her concern is that they don`t know what will happen if the artificial sun is launched and it is not dark anymore. But, Lelan kidnaps Maetel and sets her plan into motion!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528010</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51346" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">沈黙の聖地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sacred Planet of Silence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chinmoku no Seichi</title>
<summary>On the planet, the Mecca of Silence, where making loud noises is against the law, Maetel tries to stop Tetsuro when he goes to yell out the window of the 999 but fails. Tetsuro is quickly put to death for no reason other than making the loud noise, but is rescued by a woman named Sylvia. It turns out her husband was killed as well. However, they begin to chase after Tetsuro again...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528012</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51347" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">交響詩 魔女の堅琴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Symphonic Poem and the Witch`s Harp</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukyoushi Majo no Kenkin</title>
<summary>On the planet the Witch`s Harp, a land where almost all food is given as tribute to the queen and the people are in a food shortage, they meet a young man named Nichola who is killed over a tiny amount of food. Enraged, Tetsuro and Maetel set off to the queen`s island to stop this tributary system. However, there they have a surprising discovery...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528014</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51348" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧の葬送惑星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Planet of Funeral in the Mist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiri no Sousou Wakusei</title>
<summary>The Foggy Funeral Planet is a planet where, as all its inhabitants have become cyborgs, everyone is immortal and they think not much of death. They`ve begun to practice performing funerals for whoever they feel like and they make a pastime of it. Maetel and Tetsuro are attacked and buried alive but are rescued by a woman named Machiru. She tells them why the planet has become the way it has, but then she is sacrificed for a funeral herself!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528016</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51349" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙僧ダイルーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dyruz the Space Monk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuusou Dyruz</title>
<summary>Space Monk Dyruz travels the galaxy from planet to planet ringing his bell. The vibrations from his bell derail the 999 and cause Tetsuro`s teeth to fall to pieces. Because of this, they go for emergency treatment at the Emergency Medical Treatment Asteroid. There they encounter two people. One of them, a young man named Mikail, is badly injured and is ready to give up on life. Tetsuro and Dyruz compete to see who can give the young man hope again...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528018</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51350" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">好奇心という名の星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Planet Named Curiosity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouki Shin to Iu Na no Hoshi</title>
<summary>On planet Curiosity they capture humans out of curiosity and dissect their bodies. They force the 999 to land there then force Maetel to get naked. They then command the Conductor to dissect Maetel. But, when Tetsuro cuts into the planet with the knife instead...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528020</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51351" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">C62[しろくに]の反乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rebellion of C62</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">C Roku Ni no Hanran</title>
<summary>The 999`s locomotive, C62, leaves the passenger cars behind and takes off. Though it`s a test to see how Tetsuro will pass the time, Tetsuro plays merrily with the Conductor and Maetel and kills the time. But, there are two robbers who stole a good amount of money on board, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528358</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51352" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">心やさしき花の都</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Capital of Kind Flowers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro Yasashiki Hana no To</title>
<summary>The people on the Flower Capital, which is overflowing with flowers in bloom, all have a special armor. This is because the flowers there all emit a poisonous pollen. But someone has to burn all the flowers in order to save the people...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528024</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51353" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">賽の河原の開拓者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pioneer from the River of Purgatory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sai no Kawara no Kaitakusha</title>
<summary>On Limbo, a planet without grass nor trees, Tetsuro and Maetel meet a man living tough life tilling the ground in such hard conditions, and his son, Yosaku. They plan to till the ground until the crops are ripe but a monstrous bird comes attacking. In order to protect him, Tetsuro and Yosaku fight the bird...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528026</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51354" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大暗黒惑星アフリカ 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa the Great Dark Nebula: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Ankoku Wakusei Africa Zenpen</title>
<summary>Planet Kilimanjaro is a snow-laden planet with three shining suns. There, Tetsuro and the gang are captured by a race of people who are as thin as paper, the Ghost Hoppers. They`re proud of their technology and plan to use them as specimens in a scientific experiment...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528028</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51355" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大暗黒惑星アフリカ 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa the Great Dark Nebula: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Ankoku Wakusei Africa Kouhen</title>
<summary>The gang successfully escapes from jail and encounter the Ghost Hoppers` sacred queen. She says their people pushed science too far and that is why they look the way they do. The Queen helps them revert the 999`s tracks back to the way they were. She decided to rebel against her own subjects who would not heed her advice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528030</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51356" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">17億6千5百万人のくれくれ星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gimme Planet of 1,765,000,000 People</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">17 Oku 6 Sen 5 Hyaku man Nin no Kurekure Hoshi</title>
<summary>The 999 lands on a planet where every inhabitant is a beggar. But there is a married couple, Rage and Pity, who want it to stop. They board the 999 because they are sick of all the beggars and want to go to another planet where they can live on their own power alone. They steal the money and clothes from Tetsuro and Maetel, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528032</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51357" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">水の国のシャイアン 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cheyenne the Nation of Water: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizu no Kuni no Cheyenne Zenpen</title>
<summary>"Heed our requests or we`ll blow you up!" Those were the words that came from a planet that even Maetel didn`t know that forced the 999 to make an unscheduled landing. The people on the planet mostly live underwater. The one who issued the order to land was the president of an underwater race which had emigrated there, Waterpress. These people had polluted the water as much as they could and continued to fight against the planet`s natives, the Cheyenne Fish...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528034</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51436" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">76</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">水の国のシャイアン 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cheyenne the Nation of Water: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizu no Kuni no Cheyenne Kouhen</title>
<summary>The chief of the Cheyenne Fish, Navarro, gives chase to Water Press who had forced the 999 to take his people on board. He chases them in an old-fashioned space shuttle in order to continue to the fight. The Administration sends out an armored car to rescue the 999 after receiving a distress signal. But, with Tetsuro and Maetel as hostages, there is nothing they can do. Plus, they allow Navarro to enter the train after flying up in the old-fashioned shuttle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528036</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51437" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">77</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">喰命聖女 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saintly Woman Who Devours Souls: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuinochi Seijo Zenpen</title>
<summary>The next stop is the Rainy Pond. They will be stopped there for 64 hours and 23 minutes. Tetsuro and Maetel check into their hotel on this planet where the rain never stops. But, a man who was also on the 999 makes a big fuss. He spends the night reciting sutras and bothering the other 999 passengers in the hotel. The man says he is praying because there is a witch on that planet who eats people`s souls and he doesn`t want anyone to be harmed. Maetel says she`s heard of this witch before...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528038</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51438" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">78</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">喰命聖女 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saintly Woman Who Devours Souls: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuinochi Seijo Kouhen</title>
<summary>The woman says she is the most beautiful woman in the universe and she drinks people`s flames of life in order to maintain that beauty eternally. Her name is Cueflame and she is after Maetel`s flame of life. Working underneath her is the old lady from the hotel and a young woman named Arc. Following Cueflame`s orders, the two of them go to remove Maetel`s flame of life. If she drinks the flame of life from Maetel, she will die. So then, Tetsuro goes to recapture it...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528040</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51439" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">79</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時間城の海賊 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pirate of Time Castle: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikan Shiro no Kaizoku Zenpen</title>
<summary>Planet Heavy Meldar. Once they pass through here, they will leave the Earth Administration`s jurisdiction and enter Andromedan jurisdiction. Right before arrival, they encounter a man wearing a cloak. They didn`t get a good look at his face but he`s carrying a space soldier`s Cosmo Gun of which only four exist in the universe. Upon arrival, Maetel says she has to take care of some business and leaves. Feeling that was odd, Tetsuro goes to look for her and enters a drinking establishment...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528042</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51440" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">80</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時間城の海賊 中編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pirate of Time Castle: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikan Shiro no Kaizoku Chuuhen</title>
<summary>Leryuz lets Tetsuro know that Maetel went to the Castle of Time to battle with the pirate there. Tetsuro asks the people in the bar where the Castle of Time is, but everyone is fearful of Captain Harlock, who rules the Castle of Time, and refuses to help Tetsuro. But, the man in the cloak from the train saves Tetsuro from their violence. Encouraged by the words of the hooded man, one man lets Tetsuro borrow his auto-bike to go to the Castle of Time. He leaves all alone to go rescue Maetel from the duel with Harlock!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528044</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51441" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">81</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時間城の海賊 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pirate of Time Castle: Part Three</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikan Shiro no Kaizoku Kouhen</title>
<summary>Tetsuro is sent into the past. There, against all of Tetsuro`s efforts, his mother his killed just as before. Tetsuro realizes that he cannot alter the past. But then through Leryuz`s ability to manipulate time, he is brought back to the present. While this is going on, we find out what kind of a horrible man the fake Harlock is in his duel with Maetel. He used to fight to restore peace to the galaxy, just like Maetel. But, he betrayed his people, including Maetel, and disrupted their attempt at a revolution.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528046</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51442" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">82</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">短かな生命[いのち]の物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Tale of a Short Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanka na Inochi no Monogatari</title>
<summary>The next station is a plant called "The Butterfly`s Dream." There coexists graceful people with butterfly wings and a discriminated lower class without them. The people with wings live short lives that run out when the season of the cold winds comes. Because of this, they try to live their days having as much fun as possible. But, one girl, Kureha, wants to see more of the world during her short life, so she goes into the forbidden woods. There she meets a poor, wingless boy named Leaf.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528048</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51443" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">83</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第3生命帯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life-Form Number Three</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 3 Seimeitai</title>
<summary>Planet number one, Zaba, and plane number four, Maya, are engaged in a war to the death. Though they knew nearby planet number five was about to blow up, the 999 had to make a critical stop on planet number three. Upon exiting the train, Maetel and Tetsuro are attacked by a mysterious ape-man and their passes are stolen. While researching the planet, they meet a boy from planet number one, Seth. He came with his girlfriend from Zaba, which was on the verge of destruction. They plan to stop the mysterious degeneration on planet number three to create a new Zaba.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528050</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51444" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">84</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">巨象の星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Planet of the Giant Elephant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyozou no Hoshi</title>
<summary>Tetsuro spots a message in a bottle from the 999`s window. In it is a letter written by the adventurer Stanley, who is exploring the planet Arcadia. From the looks of the letter, Stanley and his crew are in grave danger in their search for the giant elephant, Flame. Tetsuro persuades the 999 to go the planet. Quickly following the clues, they come across Stanley, his wife Merusa, and their assistant, Narl. Though Merusa and Narl are happy to be rescued, Stanley stubbornly wishes to continue his exploration.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528052</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51445" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">85</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の幻影惑星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Planet of Illusive Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Gen`ei Wakusei</title>
<summary>They stop for thirty-eight hours and fourteen minutes on the Planet of Illusive Love. There, Tetsuro loses sight of Maetel and encounters a girl selling her poems, Naya. Naya is curious about the aspiring artist who lives in a room that she goes to visit, Lestel. Lestel, though, is in love with a women who poses as his model, Feras. But, Feras appears to be in love with a rich young man from the cafe she works at, Bina.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528054</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51446" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">86</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">親知らず星のUFO</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The UFO of the Planet of Forgotten Parents</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oyashirazu Hoshi no UFO</title>
<summary>The next stop is the Wisdom Tooth Planet. There many of the children have ran away from homes so there are many impatient adults who have grown weary from waiting for them to return. The son of the owners of the inn Tetsuro and Maetel stay at also ran away from home. The father, suffering from a case of stress-induced dementia, is convinced that Tetsuro his is long lost son, Tetsuo. But then the real Tetsuo, a fugitive murderer, returns home...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528056</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51447" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">87</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海からきたエルザ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Elza from the Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi kara Kita Elza</title>
<summary>On the planet built by God, people are constantly performing military drills. They are also very military in nature and perform their security checks very seriously. The Suraroids, who escaped the construction of the underwater city, are in a fierce fight with the Brittenians. The Brittenian Nazuka was looking forward to the return of his lover, the Suraroidan queen, Elza, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528058</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51448" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">88</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の分れ星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet, Crossroads of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Wakareboshi</title>
<summary>On the Planet where Fate Divides, there are refugees from a planet which was about to be destroyed, are living a very primitive lifestyle. They hunt animals by hand and wear pelts. It`s just like the Stone Age. One of these "people of the future" is a young man named Yaku who is skilled at creating tools. Because he is not physically gifted, Yaku goes to hunt game with a bow and arrow. Tetsuro sees him and he declares that, more so than his planet being destroyed, he has to focus on how he`ll live from here on out. Then he makes a big change in the way he hunts...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528060</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51449" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">89</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガンマン哀歌[えれじい]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gunman`s Elegy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gunman Elegy</title>
<summary>The Hangman`s Planet. On this desolate planet that looks like something straight out of a western, Tetsuro quickly gets himself into trouble. Two gangs, the Blacks and Whites, are in a bitter dispute over the gold being mined here. In order not to raise suspicions as to who is guilty, the White gang conscripts a lone gunman named Wester and the Black gang conscripts Tetsuro. This quickly escalates into a draw between the two, and they haven`t even realized it`s a plot by the Sheriff and Mayor yet...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528062</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51450" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">90</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンドロメダの雪女 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Snow Woman of Andromeda: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Andromeda no Yukionna Zenpen</title>
<summary>The gateway planet to Andromeda, Snowinca. Maetel tells Tetsuro a legend from this planet where if you so much as glance at the Snow Woman she will kill you. Maetel takes Tetsuro to the universe`s best ramen shop, after arriving on the planet. At night, Tetsuro goes back to the ramen shop alone. While chatting with the owner, the fabled Snow Woman enters the shop!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528066</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51451" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">91</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンドロメダの雪女 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Snow Woman of Andromeda: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Andromeda no Yukionna Kouhen</title>
<summary>While searching for Tetsuro, Maetel encounters a mechanical body salesman named Snowlock. At the same time, we learn that the "Death upon glancing" rumor was made up by the aforementioned salesman. It was to keep the Snow Woman from giving away free mechanical bodies. However, she plans to turn Tetsuro into a cyborg, then take his body to go eat hot ramen. Then Tetsuro decides he`ll agree to make ramen that even she can eat that will warm her all the way to her heart.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528068</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51452" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">92</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海底都市の最期</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Days of the Underwater City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitei Toshi no Saigo</title>
<summary>Here, on the Planet of the Rainbow Sash, the paranoid governor has forced the people to live in an underwater city due to a nuclear war he started. But, that city is about to be destroyed, too! After a chance meeting in a hotel run by an arrogant manager with a young employee, Tetsuro is allowed to stay in his apartment. He also receives a pass for the emigration capsule. He goes to escape with his coworker, Kumiko, but he is double-crossed...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528070</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51453" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">93</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">昆虫惑星の蛍子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Keiko of the Insect Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konchuu Wakusei no Keiko</title>
<summary>There are warnings about mysterious murders taking place on the Bug Planet. After arrival, Tetsuro and Maetel come across the murder scene of a business man. It seems that the key to the murders is a girl named Keiko who supports the bugs` cause and has sided with them. She then quickly asks Tetsuro if he`d become a bug-man to help save the planet`s insects. Then, some very tiny bug-men appear in front of Tetsuro.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528072</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51454" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">94</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤーヤボールの小さな世界 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yayaball`s Tiny World: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yayaball no Chiisana Sekai Zenpen</title>
<summary>The Locomotive detects something abnormal. It appears that someone or something is blocking the space rails. Upon realizing that this is sabotage, the Locomotive informs the Conductor that this is the notorious "Yayaball`s Tiny World". This is a miniature Earth that has been entirely shaped to fit the whims of its creator, Yayaball. After checking in at the hotel with Maetel, Tetsuro is invited out to dinner by Yayaball.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528074</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51455" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">95</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤーヤボールの小さな世界 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yayaball`s Tiny World: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yayaball no Chiisana Sekai Kouhen</title>
<summary>After hearing Tetsuro`s reasons for his journey, Yayaball feels that Tetsuro may indeed be strong. He is also plotting to kill those superior to him. Maetel assumes his mother is alive and didn`t die in the accident years ago so she asks Tetsuro to search the mansion. It seems the one pulling Yayaball`s strings from the shadows harbors a secret...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528076</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51456" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">96</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フライング・クロ 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flying Kuros: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flying Kuro Zenpen</title>
<summary>Quima is a place where everything is forced to become mechanized. The Conductor tells Maetel and Tetsuro to only eat at the Galaxy Railways` sanctioned establishment. They then proceed to check into the hotel. On this planet, mechanized cats named Catroids and a group of flying cats named the Flying Kuros are aggravating the police. Caught in the mix, Tetsuro and Maetel are arrested as traitors while trying to pursue the cats.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528078</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51457" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">97</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フライング・クロ 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flying Kuros: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flying Kuro Kouhen</title>
<summary>Tetsuro and Maetel met a girl named Neko while chasing Catroids. She is hiding Meow, the leader of the Catroids, from the police. She then tells Tetsuro, in tears, about the atrocities being committed by the police on the planet. The police wanted to force everyone to become cyborgs. They set up a trap in a sushi restaurant, captured people there, and converted each one to having a mechanical body. Both Neko and Meow fell victim to this plot so they are using the skills of the Flying Kuros to sniff out humans.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528080</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51458" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">98</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙に残った一冊の本</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One Book Left in the Universe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu ni Nokotta Issatsu no Hon</title>
<summary>The next stop is the Planet of the Forgotten Ones. This is a planet that was destined for destruction. There is a planet left that has been worn down by the relentlessly burning sun. The people here have to submit an application to a government official to see if they qualify to escape the planet. But, one author, Mori, decides to stay behind and finish writing the history of the planet. Tetsuro meets with him and tries fervently to convince him to escape, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528082</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51459" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">99</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">四次元エレベーター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fourth-Dimensional Elevator</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shijigen Elevator</title>
<summary>In the Bottomless City, buildings rise as high and go down as deep as is humanly possible. Tetsuro and Maetel check into their hotel there. But, it seems it to be best to not use the elevator. But, Tetsuro becomes worried when someone named Kezaluna calls out to Maetel, so he uses the elevator to search for her. But, it turns out to be a four-dimensional elevator that transports him into different dimensions. In there, of all things, Tetsuro sees Maetel and Kezaluna`s wedding ceremony!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528084</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51465" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">100</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルーズゾーンの妖怪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monster of Loose Zone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loose Zone no Youkai</title>
<summary>The Conductor lazily says, "Ehh, the next stop is Loose Zone. We`ll be stopped for twelve hours or so. Yes we`re arriving at Loose Zone." Feeling just as lazy and loose as him, Tetsuro ends up being ejected from the 999. Maetel and the Conductor search to find him, while he clings on to dear life. Unfortunately, the search is fruitless and he is flung off the train. He ends up in a space tunnel filled with garbage. Running away from the giant garbage monster there, Tetsuro ends up on the path to get to planet Loose Zone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528086</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51466" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">101</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の夢追い星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Planet of Eternal Dream Pursuit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Yumeoi Hoshi</title>
<summary>They land on the Planet of Dream Pursuit. This is a planet of overrun logic where those who do not work hard are put to death immediately. For the reason, people`s jobs are assigned by the government. A young rocket mission control officer named Aaron loves comics so much that he`s often scribbling pictures on the forms at his work place. He wanted to be a comic book author but the government assigned him to a role as a rocket mission control officer. However, he couldn`t throw his dream away...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528088</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51587" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">102</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖女王の反乱星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Planet of the Queen`s Rebellion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hijiri-jou no Hanranboshi</title>
<summary>On the planet of the Queen`s Rebellion, the Hornets, Wasps, and Honeybees all coexist. However, because of the Queen`s polarizing personality, the honeybees and the wasps are fighting. A young wasp named Damu is frightened as the sudden fighting breaks out throughout the town and the air. Filming the rebellion with a hand-made camera, he tells of the impending war to Maetel and Tetsuro.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528090</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51588" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">103</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンドロメダ千夜一夜 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">1001 Nights in Andromeda: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Andromeda Sen`ya Ichiya Zenpen</title>
<summary>The 999 is attacked suddenly on Planet Ali Baba and crash lands deep in the desert. Tetsuro and Maetel go to head to town while the Conductor heads to the station to contact the Galaxy Railways Authority. They are forced to cross the desert. Ali Baba is a land known for being filled with thieves. Not surprisingly, Tetsuro and Maetel are captured by a group of bandits before making it to town. Forced to strip to their underwear, except for the Conductor who is conspicuously missing, they are taken to Ali Baba, the leader of the bandits...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528092</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51589" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">104</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンドロメダ千夜一夜 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">1001 Nights in Andromeda: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Andromeda Sen`ya Ichiya Kouhen</title>
<summary>Tetsuro is attacked by a mysterious bird assassin, Roc, while Maetel is attacked by a mysterious woman. And it looks like a fight as begun between this woman and the bandits who captured Maetel. It turns out that this woman is the true Ali Baba. She lost her position as the top bandit in Ali Baba to the woman they met before, the fake Ali Baba. After Tetsuro and Maetel are rescued by the true Ali Baba, she joins with him to defeat the fake one.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528096</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51590" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">105</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">若き戦士の伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend of the Young Warriors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakaki Senshi no Densetsu</title>
<summary>On planet Legend, Tetsuro notices lots of people straggling by the wayside. Maetel points out that they are cyborgs who have lost the desire to live. Two young people, Meim and Saki wake up Tetsuro in his hotel room. When Tetsuro refuses to fight against the leader of the cyborgs, he is going to be put to death. When Tetsuro is spared by the leader of the cyborgs, we learn that he is trying to make this a planet only for cyborgs.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528098</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51591" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">106</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽霊駅[ゴーストステーション]13号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Station No. 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghost Station 13 Gou</title>
<summary>"I want to board the 999, too," says brothers, without form, who float off in the distance. Feeling pity for his brother Crosalis`s words, Aron stops the 999 in hopes of mechanizing themselves into Ghost Station No. 13. The 999 is forced to make an emergency stop on Station No.13. Though the Conductor agrees to stop there, when asked by the Locomotive, neither him nor Maetel have heard of this planet. Sensing something is amiss, the Locomotive orders them to withdraw.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528100</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51592" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">107</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キリマンジャロの鳥人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bird-Man of Kilimanjaro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kilimanjaro no Choujin</title>
<summary>The planet, the Knights of Kilimanjaro. Chivalry lives on here and two countries are fighting a proper, open war. There, Tetsuro witnesses a biplane dogfight. He spots one pilot who is slacking off during the dogfight. The name of this pilot is Izaka. He`s not of high lineage like the other pilots and wants nothing more than to fly the skies like a bird. But, his dear friend Kikuo is killed from another plane`s attack. Izaka explodes in rage while he watches everyone celebrating the ceasefire, ignoring the fact that his friend was sacrifices.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528102</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51908" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">109</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メーテルの旅 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maetel`s Journey: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maetel no Tabi Zenpen</title>
<summary>The 999 enters into a warp at high speed to make up for a large amount of lost time. But, the flow of time inside the warp is messed up and they encounter a 999 from a different time! They suffer a minor accident. On the 999 from the past, or maybe the future, is Maetel, the Conductor, and a young boy who looks similar to Tetsuro, named Redril. Redril has the same warrior`s gun as Tetsuro. Then they head towards a drifting planet where a new danger awaits!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528106</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51909" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">110</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メーテルの旅 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maetel`s Journey: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maetel no Tabi Kouhen</title>
<summary>The 999 has encountered a 999 from another time inside of the warp. The two Maetels ended up landing on the wandering planet, Phantom, which is populated with strange life-forms. They are let go once they realize they are humans. But, the Conductor is captured by a different create altogether! They want to use the 999 to escape. It turns out that, on this wandering planet, the cyborgs are persecuted by the humans!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528108</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51910" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">111</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">惑星こうもり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bat Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakusei Koumori</title>
<summary>The Bat Planet is the last stop before the final station, planet Promethium. Because of this, this is where many passengers come and ponder as to whether they should become cyborgs or not. Tetsuro is one of these people. There, they meet an aspiring animator named Masai. He works by drawing portraits of travelers to save money to get a mechanical body in order to overcome his weak physical body and pursue his dream of making cartoons. But then, he steals Tetsuro`s pass...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528110</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51911" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">112</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">青春の幻影 さらば999 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Vision of Youth, Farewell, 999: Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seishun no Gen`ei: Saraba 999 Zenpen</title>
<summary>Tetsuro finally arrives at the final destination, Promethium. However, he still cannot choose whether or not to become a cyborg. He is given twenty-four hours to make up his mind. But, during that time, Tetsuro speaks to a cyborg who was sick of eternal life and attempts to commit suicide. This man tells Tetsuro of Maetel`s true identity as Promethium`s daughter. Then, his guide, Mirai, tells Tetsuro that he has been chosen to be a vanguard soldier of the Mechanized Empire. Tetsuro confronts Maetel...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528112</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51912" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">113</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">青春の幻影 さらば999 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Vision of Youth, Farewell, 999: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seishun no Gen`ei: Saraba 999 Kouhen</title>
<summary>Upon choosing not to get a mechanical body, the Queen tries to send Tetsuro and the 999 into the black hole. And Maetel and her father, Ban, are both imprisoned for being traitors. But she breaks out and rescues the 999 from peril. Maetel is reunited with Tetsuro. They will use the energy from the pendant that Maetel`s father was sealed in to defeat Promethium!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528114</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="51913" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">108</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マカロニグラタンの崩壊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Destruction of Macaroni au Gratin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Macaroni au Gratin no Houkai</title>
<summary>Main and Sab are passing the time by acting out a war. They are the last two people living on this planet where everything is controlled by Mother Computer Junior But, bored with war, the two plot to use the 999 to escape the planet. Since they need two people to use as scapegoats to trick Mother Computer Junior, they choose Maetel and Tetsuro!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528104</identifier>
<identifier>galaxy-express-999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="62333" update="2006-09-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年の旅立ちと別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boy`s Departure and Parting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen no Tabidachi to Wakare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81283" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120266" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
