<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4847" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-09-01</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Evangelion Shin Gekijouban: Jo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ヱヴァンゲリヲン 新劇場版 REBUILD OF EVANGELION</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rebuild of Evangelion: 1.0</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Evangelion New Theatrical Version: The Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Evangelion 1.0</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Evangelion 1.01</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Evangelion 1.11 You Are (Not) Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Evangelion: 1.11 - You are (not) alone</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Evangelion: 1.0 Tu (Ne) Vienišas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Evangelion Shin Gekijouban: Rebuild of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Eva:1.0</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヱヴァンゲリヲン新劇場版:序</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Evangelion: 1.0 You Are (Not) Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Evangelion: 1.01 - You are (not) alone</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Evangelion : 1.0 You Are (Not) Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Евангелион 1.11: Ты (не) один</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">에반게리온: 서</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Evangelion: 1.11 You Are (Not) Alone.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Evangelion 1.0 You are not alone</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Evangelion 1.11: Você (Não) Está Só</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Evangelion: 1.11 Monstrum - Nejste sami</title>
<title xml:lang="lv" type="official">Evangelions: Tu neesi viens</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Evangelion 1.0: Sa oled/pole üksinda</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6171" type="Sequel">Evangelion Shin Gekijouban: Ha</anime>
<anime id="22" type="Alternative Setting">Shinseiki Evangelion</anime>
<anime id="9200" type="Other">Evangelion 3D</anime>
<anime id="10279" type="Other">Peaceful Times (F02) Petit Film</anime>
<anime id="11968" type="Other">Beautiful World</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="25">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="269894">I recommend watching the TV series first before watching the movie.
Pros:
-Better graphics
-Kick-ass, updated battle scenes
-more comprehensive explanation of what`s going on plotwise

Cons:
-pacing is rushed. As a result, timeline feels messed up, and shinji appears 10x more annoying than he was in the original series. 
-Battles were less intense than in the original. Dunno what it is. Maybe the screaming wasn`t as hysterical as it was in the original.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="13836">Pretty good new version of the NERV-Story.&lt;br /&gt;Very interessting, that they not only added very stylisch CGI optics, but also new elements to the story, that show serveral connections between the characters and the shadowy figures of the world of NGE. So hopefully one isn`t just sitting there thinking "wtf?" when the "End of Evangelion" has come ;D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="537611">This movie is for people who wanted a more simplistic Eva series. This is a retelling of the first 6 episodes of tv series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="199528">brutal</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="251338">The epic became epicer. Watch it dammit!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="336403">It`s freaking Evangelion! That should be reason enough to watch the remake, but it`s hard to say what i feel yet about the whole remake. Have to see the other movies first, but up to this point a loyal remake of the original masterpiece... just without the awesome opening Angels Cruel Thesis</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="237158">Precisely shaped hi-tech art remake contures boosting even more action potential of this anime, however leaving behind the original depth. Be sure to watch the original series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="292889">A very good remake of the original series. It isn`t "just" the new visuals for the modern facelift, but also the added content that makes this anime appealing to hardcore fans and a new viewers.&lt;br /&gt;A definite Must see &amp; must buy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="614177">I never watched any episode of the original series, with that in  mind i was confused and amazed, after i watched the movie i was asking myself what was happening, i was amazed, for me everything was a mystery and i had to solve it. it is superb, even if you know nothing like me, you will be surprised, amazed and confused all together and even so you will enjoy and create theories for everything that you just saw. MUST SEE for everyone!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="338163">My favorite anime ever w/ a face lift and some story tweaking. Put your fears aside. It`s amazing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="124380">To celebrate the 10th anniversary of this groundbreaking anime, Anno started this amazing remake with breathtaking animation and sound. Are you sure you want to miss it?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="253646">Just Perfect! You Must See it!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.evangelion.co.jp/1_0/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="57" type="Original Work">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="2158" type="Chief Animation Direction">Suzuki Shunji</name>
<name id="1389" type="Main Character Design">Sadamoto Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
<name id="58" type="Direction">Tsurumaki Kazuya</name>
<name id="57" type="Chief Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="3705" type="Animation Work">Studio Khara</name>
<name id="3612" type="Direction">Masayuki</name>
</creators>
<description>In 2015, fifteen years after a global cataclysm known as the Second Impact, http://anidb.net/ch309 [Ikari Shinji] is summoned to the city of Tokyo-3 by his estranged father http://anidb.net/ch5000 [Gendou], the Supreme Commander of http://anidb.net/ch5009 [NERV]. When he is caught in the crossfire between UN forces and the Fourth Angel, Lt. Colonel http://anidb.net/ch5007 [Katsuragi Misato] rescues Shinji and brings him to NERV Headquarters. Gendou then forces Shinji into piloting http://anidb.net/ch8704 [Evangelion Unit-01], a large mecha, against the Angel. Shinji initially declines, but then concedes when Gendou threatens to send http://anidb.net/ch310 [Ayanami Rei], a heavily bandaged Evangelion pilot, into battle.
Shinji pilots Unit-01 and wins the fight after it goes berserk and destroys the Angel. Afterwards, Shinji is taken in by Misato as her new housemate and enrolled in the local middle school. Shinji tries to settle in with his new-found life alongside Misato, Rei, and the others while he receives training to defend Tokyo-3 and the world from the coming Angels...
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5599">8.23</permanent>
<temporary count="5656">8.17</temporary>
<review count="4">7.54</review>
</ratings>
<picture>48905.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8420</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2759</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3866</identifier>
<identifier>skvjfo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.evangelion.co.jp/1_0/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Evangelion:_1.0_You_Are_(Not)_Alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヱヴァンゲリヲン新劇場版:序</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2785</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327253</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9091</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1179" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-21">
<name>indecisive</name>
<description>This character has trouble taking their own decisions, and may rely on others to do that instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3167" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-16">
<name>Tokyo destroyed</name>
<description>Tokyo is depicted as being or having been destroyed, either partially or completely, by some sort of disaster, such as a nuclear blast, a very large-scale fire, or rising sea levels. Should the situation be dire enough, Tokyo may be destroyed again after a recovery, or a new Tokyo may be built and subsequently destroyed, by a new disaster.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3572" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>biopunk</name>
<description>Biopunk stories explore the struggles of individuals or groups, often the product of human experimentation, against a backdrop of totalitarian governments or mega-corporations which misuse biotech as means of social control or capitalist extortion. Unlike cyberpunk, biopunk does not centre on information technology but on synthetic biology.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4555" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-22">
<name>man the hell up!</name>
<description>There is a male character in this anime that is overall not very manly. Most of the time he starts off as your typical high school student. In time there are, through major changes in his life, several more characteristics added to his personality. Usually these add up to be extremely pathetic and the character becomes quite annoying. This goes along with the viewers wish for him to get over it and do something about it. Hence, he should "Man the hell up!".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="309" type="main character in" update="2018-02-15">
<rating votes="1352">4.11</rating>
<name>Ikari Shinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ikari Shinji is the "Third Children" of the Marduk Report and the pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6997 [EVA-01]. He is the son of http://anidb.net/ch5000 [Ikari Gendou] and the late http://anidb.net/ch9620 [Ikari Yui]. Abandoned by his father when he was a toddler, Shinji has grown up to be reclusive and withdrawn, often choosing to run away from difficult situations. He is reunited with his father when he is summoned to pilot EVA-01, and because of this meets his future caretaker http://anidb.net/ch5007 [Katsuragi Misato] and the mysterious pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6996 [EVA-00], http://anidb.net/ch310 [Ayanami Rei].
Over time and with encouragement from Misato, Rei and his classmates http://anidb.net/ch7981 [Suzuhara Touji] and http://anidb.net/ch8643 [Aida Kensuke], he learns to be more confident and appreciative of others. Shinji is put to task fighting the invading Angels, and later meets a foreign pilot whom he often comes in conflict with, http://anidb.net/ch39 [Souryuu Asuka Langley].</description>
<picture>128273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="310" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-28">
<rating votes="1632">8.12</rating>
<name>Ayanami Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayanami Rei is the "First Children" of the Marduk Report and the pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6996 [EVA-00]. Shrouded in mystery, she is socially withdrawn and rarely shows emotion. Seemingly completely devoted to her duty as an EVA pilot, her only apparent human relationship being with http://anidb.net/ch5009 [Nerv] commander http://anidb.net/ch5000 [Ikari Gendou].
Rei comes to know http://anidb.net/ch309 [Ikari Shinji], and after some initial mistrust they come to better understand each other, revealing more of Rei`s emotional side and helping Shinji trust others again.
Rei`s body was created at Nerv in an attempt to bring back Gendou`s wife http://anidb.net/ch9620 [Ikari Yui], who was stuck inside http://anidb.net/ch8704 [EVA-01]. Soulless clones of her are kept hidden in the deepest levels of NERV, to be used both as replacement bodies for Rei should she die and as "cores" of the Dummy Plugs. Gendou, plans to make Rei help him control Instrumentality to reunite him with his wife.</description>
<picture>59479.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5000" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-14">
<rating votes="399">5.35</rating>
<name>Ikari Gendou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At Nerv, Gendo is responsible for the research done on the Evas and the Human Instrumentality Project. He is the father of the Third Child, Shinji Ikari. At the start of the series, he is the only person having an effective connection to Rei Ayanami.
Gendo is a brilliant scientist and politician (the master of puppets in the series) who works diligently for his organization; however, he is an extremely cold and distant father towards his son, and has no qualms about using and discarding people to achieve his goals.</description>
<picture>21249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5007" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="790">7.53</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Misato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The operations director at Nerv. Her duties at Nerv include acting as a field commander for the Eva pilots, issuing orders and relaying battle strategies as well as processing input from Akagi Ritsuko and the technicians monitoring the Evas. She also handles many bureaucratic aspects of Nerv`s operations.
At the beginning of the series, Misato first brings Shinji Ikari to Nerv and is able to convince him to pilot the Eva Unit 01. She then chooses to have Shinji move in with her rather than live alone, and later takes in Sohryu Asuka Langley. As the series progresses, through her former lover Kaji Ryouji she learns the truth behind the Human Instrumentality Project and the depths of deception that Nerv and Seele have gone to keep the Project secret, even from her.
While on the job, Misato is very professional and capable, in stark contrast to her life at home. Until Shinji`s arrival, her living space was a complete mess. She cannot cook for herself and relies solely on instant food (she is often considered gross by Shinji and Ritsuko for combining food like ramen and curry). She also drinks copious quantities of beer, and drinks one first thing in the morning to get her day started (later in the series she apparently switches to canned coffee as a supplement). She also smokes, though only occasionally and only during chaotic events.</description>
<picture>21277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5008" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="176">4.59</rating>
<name>Akagi Ritsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nerv`s head scientist and heavily involved in the repairs and maintenance of Tokyo-3`s defences against the Angels, particularly the Evas.
She is the daughter of Akagi Naoko, the developer of the MAGI supercomputer system which controls Nerv. In many ways, Ritsuko is living in the shadow of her mother, whom she both admires and despises. Naoko was the head scientist working on the Evangelion project before her death, and Ritsuko is continuing the work her mother began with the Evas, as well as continuing the development of the Magi supercomputer system. Flashbacks to a teenaged Ritsuko reveal that she is a natural brunette, just like her mother.
Ritsuko is extremely intelligent, with a strong dedication to her work and a stoic, detached attitude which is frequently contrasted against Katsuragi Misato`s hot-headness, especially during Eva combat. Her occasional jibes at Misato are a source of comic relief in the series. She has a great affinity for cats, and Misato chides her at one point for substituting her cats for human affection. She also is a heavy smoker, as evidenced by an ashtray on her desk filled with cigarette butts stained by her lipstick.</description>
<picture>21278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5009" type="appears in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="35">8.13</rating>
<name>Nerv</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An organisation led by Ikari Gendou and tasked with defending Earth against the Angels through use of the Evangelion units. It was formerly known as Gehirn, a UN Research Agency. It was reorganised into Nerv once Nerv HQ and Tokyo-3 became fully operational. There are several global branches of Nerv besides the main headquarters under Tokyo-3 itself.
The Nerv Logo is half a fig leaf covering its name, with the motto "God`s In His Heaven... All`s Right With The World" forming the quarter circle on the bottom. The motto comes from Robert Browning`s poem "Pippa Passes."
In Genesis 3:7, Adam and Eve cover their "nakedness" with fig leaves. The fig leaf has covered nakedness in art and sculpture for hundreds of years, symbolically representing the guilt of original sin.</description>
<picture>21279.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6995" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="107">4.07</rating>
<name>Ibuki Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A First Lieutenant at Nerv and a computer technician who works primarily with Akagi Ritsuko. Her main role during the battles against the Angels is to constantly monitor the Eva pilots` synchronization ratios and send various emergency commands to the Evas as ordered by Misato or Gendou. In spite of her profession, Maya despises violence of any sort, and is frequently shown becoming nauseated and averting her eyes during battles with the Angels.</description>
<picture>25248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7187" type="appears in" update="2009-07-07">
<rating votes="21">5.06</rating>
<name>Seele</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Nerv and Gehirn`s secret backers, who wish to implement the Human Instrumentality Project, and arguably the "true villains" of the series. It consists of at least twelve prominent people; five of them form the Instrumentality Committee, which directly oversees Nerv`s progress, officially in the name of the UN. Its members are referred to as the "Old Men."
Seele is a secret organisation, the real puppetmasters behind the United Nations. Its origins are shrouded in mystery; they would claim to have existed since ancient times, functioning as an Illuminati-like power cabal over most of the world`s governments. This cannot be verified, but they have been operating since at least soon after World War II, when they acquired the secret sections of the Dead Sea Scrolls. The secret Dead Sea Scrolls predicted the arrival of the Angels and of Third Impact, and Seele began striving to develop means to defeat the Angels so that a human-centred Instrumentality process would proceed. Having decided that humanity as a whole had reached an evolutionary dead end, Seele seeks to bring about Instrumentality and unite all humans into one hyper-being, the next stage of existence.
In German "Seele" means "soul".</description>
<picture>1122.jpeg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7960" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="317">6.59</rating>
<name>Nagisa Kaworu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tabris, the seventeenth and final Angel, holds the form of a human, Kaworu Nagisa. Like the other Angels, he is "born of Adam", although it is implied that he was created by Seele. He contains the soul of Adam, similar to how Rei contains the soul of Lilith. Tabris` AT field is the most powerful ever detected, strong enough to block out "light, magnetism, sub-atomic particles, everything". He may control any Evangelion unit he wishes, even from outside the entry plug, so long as the soul inhabiting the Eva is dormant. Within the entry plug, he can set his synchronization ratio at any level he wishes. The nature or even the very existence of his core is not revealed.
Tabris, as Kaworu, infiltrated Nerv under the pretense of being sent to replace Asuka as Unit 02`s pilot. During his stay in Tokyo-3, he formed an extremely close relationship with Shinji. Kaworu later revealed himself as an Angel, seizing control of Unit 02 and descending with it towards Terminal Dogma. Shinji, in Unit 01, was sent to stop him, but was forced to battle Unit 02 while Tabris proceeded to Terminal Dogma. Tabris` AT field manifested during the battle, effectively cutting both of them off from all contact with anyone outside. After he reached Terminal Dogma, Tabris was surprised to discover that the Angel held there was not Adam, but Lilith. Shinji incapacitated Unit 02 and proceeded to try to stop the Angel. Tabris, gripped in Unit 01`s hand, stated his unwillingness to destroy mankind by causing Third Impact, and asked Shinji to kill him. Shinji, after a long period of hesitation, crushed the Angel in his Eva`s hand.</description>
<picture>128274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7967" type="appears in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="76">7.45</rating>
<name>Pen Pen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pen Pen (often styled as Pen²) is a "hot spring penguin" and Misato`s pet. He lives in a custom refrigerator in Misato`s apartment, enjoys taking warm baths, eating whatever food he can get his hands (or wings) on, and going to hot springs. He also appears to have a relatively high degree of intelligence, as he is also shown watching TV and reading newspapers. He is voiced by Megumi Hayashibara in the Japanese series. He is the result of a genetics experiment at Misato`s former workplace, and she adopted him after the experiment`s conclusion rather than let him be euthanised. His wingtips have retractable claws, which normal birds do not have.</description>
<picture>27070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7981" type="appears in" update="2009-06-02">
<rating votes="97">3.84</rating>
<name>Suzuhara Touji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toji is a tough boy, the stereotypical "jock," as evidenced by the fact that he is the only student in Shinji`s class that refuses to wear the school uniform (although he does actually wear it once, in the ninth episode). Toji is good friends with Kensuke Aida, and is in constant conflict with Asuka. Toji`s younger sister was injured in the battle between Sachiel and Unit 01, and after learning that Shinji was Unit 01`s pilot, he beats Shinji up as payback. However, after witnessing firsthand the suffering Shinji experiences piloting Unit 01 in the battle against Shamshel, Toji comes to respect Shinji and the two become friends.
Unbeknownst to Toji for much of the series, his normally by-the-book class rep Hikari Horaki actually has a crush on him, which she tries to repress and disguise by bossing him around. Later in the series, she begins bringing especially big homemade lunches to school for Toji, since he loves to eat ("Toji the Stomach," as Kensuke refers to him). Subsequently, her feelings begin to come to the forefront and Toji seems to return her affection.
Toji is eventually selected to be the Fourth Child, and agrees on the condition that his sister be moved to Nerv`s medical facilities. En route to the testing facility, Unit 03 is taken over by Bardiel. When Toji is inserted in the entry plug and the Eva is powered up, Bardiel takes over and the Eva goes on a rampage. All the other Evas are deployed to stop Unit 03, but Units 00 and 02 are quickly defeated, and Shinji refuses orders to destroy Unit 03, wanting to try to save the pilot. However, Gendo orders that Unit 01`s Dummy Plug system be activated, overriding Shinji`s control. Unit 01 proceeds to tear Unit 03 to shreds and crush its entry plug. After the battle, Shinji learns that Toji is the pilot as the wreckage of the entry plug is examined. Toji survives but is critically injured, losing his left leg. Along with Kensuke and the rest of his class, he is eventually evacuated from Tokyo-3; what happens to him after that is unknown. He appears at the end of episode 26 in Shinji`s subconscious.</description>
<picture>27097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8642" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-12">
<rating votes="129">3.32</rating>
<name>Fuyutsuki Kouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nerv`s Deputy Commander and Ikari Gendou`s right hand man. He does not especially like Gendou, but he is the closest thing to a confidant that Gendou has in the series.
Once a professor of meta-biology at Kyoto University, Fuyutsuki became interested in the research and theories undertaken by Ikari Yui, and became her sponsor and mentor. Shortly thereafter, he was directed by his superiors to initiate a similar arrangement with Rokobungi Gendou.
Later, after the Second Impact, Fuyutsuki travelled with Gendou to the ruins of Antarctica, and began to suspect that Gendou and his associates in Seele were more powerful and dangerous than he originally realized. In 2003, Fuyutsuki discovered for himself the true nature of the events leading up to Second Impact and Seele`s involvement in initiating that catastrophe. Gendou led him into the GeoFront and Central Dogma, and asked Fuyutsuki to join him in "creating a new future for mankind."</description>
<picture>75303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8643" type="appears in" update="2009-06-07">
<rating votes="110">3.12</rating>
<name>Aida Kensuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An otaku, a military buff, Touji`s best friend, and one of the "Other Children," Eva pilot candidates in the same class as Shinji, Touji, Rei, Asuka, and Hikari. His hobbies include camping in the mountains surrounding Tokyo-3 and playing at simulated war re-enacting - by himself. Kensuke solidifies his friendship with Shinji after Shinji saves him and Toji during the fight against the fourth Angel, Shamshel. Kensuke dreams of becoming an Eva pilot and ceaselessly begs Shinji to pull strings in Nerv so he can be selected as a pilot, despite Shinji telling him that he has no say in the matter. He also seems oblivious to the intense physical and psychological distress endured by Eva pilots. Nevertheless, Kensuke enjoys the privileges of being the friend of an Eva pilot. Like Touji, Kensuke has a crush on Katsuragi Misato.</description>
<picture>27935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2044" picture="21387.jpg">Iwanaga Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8665" type="appears in" update="2009-06-07">
<rating votes="100">4.23</rating>
<name>Horaki Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Class representative of the class that Shinji and the other Eva pilots attend. She has a by-the-book demeanour and takes her responsibilities as "class rep" seriously. Although she frequently bickers with Touji, she reveals to Asuka that she has an enormous crush on Touji but is unable to openly express her feelings to him. She also appears to be Asuka`s only friend. Hikari is an accomplished cook who appears to take care of her two sisters.</description>
<picture>27961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8666" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<rating votes="53">4.61</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A First Lieutenant at Nerv and one of the three main computer technicians directly serving under Commanders Ikari and Fuyutsuki in the command post of Central Dogma, the others being Aoba and Ibuki. Hyuga at first gives the impression of being something of a nerd, reading manga while on his break time, but is a highly skilled technician. His quick thinking and bravery help save Nerv headquarters from the attack by Matariel, and he acts as a spy for Misato, helping her obtain information regarding Nerv`s machinations.
The true extent of his feelings for Misato is shown in The End of Evangelion as Rei/Lilith takes the form of Misato during Instrumentality and passionately kisses him; his body reverts to LCL.</description>
<picture>75305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1925" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8667" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<rating votes="58">4.05</rating>
<name>Aoba Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoba Shigeru is a First Lieutenant at Nerv and a computer technician. At times a stereotypical metalhead, he is a cynical nihilist and plays guitar (he can also sometimes be seen playing air guitar). Of the three technicians seen regularly in Central Dogma, his character is explored the least in the series.
In The End of Evangelion, during Instrumentality, Rei/Lillith appears to him not as any loved one but rather as a bombardment of Reis which forces their way through his AT Field while he cowers and screams in horror under his desk.</description>
<picture>75304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8684" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="6">3.54</rating>
<name>United Nations (Evangelion)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The world intergovernmental organisation which funds Nerv. Due to the Second Impact followed by series of warfare, the U.N. was heavily funded by superpowers (such as the United States and China) and other powerful organisations (like Seele), enabling it to mobilise a powerful military. The U.N. armed forces are made up of units from member nations, such as Japan`s JSSDF.
Many traditional air force units are replaced with VTOL (Vertical Take-Off and Landing) fighters and bombers. The naval power of the U.N. is primarily made up of a mix of many different types of ships from many navies. The U.N. Pacific Fleet operates Iowa class battleships (United States Navy), Arleigh Burke class destroyers (United States Navy), Udaloy class destroyers (Russian Navy), Ticonderoga class cruisers (United States Navy), Admiral Kuznetsov class aircraft carriers (Russian Navy), and several United States Navy aircraft carriers, specifically the flagship of the fleet, the Nimitz class carrier USS Harry S. Truman (renamed Over the Rainbow in the anime). The U.N. aircraft carriers, such as Over the Rainbow, also carry a mix of both Russian and American naval aircraft, such as Sukhoi Su-33 fighters, Yakovlev Yak-38 VTOL fighters, EA-6 Prowler electronic warfare craft, and E-2 Hawkeye airborne early warning craft. It is a strong possibility that the United Nations possesses N² bombs as well as traditional stealth planes. Much of the U.N. forces remain unknown, but it is clear that their military reforms are significant.
Unlike Nerv and Seele, the United Nations still relies on a traditional military with conventional weapons.</description>
</character>
<character id="8703" type="appears in" update="2009-06-07">
<rating votes="9">7.87</rating>
<name>EVA-00</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Rebuild version of EVA Unit 00.</description>
<picture>28011.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8704" type="appears in" update="2009-06-07">
<rating votes="11">8.74</rating>
<name>EVA-01</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Rebuild version of EVA Unit 01.</description>
<picture>28013.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8723" type="appears in" update="2009-06-07">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Lilith</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rebuild version of Angel Lilith.</description>
<picture>28067.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8726" type="appears in" update="2011-07-05">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Dai 5 no shito</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28072.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34217" type="appears in" update="2011-07-05">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Dai 4 no shito</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74785.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34218" type="appears in" update="2011-07-05">
<rating votes="4">7.58</rating>
<name>Dai 6 no Shito</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74786.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="80153" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2007-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="27">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81278" update="2009-06-13">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81279" update="2007-08-15">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81371" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177845" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebuild of Evangelion 1.01 (Making Of)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179418" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel of Doom Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217703" update="2019-05-30">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebuild Translation and Foot Notes</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
