<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="485" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1979-08-04</startdate>
<enddate>1979-08-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ginga Tetsudou 999 (1979)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Galaxy Express 999: The Signature Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">銀河鉄道999 (1979)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Galaxy Express 999 (1979)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Galaxy Express 999 (1979)</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Galaxy Express 999 - Ferrovia Galattica</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">O Expresso da Galáxia</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Galaktika Ekspress 999</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="765" type="Sequel">Sayonara Ginga Tetsudou 999: Andromeda Shuuchakueki</anime>
<anime id="484" type="Alternative Setting">Ginga Tetsudou 999</anime>
<anime id="2231" type="Alternative Setting">Ginga Tetsudou 999: Glass no Clair</anime>
<anime id="725" type="Character">Uchuu Kaizoku Captain Harlock</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/movie/999/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1107" type="Original Work">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
<name id="1107" type="Series Composition">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
<name id="148" type="Direction">Rintarou</name>
<name id="4808" type="Music">Aoki Nozomi</name>
</creators>
<description>After the death of his mother at the hands of the evil robot Count Mecha, young Tetsuro has become a delinquent street urchin who dreams only of revenge. Tetsuro lives in a far future world in which humans have the choice to travel to another planet where they can exchange their bodies for immortal, robotic counterparts. His goal is to someday acquire (through theft) enough money to board the Galaxy Express 999, a train which is capable of traveling through space, and which will take him to the planet of robots. One day, after escaping from the police, he meets the beautiful Maetel, who resembles his mother. She offers to take him on the Galaxy Express 999 to get a robotic body and to get revenge on Count Mecha. Along the journey, the two meet many varied people (including Captain Harlock and Queen Emeraldas), and Tetsuro learns what it means to be human.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="495">7.39</permanent>
<temporary count="502">7.38</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>24034.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1362</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1301</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>171</identifier>
<identifier>izjinb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/movie/999/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2445</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>146800</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m091</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2087" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-03">
<rating votes="318">9.03</rating>
<name>Captain Harlock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harlock is the archetypical romantic hero, a space pirate with an individualist philosophy of life. He is as noble as he is taciturn, rebellious, stoically fighting against totalitarian regimes, whether they be earthborn or alien. In his own words, he "fight(s) for no one`s sake... only for something deep in (his) heart".
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>2364.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3233" picture="171389.jpg">Inoue Makio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2378" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-14">
<rating votes="46">6.93</rating>
<name>Ooyama Tochirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harlock`s old friend and chief builder of the Arcadia.</description>
<picture>17631.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2493" type="main character in" update="2014-12-13">
<rating votes="434">8.57</rating>
<name>Maetel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of Queen Prometheum, ruler of a mechanised empire.</description>
<picture>38136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3703" picture="151656.jpg">Ikeda Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12667" type="main character in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="64">4.76</rating>
<name>Hoshino Tetsurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tetsuro Hoshino is a young boy who was born on Earth into poverty, and who wants nothing more than a machine body. He also wants revenge on Count Mecha, an evil man who was given a machine body and now hunts humans for sport, for killing his mother. As a street urchin, Tetsuro has no means to buy a machine body. However, he has heard that at the end of the Andromeda Galaxy, there exists a planet where such robot bodies are given away for free. All Tetsuro needs to do is get a pass on the Galaxy Express 999, the cosmic railway. And one day, Tetsuro meets the mysterious Maetel, who promises to give him her unlimited use pass for the Express on the condition that she be his travelling companion. Tetsuro happily agrees, and embarks with Maetel on an adventure across the stars. When Tetsuro starts out, he is every bit the whiny, immature, selfish child. However, the adventures he goes with Maetel on, the people he meets, and the sights he witnesses cause Tetsuro to slowly but truly grow into a strong, young man. Tetsuro also grows closer and closer to Maetel, and although the nature of their relationship might not be called romantic, they form a very strong bond of love. Though it is never explicitly stated, it is implied that Tetsuro is Captain Harlock`s son. The evidence for this includes Tetsuro`s mother saying that his father is alive but away for some reason, Captain Harlock`s mysterious attachment to Tetsuro, and simple physical resemblance.</description>
<picture>38140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12668" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="21">7.54</rating>
<name>Claire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The dining car waitress on the 999, Claire has a machine body made of clear crystal glass. Unlike others who gave up their humanity by choice, Claire was forced into this existence by her vain mother. She works on the 999 in order to save up enough money to buy back her human body, which is stored on Pluto.</description>
<picture>38141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3697" picture="78864.jpg">Asagami Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12669" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="66">5.55</rating>
<name>Shashou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main crew member of the Galaxy Express 999. He is an alien being with an invisible body; only his eyes can be seen while he is wearing his conductor uniform. The Conductor prefers to go `strictly by the book` and frequently cites the Galaxy Express rule book, but occasionally ends up bending the rules and getting into adventures with Tetsurou and Maetel.</description>
<picture>38142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3285" picture="193568.jpg">Kimotsuki Kaneta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12670" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="149">8.45</rating>
<name>Emeraldas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emeraldas has been compared many times to Captain Harlock, and the two have some similarities. They also know each other from the days of the Voice of Free Arcadia, when she fought side by side with him and Tochirou, the man who is their common bond. After the Ilumidus resistance, Emeraldas became much like Harlock, sailing the sea of stars and delivering justice in her own unique way.
Emeraldas is one of the few people who know the route of Count Mecha`s Time Castle, and when her ship, the Queen Emereldas, appears next to the Galaxy Express, Tetsuro doesn`t hesitate to get her attention. Emeraldas would`ve killed Tetsuro if it weren`t for two things. First, Maetel (whom she also knows) is with him. Second, Tetsuro has Tochirou`s hat and laser. She listens and then tells Tetsuro where the Time Castle will next appear: Trader`s Fork, on the planet of Heavy Melder.
Some time after she leaves, she realizes something is happening on Heavy Melder, something that had to do with Tochirou. She arrives too late. Harlock tells her he`s already dead. She leaves but later receives a message. It`s from Tochirou, whose soul had been successfully integrated into the Arcadia. Learning that it was Tetsuro who had helped him, she realizes that she owes him a favor, and she proceeds to Andromeda, to repay the favor. She and Tetsuro will cross path a few more times.
Emeraldas is a very lonely soul, especially after the death of Tochirou. Her closest companion, like herself, is a wanderer. You see, the reason she and Maetel know each other...is because they`re sisters. Emeraldas also has a daughter, Mayu, but she rarely sees her.
Source: Absolute Anime</description>
<picture>38143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10386" picture="38265.jpg">Tajima Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12671" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="5">5.84</rating>
<name>Ryuuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3414" picture="223019.jpg">Ohara Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12672" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="13">3.58</rating>
<name>Kikai Hakushaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12673" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="9">5.92</rating>
<name>Shadow</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38146.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12674" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="8">4.22</rating>
<name>Tetsurou no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38147.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12675" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="2">2.99</rating>
<name>Dr. Ban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38148.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12676" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="8">2.73</rating>
<name>La Andromeda Promethium</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Every 1000 years, a woman called a Millennial Queen is sent from the planet La-Metal to secretly rule over the Earth and lead an underground organization that secretly controls the entire planet. Promethium, known to Earthlings as Yukino Yayoi, is the current Millennial Queen.</description>
<picture>38150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2363" picture="146785.jpg">Kinomiya Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12677" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="2">3.76</rating>
<name>Tochirou no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mrs. Oyama lives near Grape Valley on Saturn`s moon, Titan. Tetsuro Hoshino meets her when she takes him in after his decidedly cold welcome to her planet. She tells him where he is likely to find the kidnapped Maeter, and gives him her son`s old Cosmo Gun for protection, along with a similar hat and cloak. After he successfully rescues Maeter, she allows him to keep the gun, and tells Tetsuro that if he ever encounters her son during his travels to pass along the message that she would very much like to see him again. Tetsuro does eventually meet him on Heavy Meldar, but Tochiro doesn`t live long enough to make any further journeys.</description>
<picture>38151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1801" picture="146194.jpg">Asou Miyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12678" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="6">5.75</rating>
<name>Antares</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Antares is the leader of the bandits of Grape Valley on Titan and guardian to a large collection of children orphaned by the human-hunting Count Mecha. (In the TV series, he was simply stealing in order to care for his own children.) He hates the machine people, and technology in general. Antales tells Tetsuro to seek out the pirate Emeraldas if he wishes to find the location of Count Mecha`s Time Castle, and advises the youngster to shoot the Count without giving him a moment`s pity. His body still contains a large number of unexploded energy bullets, which go off at the most inconvenient moment, just as he is about to warn Tetsuro of an important secret regarding Maeter.
Source: Cornponeflicks.org</description>
<picture>38152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10387" picture="38499.jpg">Hisamatsu Yasuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12679" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="9">7.70</rating>
<name>Arcadia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>38153.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12680" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="4">6.41</rating>
<name>Queen Emeraldas</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>38154.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12681" type="appears in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="5">7.41</rating>
<name>999</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>38155.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="11331" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>130</length>
<airdate>1979-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21054" update="2010-04-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>1979-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21055" update="2010-04-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>1979-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
