<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4852" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-25</startdate>
<enddate>2007-10-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Aika R-16</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">아이카 R-16 버진미션</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">AIKa R-16: 处女任务</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">AIKa R-16</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Aika R-16 Virgin Mission</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">AIKa R-16</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Агент Айка R-16</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6526" type="Sequel">Aika Zero</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="565552">Possibly the most perfect ecchi anime I have ever seen.

Charming comedy, a bit of sci-fi exploration, no real violence, and all with lashings of simply mouthwatering fanservice.

Watch the old series first though, because this will spoil it.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.studiofantasia.co.jp/old/aika_r16.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="2320" type="Character Design">Yamauchi Noriyasu</name>
<name id="5259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
<name id="2320" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamauchi Noriyasu</name>
<name id="758" type="Work">Studio Fantasia</name>
<name id="758" type="Original Work">Studio Fantasia</name>
<name id="2322" type="Direction">Nishijima Katsuhiko</name>
<name id="6488" type="Music">Kanezaki Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="58599" type="Music">Nomura Hiroyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7682 [Aika] is an intelligent and athletic high school girl. Competently she successfully passes the salvager`s licence test, obtaining a C-class license. Yet, she is young and hot-headed, so much so that http://anidb.net/ch7673 [Gozo] still treats her like a child. Due to this personality, no one is willing to hire her for salvaging jobs.
Eager to get started with salvaging, though, she decides to post an ad in her school to attract potential clients. She manages to get the attention of http://anidb.net/ch7684 [Eri], a daughter of a rich family and head of the school`s treasure hunting club. She asks Aika to salvage something from the sea floor and Aika accepts the assignment.
However, upon seeing the state-of-the-art submarine loaded onto Eri`s private cruiser and discovering their destination, Aika realises the dangerous nature of this mission, culminating in a clash with a group of armed high school girls on the southern islands.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1241">3.70</permanent>
<temporary count="1257">6.22</temporary>
<review count="1">6.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>26542.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7170</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2163</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3877</identifier>
<identifier>drcegn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.studiofantasia.co.jp/old/aika_r16.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>AIKa_R-16:_Virgin_Mission</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>AIKa_R-16:VIRGIN_MISSION</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1143</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326559</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9018</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="509" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-19">
<name>clone</name>
<description>This character is grown from a single somatic cell or cell nucleus and genetically identical to it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3712" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>all-female enemy crew</name>
<description>For some reason the enemy crew is solely comprised of an all-female cast.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3896" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-23">
<name>bloodless wounds</name>
<description>No matter what weapon is used in what way to attack, hurt or kill somebody, there won`t be blood. You may see ripped clothes and smoke coming from the deadly wounds, but that`s it.
So if you have an aversion towards the red liquid but still love some action going on - this is the anime for you!</description>
<picurl>39189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5284" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-22">
<name>ocean world</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7673" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="10">2.67</rating>
<name>Aida Gozo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He was an active industrial spy, but rode on the chance of the catastrophic earthquake and entered the salvaging business, setting up K2 Corporation, a Salvaging operation. He is Rion`s father. He prefers to hold onto the old ways (cheapest price for the best service) and principles of doing business, which does little good to the business. His past with Aika goes far back.</description>
<picture>73511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7678" type="appears in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="5">2.03</rating>
<name>Gust Turbulence</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gust Turbulence is the son of a company`s president. Although he is pretty well-off, he prefers to be independent and become a Salvager to earn his own bread. At first look he may be a rash person, but he has skill. He would like Aika to go out with him, but she refuses. He seems to end up in the right place to get the bounty.</description>
<picture>137003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7682" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="8">6.86</rating>
<name>Sumeragi Aika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7684" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="9">6.64</rating>
<name>Shinkai Eri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the class president of Aika`s class (1-A) and founder, club president of the school`s Treasure Hunting Club. Eri is also a mystery fanatic and comes from a very wealthy family.
Knowing that Aika has a Class C license, she roped Aika in to help with the investigation of Karen`s myster</description>
<picture>73504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7685" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="8">5.90</rating>
<name>Minamino Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Usually silent and seldom shows any facial expression, she talks only when necessary. On Eri`s investigation, Karen`s past history is unknown.
Karen has a butterfly insignia on her left breast. The insignia on magnification is made up of minute numbers which decodes to the sentence "the gate of the truth will be opened by the sleeping butterfly" and a map coordinate, which is where the group is heading to.</description>
<picture>73505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7686" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="15">7.88</rating>
<name>Nagisa Risako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>High School teacher and an agent of a secret entity that`s not disclosed. Risako-sensei is also the advisor of the High School`s Treasure Hunting Club. Has a thing for revealing lingerie and small bikinis. 26 years old.</description>
<picture>73506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2249" picture="61951.jpg">Suzuki Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="71955" update="2018-01-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シークレット・ゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Game</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogo secreto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Secret Game</title>
<summary>Aika Sumeragi, a high school age C-Class salvager, is hired by class president Eri Shinkai to pilot her salvaging vessel. After introducing Aika to the treasure hunting club, and revealing coordinates hidden in a marking on fellow classmate Karen Minamino`s chest, they embark on an adventure to see where it leads.
Source: TheTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="72058" update="2007-06-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピーチ・ピーチ・ビーチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Peach Peach Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Peach Peach Beach</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81254" update="2007-09-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ディープ・ブルー・ガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deep Blue Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deep Blue Girl</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82519" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82520" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82521" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82522" update="2007-09-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial of Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84721" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84722" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial of Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84723" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2007-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">声優メッセージ『トレハン部 定例部会』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Actor Interview "Aika-Eri-Karen"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84724" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">JAMSTEC ロケハン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Production Staff Visiting JAMSTEC</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jamstec Rokehan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227436" update="2020-03-18">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of AIKa R-16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227437" update="2020-03-18">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メイキング オブ 小清水亜美のアイカ・アクティブ・アドベンチャー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S4</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
