<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4861" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bokura no</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ours</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Наше</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Нашето...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Bokurano</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">地球防衛少年</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">地球防卫少年</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">我们的</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ぼくらの</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bokurano</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Bokurano</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Bizim</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8069" approval="86" total="115">Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica</anime>
<anime id="782" approval="58" total="81">Narutaru: Mukuro Naru Hoshi Tama Taru Ko</anime>
<anime id="22" approval="45" total="73">Shinseiki Evangelion</anime>
<anime id="3512" approval="5" total="6">Noein: Mou Hitori no Kimi e</anime>
<anime id="4575" approval="3" total="13">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</anime>
<anime id="8395" approval="2" total="16">Mirai Nikki (2011)</anime>
<anime id="7902" approval="2" total="13">Deadman Wonderland</anime>
<anime id="10750" approval="1" total="4">Yuuki Yuuna wa Yuusha de Aru</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="16">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="474730">Excellent Scy Fi Drama</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="278370">If you thought [i]Evangelion[/i] was angsty, you ain`t seen nothing yet. About as subtle as a brick to the face and has a real problem with the connecting `human element`, but an interesting watch for fans of deconstructive mecha shows.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="284821">Fantastic anime and not like the other cliched mecha animes... :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="298033">Great anime! It`s so sad and cool at the same time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="481279">I started watching this anime with low expectations, but was pleasantly surprised by how good it turned out to be.

This show is deeply character focused and driven--to the point that each of the 15 kids gets at least most of a full episode focused on their story and struggle. This gets you invested in each of the kids, all of which span different personalities and life stories that most people can identify with one of them one way or another. Sure, the animation quality is sub-par and the mecha fights are dull &amp; short, but the characters and the overall plot kept me going till the very end.

In conclusion, it`s not the best anime when it comes to characters, angst-driven drama, or mecha action. But it`s worth watching at least once.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="447033">Interesting, that`s what I think. It may be a good choice for those who like more cult stuff.

Absolutely it wasn`t made for the standard fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="1741">This anime, from the creator of Narutaru, similarly deals with the `realistic` effects of placing children into the highly unrealistic situations common in anime--in particular, piloting giant robots. It doesn`t carry it off quite as well as Narutaru, and is anything but subtle (rare are the revelations you can`t predict several episodes in advance), but it`s still worth watching once.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="478166">Excellent anime that takes place in a future time and includes mecha from a superior alternative universe.  Overall, this anime featured very deep themes and situations, and the episodic focus on each of the main characters gave the viewer a sense of relation to the hardships suffered by each character and their ultimate fates.  Recommended for fans of Angst, Mecha, Dystopia, SciFi, and Future.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="399240">masterpieace</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="224694">This anime is just awesome.&lt;br /&gt;At first i thought it was getting too serious and i wasnt sure wether to continue watching it or not, &lt;br /&gt;but i decided to stick with it. and it was a really good choice. ^^&lt;br /&gt;the story, the characters and their development made the way for this anime to join my all-time favs.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="286214">If you`re looking for a despairing watch, that is. Avoid spoilers if you can.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/bokurano/</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="4011" type="Original Work">Kitou Mohiro</name>
<name id="14013" type="Chief Direction">Yaginuma Kazuyoshi</name>
<name id="5054" type="Music">Nomi Yuuji</name>
<name id="5070" type="Direction">Morita Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="5748" type="Character Design">Konishi Ken`ichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr4011 [Kitou Mohiro]`s seinen manga serialised in the Ikki magazine.
During a summer vacation, a group of fifteen children discovered http://anidb.net/ch6330 [a mysterious man] living in a seashore cave, along with his high-tech gadgets. The man claimed to be a game developer creating a video game with fifteen giant robots defending Earth from alien invaders and asked those childs to test the game for him. The kids agreed happily at first, but soon they began to find the game horrifying, not only because of its realism but also for the first fatality among them happened right after their first victory. Worse yet, they had no idea how to stop or leave the game.
Source: Mangaupdates</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2730">6.82</permanent>
<temporary count="2761">7.57</temporary>
<review count="8">8.04</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221326.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7213</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1690</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>12877</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3933</identifier>
<identifier>kqdnsx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/bokurano/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Bokurano:_Ours</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ぼくらの</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1100</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327136</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8878</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10004</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="775" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>pregnant</name>
<description>A pregnant character carries developing offspring within the body.
A character only shown pregnant for a small segment of their total appearance(s) should not be tagged. For example, a character shown pregnant in the epilogue of the last episode in a series generally would not qualify for the tag.
For porn entries, a pregnant character can be tagged when any of the following conditions are met:

* The character is pregnant for a material portion of their total appearance(s); for example, a mother that is known to be pregnant in the series/arc/episode

Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2935 [stomach bulge] or http://anidb.net/t2727 [stomach stretch]. Engaging in at least 1 pregnant sex scene is not sufficient for this tag; tag http://anidb.net/t6999 [pregnant sex] at the anime level instead. For porn entries, pregnancy typically follows after an http://anidb.net/t3976 [impregnation] scene.
If the human character is http://anidb.net/t7148 [impregnated with larvae], use the http://anidb.net/t7151 [pregnant with larvae] tag instead.</description>
<picurl>161878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3316" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>despair</name>
<description>Involves characters that may be lost in negatively emotional atmospheres created through feelings of hopelessness and suffering.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3833" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>there can be only one</name>
<description>The long-term plot of the program revolves around a group of characters whose numbers are being slowly whittled away by one means or another, usually by killing each other. In the case of some reality shows, this is a process of elimination intended to result in a single winner. In other shows, this is a dramatic device, designed to generate tension and conflict with which to drive the overall plot of an episode or Story Arc (if any); in these cases it is sometimes combined with Anyone Can Die to especially heighten the resulting excitement, even when the apparent main character may be protected by Contractual Immortality. Compare Gotta Kill Them All.
Named for one of the catchphrases that came out of the Highlander franchise.
Source: TVTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3834" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>impending death -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>At least one character in this show is going to or very likely to die soon because of a http://anidb.net/t2574 [terminal illness], of a http://anidb.net/t2874 [disaster] such a http://anidb.net/t2925 [war], an http://anidb.net/t5466 [epidemic] (including the zombie apocalypse), or of other life-threatening reasons. Please assign the appropriate disaster tags to the anime, the terminal illness tag to the relevant characters, and any other relevant or necessary replacement tags to the corresponding entities, and then remove this tag from the anime in question. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4110" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>life force</name>
<description>Life force exists in many forms and is known under many names. It is the invisible fuel that runs human bodies and is resistent against scientific research and explanation. However, this very energy is one of the most powerful forces in the universe. Especially in mahou shoujo anime, the big bad evil will always try to steal it for their plans, bad guys from outer space will need it as food and even the good guys will often use their life force to bring back dead to life again, eventually sacrificing their life in the course of such an event.
Other energy sources known to mankind are the power of love and the power of friendship.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4301" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-22">
<name>play or die</name>
<description>The protagonist(s) are forced into a situation where they have to partake in some form of event, often a game of death, unless they want to bid farewell to their life.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4491" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>children of destiny</name>
<description>In case of nearing doomsday leave all the military equipment to kids — they will save the day. Rejoice!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4753" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>disturbing</name>
<description>Watching the show may cause the viewer to have unpleasant feelings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5872" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>bad luck</name>
<description>You are living a blessed life far from any troubles. Your sister is a famous reporter, you have a good looking girlfriend and you excel in your studies aiming to be a scientist. Your future is looking bright. But reality is, fate hates you. Your sister is killed, your girlfriend breaks up with you after being crippled in a terrorist attack and finally you end up as a pizza delivery boy.
And just when you thought it can`t get worse, it does. Your former girlfriend turns into a Darth Vader knock-off, tries to impose her world view on others by force and is out there to kill you. Yes, your life does truly suck.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5991" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-07-04">
<name>dark mood</name>
<description>Similar to `Dark Atmosphere`, but more focused on the actual characters rather than the setting. A dark mood can easily result from a dark atmosphere.
A dark mood is more than just occasionally feeling angry or down, it`s usually a permanent character trait that sours the character`s relationships with others.
However it arises, at least one character in this anime can see little good in the world or the people in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5996" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>tragic ending</name>
<description>Up to the very end of the anime the viewer will hope that the story will end well and that the characters will in some way be able to solve the problems.
Not so. The sense of foreboding doom could not be averted. The social or personal calamity strikes mercilessly.
Examples: The catastrophic meteor strike does hit Earth after all. The long sick loved one cannot be saved. After overcoming all obstacles a random cruel event ends the life of the protagonist. A almost forgotten tragedy in the past has repercussions in the present.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6315" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="8">4.00</rating>
<name>Komoda Takami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only daughter of a Navy official, it is through Komo that the army discovers the kids` involvement with Zearth. She was Maki`s best friend since childhood. At first Komo was rather quiet and bored by the world, preferring to read and play the piano alone, and secretly wondering if her father would have preferred a son instead. But as the time of her battle draws near, she goes outside to observe the world more closely and comes to appreciate how lively and beautiful it is.</description>
<picture>23611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6316" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="5">1.28</rating>
<name>Kodaka Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The boy chosen to pilot Zearth during the third battle with the robot, Cancer. He is a relatively quiet boy who likes to keep to himself. His father is a wary individual who runs a civilian contracting company. Kodama`s two gifted older brothers hate their father and try to go towards a different path, however Kodama looks up to him and his status as a "chosen" man. He even wears Kokopelli`s glasses to seem smarter like his father. Being raised by his father seems to have warped Kodama`s sense of ethics and morality to the point where he enjoys to take shots at stray cats with a pellet gun. During his time as a pilot he makes no attempt to avoid casualties and marvels at the death being caused because of him.
This sense of wonder is cut short when he is sent crashing down on top of his beloved father`s car, killing his father instantly. For a moment he is left completely stunned, but manages to shake himself out of it in time to kill Cancer using knowledge gained by having an understanding of construction. He dies unceremoniously a moment later. Kodama`s death alerts the other pilots to their fate. His chair is a plush office chair. There are 7,511 casualties during his battle, many due to his own malice.</description>
<picture>23612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6317" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="5">4.60</rating>
<name>Kirie Yousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fat and weak-willed, he was often bullied. His depressed hikikomori cousin Kazuko Motoyama, who was bulimic and cut her own wrists, made him wonder about the worth of his life and that of others.</description>
<picture>23613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6318" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="7">4.28</rating>
<name>Honda Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1439" picture="223493.jpg">Takahashi Ao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6319" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="5">7.19</rating>
<name>Moji Kunihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6320" type="main character in" update="2009-08-11">
<rating votes="10">6.49</rating>
<name>Ushiro Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6321" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="5">3.98</rating>
<name>Ushiro Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6322" type="appears in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="4">5.36</rating>
<name>Waku Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An energetic and confident young boy. He was previously a talented football player and is considered popular. He wanted to become a professional player and his friends thought he had the talent for it. However, he found out that his salary-man father was a football player just like him in his youth and even played at the national level. The fact that someone just like him didn`t make it shook Waku`s resolve and he stopped playing football. If he had not quit the team he wouldn`t have been at the summer class and become a pilot. He was chosen to become the first pilot of the children.</description>
<picture>23618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6323" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="5">7.98</rating>
<name>Tokosumi Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6324" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="2">4.97</rating>
<name>Nakarai Mako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who focuses all of her energy on living honestly and being an active benefit to the community in hopes that others would see her as a responsible and dependable person. Despite this, the well-known fact that her mother is a prostitute and her humourless, over-responsible attitude leaves her with no friends. Ever since elementary school any kind of hatred or dishonesty tortures her, so much that she can`t even raise a clenched fist at all of the kids who bully her, constantly having to keep to her duty and not protest in the slightest. Regardless, she looks up to her mother, and hopes to be able to stand proudly like she does. Nakama would even go so far as to give her mother the money she makes doing needlework. It was her mother`s idea that she go to the nature school so that she would finally make some friends.</description>
<picture>23620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6325" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="5">6.59</rating>
<name>Yoshikawa Kanji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6326" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="5">3.02</rating>
<name>Kako Isao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A spoiled and self-centred coward with a severe inferiority complex. He acted as an errand boy for a group of bullies to avoid being the subject of their abuse, and his parents would let him get away with just about anything, much to his older sister`s chagrin. Kako`s only "friend" was Kirie who also went to his school. Kako would constantly boss Kirie around since it made him feel less like a loser especially since Kirie would take this abuse without complaint. Kako in fact made Kirie accompany him to the nature school for this very reason. It was here that Kako developed a strong crush on Chizu.</description>
<picture>23622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="408" picture="17255.jpg">Fujita Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6327" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="5">6.37</rating>
<name>Machi Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6328" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="3">6.22</rating>
<name>Ano Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="690" picture="187038.jpg">Higa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6329" type="main character in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="5">7.31</rating>
<name>Yamura Daiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hard-working and responsible boy despite his gruff "no-nonsense" exterior. He dedicatedly took care of his three younger siblings: Yoshi, Futaba, and Santa. He accepted this task because their mother had died much earlier, and their father abandoned them for unknown reasons three years ago. Their uncle on their father`s side made up for his brothers disappearance by renting a home for the four siblings to live in, and paying for all expenses. Daiichi earned his keep by working as a mail and newspaper boy, and for his uncles landscaping business on his days off. He chose to live separately from his uncle with his siblings so that his father would have a place to return to if he ever decided to. When he and the other main characters first got involved with Zearth, he was the first to express any doubts and the first to try to leave the "game" before the group learned the truth of their involvement. His chair was not actually a chair, but a mere floating cushion, and he was lightly teased by a few of the other kids for this lack of imagination.</description>
<picture>23626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6330" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="2">3.86</rating>
<name>Kokopelli</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The man who involved the children with Zearth and was also the first pilot of the series. When the children first encountered him, he was hiding in a cave by the bay where the children were exploring. He seemed surprised to find them, but persuaded the children into becoming pilots of Zearth by telling them he was looking for volunteers for a new game, getting them to sign the contract.</description>
<picture>23627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6331" type="appears in" update="2009-04-19">
<name>Zearth</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>23629.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6332" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="8">7.94</rating>
<name>Coemushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="69139" update="2007-03-28">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV2:東京国際アニメフェア公開用PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV 2: Tokyo Kokusai Anime Fair Koukaiyou PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69140" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Game</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Game</title>
<summary>Seeking adventure during a school field trip, fifteen kids stumble upon a strange man in a cave, who invites them to play a game. But it turns out, the game is all too real.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694517</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71838" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジアース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zearth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zearth</title>
<summary>A strange creature named Koyemshi introduces itself to the group. Takashi is chosen as the next pilot of Zearth, and he resolves to be a "hidden hero" and protect the Earth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694519</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71857" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu</title>
<summary>Questions remain in the wake of Takashi`s death, the most pressing of which being, how did Takashi die? Both the kids, and the police, want to know. Amidst the grief and uncertainty, the next pilot is chosen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694521</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71858" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強さ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strength</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyosa</title>
<summary>Masaru`s family life has made him come to divide the world into two types of people: those born to die, and those born to survive. When it`s his turn to fight to protect Earth, which type will he end up as?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694523</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71859" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弱さ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Weakness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yowasa</title>
<summary>The children realize just what it means to be chosen as a pilot for Zearth. Meanwhile, the adults finally make their move, as the military gets involved, both with Koyemshi, and Zearth itself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694525</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="72109" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">情欲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lust</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jouyoku</title>
<summary>The next pilot is Kako, but the other kids can`t find him, though Chizu has an idea of where he might be. When the next enemy appears, the military makes an attempt a first strike.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694527</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="72110" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wound</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizu</title>
<summary>With Kako dead, but the enemy still around, the next pilot needs to be selected. As the chairs spin, Chizu recalls her past and what led to her being where she is now.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694529</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="72111" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復讐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vengeance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushuu</title>
<summary>Chizu has been chosen, and she`s determined to do one last thing before she completes her role as a pilot of Zearth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694531</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="74357" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家族</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Family</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazoku</title>
<summary>It`s Daichi`s turn in the pilot chair, but he`s not concerned about himself. Instead, he makes a decision that mirrors what his father did, all those years ago.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694533</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="74358" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仲間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Companion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakama</title>
<summary>Mako has always been embarrassed about her mother`s profession, the oldest in the world. But when she`s chosen to be the next pilot, she choses to see life from her mother`s eyes before her time runs out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694535</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75116" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inochi</title>
<summary>Moji has always been good at reading the hearts of others. But when it becomes his turn to pilot, he knows exactly where his own heart will go.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694537</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75117" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血のつながり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blood Relative</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chi no Tsunagari</title>
<summary>Maki races against time, hoping that she`ll be able to see the face of her unborn baby brother before her battle. Meanwhile, Misumi is convinced the children`s sacrifice needs to be recognized.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694539</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75118" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu</title>
<summary>The children realize that their latest fight is no where on Earth, at least, not the one they know. The awful truth behind the game comes out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694541</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="79629" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Perplexity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoi</title>
<summary>The friction between Misumi and the world`s economic and political powers grows stronger. Misumi pushes forward with her plan to save the children from their dark fate.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694543</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="79630" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">情愛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Affection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jouai</title>
<summary>Anko is next in the chair for Zearth`s pilot, coinciding with the public exposure of her father`s affair. While Anko tries to leave off on something good, the plan to help the children begins to buckle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694549</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="79631" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoutai</title>
<summary>Komo`s father exposes the political coverup behind Zearth. Kirie`s mother recovers from her ills, and Kirie himself finds the will to fight. But yet another secret is revealed in the process.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694547</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="79632" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自滅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Self-Destruction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jimetsu</title>
<summary>Kirie has always been the quiet one. With his gloomy demeanor, and his life a depressing mess, will Kirie even find the will to fight for an Earth he doesn`t care for?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694545</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81008" recap="true" update="2010-04-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">追想</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reminiscence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuisou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81133" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">現実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reality</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genjitsu</title>
<summary>The powers behind the coverup push back, and Komo`s father is caught in the middle. In the end, the sarcifices made will inspire Komo to fight in the same way her father did, for the Earth he loved.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694551</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81134" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">母</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haha</title>
<summary>Tamotsu takes Jun out to reminisce about the past. The story he tells is of the "Climbing Dragon", a young yakuza lieutenant, and his wife, Misumi, who he had a child with.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694553</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81135" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukumei</title>
<summary>Swayed by years of guilt and hopelessness, Yoko finally comes forward and speaks, telling the story of herself and her brother, who is now known as Koyemshi, and the endless cycle the two are in.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694555</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81136" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真相</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsou</title>
<summary>Kanji`s turn to pilot Zearth is marked by a strange setup, wherein the enemy appears to be targeting the Chutenro Tower research center. In the course the fight, they discover the ultimate purpose of this endless game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694559</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81137" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">道程</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doutei</title>
<summary>Jun takes Kana back to her father, and asks Yoko to go along with them. Along the way, he thinks upon his life until now, and ultimately comes to a decision about Koyemshi`s offer.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694561</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81138" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪景色</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snowscape</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukigeshiki</title>
<summary>Jun and Yoko`s plan to fight against Koyemshi goes into action. The thirteenth battle begins with Yoko as the pilot, and the government enacting their own schemes to deal with the enemy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694563</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81139" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monogatari</title>
<summary>The final fight is upon the Earth. Jun, as the final pilot, fights with the whole world looking on, and with everything he`s learned guiding him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694565</identifier>
<identifier>bokurano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96923" update="2010-04-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96924" update="2010-04-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117421" update="2010-04-04">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141514" update="2012-08-10">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM2:DVD発売告知CM2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD CM2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">CM 2: DVD Hatsubai Kokuchi CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141515" update="2012-08-10">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM1:DVD発売告知CM1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD CM1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">CM 1: DVD Hatsubai Kokuchi CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141516" update="2012-08-10">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV1:IKKI付録 アニメ化告知PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV 1: Ikki Furoku Anime Kakokuchi PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144711" update="2012-10-11">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">COMIC IKKI SPECIAL PROMOTION VIDEO -ATTACK ZEARTH-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Extended Preview Video</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Comic Ikki Special Promotion Video: Attack Zearth</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
