<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4888" restricted="false">
<type>Music Video</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-12-20</startdate>
<enddate>2006-12-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Glass Eye</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Amazing Nuts! 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">العين الزجاجية</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Glass Eye</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4887" type="Other">Global Astroliner Gou</anime>
<anime id="4889" type="Other">Tatoe Kimi ga Sekaijuu no Teki ni Natte mo</anime>
<anime id="4890" type="Other">Joe and Marilyn</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/amazing-nuts/</url>
<creators>
<name id="738" type="Animation Production">Studio 4C</name>
<name id="27972" type="Direction">Yamashita Takashi</name>
</creators>
<description>Second of the four clips on http://anidb.net/cr738 [Studio 4°C]`s Amazing Nuts! DVD, an anthology of four animated shorts with each featuring its own distinct animation style and music.
Director: Takashi Yamashita
Character designer: Koji Morimoto
Music: RAM RIDER (Smile Again)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="499">3.93</permanent>
<temporary count="499">5.80</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>11610.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7246</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1998</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/amazing-nuts/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="66725" update="2007-01-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2006-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120798" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2006-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">4C`s Amazing Nuts!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120800" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Story of Amazing Nuts!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120849" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Credits</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
