<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4891" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-13</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaze no Stigma</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Stigma of the Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Печать ветра</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Петно на Вятъра</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">风之圣痕</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">KNS</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">風のスティグマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kaze no Stigma</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">바람의 스티그마</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3408" approval="86" total="126">Shakugan no Shana</anime>
<anime id="4574" approval="56" total="70">Kekkaishi</anime>
<anime id="4516" approval="34" total="43">Busou Renkin</anime>
<anime id="6546" approval="22" total="43">Seiken no Blacksmith</anime>
<anime id="8673" approval="19" total="31">Code: Breaker</anime>
<anime id="9015" approval="9" total="19">Hagure Yuusha no Aesthetica</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="20">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="263262">Only watch this if you like annoying little brother and tsunderes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="268674">You will love the romance between Ayano and Kazuma</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="162375">The main character Kaze is really cool.
The anime series are getting interesting, unfortunately there would not be any  Kaze no Stigma ever again.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="368178">awesome main character :) i really enjoyed this</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="33349">It was a nice story, but i have to say that the author has died. i dont know if he finished the manga or the story will ever continue</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="16524">The anime is recommended for its wide variety of themes.  A touch of romance, action, drama.  Nice way of killing time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="269120">it`s one of the best animes that i`ve watched</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="292249">Must SEE Anime ,one of the best</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="251472">If you liked Shana you must see it too. :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="508851">the plot is good and the story goes on well but the BGM does not suit the play.If there is a sequel it should be corrected.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/stigma/</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="683" type="Series Composition">Sekijima Mayori</name>
<name id="3568" type="Direction">Sakata Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="12261" type="Original Work">Yamato Takahiro</name>
<name id="4397" type="Character Design">Nitta Yasunari</name>
<name id="8360" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamakawa Kouji</name>
<name id="30323" type="Music">Fukuoka Yutaka</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr12261 [Yamato Takahiro].
http://anidb.net/ch6809 [Ayano] is the heir to the house of Kannagi, a house with ties to the Spirit of Fire whose members are all fire users. All except for her cousin, http://anidb.net/ch6810 [Kazuma]. After he was defeated by Ayano, his father banished him from the house in disgrace. Kazuma runs off and changes his surname to Yagami. He forms a contract with the Spirit of Wind and becomes a powerful wind user. Four years later, he returns. Some killings in the Kannagi house by a powerful wind user lead Ayano and the Kannagi house into thinking Kazuma is taking revenge. Although claiming to be innocent, Kazuma is preparing for an all out war with Kannagi.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5116">5.76</permanent>
<temporary count="5190">7.46</temporary>
<review count="6">4.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>146833.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7473</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1691</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3978</identifier>
<identifier>btaiss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/stigma/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.fujimishobo.co.jp/sp/stigma/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20090830064306/http://pc.webnt.jp/stigma/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kaze_no_Stigma</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>風の聖痕</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1136</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327124</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8931</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1674</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/stigma</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="178" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-28">
<name>insane</name>
<description>Insanity, craziness, or madness is a spectrum of behaviors characterized by certain abnormal mental or behavioral patterns. Insanity may manifest as violations of societal norms, including a person becoming a danger to themselves or others, though not all such acts are considered insanity; likewise, not all acts showing indifference toward societal norms are acts of insanity.
In modern usage, insanity is most commonly encountered as an informal unscientific term denoting mental instability, or in the narrow legal context of the insanity defense.
A more informal use of the term insanity is to denote something or someone considered highly unique, passionate or extreme, including in a positive sense. The term may also be used as an attempt to discredit or criticise particular ideas, beliefs, principles, desires, personal feelings, attitudes, or their proponents, such as in politics and religion.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-25">
<name>contractor</name>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1783" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>immature</name>
<description>Marked by or indicating a lack of maturity</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4226" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>paradise lost</name>
<description>Derived from the Biblical story of the Fall of Man: the temptation of Adam and Eve by the fallen angel Satan and their expulsion from the Garden of Eden.
This tag is used to demonstrate the unbearable loss, the feeling of losing everything along with every single bit of happiness. It prerequisites a small peaceful period of happiness. The main reason for losing "his/her paradise" can either be the death/sacrifice of an important character or even a betrayal. Usually the anime loses a lot of its former glory afterwards.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6809" type="main character in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="55">6.15</rating>
<name>Kannagi Ayano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sixteen year old Kannagi Ayano is a skilled En-Jutsushi and the successor to the Kannagi family`s head. She is arrogant and irrational, usually taking action by herself even while going against orders. Though she seems undisciplined, she is very proud of her heritage.
Despite claiming to hate Kazuma, Ayano develops a crush on him, but is often irritated when he makes a move on her and is prone to throwing fits of rage when he gets close to another woman. She later comes to realize that she is actually in love with him. Kazuma is also the only person she sees as stronger in power and presence than even her own father.
Ayano`s power is the Crimson Flame, although she is not yet able to consciously control it. She also holds Enraiha, the Kannagi`s sacred sword, which she won by defeating Kazuma at the successor ceremony four years before the start of the story. The sword has fire properties and can be summoned by Ayano at any time.</description>
<picture>187021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6810" type="main character in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="92">8.70</rating>
<name>Yagami Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazuma is a former member of the Kannagi household. He was banished from the family by his father after he was defeated by Ayano during the Successor Ceremony for the Enraiha, his family`s sacred sword. Since Kazuma is a son from the main family, making him the legitimate successor, even his own father considered him a disgrace for lacking the power to use fire magic, his family`s specialty. Four years later, at the age of twenty-two, he returns to Japan as a skilled master of the wind arts. Though he was not responsible for the killings in the Kannagi household, he is prepared to start a war with his former family.</description>
<picture>187020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6811" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="18">4.10</rating>
<name>Kannagi Ren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazuma`s younger brother. He looks up to both Kazuma and Ayano as his older siblings. Ren`s power is the Golden Flame, said to have the largest purification effect.</description>
<picture>187006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="330" picture="171543.jpg">Morinaga Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6812" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="10">6.89</rating>
<name>Kudou Nanase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Ayano`s best friends and classmates. She and Yukari know about the existence of jutsushi. Nanase is also a very athletic student, who is part of many of their school`s athletic clubs, and is admired by many of the female students. While she is not as well connected as Yukari, Nanase is just as caring and carries much sway with the students.</description>
<picture>186989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6813" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="14">6.89</rating>
<name>Shinomiya Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Ayano`s best friends and classmates. Yukari, along with Nanase, often teases Ayano about her apparent crush on Kazuma. She is well-connected to the information network of the student body and often knows what is happening around the school. Yukari`s information extends beyond the school and into many areas of the Tokyo metropolis. She also carries a taser of unexplained origin with her.</description>
<picture>186990.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1886" picture="21014.jpg">Inokuchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6814" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-24">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Kannagi Genma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ren and Kazuma`s strict father. Though he is responsible for banishing Kazuma from the Kannagi family, he only wanted his son to find his own path.
Genma is the strongest En-Jutsushi of the Kannagi`s, and wields the blue God Flame, Shinen, which only eleven others have wielded since the founding of the clan. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>187005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6815" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-23">
<rating votes="11">6.15</rating>
<name>Kannagi Juugo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kannagi Juugo is Ayano`s father and Genma`s cousin. He is the current head of the Kannagi family. Juugo worries about his headstrong daughter. Contrary to the Kannagi doctrine that is based solely on strength, Juugo has been trying to stop discrimination against the Fuuga Clan. He also regrets not being able to stop Kazuma`s expulsion from the family. Believing that Kazuma is essential to the Kannagis, he constantly creates situations in which Ayano can form a relationship with Kazuma.</description>
<picture>186986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6816" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-23">
<rating votes="17">6.37</rating>
<name>Tachibana Kirika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A detective working for the Tokyo MPD`s Special Investigation Unit, in charge of investigating crimes related to jutsu.
She occasionally works together with Kazuma.</description>
<picture>186987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6817" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="25">5.99</rating>
<name>Katherine McDonald</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of an American family of En-Jutsushi, specially skilled in creating and controlling spirit beasts to harness flames. She manipulates myriads of spirits into a single virtual persona to grasp tremendous power. While seemingly capable of creating different spirit beasts, her favorite is Metatron, an angel-like statue equipped with a sword. Kazuma has observed and mentioned that her fighting style is similar to Ayano`s, referring to their simplistic and direct attacks, which lack any strategy or tactics. A rival against Ayano in both En-Jutsushi and Kazuma`s "love".</description>
<picture>186988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31718" type="appears in" update="2016-05-23">
<rating votes="2">5.48</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Kureha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Older daughter of the Tsuwabuki family, who are skilled "Chijutsushi" (地術師, Earth Technique Practitioner). During her father`s absence due to "illness", she becomes the head of the Tsuwabuki family. Zenon, the behemoth of Mt. Fuji, stripped her powers as a Chijutsushi. Like Kazuma, she was ostracized for her lack of power by her family. She is later killed by Zenon in a fit of rage. It is notable that once Zenon`s restriction was lifted from her, Kureha`s power was of an extremely high level as seen in her fight with Zenon.</description>
<picture>186980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1431" picture="25110.jpg">Kosuge Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31720" type="appears in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="2">4.50</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Mayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Younger daughter of the Tsuwabuki family. Her clone, Ayumi, is used as the sacrifice in Taisai, the ritual of taming the behemoth within Mt. Fuji every 30 years preventing the volcano from erupting. The ritual involves claiming the life of a Chijutsushi, who is usually a member of the Tsuwabuki family, since 300 years ago. Due to Kareha`s influence, she is a cold, heartless woman, from her portrayal and behavior towards her clone. She later feels remorse after Ayumi`s sacrifice.</description>
<picture>186982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4428" picture="26693.jpg">Miyajima Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31721" type="appears in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="2">7.44</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The clone of Mayumi Tsuwabuki. Although she has the appearance of a twelve year old, she is only a month old. According to Mayumi, she had been implanted with random memories from Mayumi and has a lifespan of about two months. Using the treasure of the Pixies, which is an egg that will hatch into the tribal leader of the Pixies, Ayumi`s growth is accelerated, so that within one month, she grew twelve years. She falls in love with Ren. She sacrifices her life to weaken Zenon, so that Kazuma, Ren, and Ayano could destroy Zenon.</description>
<picture>186981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="448" picture="158105.jpg">Sakai Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31722" type="appears in" update="2016-05-23">
<rating votes="2">1.82</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayumi`s servant and bodyguard. Completely devoted to her.</description>
<picture>186983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31723" type="appears in" update="2016-05-22">
<rating votes="2">3.61</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Iwao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of the Tsuwabuki family. Imprisoned by his daughter Kureha.</description>
<picture>186974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3337" picture="211147.jpg">Ogino Seirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31724" type="appears in" update="2016-05-22">
<rating votes="2">5.45</rating>
<name>Zenon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also called Behemoth. It is the embodiment of Mt. Fujii. Looks like a giant turtle.</description>
<picture>186976.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31726" type="appears in" update="2011-05-01">
<rating votes="2">1.82</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Ichizoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Users of Chijutsu are called Chijutsushi (地術師?, Earth Technique Practitioner). The Tsuwabuki clan is known as the most powerful of Chijutsushi. Common attacks are making spikes rise from the ground, and creating earthquakes.</description>
</character>
<character id="31771" type="appears in" update="2016-05-23">
<rating votes="2">2.87</rating>
<name>Kannagi Ichizoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The fire arts are most effective for combat. Users of Enjutsu are known as Enjutsushi (炎術師, Blaze Technique Practitioner) and can draw upon flame spirits. The Kannagi is the most powerful clan of fire users.</description>
<picture>186984.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31772" type="appears in" update="2011-05-06">
<rating votes="2">1.50</rating>
<name>Fuuga Shuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Also called Wind Fang Clan. The Fuuga clan of Fuujutsushi served the Kannagi for 300 years, but was eliminated in the course of plotting revenge for their subjugation. Before serving the Kannagi they were a criminal organisation which the Kannagi destroyed.</description>
</character>
<character id="31773" type="appears in" update="2016-05-22">
<rating votes="2">3.61</rating>
<name>Oogami Takeya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Kannagi, Takeya is part of the party initially sent to bring in Kazuma for questioning. He is killed in the first episode by Ryuuya after being knocked down by Kazuma. He was considered to be a powerful fire user by the family, but he was unprepared for Kazuma. Takeya always acts with a calm and level head.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>186968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2339" picture="151715.jpg">Taketora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31775" type="appears in" update="2016-05-22">
<rating votes="5">4.86</rating>
<name>Oogami Misao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sister of Takeya, who was the only person kind to her. Although a kind person at heart, having saved Kazuma from bullying ten years ago, Misao blames Kazuma for her brother`s death and attempts to kill him. Her attempts fail, and she becomes a pawn in Michael`s plan to take Kazuma down. In the end, Kazuma convinces her to atone for her sins by living on, and she is later instructed by Juugo to retire to a convent.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>186967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31776" type="appears in" update="2016-05-22">
<rating votes="2">1.82</rating>
<name>Oogami Masayuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misao`s and Takeya`s father. Leader of the Kannagi branch family.</description>
<picture>186966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3323" picture="24340.jpg">Shiroyama Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31777" type="appears in" update="2016-05-22">
<rating votes="2">1.03</rating>
<name>Michael Harley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young boy from the Stars of Sagacity, an organization related to Kazuma`s past and Tsui-Ling`s death. He uses Misao`s anger at Kazuma and promised to grant her wishes. In truth, he only uses her as a medium, in order to obtain enough yoki, or life energy, to kill Kazuma. He is killed by Ayano`s Shinen-empowered Enraiha.</description>
<picture>186969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31778" type="appears in" update="2016-05-23">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Vlitra</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dragon created by Michael Harley from the energy gathered by Misao.</description>
<picture>186979.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31779" type="appears in" update="2016-05-22">
<rating votes="4">5.88</rating>
<name>Tiana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tiana is the Pixie that was guarding the tree in Ayano`s school. She was also sent to retrieve the Pixie treasure from the Tsuwabuki clan.</description>
<picture>186970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31780" type="appears in" update="2016-05-22">
<rating votes="2">2.87</rating>
<name>Kazamaki Hyoue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of the Wind Fang Clan. Ryuuya`s father. He wants his clan to break free from the control of the Kannagi family, because they were seen as nothing more than servants.</description>
<picture>186963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31785" type="appears in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="2">1.81</rating>
<name>Yuuki Shinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Member of the branch family of the Kannagi clan.</description>
<picture>186978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4423" picture="26687.jpg">Okuda Keijin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31787" type="appears in" update="2016-05-22">
<rating votes="2">2.87</rating>
<name>Yuuki Shingo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinji`s older brother. He thought that Kazuma killed him so he wanted to avenge his sibling. Killed by Ryuuya.</description>
<picture>186977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3970" picture="25848.jpg">Nishiwaki Tamotsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31791" type="appears in" update="2016-05-22">
<rating votes="2">1.82</rating>
<name>Gehou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Youma that gave Wind Fang Clan his powers. Sealed by the Kannagi clan.</description>
<picture>186928.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31794" type="appears in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="2">1.50</rating>
<name>Kazamaki Ryuuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son of Hyoue Kazamaki, leader of the Fuuga Clan, which served the Kannagi for the last 300 years. In an elaborate plot to release the Fuuga Clan`s ancient master and take revenge on the Kannagi for the humiliation received since then, Ryuuya`s body becomes the host for a powerful yoma. Later on, he is killed in a joint attack by Kazuma and Ayano.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>186964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66174" type="appears in" update="2016-05-24">
<rating votes="3">4.48</rating>
<name>CuiLing</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The girl Kazuma could not protect. She was sacrificed by the head member of the Armagest Erwin Leszaar to summon a demon. Rhodes used a spell to gather her remaining essence into a being called Lapis. Before her sacrifice, she and Kazuma worked in a restaurant, and were in love. According to Lapis in the last episode, her last thoughts were that she wished Kazuma was dead. Whether this is true or lies meant to cause Kazuma pain is unknown (Kazuma notes that she may have said this out of spite towards his inability to save her). As Lapis, she is trained in anti-mage fighting.</description>
<picture>187003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66186" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-24">
<rating votes="9">3.36</rating>
<name>Lapis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The entity that was made in CuiLing`s image by Bernhardt. Lapis carries a big crystal broad sword, but wields it with ease, and is able to match Ayano in a sword duel. It is revealed in episode 21 of the anime that Lapis has a heart, so she can feel the joy in hurting others, among other emotions.</description>
<picture>187002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66201" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-24">
<rating votes="6">1.68</rating>
<name>Bernhardt Rhodes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The chairman of Armagest, a powerful organization of modern magic users. He holds a grudge against Kazuma for killing his master, the man who sacrificed Tsui-Ling.</description>
<picture>187004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82244" type="appears in" update="2016-05-28">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Isurugi Daiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A rookie detective with the police, Daiki is overwhelmed by the realities of magic and sprites, especially when Kazuma uses him to draw out a rouge magic user.</description>
<picture>187133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1630" picture="1887.gif">Tasaka Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82245" type="appears in" update="2016-05-28">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Hellhound</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A rouge magic user with a cocky attitude (like most of them), Hellhound attacks with a flaming dog he that commands, hence his name.
Kazuma uses Daiki to lure him out and get him talking about how he got his powers. After hearing what he needs to from him, Kazuma easily disables Hellhound, but a chance encounter distracts Kazuma so much that Hellhound is able to escape.
(Source: MyAnimeList)</description>
<picture>187134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7049" picture="32044.jpg">Sakai Keikou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85706" type="appears in" update="2017-02-05">
<name>Suzuhara Kanon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1931" picture="238837.jpg">Tsuji Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85707" type="appears in" update="2017-02-05">
<name>Serizawa Tatsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197821.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85721" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-05">
<rating votes="1">4.68</rating>
<name>Kurahashi Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="69254" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風の帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wind Returns</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze no Kikan</title>
<summary>Kazuma Kannagi is a descendent of an ancient Japanese family skilled the art of fire magic. Unfortunately for him, the gift seems to have skipped a generation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="71808" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去との対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confrontation with the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako to no Taiketsu</title>
<summary>Reunions come in all shapes and sizes, but when Kazuma and his father meet face to face for the first time in years, someone’s gonna end up hurt - or dead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="71809" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神凪宗家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Head of the Kannagi Family</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kannagi Souke</title>
<summary>Kazuma and Ayano join forces to save someone dear to them both. He’ll bring the wind, and she’ll supply the fire, as they take on the fight of their lives.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="71810" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">契約者(コントラクター)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Contractor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keiyakusha</title>
<summary>With Ren - Kazuma’s brother and a direct descendent of the Kannagi Family - in their possession, the Fuga Clan prepares for the sacrifice that will restore their magic.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="72571" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷いを捨てた者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One Who Casts Aside Doubt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoi o Suteta Mono</title>
<summary>Kazuma’s secret rendezvous drives Ayano crazy, but she’s not the only one obsessed with the wind mage. There’s another pretty lady tearing up the streets of Japan to get close to him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="73369" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">力の代償</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Price of Power</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikara no Daishou</title>
<summary>Kazuma better watch his back. The alluring Misao will go to any length to extract revenge for her brother’s death - and she’s convinced it’s all the wind mage’s fault.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="73375" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魂の値段</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cost of a Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamashii no Nedan</title>
<summary>Misao falls under the spell of a mysterious stranger who plans to use her to destroy Kazuma. But the windgician has some plans of his own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="73376" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">綾乃ちゃんの災難</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayano`s Disaster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayano-chan no Sainan</title>
<summary>Like it or not, Kazuma and Ayano can’t get away from each other. This time, it’s a strange disturbance at the feisty heiress’s school that’s brings them together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="73377" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月下の出会い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meeting Under the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekka no Deai</title>
<summary>Ren’s got his back against the wall and a pretty new friend to impress, so he decides to handle things the way Kazuma would - now there’s a family of earth-shakers after him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="75080" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">護るべき人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One to Be Protected</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamorubeki Hito</title>
<summary>With hormones raging and the forces of puberty dragging him in multiple directions, Ren takes a stand to protect an enchanting girl who mysteriously appears one moonlit night.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="75081" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Each Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Ketsui</title>
<summary>With time racing against them, Ren, Kazuma, and Ayano set out to rescue Ayumi and put an end to the twisted antics of the Tsuwabuki Clan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="75082" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月下の告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confession Under the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekka no Kokuhaku</title>
<summary>Kazuma meets his match in the beautiful - but deranged - Kureha. Born without the power to control Earth Magic, she hatched a plot to destroy her own clan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="75083" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遊園地に行こう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go to the Amusement Park!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuenchi ni Ikou!</title>
<summary>Fire and Wind investigate an alleged poltergeist infestation at the local amusement park. It’s not long before Ayano and Kazuma get the feeling that they’re being set up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="79755" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">綾乃ちゃんの更なる災難</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Ayano Disaster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayano-chan no Saranaru Sainan</title>
<summary>A brash, young beauty arrives from across the sea - intent on building a reputation for her own family by challenging Ayano to a fiery duel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80125" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャサリン・リターンズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Katherine Returns</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katherine Returns</title>
<summary>Katherine McDonald, an American skilled in the Fire Arts, is bound and determined to beat Ayano in a duel and lay claim to Enraiha - the Kannagi Clan’s greatest weapon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80278" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父と子と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Father and Son</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi to Ko to</title>
<summary>When Kazuma and Genma have a heart to heart at the outdoor baths, the hotel better hope it has insurance because men of their temperament let their fists do the talking.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80279" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法使いの倒し方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Defeat a Magic User</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahoutsukai no Taoshikata</title>
<summary>The secrets of the Spirit Arts are being recklessly divulged, and the city erupts into chaos as rogue wannabes make their dreams come true through a sinister and twisted game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81075" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東京RPG</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo RPG</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokyo RPG</title>
<summary>Teenagers visiting a mysterious website end up harnessing the powers of hell, Kazuma and Ayano are on the case, but they’re gonna have their hands full.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81243" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">万魔殿[パンデモニウム]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pandemonium</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pandemonium</title>
<summary>Pandemonium reigns as magic junkies take to the streets and beat each other’s skulls in. Fearing the origin of this power, Ayano and Ren put their problems on hold and search for clues.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81244" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">翠色の残影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Remnant of the Emerald</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suishoku no Zanei</title>
<summary>You can run all you want, but sooner or later, the past will catch up to you. Kazuma knows this sensation all too well since he’s been running from memories all his life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81245" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂乱の風術師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Raging Wind Mage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouran no Fuujutsushi</title>
<summary>The only woman Kazuma ever loved was cruelly slain by the same fiend behind the sinister Pandemonium that now holds Tokyo in its crushing grip.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81246" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決意と逡巡と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Determination and Hesitation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketsui to Shunjun to</title>
<summary>After their last meeting, Bernhardt pieced together what remained of Kazuma’s true love - fashioning a weapon he could use to drive the contractor of the wind to the brink of madness!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="82775" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅炎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crimson Flame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouen</title>
<summary>As Pandemonium gathers power from its victims, demons erupt from their unsuspecting hosts. Tokyo’s last chance is Ayano - to save her city, she must first save Kazuma.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="82776" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風の護りしもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protectors of the Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze no Mamorishimono</title>
<summary>As Tokyo sleeps, a new threat looms. The Prince of Hell has been summoned, and it will take the full power of the united Kannagi Clan to slay the beast.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85249" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88472" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88473" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105184" update="2009-07-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayano`s House Call All-You-Can-Eat Cakes Part 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105185" update="2009-07-18">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayano`s House Call All-You-Can-Eat Cakes Part 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105186" update="2009-07-18">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayano`s House Call All-You-Can-Eat Cakes Part 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108630" update="2009-09-19">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayano`s House Call All-You-Can-Eat Cakes Part 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108631" update="2009-09-19">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayano`s House Call All-You-Can-Eat Cakes Part 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108632" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayano`s House Call All-You-Can-Eat Cakes Part 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108729" update="2009-09-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Season 1 Part 2 Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
