<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4893" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kamichama Karin</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Chibi Goddess Karin</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Маленькая богиня Карин</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kami-chama Karin</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">小女神花铃</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">かみちゃまかりん</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3320" approval="5" total="10">Sugar Sugar Rune</anime>
<anime id="516" approval="1" total="4">Princess Tutu</anime>
<anime id="102" approval="1" total="2">Cardcaptor Sakura</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="488855">When I watched it, I automatically took it as mahou shoujo parody and so I laughed almost the whole time I was watching this... 
No, really, these series really can`t be taken seriously, because if it`s extremely stupid behind any borders (much worse than Mermaid Melody imho). Final explanations and the end were especially crazy. 
Watch this only if you can imagine it as a comedy. Otherwise: Avoid it!!!
Some positives:
+ not many episodes of this agony
+ cute design</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="287688">my fav anime!&lt;br /&gt;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372038">I thought this anime was really cute and great to watch &amp;gt;w&amp;lt;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="301451">...What did I just watch?

By most scales, this show should be considered terrible.  But that only adds to the experience.  It has a strange way of drawing you into its generally awkward pacing.

This is very much a love or hate series.  Just watch the first episode to see if you get it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="453807">If you like Card capture Sakura then you should like this as well, very similar. The anime is pretty slow but always has comedy even in the most awkward situation. The ending might be a little inconclusive, but it give it a try.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/kamichamakarin/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4252" type="Direction">Annou Takashi</name>
<name id="3066" type="Chief Animation Direction">Noguchi Takayuki</name>
<name id="6725" type="Music">Tsuji You</name>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="8933" type="Character Design">Shinohara Kenji</name>
<name id="5071" type="Series Composition">Kakihara Yuuko</name>
<name id="6163" type="Original Work">Koge-Donbo</name>
<name id="3068" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishibashi Yukiko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the shoujo manga by http://anidb.net/cr6163 [Koge Donbo] serialised in Nakayoshi.
Kamichama Karin is about a 7th grader named http://anidb.net/ch14626 [Hanazono Karin]. Her parents and beloved cat, Shi-chan recently died, she`s getting horrible grades and is forced to live with her aunt. One day, Karin meets a young, orphaned, 7th grade boy named http://anidb.net/ch14627 [Kujyou Kazune], and discovers that her mother`s ring has the power to transform her into a goddess. She soon moves in with Kazune and his cousin http://anidb.net/ch14628 [Himeka]. She and Kazune, who has godlike powers of his own, have to fight to protect Karin`s ring and Himeka from the evil intentions of http://anidb.net/ch14629 [Karasuma Kirio] (whom Karin calls Mr. Glasses Man), who is also divine. The trio embark on crazy adventures and go on trips along the way. They also meet new friends and people, such as http://anidb.net/ch14631 [Micchi], who may know a lot of information not only about the divine transformation of the gods and goddesses, but also about Kazune-kun`s long lost father...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="450">4.27</permanent>
<temporary count="461">6.54</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>12034.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7461</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1808</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3939</identifier>
<identifier>fuzlxm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/kamichamakarin/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kamichama_Karin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>かみちゃまかりん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1122</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327228</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8913</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1718</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/kamichamakarin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>꼬마_여신_카린</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>花鈴的魔法戒</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1065" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>heterochromatic eyes</name>
<description>Heterochromia Iridis is a condition where one eye is a different color from the other, or one eye is more than one color.
Characters with different eye-colour may not necessarily have the medical condition itself, as the state of different-coloured eyes can be caused by various other reasons such as possession by spiritual entities, indication of special powers or artificial changes.</description>
<picurl>63229.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1894" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-04">
<name>shota</name>
<description>Shotacon, sometimes shortened to shota, is a Japanese slang portmanteau of the phrase Shoutarou complex and describes an attraction to young boys, or an individual with such an attraction. Outside Japan, the term is less common and most often refers to a genre of manga and anime wherein pre-pubescent or pubescent male characters are depicted in a suggestive or erotic manner.
In a general sense, this is the same as http://anidb.net/t2566 [loli], just replace young girls with young boys.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>35399.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2406" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-13">
<name>talking animal</name>
<description>Talking animals are a common theme in mythology and folk tales, as well as children`s literature. Fictional talking creatures often are anthropomorphic, possessing human-like qualities but appearing as a creature. An animal that only knows how to say its name (for example, 99.9% of all http://anidb.net/t2493 [Pokemon]), are not talking animals.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2670" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>school festival - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>THIS TAG NEEDS TO BE SPLIT:
into http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=6119&amp;reltb=eptb [school culture festival]
and http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=2665&amp;reltb=eptb [school sports festival]
The obligatory school festival (or cultural fair) with cosplay cafe, haunted house, theatre performance, and food booths cannot be missing in any school setting.
For good measure there may also be an athletics or sports festival in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2781" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>first kiss</name>
<description>The first kiss plays a role in this anime. Especially for the female cast this can be quite an important moment, so that stealing ones first kiss is serious for them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4110" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>life force</name>
<description>Life force exists in many forms and is known under many names. It is the invisible fuel that runs human bodies and is resistent against scientific research and explanation. However, this very energy is one of the most powerful forces in the universe. Especially in mahou shoujo anime, the big bad evil will always try to steal it for their plans, bad guys from outer space will need it as food and even the good guys will often use their life force to bring back dead to life again, eventually sacrificing their life in the course of such an event.
Other energy sources known to mankind are the power of love and the power of friendship.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4206" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-12">
<name>magical boy</name>
<description>A cross-dressing boy that dresses like a magical girl.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5824" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>god is a girl</name>
<description>In storylines where many or all gods are portrayed as goddesses (female gods), "The God of all Gods", or the Number-One-God so to speak, is also female.
In other instances, such may just refer to a girl with god-like powers.</description>
<picurl>215285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="14626" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">4.22</rating>
<name>Hanazono Karin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karin is the protagonist of the series. Her name literally means "The Flower Bell of the Flower Garden," with the "Flower Garden" as her surname and "Flower Bell" as her given name. Karin used to live with her aunt because her parents died a long time ago, but she moved in with Kazune and Himeka after they found out about her goddess powers. She is an outgoing person, even though she does bad in school and sticks up for her friends. She had a cat named Shii-chan that passed away in the beginning of the first series. In the first series, she has recently ended 6th grade and starts 7th in volume 1, and is 14 years old. In Chu she is in 8th grade and is 15 years old (Stated in volume 1 of Chu). The ring Karin originally thought was her mother`s ring allows her to borrow godly power. Her ring is silver and has the power of the goddess Athena (Aphrodite in Chu). It is later revealed in the later volumes of the manga that Karin is actually Kazune Kujyou`s wife, Suzuka Kujyou, (Suzuka is Karin backwards, since suzu is another way to read the character rin), which was stated in Volume 7 that Karin was returned to an infant by Kazune Kujyou. It is shown that whenever Kazune becomes drunk, even with the so much as the smell of alcohol, he acts perverted towards Karin. They end up together and will end up loving each other with out either of them knowing at first in the beginning of the anime. At the end of the sequel of the manga, it is shown that she and Kazune get married.</description>
<picture>42314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14627" type="main character in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Kujou Kazune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazune is the main male protagonist. His ring has the power of Apollo Greek god of light (in the Chu sequel, he has a different ring with the power of Ouranus). He is in 8th grade. While he acts cool during much of the story, Himeka states that in the past, he was weak and cried frequently, only becoming his present self when he turned ten years old, after knowing who he was. While Himeka loves bugs, Kazune hates and fears them; in Kamichama Karin, Himeka reveals that Kazune`s fear of bugs developed when he and Himeka ran into a giant bug when he was little (which, ironically, was Karin in a bug suit). Even though he is a clone of professor Kazuto Kujyou, he is incomplete and passes out after transforming in god form. He often speaks to Karin in a way that she deems sexist, talking about things like the inherent stupidity or weakness of girls (this is used against him in Chu when Jin calls him a `girly boy`) Kazune is in love with Karin (and tells Michiru such), and has known since the age of ten that Karin is his wife, Suzuka. He himself is the clone of his "father". The older Kazune, Kazuto, put his reseach in Himeka, and then split them in half to protect his work from his former partner, Karasuma Kirihiko.
In Chu, Karin`s and his son, Suzune come from the future. He warns them that Kazune goes missing in the future (with a woman Suzune claims), and later it is discovered that he actually died soon after Suzune was born. When he learns of this, he stays away from Karin, believing what he did was horrible and had caused the future Karin too much trouble. Karin punches him after discovering this was the reason why he avoided her, saying she knew he disappeared in the future but was working hard to change that.</description>
<picture>42315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14628" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="3">4.62</rating>
<name>Kujou Himeka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Himeka is Karin`s friend and Kazune`s "cousin". She is also Suzune`s "sister" due to the fact that she is the child of Suzuka and Kazuto. Originally she contained Kazuto`s god research data, she was then split into two by Kirihiko attempting to steal the research data. One half lives with Kazune, while the other lives with the Karasumas. When one Himeka becomes stronger, the other becomes weaker. Since she was a young girl, she has always defended Kazune, who was a bit of a crybaby when they were little. She loves bugs and is a good cook. She is in 8th grade. Like Karin, she does poorly in school. It is later revealed that she is Kazuto and Suzuka`s daughter. She tells Karin at one point that while she has a strong affection for Kazune, it is not necessarily a romantic attachment, as Kazune is "kind of like a brother and kind of like a dad" to Himeka (referencing Kazune`s identity as a clone of Himeka`s father).
She also witnessed Kazune and Karin kissing in the anime. Later in the series, Kazune says that Himeka is his daughter (along with Karin in Kamichama Karin 7).</description>
<picture>42316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14629" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="2">4.83</rating>
<name>Karasuma Kirio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirio is the main antagonist. He and Kirika are adopted by Kirihiko while they were children. He is the student council president of Sakuragaoka Academy. He tests the protagonists and fights them outside the campus. Karin refers to him as "Mr. Glasses Man" (meganekko), "Four eyes-san" or "Glasses Guy". His only true relative is his twin sister Kirika, but he does have another "sister" by the name of Himeka. In the anime, he is a running gag character; often leaving before ever winning and revealing his plot to Karin and the others while they didn`t know, thinking they did. His ring has the powers of the god Ares. Later in the series, his ring is destroyed by Kazune. He then gets possessed by his father, Kirihiko, by the Zeus ring he wore after his broke, but in the end Karin and Kazune saved him. (Episode 26) He then returns in Chu. Now, with the other Himeka, he is trying to create a new Zeus ring using the `seed of chaos`,in order to save the future Kirika who is sick. To do that, he has to revive his father, whom currently resides within Kuga Jin.</description>
<picture>42317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14630" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="2">3.95</rating>
<name>Karasuma Kirika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirika is Karin`s prince charming. She is Kirio`s twin sister. At first, she does not believe that Karin is a goddess, but comes to believe in it. Kirika is unwillingly forced to fight Karin because of the other Himeka and his brother Kirio. Later on the manga in Volumes 4 and 5, it is revealed to the protagonists that he is a girl. She gives help to Karin and Kazune when her father revives through her brother, Kirio.
In Goddess form, she is Nyx, the goddess that Kirio sent out in the first book to see if Karin was actually a goddess.</description>
<picture>42318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14631" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Nishikiori Michiru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Michiru or Micchi is a fellow student of Karin and at one time lived with her, Kazune and Himeka. He was from England. When he was little, he was involved in an accident that killed his parents and crushed his left eye beyond repair, and almost died. But Kazuto made an eye for Michiru, and saved his life. Since he was in the hospital for a year, he is a year older than Karin, Kazune, and Himeka. Michiru shares a close bond to Kazune, because he first thought of him as Kazuto, and still respects Kazune. In the manga, Michiru`s friend Ami brought a notebook containing information about Himeka for Kazune to read. Michiru is a bit a pervert around Karin, and in the manga, he stole Karin`s first kiss. In Chu, his transformation is the god Neptune.</description>
<picture>42319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101849" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-05">
<name>Nyake</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="402" picture="17249.jpg">Katou Nanae</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="68475" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花鈴ちゃんのふしぎな指輪 だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Karin-chan`s Mysterious Ring</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мистическое кольцо Карин</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karin-chan no Fushigi na Yubiwa Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68476" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花鈴ちゃん, かみちゃまに変神 だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Karin-chan, Transformed to Kamichama</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Карин-чан превращается в Маленькую Богиню</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karin-chan, Kamichama ni Henshin Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68477" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">姫香ちゃんの秘密 だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Himeka-chan`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Секрет Химеки-чан</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himeka-chan no Himitsu Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69134" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しーちゃんとの再会 だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion with Shi-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Воссоединение с Шии-чаном.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi-chan to no Saikai Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="74152" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はっけよい, 踊る学園祭だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hakkeyoi! School Festival Dance</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Приготовились! Танцевальный школьный фестиваль</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakkeyoi, Odoru Gakuensai Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="74153" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">指輪が消えちゃったんだしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ring Has Disappered</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Пропажа кольца</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yubiwa ga Kiechatta Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75094" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なぞの転校生, かっこいいんだしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Transfer Student Is Cool</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Симпатичный мистический новичок</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Tenkousei, Kakkouiin Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75095" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミッチーのドキドキ温泉ツアーだしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Micchi`s Heart Thumping Hot Spring Tour</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Cердце Миччи тянет в Горячий Весенний Тур</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Micchii no Doki-doki Onsen Tour Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75145" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">和音くんの中間テスト大作戦だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kazune-kun`s Big Midterm Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">План Казунэ-куна по экзаменам в середине семестра</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazune-kun no Chuukan Test Daisakusen Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75146" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どすこい, 恋する学園祭だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dosukoi! Love at the School Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Досукой! Любовь, наполнившая школьный фестиваль</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dosukoi, Koi Suru Gakuensai Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75147" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議な光でぴったんこだしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stuck Together by a Mysterious Light</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Склеены вместе Мистическим Светом</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushigi na Hikari de Pittanko Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75148" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アデュー, 花鈴ちゃんの初恋だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adieu, Karin-chan`s First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Adyuu, Karin-chan no Hatsukoi Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75149" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">和音くんとラブラブデート!?だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Love-Love Date with Kazune-kun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazune-kun to Love-Love Date!? Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75150" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渚だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagisa Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80380" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サマータイムブルースだしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Time Blues</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Summer Time Blues Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80381" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレゼントは謎の指輪だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Present Is a Mysterious Ring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Present wa Nazo no Yubiwa Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80382" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧火先輩の告白だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kirika-senpai`s Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirika-senpai no Kokuhaku Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80383" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライバルは和音王子だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rival Is Prince Kazune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rival wa Kazune-ouji Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80384" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の劇場, 待ったなしだしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Romantic Theatre Waits for No One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Gekijou, Mattanashi Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80385" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミッチー, いらっしゃ~い♪だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Micchi, Welcome</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Micchii, Irasshai Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81674" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">姫香ちゃんと占いメガネっ子だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Himeka-chan and the Fortune Telling Mr. Glasses Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himeka-chan to Uranai Meganekko Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81676" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">和音くん? とお祭りだしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kazune-kun? And the Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazune-kun? to Omatsuri Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81682" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">烏丸さんち, お宅はいけんだしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Visit to Karasuma`s House</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karasuma-san`chi, Otaku Haiten Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82846" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あっちもこっちもメガネっ子だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Here, and There, Mr. Glasses Man Is Everywhere</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Acchi mo Kocchi mo Megane-ko Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82847" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゼウスの指輪の迷宮だしー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Labyrinth of Zeus` Ring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zeus no Yubiwa no Meikyuu Dashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82848" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時空の迷い子たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Are Lost in Time`s Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikuu no Mayoigo-tachi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
