<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4897" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-07-27</startdate>
<enddate>2007-11-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Baccano!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Murder Train</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Baccano!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Шумиха!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">باكانو</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Шумотевица!</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Баккано!</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Рейвах!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">baccano</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">バッカーノ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Baccano!</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Baccano!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">永生之酒</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6671" type="Same Setting">Durarara!!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6671" approval="478" total="520">Durarara!!</anime>
<anime id="12014" approval="9" total="19">91 Days</anime>
<anime id="5671" approval="5" total="14">Nijuu-Mensou no Musume</anime>
<anime id="1003" approval="2" total="8">Gungrave</anime>
<anime id="13276" approval="2" total="5">Hakata Tonkotsu Ramens</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="92">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="299453">A masterpiece</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="138110">Nice narrative</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="242358">very nice...(*W*)d</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="485629">I made this account solely to recommend this series.  When trying to tell a friend about it I can only describe it as an anime that successfully pulls off every genre in one package; it is without a doubt the best anime I`ve watched in 10 years (of 23 years total anime watching career)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="279051">This is one of my favorite Animes. I love the characters, the story, and it has the perfect amount of violence/gore. Its an all around good watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="275357">The Better Anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="484118">Brilliant.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="272066">amazingly awesome.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="45296">Story: 11 / 10&lt;br /&gt;Characters: 12 / 10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rating(all in One): 15 / 10&lt;br /&gt;[YES THIS ANIME ROCKS)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First: Many Characters with a different way of Handling things( ^^)&lt;br /&gt;Second: Ubergood Story &amp;gt; Godlike Epic Story&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Third: It`s also very funny, and i warn you if your heart is weak you will probably die from laughing but it`s worth ^^&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WATCH IT OR BE EATEN BY ME or THE RAIL TRACER :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="1294">Interesting way of storytelling paired with good animation and directing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="510860">A good and unique series. The amount of characters, the overlapping and back and forth time frame and events is something that`s not shown in a lot of anime to this degree I think. At face value it looks like a show that`s appealing to kids or young people, but in fact is very violent and gory which is interesting. A definite recommended title &amp; kind of underrated imo.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="321147">this owns</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="634643">“Cool” is probably the most appropriate word to describe Baccano! The slick animation and the catchy music only adds to the overall sexiness of the show. If you want a dash of style and a pinch of epic this season, pick up this anime. There’s comedy; there’s drama. There’s action; there’s romance. All you need now is popcorn and soda.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="330647">Although confusing at first, the plot really begins to shine once you start realising how the pieces fit together. This series was a very, very good laugh, along with decent intrigue and anticipation. A recommended series to watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="14486">pretty awesome</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="128307">Very unique and interesting anime.  Definitely worth a look.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="293910">Intrigant and funny</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="291869">Not bad...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="381652">It takes a very progressive way of storytelling where a large cast of characters are given just enough screen time to leave a lasting impression. The non-linear approach to this series` presentation is meant to push our imagination,make us think and connect the dots on our own and for the whole process to be enjoyable.  

We get to witness and delve deep into each character`s past through a focus lens via interchangeable scenes going back and forth in time.  I found it to be one of the most charming and artistic ways of giving character exposition. 

The story is a rather simple one and the animation is of a very good quality. There is fluent action, plenty of violence and gore(heaps of blood) and plenty of wacky characters(Baccano! = ruckus).  

Don`t let the opening sequence overwhelm you with the large amount of characters. By the end of it you will remember and connect with most of them.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="397570">confusing, refreshing, intelligent, satisfying.&lt;br /&gt;(that was my order, ymmv)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="192240">what a remarkable anime...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="303972">Hilarious at some points, very serious at others. The story is not in chronological order, but it adds to the tension and provides background information.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="217458">The #1 anime on my mylist. Simply brilliant!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="167250">Great anime.!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="68741">Fantastic plot developement</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="262222">trains&lt;br /&gt;comedy&lt;br /&gt;violence&lt;br /&gt;superstition&lt;br /&gt;the search for immortality &lt;br /&gt;and a little romance (as warped as it is)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the only thing missing are robotic maids with super powers.  Maybe not appropriate for 1930`s mafia story.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;this really is a must see&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="363192">WATCH IT!  The show has some of the most awesome action scenes I`ve seen and the story is gorgeous. Albeit difficult to follow until about disc three, but gorgeous. Immortals and bad ass people... Just watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="340000">Baccano is pulpish fiction to the max. if you are used to easy viewing you`ll have a hard time at first, but it`s really worth it. at least once per episode there is a "wtf just happened?!??!??"-moment - but in a good way. it`s definitely an anime you won`t forget that fast (even if you try *g*)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="65577">don`t forget durarara</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="6872">This is the best anime I`ve seen in the past 5 years.
A perfect mix of story, great characters, action and romance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="452346">Great story. But this puzzle showing really confusing. U must have great memory to collect all of them in a complete picture. I don`t, so it wasn`t as enjoyable as it could`ve been.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="464063">This is FANTASTIC!!!! It may be confusing at first but it all comes together at the end. I loved it after the first watch. The second watch made me love it even more since now I could focus on the finer details after knowing the core of the story.It`s a thriller-packed show that you will definitely regret if you miss out!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="535802">Simply one of the best out there. If you haven`t already watched it you should, It`s just that good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="660321">With a very diverse cast of cool characters and an entertaining storyline, this is truly a must-see for anime watchers. I rarely recommend watching anime dubbed in English, but this one has quite possibly the best dub I`ve heard in anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="299976">Unique story that may seem confusing at times but in the end, everything blends together perfectly and the result is a great experience. There`s enough action, violence, drama and romance to make this series appealing to most collectives. Just watch it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="418076">An amazing yet complicated anime. I strongly recommend for mystery and mafia genre fans. Very strong characters and good music. The first episodes may confuse you regarding the plot but everything is made crystal clear in the end..... or not?
Enjoy</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="443546">At first it seemed hard to watch, because it jumps from one year to another. But the last dozen of episodes goes on one breath.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="456856">Awesome! But if you`re going to watch it be prepared to pay attention to details and scenes. this is a story that jumps across all combinations of future, past, and current timelines throughout the story it`s telling. Totally worth it and soooooooooo good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="550129">You may be confused in the beginning but characters, storylines and motives are all parts of one of the best anime plots there is.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="162486">One of mostly well-made story plots ever.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="548309">I don`t generally post here, and I know another glowing review for this show wont do much good, but I should mention that the English Dub is superior to the Jap Dub. They nailed the accents and the emotion runs high. If you ever into Dubs, give this one a shot</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="418191">Amazing and unique anime. I found it hard to follow due to the amount and characters and the storytelling. For me it was a good idea rewatching the 4 first eps. A full rewatch is equally recommended. 100% Must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="468675">a really good anime. a must see!
a bunch of people and how their lifes intersect. with a guiding thread that doesn`t follow the linear course of time, this story grabs more of your interest in each episode.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="591695">DRRR was one of my all time favorites and I thought nothing can match it but Baccano! is definitely on the same level. I`m glad they have kept the same animation staff, music staff etc because you really do feel the similarity between these two yet very unique in its own way!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="563093">Just recently watched this for the second time and It`s even more spectacular than I remember.

The engaging direction, flawless execution and amazing soundtrack—combined with some of the best and most diverse characters I`ve seen—establishes Baccano! as a masterpiece in anime.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.baccano.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6455" type="Original Work">Narita Ryougo</name>
<name id="7428" type="Series Composition">Takagi Noboru</name>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="4147" type="Character Design">Kishida Takahiro</name>
<name id="4359" type="Direction">Oomori Takahiro</name>
<name id="6006" type="Music">Yoshimori Makoto</name>
</creators>
<description>Baccano! (which translates to "ruckus" or "stupid commotion") focuses on the stories of different characters in the Prohibition Era of America. Originating back to 1711, a group of alchemists seeking eternal youth are given a special potion by a mysterious demon, making them immortal. However, alchemists began disappearing, and realizing the danger of being close to one another they scatter around the world.
Now in the 1930`s, all of the immortals have come together once again. Baccano! tells the stories of each of these immortals, ranging from alchemists, street gangs, thieves, FBI agents and even the mafia.
Source: Absolute Anime
Note: the 3 special episodes that were included with the DVD releases directly continue the story of the TV series.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="8158">8.59</permanent>
<temporary count="8257">8.42</temporary>
<review count="10">8.68</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221565.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7492</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2251</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3901</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3946</identifier>
<identifier>fhjkbs</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.baccano.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Baccano!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>バッカーノ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>590</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327830</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9072</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2048</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/baccano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10091</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10902</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1286" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-28">
<name>megalomaniac</name>
<description>Megalomania is a psychopathological condition characterized by delusional fantasies of power, relevance, and omnipotence, and by inflated self-esteem.&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>70559.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1999" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-29">
<name>tomboy</name>
<description>A girl who acts and dresses like a boy and enjoys rough, noisy activities traditionally associated with boys.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2131" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-19">
<name>psychotic</name>
<description>People suffering from psychosis can be described as having lost their contact with reality and deteriorated their social functioning to the point of becoming deranged. Sometimes, these people will try to achieve some absurd goal through trampling on other people, and that`s the point they become villains. Usually, psychotic villains will not show themselves to suffer from mental disorders at first, and will seem like completely normal people; however, as their story unfolds and the show progresses towards its climax, it is usual to have psychotic villains become more and more deranged, to the point of being best described by "batshit insane".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2689" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-02">
<name>1920s</name>
<description>During the 1920s, we had gangsters, Mafia, alcohol, and gambling prohibition.
The Corleones ruled that time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3487" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-18">
<name>talks too fast</name>
<description>This character speaks with a pace so frenetic that it can get hard to follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3823" parentid="6348" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-03">
<name>recap in opening</name>
<description>A short recap of the previous episode(s) is included in the opening sequence. This can result in an opening longer than the traditional 1m30s.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3934" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-10">
<name>non-linear</name>
<description>The story is told achronologically.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4558" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-12">
<name>long time span</name>
<description>The anime spans a much longer than usual (for that genre) period of time, typically several years (possibly decades or even centuries).
Example: In a school setting this could mean the character development is followed from school through college right into working life and the founding of a family with children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5119" parentid="2812" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Chicago</name>
<description>Chicago, officially the City of Chicago, is the third-most populous city in the United States. It is the county seat of Cook County. The Chicago metropolitan area, often referred to as Chicagoland, has nearly 10 million people and is the third-largest in the United States. Chicago has often been called a global architecture capital and is considered one of the most important business centers in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214272.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5553" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-31">
<name>twisted love</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5649" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>jazz</name>
<description>A style of music originating in the Southern USA in the early 20th century, emerging from Blues and Ragtime. Jazz is often associated with the city of New Orleans.
Jazz music is typified by improvisation and syncopation.
Instruments often associated with Jazz are the trumpet, trombone, piano and clarinet.
The anime features a vast amount of jazz, or the theme revolves around it.</description>
<picurl>10253.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6348" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2015-02-19">
<name>old animetags - OP ED</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1774" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="117">8.26</rating>
<name>Chane Laforet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mute daughter of Huey Laforet and an excellent knife fighter. She joins her father`s followers in holding the passengers of the Flying Pussyfoot hostage, despite claiming to disapprove of such acts. She can communicate telepathically with Huey, though it is unknown whether the ability is hers, his, or mutual. Chane is devoted to her father, believing him to be the only person to ever love her. She later tells Claire to find her in Manhattan, saying she would always be waiting. It is revealed that, when offered anything for keeping Huey`s secrets, she asked him to take her voice so that she would never betray him, something Huey finds highly interesting. After the kindness of Jacuzzi and his gang, and Claire`s continued professions of love, her world begins to open up past the one that just included herself and Huey.</description>
<picture>16378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1775" type="main character in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="231">8.69</rating>
<name>Isaac Dian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isaac is an idiot thief who owes his success to the insanity of his crimes (i.e. stealing non-valuable items such as chocolate, or breaking into a watch shop to "steal time") and the garish costumes he habitually wears, leading witnesses to assume that he is a performer of sorts rather than a thief. He is in love with his partner-in-crime, Miria. He becomes immortal in 1930, after drinking the immortality liquor.</description>
<picture>16352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1776" type="main character in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="242">8.52</rating>
<name>Miria Harvent</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another idiot thief, she is the partner and lover of Isaac Dian. Miria wholeheartedly believes and supports everything Isaac says, often even going so far as to mimic his body language. She also unintentionally becomes an immortal in 1930. Together they appear extremely stupid, whimsical and oblivious, but they have great affection for the people they meet—whom they always make a big impression on—and always believe the best of them.</description>
<picture>16353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="410" picture="228116.jpg">Aoki Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1777" type="main character in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="75">7.81</rating>
<name>Firo Prochainezo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Firo is a Camorra member that is an exceptionally skilled fighter. He is a good friend of the Gandors and Claire. Like a number of cast members, he becomes immortal in 1930, by drinking the liquor of immortality brewed by Barnes when the elixir is mistaken for a celebratory bottle of alcohol. Mistakenly sent to Alcatraz prison in 1934, along with Isaac.
He falls in love with Ennis, later "eating" Szilard to save her from death.</description>
<picture>16354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1778" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="25">6.81</rating>
<name>Maiza Avaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Camorra member and one of the original immortals. He was the alchemist who summoned the demon aboard the Advena Avis, and in turn the only one given knowledge of the immortality elixir`s recipe. His younger brother, Gerd, was one of the first to be "eaten" for knowledge of the elixir`s recipe. Despite being a mafia member, he does not advocate violence, and is rather tenderhearted. Maiza perenially wears a kind expression.</description>
<picture>16355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1779" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-27">
<rating votes="65">8.06</rating>
<name>Ennis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Szilard`s homunculus, although not his first creation. She was created as his subordinate, and is supposed to have no thoughts or emotion when executing his commands; recently, however, she has been gaining more human emotions, as well as independent thought. Eventually, she helps Firo by giving him the necessary knowledge to destroy Szilard.</description>
<picture>191865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1780" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="11">2.64</rating>
<name>Keith Gandor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keith is a mafia boss that perpetually scowls and remains silent throughout the series. He and his brothers all become immortal in 1930.</description>
<picture>16357.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1781" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="15">3.60</rating>
<name>Berga Gandor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Berga is a very large and violent Mafia boss who enjoys softening up other thugs for Mr. Tick.</description>
<picture>16358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1782" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="32">7.37</rating>
<name>Luck Gandor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Luck Gandor and his two brothers lead the Gandor Family; he is almost always seen with a quaint smile. He is a good friend of Firo`s, thus his family has a close relationship with the Martillo`s because of this. Luck is professional, but in accordance with his profession, is merciless against those that do his "family" harm.</description>
<picture>16360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1783" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="21">2.93</rating>
<name>Szilard Quates</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An immortal alchemist who is seeking the recipe of the immortality elixir. The first among the alchemists on the Advena Avis to gain immortality, he went on a killing spree soon after, "eating" many fellow alchemists, including Maiza`s brother, thereby obtaining part of the elixir`s recipe. Using this incomplete formula, Szilard developed a potion that created "quasi-immortals" capable of healing from any wound, but still susceptible to ageing and being "eaten" by full Immortals. He created Ennis as a homunculus. Despite having the body of an old man, Szilard is exceptionally fast and strong, capable of defeating most opponents in physical combat. By the 1930s, Szilard has tracked down and "eaten"` eighteen of the original Advena Avis immortals.</description>
<picture>16361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1784" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="31">4.80</rating>
<name>Czeslaw Meyer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young boy who gained immortality aboard the Advena Avis. Because of the way his guardian treated him, he is extremely afraid of the other immortals and wants to "eat" them all before they can "eat" him.</description>
<picture>16362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1785" type="main character in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="28">2.12</rating>
<name>Dallas Genoard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dallas is a small-time thug and brother of Eve Genoard. After Isaac and Miria steal his family`s fortune, Dallas goes on a string of robberies with his friends, and getting mixed up with Szilard`s plans. He and his group are later captured by Szilard, and made into quasi-immortals (they can`t be killed, but they do age). Dallas goes looking for revenge with his newfound powers, but eventually gets captured by the Gandors, cemented in a steel barrel, and dropped to the bottom of the Hudson river. Eve later agrees to allow him to be dredged up and experimented on, believing it preferable to his spending the rest of his life drowning and reviving.</description>
<picture>16365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1786" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="25">5.00</rating>
<name>Eve Genoard</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eve is the little sister of Dallas Genoard. Despite her quiet personality and aristocratic upbringing, Eve has very little fear of the New York streets, going directly against the mafia as she searches for her brother. Eve truly believes that Dallas has a kind heart. She also allows Isaac and Miria to steal the family fortune when others are fighting over it.</description>
<picture>16363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1787" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="85">8.19</rating>
<name>Nice Holystone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Explosive expert with a mellow disposition. Nice makes top-notch explosives, but lost her right eye and has extensive scarring on her body from an accident with her homemade explosives when she was a child. She and Jacuzzi are childhood friends, she explains that they`ve been "together" for 10 years.</description>
<picture>16369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1788" type="main character in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="103">5.71</rating>
<name>Jacuzzi Splot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A crybaby who is nonetheless capable of exceptional courage and leadership ability when the situation calls for it. At first, Jacuzzi seems almost cripplingly shy, even with a tendency to stutter in front of strangers. However, when his loved ones are in danger, he will summon the strength to face his problems directly, even though he`ll continue to cry. After a member of his gang was killed, Jacuzzi robbed a record number of neighbourhood stores, clutching a machine gun as tears stream down his face. Jacuzzi went out and received his "sword tattoo" on his face when Nice was injured in an explosives accident,so that they would both be similarly marked.</description>
<picture>16370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1789" type="main character in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="116">7.78</rating>
<name>Ladd Russo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ladd is a sadistic hitman for the Russo family. His love for acts of violence truly shows in the maniacal glee he exhibits while fighting or killing. He is exceptionally skilled in hand-to-hand combat—particularly boxing—and the use of firearms. Ladd is deeply in love with his fiancée, Lua, although he expresses it through a passionate promise to kill her someday. After the Flying Pussyfoot incident, is thrown into Alcatraz prison for murder of the majority of the deceased on board the Flying Pussyfoot, despite pleading not guilty, the murders being in self-defence. This is technically true, since only one civilian was killed, and was killed by Dune, one of Ladd`s accomplices.</description>
<picture>16371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1790" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="36">3.31</rating>
<name>Lua Klein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ladd`s lover and fiancée. She is fair-haired and beautiful, despite sporting a somewhat vacant (albeit serene) expression. She is completely devoted to Ladd and is likely a masochist, as she seems to take pleasure in his promise that he will be the one to kill her.</description>
<picture>16372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="412" picture="25833.jpg">Yasui Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1791" type="appears in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="7">4.37</rating>
<name>Sylvie Lumiere</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the original members of the Advena Avis. She is the only one who does not drink the immortality elixir immediately and instead saves her portion in a bottle. She was the lover of Maiza`s brother, Gerd. By the 1930s, she became a lounge singer.</description>
<picture>16373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1792" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="21">2.65</rating>
<name>Huey Laforet</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The father of Chane Laforet and one of the first to gain immortality on the Advena Avis, he is currently imprisoned by a government organisation in Newfoundland. He has an avid following who go to great lengths to free him, including taking an entire train hostage in exchange for their leader`s freedom. Huey does not agree with their methods and is aware that some of his followers only wish for the secret of his immortality.</description>
<picture>16374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1793" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="30">7.16</rating>
<name>Rachel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A woman working for Daily Days information center. She sneaks on board the Flying Pussyfoot to collect information. She survives the train incident and reveals some important aspects of the incident on the train. She is later approached by Czeslaw, who offers to tell her everything about immortality.</description>
<picture>16375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1794" type="main character in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="158">8.63</rating>
<name>Claire Stanfield</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Claire was raised with the Gandor brothers, and as such, is a part of the family. Claire is now an assassin named Vino—Spanish for "wine"—earning the name because of his predilection for mutilating the bodies of his victims beyond recognition, which usually leaves him covered in a thick layer of blood. A former trapeze artist, he now works undercover as a conductor on the Flying Pussyfoot, and later happily takes on the persona of the vengeful "Rail Tracer" monster. Claire is a thorough-going solipsist who believes that the world is a show put on for him, and that he has complete control over it. He proposes to Chane at their first meeting, and searches for her in Manhattan in 1932. He finds her after clearing his contract with the Gandor family, assassinating members of the Runorata family for them.</description>
<picture>16376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1795" type="appears in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="6">6.68</rating>
<name>Chick Jefferson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young man always seen smiling with a pair of scissors. Helps out in the Gandor family by `taking care` of their enemies.</description>
<picture>16377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15110" type="appears in" update="2010-02-21">
<rating votes="6">6.07</rating>
<name>Gustave St. Germain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Vice-President of the Daily Days newspaper company is called Gustave St. Germain and as the plot revolves around immortal, it may be possible he is Count of St.Germain, being based on him, and also the possibility of him being the true main character, as noted in the first episode`s title.</description>
<picture>43268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17316" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="8">5.14</rating>
<name>Carol</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s the assistant of Daily Days` Vice-Director http://anidb.net/ch15110 [Gustave St. Germain].</description>
<picture>47260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17317" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-01">
<rating votes="8">1.64</rating>
<name>Gustavo Bagetta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47261.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3441" picture="149777.jpg">Sasaki Seiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17318" type="appears in" update="2011-09-19">
<rating votes="3">1.64</rating>
<name>Bartolo Runorata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bartolo Runorata is the boss of the Runorata family.</description>
<picture>48005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3383" picture="24325.jpg">Oobayashi Ryuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17319" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Bill Sullivan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>FBI Special Investigator</description>
<picture>47988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17321" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Edward Noa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He`s also an Investigator for the FBI alongside Bill Sullivan.</description>
<picture>66691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2339" picture="151715.jpg">Taketora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17378" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Roufujin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="344" picture="2116.gif">Matsushima Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17379" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="3">2.27</rating>
<name>Rou Shinshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3064" picture="24692.jpg">Asou Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17380" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="4">3.38</rating>
<name>Nicholas Wayne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3124" picture="24096.jpg">Furusawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17382" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="3">2.05</rating>
<name>Pezzo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42817" picture="90853.jpg">Kobushi Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17383" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="2">2.02</rating>
<name>Randy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5400" picture="29628.jpg">Souma Yukito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17386" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="2">4.37</rating>
<name>Nick</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4726" picture="54694.jpg">Kawamoto Kunihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17387" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="11">3.41</rating>
<name>Donnie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47337.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="376" picture="53996.jpg">Sonobe Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17388" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="5">2.79</rating>
<name>Samatha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2460" picture="22350.jpg">Nagasawa Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17389" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="2">2.02</rating>
<name>Barnes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17390" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="4">3.24</rating>
<name>Erean Dooger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17391" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="3">2.70</rating>
<name>Placido Russo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3356" picture="24386.jpg">Kamei Saburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17395" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="5">2.50</rating>
<name>Natalie Beriam</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47348.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17396" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="7">2.75</rating>
<name>Goose Perkins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47349.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17397" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<rating votes="5">2.50</rating>
<name>Mary Beriam</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47350.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17647" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="3">2.50</rating>
<name>Gretto Avaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17648" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="8">4.70</rating>
<name>Elmer C Albatros</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2071" picture="74324.jpg">Oohata Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17650" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="6">1.47</rating>
<name>Fermeto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17651" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Nile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="377" picture="17223.jpg">Sakaguchi Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17652" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="3">2.27</rating>
<name>Shochou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head of Police</description>
<picture>47989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2573" picture="240892.jpg">Shirokuma Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17657" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="3">1.85</rating>
<name>Nenpai no Shashou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elderly (Train) Conductor</description>
<picture>47994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4726" picture="54694.jpg">Kawamoto Kunihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17658" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="2">2.02</rating>
<name>Dune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17681" picture="47308.jpg">Okada Sanri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17660" type="appears in" update="2010-06-02">
<rating votes="3">1.57</rating>
<name>Manfred Beriam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="242" picture="238968.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17663" type="appears in" update="2011-09-19">
<rating votes="5">3.38</rating>
<name>Lia Linshan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lia Linshan is a waitress at a Marillo family speakeasy.</description>
<picture>48003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18025" picture="183213.jpg">Matsuzaki Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17665" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Kanshichirou Yaguruma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="385" picture="215702.jpg">Tsukada Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17666" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="4">2.46</rating>
<name>Ronny Skiatto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17667" type="appears in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="17">5.00</rating>
<name>Graham Spector</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17678" type="appears in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Fan Linshan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6918" picture="222918.jpg">Densaka Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17679" type="appears in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="3">5.28</rating>
<name>Youn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="378" picture="46436.jpg">Oota Tetsuharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17703" type="appears in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="2">2.02</rating>
<name>Spike</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3845" picture="25484.jpg">Nishimoto Riichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17704" type="appears in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="3">2.85</rating>
<name>Benjamin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6082" picture="222919.jpg">Hirano Toshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17708" type="appears in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="2">3.22</rating>
<name>D.D. Shinbunsha Shachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The director of the Daily Days Newspaper Agency. His face is never shown, instead a desk with a big pile of books and papers, where he must sit behind.</description>
<picture>48053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17709" type="appears in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="4">4.80</rating>
<name>Kakuzatou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kakuzatou, meaning cube sugar, is just a nickname for this man who`s been seen eating cubed sugar like normal candy.</description>
<picture>48055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17710" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="2">4.28</rating>
<name>Martillo Family</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>66699.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17711" type="appears in" update="2011-09-19">
<rating votes="2">2.02</rating>
<name>Morsa Martillo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morsa Martillo is the boss of the Martillo family.</description>
<picture>66693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3102" picture="24178.jpg">Chou Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17712" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="2">3.52</rating>
<name>Gandor Family</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>66704.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17713" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="2">1.90</rating>
<name>Russo Family</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>66703.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17714" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="3">2.27</rating>
<name>Shaft</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17715" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="2">1.90</rating>
<name>Runorata Family</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>66705.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17716" type="appears in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<name>Jacuzzi Ichimi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Jacuzzi Gang.</description>
</character>
<character id="17717" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<name>Daily Days Shinbunsha</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>66701.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29331" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Begg Garotto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46781" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Federal Bureau of Investigation (Baccano!)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="50157" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Lemures</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="73746" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="43">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">副社長は自身が主役である可能性について語らない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Vice President Doesn`t Say Anything About the Possibility of Him Being the Main Character</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Vice-Diretor Não Fala Sobre A Possibilidade Dele Mesmemo Ser O Protagonista!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushachou wa Jishin ga Shuyaku de Aru Kanousei ni Tsuite Kataranai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73747" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="36">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">老婦人の不安をよそに大陸横断鉄道[フライング・プッシーフット号]は出発する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Setting the Old Woman`s Qualms Aside, the Flying Pussyfoot Departs</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Ignorando A Ansiedade Da Velha Mulher, Flying Pussyfoot Parte!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roufujin no Fuan o Yoso ni Flying Pussyfoot Gou wa Shuppatsu Suru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73748" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="33">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ランディとペッチョはパーティの準備で忙しい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Randy and Pecho Are Busy Getting Ready for the Party</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Randy E Pezzo Estão Ocupados Com Os Preparativos Para A Festa!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Randy to Pecho wa Party no Junbi de Isogashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73749" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="32">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラッド・ルッソは大いに語り大いに殺戮を楽しむ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ladd Russo Enjoys Talking a Lot and Slaughtering a Lot</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Ladd Russo Curte Falar Muito E Matar Muito!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ladd Russo wa Ooini Katari Ooini Satsuriku o Tanoshimu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73750" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="31">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャグジー・スプロットは泣いて怯えて蛮勇を奮う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jacuzzi Splot Cries, Gets Scared and Musters Reckless Valor</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Jacuzzi Splot Chora E Está Assustado, Ainda Assim Mostra Coragem Impulsiva!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jacuzzi Splot wa Naite Obiete Ban`yuu o Furuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73751" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="30">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レイルトレーサーは車内を暗躍し虐殺をくりかえす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rail Tracer Covertly, Repeatedly Slaughters Inside the Coaches</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Perseguidor Dos Trilhos Continua Secretamente Matando Pessoas No Trem!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rail Tracer wa Shanai o Anyakushi Gyakusatsu o Kurikaesu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73752" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="29">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すべてはアドウェナ・アウィス号の船上からはじまる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everything Starts Aboard the Advenna Avis</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Tudo Tem Início A Bordo Do Advena Avis!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subete wa Advenna Avis Gou no Senjou kara Hajimaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73753" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="32">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイザックとミリアは我知らず周囲に幸福をまきちらす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Isaac and Miria Unintentionally Spread Happiness Around Them</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Isaac E Miria Espalham Alegria Sem Perceber!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isaac to Miria wa Wareshirazu Shuui ni Koufuku o Makichirasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73754" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="27">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クレア・スタンフィールドは忠実に職務を遂行する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Claire Stanfield Faithfully Carries Out the Mission</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Claire Stanfield Cumpre Sua Tarefa Com Fé!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Claire Stanfield wa Chuujitsu ni Shokumu o Suikousuru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73755" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="27">6.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チェスワフ・メイエルは不死者の影に怯え策略をめぐらせる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Czeslaw Meyer Is Forced to Rework His Tremble-Before-the-Specter-of-Immortals Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Czeslaw Meyers Tem Medo Da Sombra De Um Imortal E Reflete Sobre Seu Plano!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Czeslaw Meyer wa Fushisha no Kage ni Obie Sakuryaku o Meguraseru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73756" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="28">8.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャーネ・ラフォレットは二人の怪人を前に沈黙する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chane Laforet Remains Silent in the Face of Two Mysterious People</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Chane Laforet É Silenciosa Diante Das Duas Pessoas Misteriosas!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chane Laforet wa Futari no Kaijin o Mae ni Chinmoku Suru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73757" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="29">8.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フィーロとガンドール三兄弟は凶弾に倒れる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Firo and the Three Gandor Brothers Are Felled by Assassins` Bullets</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Firo E Os Irmãos Gandor Caem Sob Balas Assassinas!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Firo to Gandor Sankyoudai wa Kyoudan ni Taoreru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73758" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="33">8.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不死者もそうでない者もひとしなみに人生を謳歌する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Both the Immortals and Those Who Aren`t Sing the Praises of Life Equally</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Aqueles Que São Imortais E Aqueles Que Não São Aproveitam A Vida Igualmente!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushisha mo Sou de Nai Mono mo Hitoshi Nami ni Jinsei o Ouka Suru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79784" update="2007-07-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="5">1.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80293" update="2007-07-19">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88250" update="2010-09-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88251" update="2010-09-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88259" update="2008-02-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14 preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88824" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="28">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グラハム・スペクターの愛と平和</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graham Specter`s Love and Peace</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Graham Spector É Paz E Amor!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Graham Specter no Ai to Heiwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88825" update="2008-03-17">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88826" update="2008-03-17">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90355" update="2018-10-29">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="23">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">物語に終わりがあってはならないことを キャロルは悟った</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Carol Realises That the Story Cannot Have an Ending</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Carole Percebe Que Pode Não Existir Um Fim Para A História!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monogatari ni Owari ga Atte wa Naranai Koto o Carol wa Satotta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90356" update="2018-10-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高級住宅街に辿り着いた不良少年たちはそれでもいつもと変わらない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Delinquents That Arrive at the High-Class Neighborhood Are the Same as Always</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Os Jovens Delinquëntes Que Chegaram no Luxuoso Bairro Residencial Ainda São Os Mesmos De Sempre!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukyuu Juutakugai ni Tadoritsuita Furyou Shounen-tachi wa Soredemo Itsumo to Kawaranai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129155" update="2011-04-04">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2008-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extra 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129156" update="2011-04-04">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2008-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extra 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129157" update="2011-04-04">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2008-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extra 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129158" update="2011-04-04">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2008-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extra 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129159" update="2011-04-04">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2008-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extra 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129160" update="2011-04-04">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2007-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extra 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129161" update="2011-04-04">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2007-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extra 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129162" update="2011-04-04">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2007-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extra 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129163" update="2011-04-04">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2007-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extra 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
