<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4901" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>49</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-02-04</startdate>
<enddate>2008-01-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yes! Precure 5</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Yes!プリキュア5</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">光之美少女 第5季</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">precure5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">YPC5</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Yes! プリキュア5</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Yes! Pretty Cure 5</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5593" type="Sequel">Yes! Precure 5 Go Go!</anime>
<anime id="1413" type="Same Setting">Futari wa Precure</anime>
<anime id="5572" type="Side Story">Eiga Yes! Precure 5: Kagami no Kuni no Miracle Daibouken!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="54433">Excellent Magical Girl anime, the best of the last 5 years i think</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="130582">Part of the Best of all precure follow on by HeartCatch Precure. If you like hero character being seen by public or such like identity secret being found out by other, is a must see</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/yes_precure5/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1834" type="Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="996" type="Work">Asatsu-DK</name>
<name id="3328" type="Character Design">Kawamura Toshie</name>
<name id="6233" type="Direction">Komura Toshiaki</name>
<name id="2808" type="Original Work">Toudou Izumi</name>
<name id="4131" type="Music">Satou Naoki</name>
<name id="2169" type="Series Composition">Narita Yoshimi</name>
<name id="1119" type="Work">Asahi Housou</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch9361 [Yumehara Nozomi], a regular student, finds a magical book called the Dream Collet in the library and meets Coco and Nuts, two creatures from the Palmier Kingdom. They plead with Nozomi to restore their world, which has been destroyed by an organization called the Nightmares, by completing the Dream Collet and finding the 55 Pinkies to make any wish come true. Meanwhile, the Nightmares are moving into the real world. Once Nozomi agrees to help, Coco and Nuts transform her into the magical girl Cure Dream and turn four fellow students into her Pretty Cure team.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="181">5.63</permanent>
<temporary count="182">6.68</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>28057.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7465</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1932</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3938</identifier>
<identifier>clzlbp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://asahi.co.jp/precure5/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/yes_precure5/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Yes!_PreCure_5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Yes!_プリキュア5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1089</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326871</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8789</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1816" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-09">
<name>uniform -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>The "uniform" tag is to be split and removed. Please help by tagging the character with the appropriate kind of uniform (e.g. school uniform, maid dress, etc) and removing this tag from them, and by not adding this tag to any further characters. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3824" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-05">
<name>sentai</name>
<description>In Japanese, sentai is a military unit, and may be translated as "squadron", "task force", "group" or "wing". In the anime fandom, however, it usually refers to the Super Sentai Series, a long-running superhero team franchise of http://anidb.net/t5000 [tokusatsu] shows featuring live action characters and colorful special effects, and other similar shows. A prominent characteristic of such shows is that the colour- and elemental-coded heroes, usually numbering around five or more, fight to save the world from the evil that terrorizes the area, which may even span the entire universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4110" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>life force</name>
<description>Life force exists in many forms and is known under many names. It is the invisible fuel that runs human bodies and is resistent against scientific research and explanation. However, this very energy is one of the most powerful forces in the universe. Especially in mahou shoujo anime, the big bad evil will always try to steal it for their plans, bad guys from outer space will need it as food and even the good guys will often use their life force to bring back dead to life again, eventually sacrificing their life in the course of such an event.
Other energy sources known to mankind are the power of love and the power of friendship.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9361" type="main character in" update="2012-02-10">
<rating votes="29">6.31</rating>
<name>Yumehara Nozomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A second-year student at L`École des Cinq Lumières Middle School, Nozomi appears to be a typical shoujo heroine, and does not know what to do with her life. Her father works as an author of children`s stories and her mother runs a beauty shop. She has a habit of saying "It`s decided!" when she decides on something not exactly with everyone`s permission. Formed a crush on Coco (in his human form) at first sight, and her feelings grow as the series progresses. This also has started a love triangle between her and Milk for Coco, because both have feelings for him. Though her teammates are vastly different from her, Nozomi learns how to become their friend, and their leader. Cure Dream wears pink, and her costume has a design resembling that of Cure Rouge. Her given name is pronounced, though not written, the same way as the Japanese word for hope, nozomi, and part of her surname (yume) means "dream" in Japanese. According to the release date of the movie Yes Precure 5 Gogo Happy Birthday in the Land of Sweets, Nozomi`s birthday is 8th November.
She introduces herself as "Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!"
In the first movie, her counterpart is Dark Dream, who is voiced by Nishimura Chinami. In the second movie, she gets a power-up: Shining Dream.</description>
<picture>81332.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9362" type="main character in" update="2012-02-10">
<rating votes="58">7.87</rating>
<name>Cure Dream</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9363" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="25">8.56</rating>
<name>Natsuki Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This second-year student appears as a tomboy and plays enough sports to have every team clamouring for her to join them, but indulges in a few feminine pursuits, such as a love of boys. She has a very straightforward and down-to-earth personality that sharply contrasts with the cheery and optimistic Nozomi. Her parents run a flower shop. Rin wears red-orange, and she transforms into Cure Rouge; her counterpart is her best friend, Cure Dream. She introduces herself as "Red Flame of Passionate, Cure Rouge!"</description>
<picture>81324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9364" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="10">2.14</rating>
<name>Cure Rouge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9365" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="34">5.68</rating>
<name>Kasugano Urara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urara is the youngest member of the Pretty Cure. She is a sweet blonde first-year and a transfer student. She puts on a smiling face to all, but can only be herself around Nozomi and her friends. Because she is always busy and is now acting in a TV drama, she has no friends outside of the Cures. Before she joined the team, she learned of Nozomi`s and Rin`s identities, and was not nearly as shocked as the others, likely because the drama that she had been cast in appears to be based on the Splash Star series. Her mom died when she was young. She is half Japanese (from her mom) and half French (from her dad). Cure Lemonade wears yellow and has no counterpart. She introduces herself as "Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!"</description>
<picture>81320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9366" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="15">8.36</rating>
<name>Cure Lemonade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9367" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="27">5.72</rating>
<name>Akimoto Komachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another third-year, Komachi is kind and shy, and likes to read books and write. However, once she is angered enough, she will snap and release her temper. Along with her best friend Karen, Komachi is also a popular senior at her school. She is a volunteer at the school library, along with Karen/Cure Aqua, and often spends her time there writing stories. Her dream is to become a writer, and she exhibits particular talent in this: Nuts praised her first completed story (upon the 7th revision), and he does not give praise lightly. She has romantic feelings for Nuts, which she expresses in the form of her second novel. Her parents own a traditional Japanese sweetshop.
The green-clad Cure Mint is the counterpart of Cure Aqua. Fans noted that her appearance is similar to Lettuce Midorikawa of Tokyo Mew Mew. She introduces herself as "Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!"</description>
<picture>81329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9368" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="17">7.03</rating>
<name>Cure Mint</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another third-year, Komachi is kind and shy, and likes to read books and write. However, once she is angered enough, she will snap and release her temper. Along with her best friend Karen, Komachi is also a popular senior at her school. She is a volunteer at the school library, along with Karen/Cure Aqua, and often spends her time there writing stories. Her dream is to become a writer, and she exhibits particular talent in this: Nuts praised her first completed story (upon the 7th revision), and he does not give praise lightly. She has romantic feelings for Nuts, which she expresses in the form of her second novel. Her parents own a traditional Japanese sweetshop.
The green-clad Cure Mint is the counterpart of Cure Aqua. Fans noted that her appearance is similar to Lettuce Midorikawa of Tokyo Mew Mew. She introduces herself as "Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!"</description>
<picture>81328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9380" type="main character in" update="2012-02-10">
<rating votes="16">7.43</rating>
<name>Minazuki Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karen is the oldest member of the team. This third-year student comes from an affluent family and is a member of the student council. Her parents are musicians and often go on tour. She misses them, but will not ask for them to come home for fear of disturbing their work, so despite wealth and popularity, she is often lonely. Komachi is her best friend and a fellow student council member.
Seen around school as cool and inspiring, most of the students look up to her. She, as Nozomi learns, is the most trustworthy Cure. In the beginning, she is reluctant to join the Cure team. In episode 6, as the girls are being manhandled, Karen stands up to her friends, vowing to protect them regardless of transformation. The butterfly that eluded her previously reappears and successfully lands on her wrist, enabling her to transform to Cure Aqua. As Cure Aqua; counterpart of Cure Mint, she wears deep blue in her outfit, resembling Cure Mint`s outfit. She introduces herself as "Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!" Like Nozomi and Komachi with Coco and Nuts respectively, she has a special bond with Milk.</description>
<picture>81330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9381" type="main character in" update="2012-02-10">
<rating votes="14">7.23</rating>
<name>Cure Aqua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9384" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="7">1.63</rating>
<name>Coco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the mascot creatures from the Palmier Kingdom, Coco is a yellow-furred tanuki searching for the Dream Collet to restore his kingdom. He can transform into a human, and later becomes a teacher at Nozomi`s school to keep watch of her. Coco has expressed that he has strong feelings for Nozomi, but is hesitant to act on them because of the knowledge that they will have to go their separate ways as soon as his kingdom is restored. Fittingly, his human name "Kokoda" sounds like the way one would say "I`m Coco" in Japanese.
Halfway through the series, it is revealed that he and Nuts are actually princes from separate parts of the Palmier Kingdom.
He is given Palmier`s crown in episode 24 of Yes! PreCure 5 GoGo, allowing PreCure 5 to use Cure Fleur. Both he and Nuts combine powers in GoGo episode 38 to allow Cure Dream and Milky Rose to combine powers.</description>
<picture>81314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9385" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Kokoda Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Coco`s human form as teacher at Nozomi`s school.</description>
<picture>81312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9386" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="7">1.63</rating>
<name>Nuts</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The other creature from the Palmier Kingdom, Nuts is a brown squirrel that can transform into a human, the clerk of a jewelry shop called Nuts House. In the beginning of the series, he is sealed within the Dream Collet and was freed after the 5 Cures received their powers. Coco describes him as a good friend, comparable to the relationship between Nozomi and Rin. In Episode 7 Nuts is released from the Dream Collet and is revealed to have an aloof, somewhat cold personality. Because of the events of his past he has difficulty trusting anyone, and did not trust Coco at first. His human form is so good looking that it causes the other Pretty Cure girls to blush, as well as most other girls who see him.
Komachi exhibits romantic feelings for Nuts, and though his stoicism does not make him an easy character to read, it is made clear that he feels a special bond with Komachi.
He is given Palmier`s crown in episode 31 of Yes! PreCure 5 GoGo, allowing Milky Rose to use the Milky Mirror. Both he and Coco combine powers in GoGo episode 38 to allow Cure Dream and Milky Rose to combine powers.</description>
<picture>81316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9387" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="4">1.63</rating>
<name>Natts</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nuts` human form as the clerk of a jewelry shop called Nuts House.</description>
<picture>81317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14710" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="6">2.14</rating>
<name>Milk</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Debuts in episode 21. A white-and-pink lop rabbit who, unlike Nuts and Coco, is unable to transform into a human. Milk and Nozomi are always in constant disagreements over food, especially chocolate. In Gogo she obtained the ability to turn into a human, her alias Kurumi Mimino, after picking up a glowing blue seed in episode 7. Milk may also have a crush on Coco, as she has shown affection around him, and is jealous when Nozomi shows affection to him.
Like Coco is close to Nozomi and Nuts is close to Komachi, Milk and Karen share a close friendship.</description>
<picture>42383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14711" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Girinma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The first of the villains to appear. He can transform into a deadly praying mantis with arms that slice. He greatly fears his superiors, and is often threatened by Bunbee. In his human form, he wears a hat and holds a cane.</description>
<picture>42385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14712" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Gamao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A large man that resembles a hobo. He is seen to be extremely lazy and often refuses to do any work, even if his survival and duty as a Nightmare depend on it. He transforms into a toad. His name is from the Japanese "gama", meaning toad. In his human form he looks very fat.</description>
<picture>42386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14713" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Arachnea</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The lone woman of the team, she resembles Poisony from the first season. She transforms into a spider. Many episodes featuring her have her pulling the girls into the sewers to fight, for reasons unknown. Her name is based on the Greek "arachne" (spider). In her human form she has short light purple hair and wears a red office dress.</description>
<picture>42387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2049" picture="228615.jpg">Soumi Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14714" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="6">5.09</rating>
<name>Bunbee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The boss of Girinma, Gamao and Arachnea. He transforms into a bee. For the first part of the series he was believed to be leading the Nightmares, but it is soon revealed that he takes orders from Kawarino. He joined Eternal in the sequel after surviving a fatal fall near the end of the prequel.</description>
<picture>42388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14715" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Kawarino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Desparaia`s secretary. He conveys her intentions and orders to other Nightmares, and report to her on the missions. Most of the other Nightmares fear him. His name is a play on the Japanese word "kawari" which means substitute.</description>
<picture>42389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1925" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14716" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Hadenya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the villains appearing in the second part of the season. She can transform into a bird-like, very colorful costume reminiscent of Brazil Carnival. She likes to take what she wants and often lets Bunbee serve her in some way. In her human form she is very fat and wears a red jacket and blue pants; she also wears jewelry.</description>
<picture>42390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9679" picture="203641.jpg">Komiya Kazue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14717" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Bloody</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This is the last Nightmare member showing up in the first season. Bloody can transform into a bat-like creature, shooting sonic waves at his enemies. In the first place, however, he tries to win by persuasion and talking, only using Kowaina to help him. He always uses rooms or places to transform into Kowaina rather than objects.</description>
<picture>42391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2144" picture="21622.jpg">Maruyama Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14718" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Desparaia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The top of the Nightmares. She intends to gain eternal life to bring despair to all the world, and has ordered her subordinates to obtain the Dream Collet. Her name appears to play off of the words "pariah" and "despair". She has long brown hair and wears a purple dress and a mask.</description>
<picture>42392.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2890" picture="23182.jpg">Sugiyama Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14719" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="4">4.92</rating>
<name>Masuko Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This second-year student is the chief editor of the Cinq Lumières Tsuushin (a school paper). She tends to appropriate the paper for herself a little. Her name is a pun of masukomi (mass communication/media). Mika gets close to getting her "scoop" on the Pretty Cures, but is always distracted by Nuts` human form, making the next day`s paper all about him and her and reducing the article on the Cures to a small, almost unreadable size.</description>
<picture>42393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12582" picture="172647.jpg">Yamada Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14720" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Otaka-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The mistress of the cafeteria in girls` school where they always eat lunch, rather like the Tako Café in Pretty Cure Max Heart. She is a cheerful, middle-aged woman who sometimes gives them good advice. She is also the Headmistress of the school.</description>
<picture>42395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9800" picture="36489.jpg">Koujiro Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14721" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="4">6.19</rating>
<name>Akimoto Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Komachi`s older sister.</description>
<picture>42396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14722" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Yumehara Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nozomi`s mother. She is a beautician and runs a beauty shop "Espoir" (which is French for hope). She and Kazuyo are childhood friends just like Nozomi and Rin. Kazuyo says that she had been a more blunderer than Nozomi.</description>
<picture>42397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2879" picture="170992.jpg">Hino Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14723" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="4">4.32</rating>
<name>Natsuki Kazuyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rin`s mother. She and her husband run a flower shop "Fleuriste Natsuki". She is called "Kazu-chan" by Megumi like Rin by Nozomi.</description>
<picture>42398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14724" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Kasugano Michelle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urara`s father. He is from France, but he moved to Japan 20 years ago and is fluent in Japanese.</description>
<picture>42399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9195" picture="33999.jpg">Kanemaru Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14725" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Kasugano Heizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urara`s bright and energetic grandfather.</description>
<picture>42400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14726" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Washio Kouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Production Eagle and Urara`s manager. He has a lot of enthusiasm for his job and is friends with the Kasugano family.</description>
<picture>42401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14727" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Jiiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the Minazukis` butler and takes care of Karen when her parents aren`t home. He is very respectful to her and calls her `ojou-sama` ("young lady"), but he also seems to be fond of her, like a father. Jiiya is the term which an old servant is called (similarly Baaya means an old nanny or housemaid), and not his own name.</description>
<picture>42402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4719" picture="27542.jpg">Ikeda Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14728" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Rosette-hakushaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ghost that appears in an old school building.</description>
<picture>42403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14729" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Suehiro Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madoka`s close friend. She used Rin`s tiara design in her wedding.</description>
<picture>42404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14753" type="appears in" update="2010-02-04">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Natsuki Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rin`s younger brother and Ai`s twin.</description>
<picture>42467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14754" type="appears in" update="2010-02-04">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Natsuki Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rin`s younger sister and Yuu`s twin.</description>
<picture>42468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41374" type="appears in" update="2012-02-15">
<name>Nozomi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5021" picture="188516.jpg">Taki Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57896" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-16">
<rating votes="9">6.88</rating>
<name>Bunbee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93127" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<name>Nightmare</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Nightmare is a company seeking to acquire the Dream Collet.</description>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="67354" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">希望のプリキュア誕生!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Make Your Entrance, the Pretty Cure of Hope!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una Nuova Pretty Cure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kibou no Precure Tanjou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67355" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">情熱全開キュアルージュ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Full Throttle Passion Cure Rouge!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Benvenuta Cure Rouge!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jounetsu Zenkai Cure Rouge!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67438" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじけるプリキュアは誰?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who`s That Pretty Cure Bursting Forth?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Cure Lemonade!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajikeru Precure wa Dare?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67728" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やすらぎのキュアミント!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cure Mint of Tranquility!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Cure Mint</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasuragi no Cure Mint!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67766" update="2012-04-28">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリキュアの資格</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Qualifications of Pretty Cure</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Alla Ricerca Della Quinta Pretty Cure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Precure no Shikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68309" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリキュア5全員集合!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pretty Cure 5 Assembled!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Le Cinque Pretty Cure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Precure 5 Zen`in Juugou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68517" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">親友ナッツ現る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Best Friend, Nuts, Appear!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La Liberazione di Nuts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin`yuu Nuts Arawaru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69024" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">相性最悪? りんとかれん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Compatibility: Zero? Rin and Karen</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Questione di carattere</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aishou Saiaku? Rin to Karen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69276" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリキュアがばれちゃった!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pretty Cure is Discovered?!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Uno scoop giornalistico</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Precure ga Barechatta!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71763" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">腹ぺこナッツを救え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Save the Starving Nuts!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Le Pretty Cure fanno Pubblicità</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Harapeko Nuts o Sukue!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71929" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">のぞみとココの熱気球</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nozomi and Coco`s Hot air Balloon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nozomi to Coco no Netsu Kikyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72336" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うららのステージを守れ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect Urara`s Stage!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Urara no Stage o Mamore!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72337" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">りんちゃんの部活決定ーっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rin-chan`s Club is Decided!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rin-chan no Bukatsu Kettei!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72339" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悩める生徒会長かれん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Worrying Student Council President, Karen!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nayameru Seitokaichou Karen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78032" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純情乙女の恋物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Story of a Girl With a Pure Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junjou Otome no Koi Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78033" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突撃! かれんの私生活</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack! Karen`s Private Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsugeki! Karen no Shiseikatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78034" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うららの秘密を探れ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Search for Urara`s Secret!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Urara no Himitsu o Sagure!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78035" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハッスルのぞみのお手伝い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hustle! Nozomi Helps out!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hustle no Nozomi no Otetsudai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78036" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こまち小説家断念!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Komachi Abandons Being a Novelist?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komachi Shousetsuka Dannen!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78037" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリキュア5歌手デビュー!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pretty Cure 5`s Singing Debut?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Precure 5 Kashu Debut!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79362" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お世話役見習いミルク登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Apprentice Caregiver Milk Makes Her Appearance!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osewayaku Minarai Milk Toujou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79363" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクの家出で大騒ぎ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Milk`s Tumultuous Runaway!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Iede de Oosawagi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79364" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大ピンチ! 悪夢の招待状</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Trouble! An Invitation from the Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Pinch! Akumu no Shoutaijou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79365" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる5人の力!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Power of the Five Girls!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratanaru 5 Nin no Chikara!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80458" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリキュア合宿大作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pretty Cure`s Epic Boarding House Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Precure Gasshuku Dai Sakusen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81176" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロマンス全開リゾートライフ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Romantic Super-charged Resort Life!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Romance Zenkai Resort Life!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81269" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">りんちゃんイケメン幽霊とデート!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rin-chan, a Cool Guy, a Ghost, and a Date!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rin-chan Ikemen Yuurei to Date!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81270" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こまちの夏祭り奮闘紀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Komachi`s Festival Efforts Chronicled</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komachi no Natsu Matsuri Funtou Ki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81271" update="2007-09-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">のぞみの一日マネージャー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nozomi`s Manager for a Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nozomi no Ichinichi Manager</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82759" update="2007-09-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクの決意とみんなの力!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Milk`s Decision and Everyone`s Powers!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Ketsui to Minna no Chikara!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82760" update="2007-09-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">のぞみとココのラブレター事件!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nozomi and Coco`s Love Letter Scandal!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nozomi to Coco no Love Letter Jiken!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82842" update="2007-09-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大スクープ!プリキュア5独占取材!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Big Scoop! Covering Pretty Cure 5`s Monopoly!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Scoop! Precure 5 Dokusen Shuzai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82843" update="2007-09-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">りんちゃんのハッピーウェディング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rin-chan`s Happy Wedding!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rin-chan no Happy Wedding</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83948" update="2007-10-16">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクを守れ! 白馬の騎士かれん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect Milk! Karen, Knight on a White Horse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk o Mamore! Hakuba no Kishi Karen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84329" update="2007-10-16">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナッツの鍵とこまちの心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuts` Key and Komachi`s Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuts no Kagi to Komachi no Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84400" update="2007-10-16">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目指せ完走! マラソン大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aim for the Finish Line! A Marathon Championship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezase Kansou! Marathon Taikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84401" update="2007-10-16">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ココのヘルシー大作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coco`s Healthy Epic Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Coco no Healthy Daisakusen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84402" update="2009-10-09">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリキュア5のシンデレラ物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pretty Cure 5`s Cinderella Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Precure 5 no Cinderella Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85225" update="2009-10-10">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖! デスパライア現る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Horror! Despairiah`s Reality</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu! Despairiah Arawaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85286" update="2012-04-28">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">りんとかれんのひそかな約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rin and Karen`s Secret Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rin to Karen no Hisoka na Yakusoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85287" update="2009-10-10">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝わる気持ち こまちとうらら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Feelings that are Handed Down: Komachi and Urara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsutawaru Kimochi Komachi to Urara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85288" update="2009-10-10">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">理事長の正体を探れ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Search for the Chairman`s True Identity!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rijichou no Shoutai o Sagure!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85795" update="2009-10-10">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こまちの決意とナッツの未来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Komachi`s Decision and Nuts` Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komachi no Ketsui to Nuts no Mirai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85874" update="2009-10-10">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カワリーノ非情の策略!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tactics of Kawareno the Heartless!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawareno Hijou no Sakuryaku!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85875" update="2009-10-10">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">のぞみとココのクリスマスの誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nozomi and Coco`s Christmas Vow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nozomi to Coco no Christmas no Chikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85876" update="2009-10-10">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お世話役ってどんな人?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Kind of a Man is a Manager?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osewayakutte Donna Hito?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87034" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドリームコレットを取り戻せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reclaim the Dream Collet!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dream Collet o Torimodose!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87035" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">希望VS絶望 最後の対決!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hope VS Despair: The Final Showdown!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kibou VS Zetsubou Saigo no Taiketsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87036" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢と希望のプリキュア5!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With Hopes and Dreams, Pretty Cure 5!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume to Kibou no Precure 5!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130915" update="2015-11-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130916" update="2015-11-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130917" update="2015-11-05">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130918" update="2015-11-05">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
