<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4906" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Darker Than Black: Kuro no Keiyakusha</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">黑之契约者</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Darker than Black: The Black Contractor</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Темнее чёрного</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Ciemniejszy od czerni</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Czarny Kontraktor</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Mroczny Kontraktor</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">أحلك من السواد</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">אפל משחור</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Zifiri Karanlık</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">Mai întunecat ca negrul</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">По-тъмно от черното</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Темніше за чорне</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">DtB</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">dtb1</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">DARKER THAN BLACK 黒の契約者</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Darker Than Black</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Darker than Black</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">Darker than BLACK -흑의 계약자-</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Brama piekieł</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Darker Than Black</title>
<title xml:lang="id" type="official">Lebih Gelap dari Hitam : Sang Kontraktor Hitam</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Светът на мрака</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">DARKER THAN BLACK -黑之契約者-</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6644" type="Sequel">Darker Than Black: Ryuusei no Gemini</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7278" approval="87" total="121">Senkou no Night Raid</anime>
<anime id="2696" approval="41" total="53">Speed Grapher</anime>
<anime id="6256" approval="35" total="69">Phantom: Requiem for the Phantom</anime>
<anime id="23" approval="20" total="70">Cowboy Bebop</anime>
<anime id="5531" approval="20" total="32">Blassreiter</anime>
<anime id="10169" approval="19" total="30">Hamatora The Animation</anime>
<anime id="11345" approval="11" total="24">Dimension W</anime>
<anime id="3302" approval="7" total="36">Ergo Proxy</anime>
<anime id="3395" approval="5" total="22">Black Lagoon</anime>
<anime id="8184" approval="5" total="12">Towa no Quon</anime>
<anime id="10069" approval="4" total="15">Gokukoku no Brynhildr</anime>
<anime id="13" approval="2" total="18">Noir</anime>
<anime id="4416" approval="2" total="14">Black Blood Brothers</anime>
<anime id="4472" approval="2" total="7">Night Head Genesis</anime>
<anime id="272" approval="1" total="8">GetBackers: Dakkan`ya</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="56">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="140864">Great ^_^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="241061">if you are looking for action/drama this is it, the only drawbacks are the rushed ending and the low tone. dnt expect a lot of mind blowing action in the end. but drama and action is unmatched in the early episode. just watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="109369">Different and remarkable storyline, have to pay attention closely or you will miss the story. Spectacular drama and action!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="290120">Action Action Action! With an underlying story that recalls Howl`s contract with the falling star/fire demon Calcifer (see Howl`s Moving Castle).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="93928">Fun to watch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I wish they would have explained a few things though e.g. why and how the contractors came into existence, what the basis of their power was, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Very fun to watch regardless :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="296364">this was so godlike, it gave off that BlackCat feel...even better then BlackCat did hehe</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="438022">Awesome fight scenes and storyline. One of my favorites.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="228848">Awesome story line, and great characterization. The series does a great job of keeping you hooked and the contractors all had unique powers.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="510860">I enjoyed this series, the dark atmosphere and mutant like powers like x-men in a urban city is awesome. It`s also almost like a psychological thriller in a way and the dark nature of human beings. So glad I finally finished watching this since I saw the first few episodes when this first came out, did not disappoint.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="270712">Awesome</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="88347">Nice story. I`ll try to get the DVD in jap with eng subs</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="299976">Amazing! It`s one hell of a show! Great action scenes, gore and plot twists that build up an intense atmosphere. Characters were also great and so was their development. Enjoyed every minute of it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="535316">one of the best evermade! must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="38978">This was very good anime, although it has a setting for children,(people with super power and fighting), the story was pretty good and interesting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="56005">you should</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="584658">One of the best animes ever.

It`s a must see!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="181147">Just awesome.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="282239">One of the best</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="417064">Great anime! Full of interesting characters with superpowers like in the Western comic book.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="170697">Awesome !!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="106227">its an awesome anime everyone should watch..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="177797">Awesome anime both in plot and design. Great  action , fights and music. Highly recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="405614">epic figths storry and mistery !
THIS IS BY FAR A MUST SEE!
DONT FORGET TO SEE 2nd SEASON as well!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.d-black.net/1st/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
<name id="755" type="Original Work">Bones</name>
<name id="6062" type="Chief Animation Direction">Komori Takahiro</name>
<name id="6062" type="Character Design">Komori Takahiro</name>
<name id="3053" type="Original Work">Okamura Tensai</name>
<name id="3053" type="Direction">Okamura Tensai</name>
<name id="241" type="Music">Kanno Youko</name>
<name id="4313" type="Series Composition">Suga Shoutarou</name>
</creators>
<description>Ten years ago, a bizarre phenomenon appeared in Tokyo. Three days later, two types of humans with supernatural abilities appeared: emotionless dolls that only do what they`re programmed to and wield the ability of surveillance, and powerful contractors, feared and hated by the humans that know of their existence. Rationally self-preserving and without the feeling of guilt, it`s not long before contractors are used as ideal assassins and weapons of war.
Unable to analyze the phenomenon that created these beings safely, it`s decided that a huge wall be built around it, called "Hell`s Gate." PANDORA, an international research group, protects this wall and analyzes what little they can, while the government struggles to suppress dangerous contractors and the publics` knowledge of them.
In all the police force`s efforts and doll-assisted surveillance of the city, one contractor continues to evade them. BK201, as the police force knows him, stands out as an exceptional killer, while those in the syndicate who know him as Hei see him as a powerful, yet strangely irrational contractor...
Summary written by Quaenorde.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="10413">7.78</permanent>
<temporary count="10601">8.23</temporary>
<review count="11">7.45</review>
</ratings>
<picture>23827.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7382</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2025</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4182</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3944</identifier>
<identifier>xesbcb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/dtb</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.d-black.net/1st/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Darker_than_Black</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>DARKER_THAN_BLACK_-黒の契約者-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1099</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326663</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8853</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1707</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B071H4RCZP</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-25">
<name>contractor</name>
</tag>
<tag id="587" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>doll</name>
</tag>
<tag id="904" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-18">
<name>eccentric</name>
<description>Because normal people are no fun.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1438" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-18">
<name>ruthless</name>
<description>This character will stop at nothing to achieve their goals and will be unbound by any constraints</description>
<picurl>214979.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1444" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-17">
<name>spy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1719" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-28">
<name>orphan</name>
<description>The character (in common usage: only a child, or the young of an animal) has lost both parents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2621" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>bullet time</name>
<description>Bullet time refers to a simulation of variable speed (i.e. slow motion, time-lapse, …) and is characterized both by its extreme transformation of time and space to show normally imperceptible and un-filmable events, such as flying bullets.
Most infamous scene using this technique, Neo dodging bullets in The Matrix film.</description>
<picurl>211279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2777" parentid="2809" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>London</name>
<description>London is the capital and most populous city of both England and the United Kingdom. Standing on the River Thames in the south east of the island of Great Britain, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. It was founded by the Romans, who named it Londinium.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214379.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2813" parentid="2832" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-05">
<name>Brazil</name>
<description>Brazil, officially the Federative Republic of Brazil, is the largest country in both South America and Latin America. As the world`s fifth-largest country by both area and population, it is the largest country to have Portuguese as an official language and the only one in the Americas. Bounded by the Atlantic Ocean on the east, Brazil has a coastline of 7,491 km. It borders all other South American countries except Ecuador and Chile and covers 47.3% of the continent`s land area. Its Amazon River basin includes a vast tropical forest, home to diverse wildlife, a variety of ecological systems, and extensive natural resources spanning numerous protected habitats. This unique environmental heritage makes Brazil one of 17 megadiverse countries, and is the subject of significant global interest and debate regarding deforestation and environmental protection.
Brazil`s economy is the world`s ninth-largest by nominal GDP and seventh-largest by GDP (PPP) as of 2015. A member of the BRICS group, Brazil until 2010 had one of the world`s fastest growing major economies, with its economic reforms giving the country new international recognition and influence. Brazil`s national development bank plays an important role for the country`s economic growth. Brazil is a founding member of the United Nations, the G20, BRICS, Unasul, Mercosul, Organization of American States, Organization of Ibero-American States, CPLP, and the Latin Union. Brazil is a regional power in Latin America and a middle power in international affairs, with some analysts identifying it as an emerging global power. One of the world`s major breadbaskets, Brazil has been the largest producer of coffee for the last 150 years.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>93342.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2884" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>psychoactive drugs</name>
<description>Psychoactive drugs are chemical substances that affect the function of the central nervous system, altering perception, mood or consciousness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2962" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-14">
<name>neo-noir</name>
<description>Neo-noir is a style that prominently utilizes elements of the now declined film noir, but with updated themes, content, style, visual elements, or media that were absent in films noirs of the 1940s and 1950s.
Films noirs were typically crime dramas or psychological thrillers featuring a pessimistic worldview and starring conflicted antiheroes trapped in difficult situations and making choices out of desperation or nihilistic moral systems, with crime, especially murder, being featured on the majority of them. Some of the most obvious visual elements included low-key lighting, striking use of light and shadow, black-and-white filming, and unusual camera placement such as low-angle, wide-angle, and Dutch angle shots.
Film noir is often associated with urban settings, private detectives, femmes fatales, and bleak endings, but they are not necessary to the genre; a large number of these films, including some of the genre classics, take place in small towns, suburbia, rural areas, or on the open road, feature neither character type, and have clearly happy endings.
Film noir and the early neo-noir would come to influence the formation of tech noir, a crossover of neo-noir and science fiction, in the late 1970s; some the most influencial tech noir works are the American movies Alien (1979), Blade Runner (1982), and The Terminator (1984). Tech noir itself would also help form http://anidb.net/t2861 [cyberpunk] in the early 1980s.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3004" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-17">
<name>skilled main character</name>
<description>The main character in the show is very skilled in one or more tasks, often to the amazement of those around him/her.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3075" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-27">
<name>nervous breakdown</name>
<description>A character sees his entire world being destroyed around him, and his brain can`t take it anymore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3086" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>parricide</name>
<description>Parricide, or the murder of family members, is the act of taking the life of of one or more of one`s own close family members, or even one`s entire family; that may include spouses, parents, grandparents, children, grandchildren, siblings, cousins, uncles, aunts, nephews, and nieces, among others.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4524" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-23">
<name>stars</name>
<description>Heavenly bodies that twinkle and sparkle in the night sky; sometimes beautifully and serenely, sometimes ominously. 
In some way, the plot is related to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5981" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-12">
<name>seeking protagonist</name>
<description>The main character has a main objective that is referenced to through the whole series; he is in search of something, or someone
Should it be treasure, friends, money, power or all of the above nothing will stop our lead character in his quest to find his passion</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6066" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>improvised weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be split and deleted. Please apply any applicable http://anidb.net/tag/?parentid=7405&amp;reltb=chartb [weaponized object tags] to the relevant characters, or create new tags if necessary, and delete this tag from the anime/character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6327" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>chemical weapons</name>
<description>A chemical weapon is a device that uses chemicals formulated to inflict death or harm on human beings. The term may also be applied to any toxic chemical or its precursor that can cause death, injury, temporary incapacitation, or sensory irritation through its chemical action. Munitions or other delivery devices designed to deliver chemical weapons, whether filled or unfilled, are also considered weapons themselves. Under the Chemical Weapons Convention, there is a legally binding, worldwide ban on the production, stockpiling, and use of chemical weapons and their precursors. Notwithstanding, large stockpiles thereof continue to exist, usually justified as only a precaution against putative use by an aggressor.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2142" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="164">7.72</rating>
<name>Kirihara Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirihara Misaki is the Section-Chief of the Foreign Affairs Section 4 who is investigating matters that concern Contractors. Misaki has long brown hair and glasses and rarely smiles or laughs. She has a strong sense of justice and a sharp intuition. Kirihara became a policewoman in order to protect the weak, has a distaste for smokers due to their smell, and is sensitive about the exposure of her body. She likes eating greasy food but claims to stay fit due to constantly moving around everyday as part of her job. Her father is Superintendent Supervisor Naoyasu Kirihara of the National Police Agency.It appears that she has feelings for Hei.</description>
<picture>17000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7571" type="main character in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="631">8.66</rating>
<name>Hei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hei is the main protagonist and an elite Contractor with the Messier Code BK-201. In his team, Hei acts as the spy and assassin, swiftly dealing death without fail. Hei`s "mundane identity" is a gentle-hearted student from China named Li Shun Sheng (李舜生 (リ・シュンシェン), Ri ShunShen), but when "working" he takes on the role of a seemingly (at first) affectless and ruthless killer nicknamed "The Black Reaper"; this alias was earned based on stories of BK-201`s accomplishments as an assassin during the war at Heaven`s Gate.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>26352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7577" type="main character in" update="2011-01-31">
<rating votes="367">8.08</rating>
<name>Yin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7591" type="main character in" update="2010-07-03">
<rating votes="47">5.61</rating>
<name>Huang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7593" type="main character in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="101">7.04</rating>
<name>Mao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mao is a Contractor who has the ability to possess animals, subduing their natural instincts.</description>
<picture>2961.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7594" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="22">5.53</rating>
<name>Bai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bai is http://anidb.net/ch7571 [Hei]`s younger sister. Bai is the Contractor responsible for the disappearance of Heaven`s Gate five years prior to the story`s setting and had since vanished.
The Messier code BK-201 belongs to her star. Bai`s abilities are said to be vast, with generating abnormal electricity as only the tip of the iceberg. In addition to this, she also has the power of molecular reconstruction. Her remuneration is to sleep.</description>
<picture>31569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6847" picture="31570.jpg">Fujii Yuna</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7595" type="appears in" update="2010-07-03">
<rating votes="3">5.24</rating>
<name>Shinoda Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7597" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="2">2.00</rating>
<name>Louis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7598" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="2">2.80</rating>
<name>Jean</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7601" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<name>Physicalquantity Alternation Natural Deconstruction Organized Research Agency</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="10387" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="40">6.66</rating>
<name>Kayanuma Kiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31059.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10554" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="34">8.24</rating>
<name>November 11</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10555" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="107">6.80</rating>
<name>Amber</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10556" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Evening Primrose</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="10557" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="6">6.05</rating>
<name>Maki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maki is a young boy with heterochromatic irises. Maki`s ability allows him to perform a type of spontaneous combustion on objects that he touches with his hands. The explosions can occur remotely as he often prepares handprints before activating his ability. He uses this to cause attacks on the embassies in Tokyo. His remuneration is drinking hot milk. Maki seems to be infatuated with http://anidb.net/ch10555 [Amber] and says he would do anything for her. He attempts to kill http://anidb.net/ch7571 [Hei] out of jealousy, after learning Hei is the "him" that Amber frequently spoke of, convinced that he (Maki) is the only one fit of her love. He is killed by http://anidb.net/ch10554 [November 11].</description>
<picture>39265.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10558" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="12">3.91</rating>
<name>Amagiri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="294" picture="53586.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10559" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-04">
<rating votes="8">5.80</rating>
<name>Wei ZhiJun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10560" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="11">6.48</rating>
<name>Brita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blonde-haired woman whose cover was as a secretary in the American embassy in Japan. Her ability is to teleport herself and anyone she is in contact with; however, any clothing is left behind. The price of Brita`s contract is to kiss other people, which she often combines into one convenient act when teleporting others.</description>
<picture>46193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="234" picture="244740.jpg">Nakamura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10561" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>France Taigai Anzen Sou Kyoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="10562" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="4">3.65</rating>
<name>Alain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="301" picture="186193.jpg">Oonishi Takeharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10563" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="3">5.15</rating>
<name>Paul</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6848" picture="86100.jpg">Ooguro Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10564" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>MI6 (Darker Than Black)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="10565" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="30">5.74</rating>
<name>April</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10566" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-28">
<rating votes="51">5.55</rating>
<name>July</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>July is a young child most often seen being led around by April. He is a Doll whose observation powers rely on glass as a medium. He considers November and April to be his friends, a fact that initially astonishes Misaki and November as dolls are not supposed to think outside of their programming. April and July frequent November 11`s roadside site of death with offers of a bouquet or cigarettes and a beer or two. In the third episode of the 2nd season, July assists Suou by helping her direct her new-found powers against the FSB and the MIAC, and later joins up with Hei`s group, although his motivations for joining them remains unclear. However, it is implied later on that he has fallen in love with Suou. After he and Suou are killed by Izanami, they are both seen in the alternate world Shion created, with July being a normal boy instead of a doll.</description>
<picture>37317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2344" picture="37361.jpg">Asai Kiyomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10567" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="4">3.09</rating>
<name>Decade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head of Secret Intelligence Service (MI6), far-eastern division.</description>
<picture>46187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3093" picture="38195.jpg">Nojima Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10568" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="7">2.24</rating>
<name>Eric Nishijima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10569" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="5">5.31</rating>
<name>Robert Schroder</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2143" picture="178043.jpg">Kayumi Iemasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10570" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Qing Long Tang</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="10571" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-11">
<rating votes="9">6.37</rating>
<name>Alice Wang</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10572" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Central Intelligence Agency (Darker Than Black)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="10573" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-18">
<rating votes="3">5.12</rating>
<name>Nick Hillman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nick Hillman is a scientist who Hei meets as he infiltrates PANDORA. Nick and Hei become friends and both have a fascination with the "real sky". Nick turns out to be a contractor and is revealed to have the ability to manipulate electricity, apparently the same as Hei`s ability. His remuneration is putting people`s shoes on the ground upside-down next to each other. He became close to Hei, thinking that they were both alike, not just in their abilities, but even their dream of wanting to see the real starry sky. He felt that of all the people, he didn`t want Hei to know he was a contractor and to get him involved. After he and Hei battle for the artifact known as the "meteor fragment" Nick disappears as soon as the artifact is activated. Apparently, the meteor fragment reacted with Hei and allowed him to make Nick`s "dream" come true, which is to have a rocket (which looks very comical) to send both Nick (who became a young boy in his dream) and his sister to space. Nick`s ability to have an ambition is a mystery even to himself since contractors shouldn`t have emotion.</description>
<picture>40864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3189" picture="81680.jpg">Honjou Yuutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10574" type="appears in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="4">5.16</rating>
<name>Corinna Moku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2945" picture="177565.jpg">Ishizuka Sayori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10575" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Russia Renpou Hoanchou (Darker Than Black)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="10576" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="6">5.21</rating>
<name>Itzhak</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10577" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="6">3.77</rating>
<name>Bertha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="256" picture="188450.jpg">Satou Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12470" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="8">4.90</rating>
<name>Saitou Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A subordinate of Kirihara`s. Traditionally wears a business suit. Despite being an officer, he seems to have little common sense as he infiltrated a gang operation undercover using his real name. He has admitted to finding Kirihara scary. However, Saitou is loyal to Kirihara and protects her from harm, even when he thinks she`s frightening. It is revealed in the OVA that Saito has feelings for Kirihara, however soon after verbalizing them his memory along with Kirihara`s is erased due to a memory erasing substance accidentally released by Mao.
In Ryuusei no Gemini he is still a member of Section 4 and gets contacted by Kirihara over the phone regarding to the disappearance of BK-201`s star.</description>
<picture>40866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12471" type="appears in" update="2010-07-03">
<rating votes="6">5.63</rating>
<name>Ishizaki Kanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ishizaki Kanami is Kirihara`s friend since high school and a head staffer at the observatory.</description>
<picture>40860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13306" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="16">6.10</rating>
<name>Kurasawa Gai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurasawa Gai is Japan`s number one detective. Formerly known as Matsukichi Gai, he was a police officer who quit the force to start his own detective agency. He uses unorthodox methods to solve mysteries and crimes, afraid of cats, has horrible body odor and athlete`s foot, and is struggling financially.</description>
<picture>40862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13608" type="appears in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="11">3.64</rating>
<name>Mayuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayuko is an otaku friend of Kayanuma Kiko.</description>
<picture>40863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="642" picture="156264.jpg">Hazuki Erino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16624" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="4">3.26</rating>
<name>Kouno Yutaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A detective of the Tokyo Metropolitan Police.</description>
<picture>46165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16625" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="7">2.46</rating>
<name>Hourai Yoshimitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chief of the Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department, Public Security Bureau.
It is later revealed that he is actually planning the genocide of contractors with other influential members of the Syndicate.</description>
<picture>46167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3312" picture="24691.jpg">Ikemizu Michihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16626" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="3">3.63</rating>
<name>Matsumoto Kunio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Officer of the Tokyo Metropolitan Police, oldest member of Section 4.</description>
<picture>46168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3362" picture="69121.jpg">Fukuda Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16627" type="appears in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="2">3.91</rating>
<name>Kirihara Naoyasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirihara Naoyasu is Misaki`s father, Superintendent Supervisor of the National Police Agency.</description>
<picture>46170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16632" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="8">6.16</rating>
<name>Ooyama Misuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Landlady of the house Hei is residing in. She is usually seen chasing Mao away from the house.</description>
<picture>46184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16633" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="19">6.97</rating>
<name>Havoc</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A contractor who lost her powers and a significant portion of her memories after Heaven`s Gate disappeared in South America, five years prior to the story`s setting.</description>
<picture>46186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16634" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="8">4.41</rating>
<name>Meena Kandaswamy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16635" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="6">6.55</rating>
<name>Ootsuka Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Section 4`s liaison officer within the Astronomy Bureau. In her private time, she`s an otaku who enjoys anime and writes her own doujinshi.</description>
<picture>46194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2227" picture="73301.jpg">Inamura Yuuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16636" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="4">3.41</rating>
<name>Eelis Kastinen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eelis Kastinen is a famed Finnish pianist and Yin`s former teacher.</description>
<picture>46195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="633" picture="33549.jpg">Inoue Norihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16693" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="4">6.73</rating>
<name>Sakurai Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16695" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="5">6.11</rating>
<name>Kishida Shihoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An operative of the syndicate even longer than Huang, Shihoko is a contractor tasked with the job of infiltrating Alma`s organization to gather intel for an eventual assassination.</description>
<picture>46286.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4941" picture="222847.jpg">Ukai Rumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16719" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-03">
<rating votes="10">5.33</rating>
<name>Kashiwagi Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kashiwagi Mai is a high school student and the daughter of http://anidb.net/ch16729 [Tahara Kouzou], the only survivor from Hell`s gate. There is a significant emotional detachment between Mai and her father and Mai chose to adopt her deceased mother`s maiden name.</description>
<picture>46310.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4710" picture="27532.jpg">Nasu Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16729" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-03">
<rating votes="2">3.54</rating>
<name>Tahara Kouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tahara Kouzou is the sole survivor of an excursion to Hell`s Gate. He dedicates his life to suppressing the latent contractor powers of his daughter, http://anidb.net/ch16719 [Mai].</description>
<picture>46318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20546" picture="2047.gif">Meguro Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16731" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="4">5.62</rating>
<name>Yuzuki Arisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young widow of the late president of Fiore Cosmetics.</description>
<picture>46324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16733" type="appears in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="2">3.91</rating>
<name>Sergei Viktorov</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Senior researcher at Pandora`s Hell`s Gate facility.</description>
<picture>46327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16734" type="appears in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="3">4.95</rating>
<name>Anni</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of Kirsi (Yin).</description>
<picture>46328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3890" picture="186170.jpg">Takamori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19450" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="3">4.23</rating>
<name>Hoshimi-sama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stargazer-sama is a strange monk who sits in the center of the observatory and appears to be the chief observer of the stars. She speaks riddles or prophecy, and has been seen to be able to speak during http://anidb.net/ch10555 [Amber]`s freezing of time.</description>
<picture>50917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2029" picture="236292.jpg">Matsuo Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19451" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<name>National Astronomical Observatory of Japan (Darker Than Black)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>50918.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19452" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="4">2.99</rating>
<name>Hitotsubashi Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2730" picture="22755.jpg">Sugawara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19453" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="2">6.27</rating>
<name>Nakazawa Gumi no Doll</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50931.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19454" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="2">3.91</rating>
<name>Irene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Irene is a dark skinned woman with orange hair who lives beneath http://anidb.net/ch7571 [Hei]. She lived in the Philippines before moving to Japan to make money for her family back in her homeland by working as a hostess.</description>
<picture>50940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19455" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="2">3.91</rating>
<name>Joshua</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joshua is http://anidb.net/ch7571 [Hei]`s Neighbor. He came to Japan from Israel. He has an interest in Japanese animation, claiming it is #1 in the world.</description>
<picture>50941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5034" picture="33312.jpg">Fukuhara Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19457" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="2">6.71</rating>
<name>Louis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Louis is http://anidb.net/ch7571 [Hei]`s Neighbor. Almost never seen without his guitar.</description>
<picture>50942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4270" picture="197671.jpg">Nakagawa Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19461" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="3">3.75</rating>
<name>Babo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Babo is http://anidb.net/ch7571 [Hei]`s Neighbor, has only one line, at the end of the OVA episode, despite appearing more frequently than other tenants. Caught Ootsuka Mayu spying on Hei and became convinced she was stalking himself. Brought flowers for her at the end of the OVA but stated in his one line that, "She isn`t coming, is she?"</description>
<picture>50948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4196" picture="26343.jpg">Takeda Masanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19462" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="2">2.80</rating>
<name>Isozaki Souichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isozaki Souichi was http://anidb.net/ch7591 [Huang]`s partner.</description>
<picture>50959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19464" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="3">5.24</rating>
<name>Isozaki Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isozaki Shizuka is Souichi`s wife.</description>
<picture>50950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19469" type="appears in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="2">2.80</rating>
<name>Alma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="685" picture="24841.jpg">Takano Urara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19729" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="2">3.91</rating>
<name>Ooyama Toshirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ooyama Toshirou is Misuzu`s husband. He speaks very rarely and mostly tends his plants.</description>
<picture>51435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3244" picture="37803.jpg">Iwata Yasuo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="69110" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="50">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">契約の星は流れた... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fallen Star of a Contract... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der zu einem Kontrakt gehörenden Stern ist gefallen - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keiyaku no Hoshi wa Nagareta... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69111" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="33">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">契約の星は流れた... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fallen Star of a Contract... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der zu einem Kontrakt gehörenden Stern ist gefallen - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keiyaku no Hoshi wa Nagareta... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69112" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="25">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新星は東雲の空に煌く... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Star Shines in the Dawn Sky... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein neuer Stern am Morgenhimmel - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsei wa Shinonome no Sora ni Kirameku... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69113" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="24">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新星は東雲の空に煌く... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Star Shines in the Dawn Sky... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein neuer Stern am Morgenhimmel - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsei wa Shinonome no Sora ni Kirameku... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69155" update="2007-03-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69156" update="2007-03-29">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69157" update="2007-03-29">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69158" update="2007-03-29">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69159" update="2007-03-29">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71762" update="2007-04-08">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">15 second promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71862" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="25">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">災厄の紅き夢は東欧に消えて... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Giant over Eastern Europe... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Blutrote Vorstellungen von einem Desaster verschwinden gen Osteuropa - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiyaku no Akaki Yume wa Touou ni Kiete... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71863" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="27">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">災厄の紅き夢は東欧に消えて... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Giant over Eastern Europe... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Blutrote Vorstellungen von einem Desaster verschwinden gen Osteuropa - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiyaku no Akaki Yume wa Touou ni Kiete... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72099" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="26">2.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">五月雨にクチナシは香りを放ち... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scent of Gardenias Lingers in the Summer Rain... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Duft der Gardenien im Frühsommerregen - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satsukiame ni Kuchinashi wa Kaori o Hanachi... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72100" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="23">4.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">五月雨にクチナシは香りを放ち... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scent of Gardenias Lingers in the Summer Rain... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Duft der Gardenien im Frühsommerregen - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satsukiame ni Kuchinashi wa Kaori o Hanachi... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72391" update="2007-05-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73550" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="26">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純白のドレスは少女の夢と血に染まる... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The White Dress, Stained with the Girl`s Dreams and Blood... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Träume eines Mädchens im schneeweissen Kleid, durchtränkt von Blut - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junpaku no Dress wa Shoujo no Yume to Chi ni Somaru... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73551" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="26">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純白のドレスは少女の夢と血に染まる... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The White Dress, Stained with the Girl`s Dreams and Blood... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Träume eines Mädchens im schneeweissen Kleid, durchtränkt von Blut - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junpaku no Dress wa Shoujo no Yume to Chi ni Somaru... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73668" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="22">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壁の中, なくしたものを取り戻すとき... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When One Takes Back What Was Lost Within the Wall... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wo man zurückbekommt, was man verloren hat - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kabe no Naka, Nakushitamono o Torimodosu Toki... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73669" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壁の中, なくしたものを取り戻すとき... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When One Takes Back What Was Lost Within the Wall... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wo man zurückbekommt, was man verloren hat - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kabe no Naka, Nakushitamono o Torimodosu Toki... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73670" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="23">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀色の夜, 心は水面に揺れることなく... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Heart Unswaying on the Water`s Surface... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mondhelle Nächte, die sich nicht im Wasser spiegeln - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gin`iro no Yoru, Kokoro wa Suimen ni Yureru Koto Naku... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73671" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀色の夜, 心は水面に揺れることなく... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Heart Unswaying on the Water`s Surface... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mondhelle Nächte, die sich nicht im Wasser spiegeln - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gin`iro no Yoru, Kokoro wa Suimen ni Yureru Koto Naku... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79137" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切りの記憶は琥珀色の微笑み... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories of Betrayal in an Amber Smile... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein bersteinfarbenes Lächeln ist Erinnerung an einen Verrat - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri no Kioku wa Kohakuiro no Hohoemi... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79138" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切りの記憶は琥珀色の微笑み... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories of Betrayal in an Amber Smile... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein bersteinfarbenes Lächeln ist Erinnerung an einen Verrat - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri no Kioku wa Kohakuiro no Hohoemi... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80443" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">掃きだめでラブソングを歌う... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Love Song Sung from a Trash Heap... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebeslied einer gescheiterten Existenz - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakidame de Love Song o Utau... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80444" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">掃きだめでラブソングを歌う... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Love Song Sung from a Trash Heap... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebeslied einer gescheiterten Existenz - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakidame de Love Song o Utau... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80966" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あさき夢見し, 酔いもせず... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreaming Shallow, Uninebriated... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nicht seichte Träume noch tiefe Trunkenheit - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asaki Yumemishi, Yoi mo Sezu... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80967" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あさき夢見し, 酔いもせず... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreaming Shallow, Uninebriated... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nicht seichte Träume noch tiefe Trunkenheit - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asaki Yumemishi, Yoi mo Sezu... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80968" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">粛正の街は涙に濡れて... (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">City Under Crackdown, Moist with Tears... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Ort des Rechts, von Tränen durchdrungen - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukusei no Machi wa Namida ni Nurete... (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80969" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">粛正の街は涙に濡れて... (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">City Under Crackdown, Moist with Tears... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Ort des Rechts, von Tränen durchdrungen - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukusei no Machi wa Namida ni Nurete... (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81180" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="21">8.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神は天にいまし...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">God Is In His Heaven...</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gott, der Du bist im Himmel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami wa Ten ni Imashi...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81542" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流星雨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meteor Shower...</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Meteoritenregen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuuseiu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81543" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死神の見る夢は, 黒より暗い暗闇か?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Does the Reaper Dream of Darkness Darker Than Black?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sind die Träume des Todes dunkler als schwarz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinigami no Miru Yume wa, Kuro yori Kurai Kurayami ka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89020" update="2010-05-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="37">7.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜の花の満開の下</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beneath Cherry Blossoms in Full Bloom...</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Unter voll erblühten Kirschbäumen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Hana no Mankai no Shita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106625" update="2010-12-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">9.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111851" update="2010-12-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111852" update="2009-12-04">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189296" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Contractor Drama CD</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
