<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4917" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-01</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hayate no Gotoku!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Hayate le majordome</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Хаятэ, боевой дворецкий</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">הייטה גוטוקו!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Kovinis liokajus Hajatė</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Chàng quản gia</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Хаяте:Бойният прислужник</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hayate no Gotoku</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">旋风管家</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">HnG!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">cbh</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Hayate</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ハヤテのごとく! Hayate the combat butler</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hayate the Combat Butler</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Hayate the Combat Butler</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">하야테처럼</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ฮายาเตะ พ่อบ้านประจัญบาน!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6389" type="Sequel">Hayate no Gotoku!! 2nd Season: Atsu ga Natsui ze - Mizugi Hen!</anime>
<anime id="9291" type="Alternative Setting">Hayate no Gotoku! Can`t Take My Eyes Off You</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8062" approval="36" total="60">Astarotte no Omocha!</anime>
<anime id="5235" approval="35" total="52">Kimi ga Aruji de Shitsuji ga Ore de: They Are My Noble Masters</anime>
<anime id="7009" approval="31" total="82">Ladies versus Butlers!</anime>
<anime id="4146" approval="6" total="22">Zero no Tsukaima</anime>
<anime id="2165" approval="5" total="17">School Rumble</anime>
<anime id="5674" approval="4" total="10">Zettai Karen Children</anime>
<anime id="4821" approval="3" total="7">Seto no Hanayome</anime>
<anime id="14026" approval="3" total="5">Uchi no Maid ga Uzasugiru!</anime>
<anime id="4148" approval="3" total="3">Ouran Koukou Host Club</anime>
<anime id="7008" approval="2" total="17">Kaichou wa Maid-sama!</anime>
<anime id="11543" approval="2" total="9">Shounen Maid</anime>
<anime id="13037" approval="2" total="7">Hatena Illusion</anime>
<anime id="6304" approval="1" total="4">Isekai no Seikishi Monogatari</anime>
<anime id="4112" approval="1" total="4">Kage kara Mamoru!</anime>
<anime id="5277" approval="1" total="2">Kamen no Maid Guy</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="24">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="253442">Refreshing Ani ... so funny to watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="341142">For people who wants to see some of their favorite anime parodied you should be watching this by now!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="217654">Great series ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="231511">Tohle vypadá docela dobře... stáhnul bys to?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="233941">Very funny, especially how Hayate comments about the very crappy life he`s lived, but he`s always smiling about it. Also has some action, sometimes involving attacks and characters from other animes, making the dialog "bleep". Great to just relax and laugh.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="181980">fun to watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="69126">A series that any otaku will enjoy! Plus Rie Kumigiya!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="421535">An enjoyable anime.  The story is good and it has alot of funny jokes in it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="655071">Nice anime with a great ending!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="237023">fuck yeah!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="276125">One of the many gems hidden in the vast expanses of anime. While JCStaff stayed a little truer to the story, SynergySP did a fabulous job nonetheless. Quality humor, quality animation, without a doubt one of the best anime around.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="133190">One of the best comedy-anime around</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="160108">Extremely funny. Does lots of reference to other animes but can be extremely funny even if the references are not catched.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="183526">Very funny anime. One of the best comedies. It is very underrated. It`s humour is very specific. There are also a lot of references and puns on various anime and many other things.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="54433">Best comedy/parody ever !</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://hayatenogotoku.com/1ki/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1163" type="Animation Work">SynergySP</name>
<name id="3634" type="Series Composition">Takegami Junki</name>
<name id="4314" type="Main Character Design">Horiuchi Osamu</name>
<name id="1783" type="Original Work">Hata Kenjirou</name>
<name id="6090" type="Direction">Kawaguchi Keiichirou</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
<name id="7880" type="Series Composition">Inotsume Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="13488" type="Work">Kawasaki Yukio</name>
<name id="3693" type="Work">Kawamura Akihiro</name>
<name id="10734" type="Work">Yasuda Masaki</name>
<name id="24171" type="Work">Saitou Yutaka</name>
<name id="5259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
<name id="4938" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nagamori Yoshihiro</name>
</creators>
<description>The 16-year-old http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] is really down on his luck. Because his unemployed parents are good-for-nothings who waste what money they have on gambling, Hayate had to start working at a young age to help out his family. Although such experience has made him inhumanly fast, tough and skilled at things boys are not normally skilled at, it has also left him in an awkward position, since his parents have racked up such a huge gambling debt that they have sold Hayate to the yakuza for the value of his organs. In a desperate attempt to avoid that fate, Hayate decides to become a "bad guy" and kidnap someone to be held for ransom, but his efforts to do so are mistaken for a confession of love by the girl he targets.
When he helps save the (as it turns out) very wealthy 13-year-old http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi] from real kidnappers, she takes him in and gives him a job as her new personal butler (and love interest) until he can pay off his debt. But Hayate is more attracted to Nagi`s beautiful teenage maid http://anidb.net/ch529 [Maria], and head butler http://anidb.net/ch630 [Klaus] is initially disapproving of the boy with such a poor look. And then there is Nagi`s pet http://anidb.net/ch679 [Tama], who is also a force to be reckoned with.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4998">6.74</permanent>
<temporary count="5072">7.79</temporary>
<review count="3">7.05</review>
</ratings>
<picture>12018.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7490</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2026</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3961</identifier>
<identifier>dseptv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hayatenogotoku.com/1ki/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hayate_no_Gotoku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ハヤテのごとく!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1133</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327104</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8867</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2769" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>hyperspace mallet</name>
<description>It comes from nowhere, it strikes without mercy, and disappears again. It`s a mallet the size of a circus sledgehammer, and it`s evidence that anime characters watch too many Bugs Bunny cartoons or Three Stooges shorts. An angry character — usually but not restricted to short-tempered schoolgirls — can often whip out a massive hammer with which to slam the target (and cause) of her ire.
In Fan Fic circles, the notional storage place for mallets when not in use is known as hammerspace or malletspace.
A recent variation is to have the character pull out a http://anidb.net/t1662 [harisen], a huge folded fan made out of paper or metal, a.k.a. the Paper Fan of Doom, and smack them with that. This is usually less painful-looking than the mallet, unless she uses it to deliver a Megaton Punch.
Ironically, this is now a Dead Horse Trope in the West, where it originated; modern Western examples are typically from shows invoking anime, which has added its own touches to the mix, or from homages to Warner Brothers cartoons.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>10253.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3108" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-20">
<name>catastrophic gadgets</name>
<description>Comedy element: One of the characters in the anime tends to "invent", "create", or "call into existence" all sorts of wacky gadgets. The intent is to help the other protagonists in some way. Only that this fails every single time, ending in a catastrophe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4085" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-17">
<name>unlikely duo</name>
<description>Comedy element: There is usually not only a difference in gender but also in appearance, character, and background concerning the main characters of this anime. Making it very unlikely for them to appear in the same context. Non-the-less they share the same adventure, as in "opposites attract".
These differences are exploited to come up with all sorts of wacky situations.
Examples: A demon-killer or Hero and the daughter of the Demon King. A girl from a normal family and a very intelligent and attractive boy from a very rich background (Shoujo). A very energetic outgoing girl and her very calm almost introverted best friend.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="32" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-12-28">
<rating votes="653">8.96</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Kagami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukasa`s elder twin sister. Konata`s close friend. Her thought process is normal, so she often pokes fun at Konata. She may be the most right-minded character. An aloof-chummy type, who is warm-hearted only when she has gotten to know you.</description>
<picture>18662.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="528" type="main character in" update="2011-05-18">
<rating votes="497">5.90</rating>
<name>Sanzen`in Nagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanzen`in Nagi is the only heir to the Sanzen`in fortune. She has an otaku-level hobby with manga, anime and video games, and draws her own manga, which is called Millennium Legend: Magical Destroy. She is good at finance and likes to learn. She has a crush on Hayate, and has misunderstood that Hayate loves her since they first met. But because this is only a misunderstanding, she often feels that Hayate isn`t interested in her. She sometimes tries to make him have interest in her in many ways. Nagi is afraid of dark places and has absolutely no sense of direction. Her only surviving family is her grandfather, whom she doesn`t like. She regards Maria as a mother or older sister figure, and warns Hayate not to touch Maria in any indecent way or she will never forgive him. She totally lacks experience with cooking and accordingly is prone to making mistakes (such as mistaking dish-washing detergent for cooking oil) when she attempts to cook. She has a pet tiger, Tama, whom she refers to as a cat.</description>
<picture>71769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="529" type="main character in" update="2009-08-16">
<rating votes="308">7.95</rating>
<name>Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maria is Nagi`s maid and surrogate older sister/mother, and is the only one who understands the problem between Hayate and Nagi. She is the character with the most common sense in the series, and appears to be the one in charge of everything in Nagi`s manor, since everyone from the head butler to the SP either obeys or fears her (or both in some cases). She`s good at general housework and likes games of all kinds, though she is deathly afraid of cockroaches, which she refers to as "the dark life-form that exists in the kitchen and other places". She has also proved capable of self-defence techniques in times of need.</description>
<picture>33340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="530" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="1086">9.09</rating>
<name>Katsura Hinagiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsura Hinagiku is the current http://anidb.net/ch16568 [student council] president, and kendo club president at http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuou Academy], the school that http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi], http://anidb.net/ch531 [Isumi], and eventually http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] attends. She is fifteen and is an expert with swords, specifically kendo. She first meets Hayate when he gets lost on the huge Hakuou campus and ends up rescuing her. She had been helping a baby bird who had fallen out of its nest, but due to her fear of heights, had become stuck without her realising it. Hayate ends up helping her down the tree, and then promises that he will come to help her should she ever call for him. In gratitude, she invites him to the top of the clocktower, where only student council elites are allowed. She allows Hayate to call her by her first name and also seems to be infatuated by Hayate and his attractive personality. Her family, while shown to be well off in volume 8 (chapter 76), does not show any signs of being rich in comparison to much of the cast.</description>
<picture>24934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="531" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-27">
<rating votes="210">8.26</rating>
<name>Saginomiya Isumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saginomiya Isumi is a purple-haired girl who is always wearing a kimono, and sometimes, a stole. She is http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi]`s best friend who they met at a party a long time ago. When all the other children, http://anidb.net/ch613 [Sakuya] included, laughed at Nagi`s first attempt at writing her own manga, Isumi took interest in it and asked Nagi how it ends; Nagi then asked Isumi (in a childish sense) to marry her. Like Nagi, Isumi is very rich. Unlike Nagi, Isumi is soft-spoken, kind, and can cook well. While she does not have an awful sense of direction, she constantly gets lost due to the fact that she is apt to forget her destination, and the fact that she can disappear from people`s eyes instantaneously only complicates the matter. She also has a habit of saying, when she doesn`t understand how to use a machine such as a cellular phone or a vending machine, that the machine is broken. She displays a high level of empathy for Nagi`s feelings; however, she does not recognise http://anidb.net/ch618 [Wataru]`s love for her, a fact that Nagi, Maria, and http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] comment on.</description>
<picture>59761.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="532" type="main character in" update="2010-04-16">
<rating votes="292">6.45</rating>
<name>Ayasaki Hayate</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayasaki Hayate is the butler of the Sanzenin family, Hayate has had to work to support his parents` bad habits since the age of nine, always moving from job to job by the time he is found out to be underage. The experience gained does mean, however, that he of all characters possesses the most extensive practical knowledge as to how the world operates. Hayate`s dad has refused to get employed,while his mother is a compulsive gambler, and the whereabouts of Hayate`s older brother who is not named, are unknown. These events led to their bankruptcy - they abandon Hayate after selling his organs to the Yakuza to ease their financial burdens. With not many choices left to him, Hayate conspired to kidnap someone to get ransom money. He found a girl, http://anidb.net/ch528 [Sanzenin Nagi], and told her that he would kidnap her. However, Nagi mistook his words for his confession of love, so later he was employed as Nagi`s new butler but as the story progresses, Hayate began to like Nagi without realising it. In the beginning of the story he often mentioned Nello and Patrasche from the novel A Dog of Flanders and compared his miserable situation to the characters` life.</description>
<picture>14830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="612" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="32">5.73</rating>
<name>Makimura Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makimura Shiori is a genius scientist with the Mikado Hyper Energy (M.H.E) Electronics Corporation as the Chief of Development, Humanoid Nursing and Battlefield Weapons Department, and Advanced Technology Development Division. Her specialities are computers and mechas. Her development team created Nursing Robot Eight and other mechas seen in the series. She is in fact so talented, that she even built a mecha when she was half asleep.</description>
<picture>14921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="613" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-18">
<rating votes="153">7.05</rating>
<name>Aizawa Sakuya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aizawa Sakuya is a cousin of http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi] and from Kansai. Like Nagi, Sakuya is very rich and has a similar personality — loud, arrogant, abusive of servants, and unwilling to accept defeat in anything. Nagi is one of the only people who can stand up to her, once again showing their similar personalities. Sakuya is the eldest daughter in her family with three sisters and one brother. Her illegitimate half brother http://anidb.net/ch16045 [Gilbert] is one of the people who is constantly harassing Nagi for her fortune. Sakuya is obsessed with stand-up comedy especially Manzai style. She encourages http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] to become a comedian because she believes Hayate`s life up to now is nothing more than a comedy.</description>
<picture>71770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="615" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="76">5.47</rating>
<name>Kijima Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kijima Saki is Wataru`s maid. She is significantly older than Wataru and lives with him in his video-rental store. Her biggest fear is that Wataru will start watching porn when he reaches puberty, which he denies. She takes a mixture of a servant and elder sister role to Wataru, often changing from being subservient to scolding him depending on the situation. She also reacts strongly whenever Hayate touches her anywhere, such as tapping her on the shoulder or carrying her away from danger, worrying about whether or not their physical contact will affect her chances of getting a husband later in life. This is not only limited to Hayate, but other men as well.</description>
<picture>4183.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="215" picture="151687.jpg">Nakajima Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="618" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="64">3.70</rating>
<name>Tachibana Wataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tachibana Wataru is Nagi`s fiancée, but they have no feelings for each other; Wataru claims his parents arranged their future marriage entirely for the money. He lives and runs a video-rental store in the city, the last store owned by the Tachibana group which lost all their assets and is on the verge of bankruptcy due to the recession. His dreams is to make his store great and acquire a fortune greater than Nagi`s. Wataru is in love with Isumi. He first hates Hayate for accidentally stealing Isumi`s affection, but later he looks up to him and strives to be as good as he is. Regardless of that, he still calls Hayate by his own personal nickname for him, "the Butler In Debt" (or a variation thereof), and doesn`t hide his usual irritation.</description>
<picture>14926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="623" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="139">4.49</rating>
<name>Katsura Yukiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsura Yukiji is the twenty-eight year old sister of Hinagiku. She is a world history teacher at http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuou Academy] and doubles as a twenty-four-hour gate guard. She refuses to let http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] enter the school when they first meet because she is afraid that letting unauthorised personnel on campus will result in a salary deduction for her. Her attitude softens after Hayate first saves her from falling off the clock tower, but she still almost causes Hayate to be rejected from Hakuou by unnecessarily making him anxious during his entrance exam. She repays Hayate by telling everyone in her class on Hayate`s first day that he is a super cool person. She has a group of underachieving students (http://anidb.net/ch640 [Izumi], http://anidb.net/ch641 [Miki], and http://anidb.net/ch642 [Risa]) who hang out with her a lot. She lives on the Hakuou campus; she tells Hayate that she does this so that she can save rent money and use that money to buy alcohol instead. It is a recurring gag that she will do anything for money, going as far as to allow an evil spirit to possess her because it told her it would give her a million yen. When http://anidb.net/ch612 [Makimura Shiori] is sent to teach at Hakuou, Yukiji is demoted to sub-homeroom teacher.</description>
<picture>130799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="628" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="154">6.22</rating>
<name>Nishizawa Ayumu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nishizawa Ayumu is a girl from Hayate`s school before he became a butler. She always had feelings for Hayate and is happy when he pays his old school a visit. She violently lashes out at anyone who badmouths her and Hayate, including a teacher who called Hayate a dropout because his parents had refunded all his school fees the day Hayate was sold. She confesses her feelings to Hayate, but Hayate rejects them after getting a vision of Nagi. Undeterred, she tries to talk to Hayate when she sees him a week later, but she runs into Nagi. She is shocked that, in terms of metaphoric strength, Nagi is a dragon while she is a hamster. Nishizawa retreats, vowing next time to bring a stronger hamster. She later challenges Nagi to karaoke, only to lose. In the anime, it is a running gag that she appears in every episode, usually for less than thirty seconds doing something entirely unrelated to the episode`s plot, though always related to food. However, in the manga, she is the only girl who has successfully confessed her love towards Hayate, which often places her in situations where she is alone with him. Most of the time she is shown eating something.</description>
<picture>71942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="630" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="60">4.49</rating>
<name>Klaus Seishirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Klaus is the head butler of the Sanzen`in family, who is usually away on business. He once fell in love with Hayate without knowing that Hayate was forced to crossdress as a catgirl by Nagi and Maria. He is self-centered, has a low alcohol tolerance, doesn`t do well with tobacco or women, and likes cars and bikes.</description>
<picture>14941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="640" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="153">7.72</rating>
<name>Segawa Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Segawa Izumi is the chairman.She is the younger fraternal twin sister of http://anidb.net/ch9408 [Segawa Kotetsu]. She met http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] when they were young (Volume 18 flashback) as she was getting attacked by a dog, although she mentioned nothing about that incident when she first met Hayate at http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuou Academy].</description>
<picture>14952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="641" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="107">4.72</rating>
<name>Hanabishi Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanabishi Miki is a member of the Student Council. She specialises in investigation work, which may be the result of being the daughter of an important government official.</description>
<picture>14953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="218" picture="17036.jpg">Nakao Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="642" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="102">4.57</rating>
<name>Asakaze Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asakaze Risa is the head of the disciplinary committee.</description>
<picture>14954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="679" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-09">
<rating votes="63">7.43</rating>
<name>Tama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tama is a white tiger from Africa, who was rescued by http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi] as a cub, and was raised on Matsuzaka beef and expensive tuna fish, making it incapable for him to go to the zoo or back to the wild. He can speak the human language, though he does not reveal this to http://anidb.net/ch529 [Maria] or Nagi because he doesn`t want to shatter the young girl`s dreams. He will lay his life down to protect Nagi, because his situation was a lot like http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate]`s. To him, Maria is the highest power there is, followed by an impassable wall, Nagi, then himself, and everyone else is below him.</description>
<picture>14973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6698" type="appears in" update="2009-06-02">
<rating votes="15">3.46</rating>
<name>Kaoru Kyounosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teacher at Hakuou Academy. He is seen building Gundam models in the staff room or during lunch. He spends all his money buying Gundam models and even borrows money from Yukiji to buy more. He is 28 years old but he is still single and without a girlfriend.
In episode 29, it is revealed that he`s had feelings for Yukiji, whom he`s known from childhood.</description>
<picture>27081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6699" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-05">
<rating votes="9">2.49</rating>
<name>Ookouchi Taiga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Himuro`s master, but it is difficult to tell which one is the master and which one is the butler. Taiga follows Himuro around throwing rose petals creating a rose storm.</description>
<picture>24533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="215" picture="151687.jpg">Nakajima Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6700" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-05">
<rating votes="10">4.32</rating>
<name>Saeki Himuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The combat butler of the Ookouchi family. He is seen smelling a single rose or reading a book with his master throwing rose petals behind him. Himuro loves money more than anything in the world but he does not try to gain the Sanzen`in inheritance because he already has his master`s money.</description>
<picture>24527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6701" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-05">
<rating votes="18">2.63</rating>
<name>Azumamiya Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The master of Nonohara Kaede and a member of the kendo club. He is considered the weakest member of the club because his strikes are random and dangerous. He has a vulgar mouth, but it is Kaede`s duty to refine him into a gentleman. When he is in trouble, he calls for Kaede to fight for him. Out of jealousy, he challenges Hayate to a duel when he sees him being friendly with Hinagiku. He is often beaten up mercilessly by Kaede for his weaknesses.</description>
<picture>24529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6702" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-05">
<rating votes="15">5.92</rating>
<name>Nonohara Kaede</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The combat butler of the Azumamiya family. He appears to have white hair and an almost always smiling face. His eyes are always closed and he is very polite. He encourages his master to be a gentleman and to be manly enough to fight his own battles even if he were to lose.
In contrast with his gentle and polite exterior, Nonohara is very brutal, senselessly beating his master when he acts like a weakling. In combat, whenever Kotarou asks for his help, he does the opposite, either throwing the Azumamiya into the battle zone or beating the boy up.</description>
<picture>24528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6778" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-20">
<rating votes="128">9.29</rating>
<name>Ten no Koe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Voice of the Heavens is the narrator of the series.
Throughout both the anime and the manga, he narrates on what happens in the series while at the same time mocking and ridiculing the characters about what they are doing, with frequent snarks at the absurd plot and the silly nature of the story. Some of the cast can hear him and respond accordingly.
He appeared in episode 50 of the anime as a tall man with no face hosting a quiz game.</description>
<picture>35924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6819" type="appears in" update="2009-05-08">
<rating votes="14">7.23</rating>
<name>Hinagiku no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7357" type="appears in" update="2009-05-26">
<rating votes="184">7.43</rating>
<name>Nabeshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3963" picture="25823.jpg">Watanabe Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7683" type="appears in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="6">2.40</rating>
<name>Eight</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A robot in love with his creator. He was created to be the ultimate nursing robot by the Sanzen`in Technology Division. He is waterproof and equipped with "nursing missiles" and rocket boosters. Eight`s downfall is his quick temper. He snaps after being called "ugly" and seeks revenge after he is defeated. Through his dialogue, he reveals that he only desires revenge in order to prove himself to one he loves: his creator. Sadly, Shiori has a habit of being totally dismissive of him, going as far as telling him she made a "mistake" in putting him in line for incineration when he actually needed to be trashed in a more appropriate category. Nonetheless, he eventually gets a reprieve after his latest upgrade, when he becomes Shiori`s boyfriend after finally confessing to her.
Eight receives an upgrade before each appearance. He is upgraded to v8.1 after his first defeat, upgraded to v8.2 before meeting Hayate in the amusement park, v8.3 after he becomes a couple with Shiori, and upgrades his form after Shiori is transferred to Hakuou Academy. Eight upgrades himself to v8.1 after he steals the control chip from Nursing Robot Nine and upgrades to 8.2 as his second form, but he is reverted back to v8.1 after he is beaten by Yukiji and Hayate.</description>
<picture>26543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7687" type="appears in" update="2009-09-20">
<rating votes="4">2.17</rating>
<name>Hannin A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of two brothers who owe money to the Yakuza. They attempt to get money by obtaining ransom by kidnapping. They kidnap Nagi and later Saki.</description>
<picture>26552.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7688" type="appears in" update="2009-09-20">
<rating votes="4">2.49</rating>
<name>Hannin B</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of two brothers who owe money to the Yakuza. They attempt to get money by obtaining ransom by kidnapping. They kidnap Nagi and later Saki.</description>
<picture>26553.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9407" type="appears in" update="2009-06-15">
<rating votes="24">7.25</rating>
<name>Ayasaki Hermione</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9408" type="appears in" update="2010-04-09">
<rating votes="16">3.02</rating>
<name>Segawa Kotetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Segawa Kotetsu is the combat butler of the Segawa family and the older fraternal twin brother of http://anidb.net/ch640 [Segawa Izumi]. As a running gag, his hobby is his extreme love of trains and train turntables. He seems to be shy as he has never had the confidence to ask a girl out. It seems that his terrible luck with women has left him feeling bitter about the entire female gender, but while he is at http://anidb.net/ch530 [Hinagiku]`s birthday party, he runs into http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] and immediately falls in love with him, or rather his alter-ego http://anidb.net/ch9407 [Hermione]. He soon learns of Hayate`s identity from Izumi. Angered by this, he kidnaps http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi] in order to bring Hayate out. After Nagi confronts him on his shallow attitude towards love in general, he vows to change his attitude and still likes Hayate even after discovering that he is male. He seems extremely hung up on Hayate and uses various methods to try to spend time with him, such as challenging him to ping pong to get him to spend time in a hot spring they were both visiting. He is rarely seen in the first season of the anime, making brief appearances once in a while, although Izumi has referred to him several times; he gets a larger role in the second season.</description>
<picture>28942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10198" type="appears in" update="2009-08-16">
<rating votes="113">6.37</rating>
<name>Harukaze Chiharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The secretary of the student council. Secretly, under the alias of "Haruko", she works as Sakuya`s maid. Although nobody in Hakuou is aware of that, with the exception of Aika Kasumi, who found everything about her out soon enough.</description>
<picture>33328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10768" type="appears in" update="2012-11-04">
<rating votes="11">4.52</rating>
<name>Sanzen`in Mikado</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nagi`s grandfather and the head of the Sanzen`in family, as well as one of the five directors in charge of Hakuou Academy. He lives in a mansion much bigger than Nagi`s mansion with many servants. It is unknown where the Sanzen`in fortune comes from but Nagi calls her grandfather an oil tycoon. He has the ability to judge a person`s character just by looking at them.</description>
<picture>127688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10828" type="appears in" update="2010-04-03">
<rating votes="4">7.70</rating>
<name>Himegami Akane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Himegami was http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi]`s butler before http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate]. He has yet to make an appearance in the manga, but judging from the way Nagi and http://anidb.net/ch529 [Maria] speak of him, he quit due to a problem related to Nagi`s personality traits. Neither Nagi nor Maria seem to want to elaborate on his departure. Also with references from the first volume he was close to Nagi. He wrote a book on how a butler can acquire a one-hit kill technique, but later Nagi burnt the book. Maria addresses him with the title "-kun", which means he is probably around Hayate and Maria`s age. In episode 34 of the anime, he makes his appearance, but with his face obscured by the shadows. He returns once more in episode 38 wearing a mask. In episode 39 his face is shown. In the anime, it is stated he was fired from his position rather than him personally resigning, and it is implied that it is partially because he always hit Nagi back after she would hit him. He also insists that he be called "Princess God" (in English) rather than Himegami, which is a direct translation of his surname.</description>
<picture>32307.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11542" type="appears in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="20">7.84</rating>
<name>Kasumi Aika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kasumi Aika is the vice president of the http://anidb.net/ch16568 [Student Council]. Like many other http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuo Academy] students, she comes from a rich family. While she may be seen as a sweet, kind, and gentle girl to most people, secretly she is also very manipulative and takes advantage of any situation she sees, a fact only http://anidb.net/ch530 [Hinagiku] and http://anidb.net/ch10198 [Chiharu] are aware of.</description>
<picture>34677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11870" type="appears in" update="2009-09-20">
<rating votes="4">5.99</rating>
<name>Maou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maou the Great Stygian of Abe (Temp) is a demon and last boss of the game that Nagi is playing in episode 10.
She is cute, naive, and incredibly busty, and wears a talking skull named Gaikotsu on her head who punishes her when she tries to help the good guys.
She also appears on episode 50 of the first series as a host of the quiz game, and appears on the inner cover comic of Volume 13.</description>
<picture>35926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12669" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="66">5.55</rating>
<name>Shashou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main crew member of the Galaxy Express 999. He is an alien being with an invisible body; only his eyes can be seen while he is wearing his conductor uniform. The Conductor prefers to go `strictly by the book` and frequently cites the Galaxy Express rule book, but occasionally ends up bending the rules and getting into adventures with Tetsurou and Maetel.</description>
<picture>38142.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16045" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">2.43</rating>
<name>Gilbert Kent</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gilbert Kent is http://anidb.net/ch613 [Sakuya]`s illegitimate half brother. He does not look Japanese because of his brown curly hair and dark complexion, but Sakuya thinks they look alike. After Nagi`s grandfather announced a condition to inherit the Sanzen`in fortune, Gilbert quickly begins to pursue the fortune, even begging for it.</description>
<picture>45152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16068" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-25">
<rating votes="6">4.00</rating>
<name>Kuzuha Kirika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuzuha Kirika is the Superintendent of http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuou Academy] who first appears asking http://anidb.net/ch623 [Yukiji] to tell http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] that he had failed the entrance exam, but it is only in the anime that her character was developed. In the anime, she possesses a power level three times that of an ordinary person, but the moment she uses all her energy, she drops to the floor. She tends to do extreme things to kill her boredom.</description>
<picture>45155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16069" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-11">
<rating votes="4">1.98</rating>
<name>Kuresato Shion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shion is the devoted butler of http://anidb.net/ch16068 [Kirika Kuzuha].</description>
<picture>45157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16070" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-25">
<rating votes="8">5.27</rating>
<name>Kuresato Shion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shion`s real form.</description>
<picture>45158.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16370" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-04">
<rating votes="7">4.22</rating>
<name>Kuzuha Kirika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuzuha Kirika`s cursed form.</description>
<picture>45679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16459" type="appears in" update="2011-12-01">
<rating votes="4">7.76</rating>
<name>Hakuou Gakuin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>77852.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16558" type="appears in" update="2010-04-09">
<rating votes="2">8.61</rating>
<name>Douga Kenkyuu Bu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Motion Picture Research Club</description>
<picture>46009.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16568" type="appears in" update="2010-04-15">
<rating votes="2">7.25</rating>
<name>Seitokai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Student Council (Seitokai) of http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuou Academy].</description>
<picture>46385.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32533" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Santa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Santa Claus first appeared to Hayate in a dream when he was eight years old, telling him he had to work in order to live. He was Hayate`s prime source of motivation, and the sole reason he worked so hard at such a young age and onwards. Outside of Hayate`s head, he appeared as a doctor after Hayate saves Nagi from a kidnapping. In the anime, Santa takes the role of other minor characters such as a delivery man, a construction worker, a monster in a game, a waiter, Klaus`s play school evaluator, a grocery store clerk, and a garbage man. Inside Hayate`s imagination, Santa Claus looks much like Mikado.</description>
<picture>71933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32534" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Ayasaki Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32535" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Hayate no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32536" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<name>Aniki Bun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2573" picture="240892.jpg">Shirokuma Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32537" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<name>Kashiwagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32538" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<name>Shatei B</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6077" picture="10491.jpeg">Oosuka Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55820" type="appears in" update="2013-05-14">
<name>Kunieda</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="6077" picture="10491.jpeg">Oosuka Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55821" type="appears in" update="2013-05-14">
<name>Makita</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77542" type="appears in" update="2015-09-23">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Duel Shitsuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177818.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77545" type="appears in" update="2015-09-23">
<name>Parisian</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77546" type="appears in" update="2015-09-23">
<name>Itsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77547" type="appears in" update="2015-09-23">
<name>Shunji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77548" type="appears in" update="2015-09-23">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Mini Yon Shitsuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="68678" update="2007-03-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short Animation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69150" update="2010-03-17">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69277" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="32">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命は, 英語で言うとデスティニー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In English, "Unmei" Means Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei wa, Eigo de Iu to Destiny</title>
<summary>It`s Christmas Eve. Normally around this time, people prepare to celebrate this sacred holiday. However, there`s one person in this world who won`t have a Merry Christmas, and that person is an poor, unlucky boy named Hayate Ayasaki, when his aloof parents get a debt worth 156,804,000 yen (approximately 1.3 million US dollars) and sell Hayate to the Japanese mafia to pay it off!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543104</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71692" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三千院ナギの屋敷と, 新たなる旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sanzenin Nagi`s Mansion and a New Start</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanzenin Nagi no Yashiki to, Arata Naru Tabidachi</title>
<summary>On his first day as a butler, Hayate stumbles upon a room with a private work of Nagi`s manga collection. He insults it and is eventually kicked out of the mansion and taken back to the Japanese mafia! Who will save him?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543106</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71693" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はぢめてのおつかい~こちらスネーク. 誰も応答しない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Mission. This is Snake. No One`s Responding.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Otsukai. Kochira Snake. Daremo Outoushinai.</title>
<summary>One day at school, Nagi forgets her lunch. As her butler, Hayate is determined to deliver her lunch on time. While navigating the school grounds, he meets a couple of people, one who is friendly and one who wants to destroy him!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543110</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71694" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="17">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界の中心でアイを叫んだり叫ばなかったりする獣とロボと執事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beast, Robot, and Butler Who Kinda Shout Love at the Center of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai no Chuushin de Ai o Saken Dari Sakeba Nakattari Suru Shishi to Robo to Shitsuji</title>
<summary>One morning, Hayate goes to Nagi`s room to wake her up for breakfast, but he sees a large white tiger named Tama sleeping right next to her!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543108</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71979" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不用意なボケと優しさが不幸を呼ぶ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unneeded Gags and Kindness Bring Misfortune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuyoui na Boke to Yasashisa ga Fukou o Yobu</title>
<summary>Hayate meets Sakuya Aizawa, Nagi`s childhood "friend", who, like Klaus the head butler, can`t accept Hayate as Nagi`s butler, but not just because he`s poor and unlucky, but because he`s not funny!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543112</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71980" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時が見えると君は言うけど, たぶんそれは走馬灯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Said You Can See Time, But That`s Probably Your Life Flashing By</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki ga Mieru to Kimi wa Iu Kedo, Tabun Sore wa Soumatou</title>
<summary>Hayate cannot bring himself to return to the Sanzenin mansion after he damages the cashmere coat that Maria lent him. While contemplating on what to do, he meets the "generous" people who tried to take him away and ends up fighting them all!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543114</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73051" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">男の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Man`s Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko no Tatakai</title>
<summary>The boy who Hayate meets is revealed to be Wataru Tachibana, Nagi`s fiancé. However, Nagi and Wataru can`t stand each other.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543116</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73379" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネコミミ・モードで地獄行き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cat Ear Mode Sends You to Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neko Mimi Mode de Jigoku Iki</title>
<summary>Nagi dresses Hayate in a girl`s sailor uniform, but things continue as it goes on to the point where Hayate looks like a cat girl!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543118</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73380" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エロイムエッサイム. ウシくんウシくん! なんだいカエルくん?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eloim Essaim. Mr. Cow, Mr. Cow! What is It, Mr. Frog?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eloim Essaim. Ushi-kun Ushi-kun! Nandai Kaeru-kun?</title>
<summary>Hayate wants Nagi to attend school on a daily basis. One day, however, when returning from school, Nagi forgets a notebook, and as her butler, Hayate goes to the academy to get the notebook. However he arrives at night.... in an area that`s supposed to be haunted!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543120</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73381" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世にも微妙なハイデフレ. ゲームは積まずにプレイしろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World`s Bizarre High Deflation. Don`t Stack Up Games and Play Them</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yo ni mo Bimyou na High Defure. Game wa Tsumazu ni Play Shiro</title>
<summary>The student council trio, Izumi, Miki, and Risa, check in on the Sanzenin Mansion to see what the new butler is like. When they arrive, Miki picks up a controller and, along with the other two, gets pulled into a game world set up by the demon of Nagi`s Famicom!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543122</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73658" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕の命の価値はプライスレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Life is Priceless</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku no Inochi no Kachi wa Priceless</title>
<summary>Hayate, Nagi, Maria, and Sakuya go to the Sanzenin Main House to visit Mikado Sanzenin, the head of the family and Nagi`s grandfather.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543124</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75078" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕らは昔, 宇宙の刑事に若さとは振り向かない事だと教わった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Were Once Taught by the Space Police That Youth is to Not Look Back</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokura wa Mukashi, Uchuu no Keiji ni Wakasa to wa Furimukanai Koto Da to Osowatta</title>
<summary>After recalling his childhood dream, Hayate gets a day off work and takes a walk around the city.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543126</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75079" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏を制する者は受験を制するらしいっすよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Seize the Summer Seize the Application Process</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu o Seisuru Mono wa Juken o Seisuru Rashiissu yo</title>
<summary>Hayate learns that Nagi transferred him to her school, Hakuou Academy. Although Hayate wants to go back to school, he`ll have a hard time when his grades from his old school were on the cutoff line and the transfer exam is tomorrow!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543128</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75097" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちょっとちょっと! パーティー行かなあかんねん. 早よして. ホント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wait a Moment! I Have to Go to the Party. Make It Fast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chotto Chotto! Party Ikana Akannen. Hayayo Shite, Honto</title>
<summary>Nagi, positive Hayate passed his transfer exam, she decides to throw a huge banquet to celebrate.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543130</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75098" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サムライ, ブシドー, 動くヴァンダム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Samurais, Bushido, and Moving Vandams</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samurai, Bushidou, Ugoku Vandam</title>
<summary>It`s morning and Hayate wakes up in a good mood, excited about his first school day with Nagi, which has become a reality thanks to Maria.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543132</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="79929" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">負けてもマケンドー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Won`t Lose Even If I Lose</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makete mo Makendou</title>
<summary>Following the events of the previous episode, Hayate has been challenged to fight Koutarou Azumamiya`s combat butler "Kaede Nonohara", for his disrespect.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543134</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80241" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたのためにメイっぱいナギ倒します♡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Your Sake, I`ll Give My Best Blasting Through Everything</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata no Tame ni Meippai Nagi Taoshimasu</title>
<summary>Nagi has another one of her mangas rejected. She believes that this is due to her lack of experience in life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543136</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80433" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レアカードは水着です</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rare Card is a Swimsuit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rare Card wa Mizugi Desu</title>
<summary>Hayate, Nagi, and their classmates attend an outdoor beach class held on Hakuou Academy`s private island. It`s time for fun in the sun!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543138</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80917" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サキさんのヤボ用(全国版)2007</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Saki-san`s Personal Business (National Ver.) 2007</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saki-san no Yaboyou (Zenkokuhan) 2007</title>
<summary>Wataru`s maid Saki has been feeling worried lately, and refuses to talk about it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543140</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81097" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本は好きですが, 歌え大竜宮城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Like Books, but Sing It, Great Submarine Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hon wa Suki Desuga, Utae Dairyuuguujou</title>
<summary>It`s summer vacation, and Hayate decides to spend this free time trying to create an ultimate attack.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543142</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81239" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピーターさんもいい迷惑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Even Peter-san Has Had Enough</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Peter-san mo Ii Meiwaku</title>
<summary>Hayate and Nagi spend an entire day at an amusement park next to the mansion.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543144</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81365" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カポーンって擬音は誰が考えたんだろう? スゲーよね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who Came Up With the Onomatopoeia "Kapo~n"? It`s Amazing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kapoontte Gion wa Dare ga Kangaetandarou? Sugee yo ne</title>
<summary>Nagi decides to go fishing in the lake with Hayate and Maria.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543146</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81372" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちびっ子ではない天才先生来たる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Not a Kid, Genius Teacher is Here</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chibikko de wa Nai Tensai Sensei Kitaru</title>
<summary>It`s the beginning of the new semester at Hakuou Academy. Hayate is eager to start the new school year, however Nagi has fallen ill and will not be going.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543148</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81399" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モテすぎて困る苦労はしたこと無いなぁ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There are No Common Troubles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motesugite Komaru Kuro wa Shita Kotonaina</title>
<summary>Isumi takes a trip to the mansion, but she seems to have lost her stole.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543150</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82734" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心を揺らして</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shake the Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro o Yurashite</title>
<summary>Because of a misunderstanding from the last episode, Nagi sells off Hayate to Isumi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543152</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82807" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お届けまで29分でしたので, 規定通りの料金でお支払いお願いします...... は, 遠い前世紀の話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Took 29 Minutes to Deliver, So Please Pay the Amount We Had Originally Asked For... Is an Old Myth Now</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otodoke made 29-fun Deshita no de, Kitei Toori no Ryoukin de Oshiharai Onegaishimasu...wa, Tooi Zenseiki no Hanashi</title>
<summary>While running an errand for Nagi, Hayate is attacked by Gilbert piloting a robot.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543154</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82808" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハヤテ大地に立つ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hayate Rises Upon the Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hayate Daichi Tatsu</title>
<summary>Hakuou Academy is having a Butler Battle Tournament, in which first prize is 100 school credits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543156</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82809" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒いハヤテ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Hayate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Hayate</title>
<summary>The Butler Battle Tournament continues.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543158</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84150" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marriage Meeting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miai</title>
<summary>One night, Saki stays over at her parents` home, where her mother suggests for Saki to have a marriage meeting.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543160</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84379" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美人お嬢さま名探偵は見た! 湯けむり女教師殺人事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beautiful Young Lady Saw Great Detective! Case of Murdered Teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bijin Ojou-sama Meitantei wa Mita! Yukemuri Onna Kyoushi Satsujinjikon</title>
<summary>Hayate, Nagi, and Maria all go to a hot spring inn, only to find that Yukiji has been murdered!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543162</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84380" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お金持ちでキレイなお姉さんは好きですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do You Like Rich, Pretty Ladies?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okanemochi de Kirei na Onee-san wa Suki Desuka?</title>
<summary>Sakuya teases Nagi explaining that she is so bratty that she can`t take care of young children. Furious, she asks Hayate to go out and find her kids to take care of.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543164</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84381" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔物ハンターようこそ伊澄, とナベシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome Demon Hunter Isumi, and Nabeshin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamono Hunter Youkoso Isumi, to Nabeshin</title>
<summary>It`s another Butler Battle, and this time it is Hayate vs. Shinichi Watanabe!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543166</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84926" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なぜだ?! 学院文化祭・前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Why?! School Festival - Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naze Da!? Gakuin Bunkasai - Zenpen</title>
<summary>It`s time for Hakuou Academy`s Culture Festival!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543168</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85279" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なぜ死んだ?! 学院文化祭・後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Why Did It Die?! School Festival - Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naze Shinda!? Gakuin Bunkasai - Kouhen</title>
<summary>Hakuou Academy has gone from a cultural festival to a Comiket site in one night!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543170</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85392" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">必見! ナウなヤングのための最新オシャレデートスポット完全ガイド2007秋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Must See! 2007 Autumn Complete Guidebook for the Latest Trendy Date Spots for Teenagers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikken! Nau na Yange no Tame no Saishin Oshare Date Spot Kanzen Guide 2007 Aki</title>
<summary>Close to completing another manga, Nagi sends Hayate out on a mission to locate hot dating spots for teenagers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>558248</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85591" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クラウスは倉臼と書いて日本人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Klaus is Japanese Because the Kanji is "Klaus"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Klaus wa Klaus to Kaite Nihonjin</title>
<summary>Klaus is depressed after Nagi tells him to retire.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>558250</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85592" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">普通の女の子に戻りたい, でもキャラソンは買ってね♥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Go Back to Being a Normal Girl, but Please Buy My Character Song</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futsuu no Onnanoko ni Modoritai, demo Chara Song wa Katte ne</title>
<summary>Nagi asks Hayate about the type of girls he likes. His answer: he likes normal girls.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>557926</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85802" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危うしハヤテ! 機能完全停止!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hayate in Danger! Complete Shut Down!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayaushi Hayate! Kinou Kanzen Teishi!!</title>
<summary>Christmas time is in the atmosphere, meaning that it`s been a whole year since that fateful meeting between Hayate and Nagi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>557928</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85803" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よいこの友達 借金執事万才!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friends of the Well-Behaved. Praise the Debt-Ridden Butler!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoiko no Tomodachi Shakkin Shitsuji Banzai!</title>
<summary>After Hayate stated that if anyone defeats him will get the Sanzenin estate, Hayate decides to quit being Nagi`s butler!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>557930</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85804" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おせちもいいけどハヤテもね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Osechi is Also Good, but Enjoy Hayate, Too</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osesa mo Ii kedo Hayate mo ne</title>
<summary>On New Years Eve, Nagi orders Hayate to bring her to Kujukuri Beach to have a romantic date but he has to take he on a bike.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>557932</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86722" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">RADICAL DREAMERS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Radical Dreamers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Radical Dreamers</title>
<summary>Hayate accidentally travels back in time and meets an even younger and more demanding version of Nagi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569232</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86723" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">春</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haru</title>
<summary>Nagi plans a surprise graduation party for Hayate, but he gets a surprise job offer.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569230</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86724" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クイズ! 宿敵と書いて友と読む!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Quiz! Written as "Rival" and Read as "Friend"!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Quiz! Shukuteki to Kaite Tomo to Yomu!!</title>
<summary>Nagi and Ayumu compete together in the 4256th High School Girls Ultra Quiz tournament for very different reasons.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569228</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86725" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">普通の話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Ordinary Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futsuu no Hanashi</title>
<summary>Izumi, Miki, and Risa invite Hayate and Nagi to their school club which Hayate uses as a way for Nagi to socialize.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569226</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86726" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="8">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒナ♥ラブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hina Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hina Love</title>
<summary>Hinagiku`s upcoming birthday begs the question of how she really feels about Hayate
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569224</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86727" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そりゃ安室には帰れる場所があったでしょうけど...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sure, Amuro Had a Place To Return To, But...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorya Amuro ni wa Kaereru Basho ga Atta de Shou Kedo</title>
<summary>Nagi gives Hayate time off to study and Hayates buttler duties are taken over by a robot called Thirteen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569222</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86728" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奴の名は魔球投手ワタル!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">His Name is Miracle Ball Pitcher, Wataru!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakko no Na wa Makyuu Toushuu Wataru!!!</title>
<summary>Wataru goes to ask Nagi why Isumi is dressed in another high school`s uniform, and finds out that Izumi has fallen for another guy in another high school and attempts to see him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569220</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86729" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二月のマリアさん感謝デー! ですわ♥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The February Day of Gratitude Towards Maria-san!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nigatsu no Maria-san Kansha Day! Desu wa</title>
<summary>Nagi and Hayate decide to treat Maria to a relaxation hotel for all the hard work she has been doing for them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569218</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86730" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">就職率120パーセントの謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mystery Behind the 120% Acceptance Rate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuushokuritsu 120 Percent no Nazo ka</title>
<summary>Nagi completes her new Manga and manages to get it animated - despite her unrealistic demands.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569216</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86731" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポセイドンアドバンスジェネレイターガバス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Poseidon Advance Generator Gavas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Poseidon Advance Generator Gavas</title>
<summary>The Sanzenin group take a ride on Sakuya`s new cruiser, but while on it, terrorists blow a hole in the ship!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569214</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86732" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それは犬と鼠とブルドックのように</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Just Like Dogs, Rats, and Bulldogs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Inu to Nezu to Bulldog no You ni</title>
<summary>Nagi is perplexed by Hayate`s apparent lack of weaknesses and wants to expose them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569212</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86733" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先生さよなら絶望~卒業スペシャルSe</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teacher Goodbye Despair - Graduation Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensei Sayonara Zetsubou: Sotsugyou Special Se</title>
<summary>Yukiji is in a strange mood and the group soon discover why when they find a resignation letter in her bag.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>569210</identifier>
<identifier>hayate-the-combat-butler-season-1-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116919" update="2010-03-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">30s Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125801" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125802" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125803" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125804" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125805" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125806" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
