<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4941" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-06-25</startdate>
<enddate>2001-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Afro-Ken</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アフロ犬</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="433112">A psychedelic trip that will make you find enlightenment and let yourself grow out your hair. Afro/10.

Best watched under the influence.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.san-x.co.jp/afro/afro.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="659" type="Direction">Imanishi Takashi</name>
<name id="8261" type="Music">Kawabe Takehiro</name>
</creators>
<description>Afro-Ken (アフロ犬) is a Japanese character created by the San-X company, which creates other anime-style characters such as Kogepan. He is a dog with a rainbow-coloured afro. He is innocent and blameless and always in a good mood. Afro-Ken is always willing to try new things. Afro-Ken is attracted to objects that look like he does. His hair changes to look like these things as he gets close to them.
There is an Afro-Ken Family Tree with other dog characters who have outrageous names, such as Techno-Ken, Funky-Ken, Lord-Ken, Super Afro-Ken, and Normal-Ken. Unlike the others, Normal-Ken does not have wild hair.
In 2001, Bandai Visual and Sunrise produced a 3DCG OVA adaptation based on the character. The OVA was also broadcast worldwide by the anime satellite television network Animax.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="189">2.10</permanent>
<temporary count="192">4.52</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>157213.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8456</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2796</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.san-x.co.jp/afro/afro.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アフロ犬</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234254</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4664</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3671" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>footage reuse</name>
<description>Footage reuse is the employment of a sequence of frames many times, generally as a side effect of a constrained anime production budget. This can happen by using the same footage once at a time, but many times over the course of the show, or by directly looping it. Types of scenes that tend to get reused include: transformations, such as those typical of superheroes or magical girls, characters that change into powered-up versions of themselves, or robots changing shape; attacks, especially when involving a series of steps that must be followed before the attack can be launched; and any kind of action that involves repeating the same movement.
This tag does not apply if the footage changes significantly between iterations. An example of that is the infamous Endless Eight arc of http://anidb.net/a6367 [the 2009 iteration of Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu]; even as the plot repeated itself, each episode of the arc showed it in different ways.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="66426" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-12-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフロ犬の基礎講座 / アフロのお勉強 (初級) / アフロな食卓 / 信じれば不可能も可能になる / 先祖 / 危機一髪! / サッパリ! / アフロな晩酌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Afro-ken no Kiso Kouza / Afro no Obenkyou (Shokyuu) / Afro na Shokutaku / Shinjireba Fukanou mo Kanou ni Naru / Senzo / Kikiippatsu! / Sappari! / Afro na Banshaku</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
