<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="496" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-08-01</startdate>
<enddate>1998-08-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shin Kidou Senki Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz Tokubetsu Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mobile Suit Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Mobile Suit Gundam Wing - Le film</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">기동전사 건담 Wing: Endless Waltz Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shin Kidou Senki Gundam W: Endless Waltz Gekijouban</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">高达W剧场版: 无尽的华尔兹</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新機動戦記ガンダムW[ウイング] Endless Waltz -特別篇-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam Wing - Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam Wing The Movie: Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">กันดั้มวิง เอนเลสวอลซ์</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="229" type="Prequel">Shin Kidou Senki Gundam Wing</anime>
<anime id="908" type="Full Story">Gundam-W: Endless Waltz</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.gundam.channel.or.jp/program/_gw_movie.shtml</url>
<creators>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="1761" type="Character Design">Murase Shuukou</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
<name id="5680" type="Direction">Aoki Yasunao</name>
</creators>
<description>At the climax of the Eve Wars, on December 24 of the year AC 195, the armies of the World Nation and White Fang met in a ferocious battle. World Nation leader Treize Khushrenada was slain, White Fang leader http://anidb.net/ch2857 [Zechs Merquise] disappeared, and Earth was saved from destruction by the intervention of the five Gundam pilots. Having witnessed the consequences of war and hatred, the people of Earth and the space colonies put aside their differences and together founded a new world government. Under this newly-formed Earth Sphere Unified Nation, a year has passed in peace. The government and the populace have disarmed themselves, and almost every remaining mobile suit has been destroyed. Deciding to follow suit, Gundam pilots http://anidb.net/ch2851 [Heero Yuy], http://anidb.net/ch2853 [Duo Maxwell], http://anidb.net/ch2854 [Trowa Barton], and http://anidb.net/ch2855 [Quatre Rabarba Winner] place their mighty mobile suits inside an asteroid and send them on a one-way voyage into the sun. But even as they bid their Gundams farewell, a new conflict is drawing near.
Note: This movie is a compilation of the 3 OVA episodes with approximately 8 minutes of additional footage and a slightly changed music soundtrack.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1702">6.46</permanent>
<temporary count="1718">7.56</temporary>
<review count="2">8.75</review>
</ratings>
<picture>149067.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2358</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2273</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2508</identifier>
<identifier>vwxbby</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gundam.channel.or.jp/program/_gw_movie.shtml</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>799</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>153650</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1713</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-wing-endless-waltz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2764" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>space colony</name>
<description>The human race (or possibly some alien race) has mastered space travel and founded at least one colony either in space, on a moon or another planet. This usually also includes colony-life episodes that not only show the technical staff of professionals (astronauts, scientists, etc.), but also their families (i.e. children).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3779" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-06">
<name>fight for peace</name>
<description>Don`t they all... 
The protagonists are trying to ensure long-lasting peace by fighting a vicious enemy, hoping to defeat the threat permanently.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3852" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>Bright slap</name>
<description>"You hit me! Not even my father ever hit me!" 
You are the commander of a spaceship, leader of a faction or a team and your best mecha pilot stops fighting and grows increasingly hysterical and angsty, while the enemy could strike you at any time. What are you going to do? 
You slap or punch him, preferably in the face, and back to his senses while delivering a heroic speech that would turn any wimp into a man of destiny.
Named after Bright Noa of Mobile Suit Gundam, a prominent user of this for-sure method.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2851" type="main character in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="41">6.10</rating>
<name>Heero Yuy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This mysterious youth was sent from the L1 space colony cluster to fight against Oz. He goes by the alias Heero Yuy, after the martyred leader of the space colonies; his real name, like almost everything else about him, is unknown. Heero has been trained since childhood for his role as pilot of the Wing Gundam, an upbringing that has made him cold and ruthless. But thanks to his years of training, Heero has become a perfect soldier equally skilled in personal combat, explosives, and computer hacking.</description>
<picture>72625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2852" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="39">5.63</rating>
<name>Relena Darlian</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Relena is the pampered daughter of the Earth Alliance`s vice minister for foreign affairs. Her father is responsible for the negotiations with the space colonists, an assignment which leaves Mr. Darlian little time for his wife and child. Her family`s wealth and status make Relena the star of her private school`s social scene, but do little to reduce her boredom and loneliness. When her quiet existence is disrupted by the Gundam pilots, this poor little rich girl discovers her own, previously untapped, reserves of strength and courage.</description>
<picture>72617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2853" type="main character in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="21">7.05</rating>
<name>Duo Maxwell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Duo is a member of the scavenger organisation known as the Sweeper Group, which sent him to Earth to battle Oz. Despite the hardships he`s suffered in his young life, and the seriousness of his mission, Duo is always cheerful and good-natured. But when he goes into battle as pilot of the Gundam Deathscythe, striking from the shadows with its lethal beam scythe, he truly earns his nickname "God of Death."</description>
<picture>72899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2854" type="main character in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="13">2.24</rating>
<name>Trowa Barton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most mysterious of the Gundam pilots, the young man who calls himself Trowa was sent to Earth as the pilot of the Gundam Heavyarms. The cool, quiet Trowa has nerves of steel and superb reflexes, qualities which serve him well in his cover identity as an acrobatic clown in a traveling circus troupe. He also has soldiering experience far beyond his years. When combined with his heavily-armed Gundam, Trowa`s tactical skill and combat ability make him a veritable one-man army.</description>
<picture>72900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2855" type="main character in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="14">4.45</rating>
<name>Quatre Rabarba Winner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quatre is a young aristocrat, the thirtieth child - and only son - of a wealthy family of space colony developers. Though he`s the most tender-hearted and gentle of the Gundam pilots, Quatre is just as brave and determined, and has defied his family`s wishes in order to join the battle against Oz. Quatre is aided by a troop of forty loyal underlings and can draw on the Winner family`s vast resources, assets which more than make up for his relative lack of fighting skill.</description>
<picture>72932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2856" type="main character in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="8">2.57</rating>
<name>Chang Wufei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wufei is the descendant of a legendary Chinese warrior clan, who sent him to Earth to fight against Oz. This proud fighter lives by a strict code of honour, punishing evil and enforcing justice as he sees fit. Wufei prefers to operate solo, since he has little patience for lesser warriors. These high standards make him equally contemptuous of his own failings in battle. The only ally he trusts is his Shenlong Gundam, which he has nicknamed "Nataku" after a hero of Chinese mythology.</description>
<picture>72933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2219" picture="23794.jpg">Ishino Ryuuzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2857" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="13">7.74</rating>
<name>Zechs Merquise</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This masked warrior is Oz`s top mobile suit pilot. Up until now, Oz has disguised itself as the Earth Federation`s elite "Specials" taskforce, and Zechs has accumulated numerous distinctions during his career in the Specials. He earned the highest marks in the history of the Lake Victoria military academy, received the first two-rank promotion in the history of the Specials, and acquired the nickname "Lightning Baron" for his exploits. Zechs` accomplishments have made him a hero among Oz`s soldiers, but this master soldier is cunning enough not to overestimate his own abilities or underestimate those of his enemies.</description>
<picture>72934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2858" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="20">7.41</rating>
<name>Lucrezia Noin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noin is a good friend of Zechs from his days at the Lake Victoria military academy. After graduation, she joined the academy`s staff, and now trains new Specials recruits in the art of space combat. Though Noin is a formidable mobile suit pilot, she doesn`t much care for fighting, and she often uses her influence with Oz`s leader to try to resolve crisis situations peacefully.</description>
<picture>72939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="491" picture="38232.jpg">Yokoyama Chisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2860" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="28">4.84</rating>
<name>Lady Une</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lady Une is Treize`s loyal aide and agent, whom he often assigns to assassinate enemies or command important field operations. While she is passionately devoted to Treize, Lady Une shows no mercy to her master`s foes, and is infamous for her overzealous cruelty. One day she`s demurely running water for Treize`s bath, the next she`s bombing diplomats or threatening to attack unarmed space colonies. You`d almost think she had some kind of split personality..</description>
<picture>72961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2221" picture="83141.jpg">Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2861" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="13">4.63</rating>
<name>Sally Po</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sally is a honest and well-meaning young officer, assigned to the Earth Alliance`s intelligence bureau. She captures Heero early in the story, and is intrigued by the mysterious young Gundam pilot. She will reappear later in the story, and encounter Heero and his friends again...</description>
<picture>72962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2862" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<name>Rashid Kurama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the Maganac Corps, the large, bearded Rashid is one of Quatre`s best friends and allies. Above all else, he values his teammates` lives and treats each of them as family.</description>
<picture>18496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42809" picture="223789.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2863" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="8">4.62</rating>
<name>Dorothy Catalonia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The granddaughter of Duke Dermail and daughter of former OZ leader General Catalonia, Dorothy first appears masquerading as an ordinary student at the school Relena runs in the Sanc Kingdom. Though she says she admires Relena, she holds many opposite beliefs, such as her belief that war is an essential part of humanity and will never go away.</description>
<picture>72964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2864" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="22">5.95</rating>
<name>Catherine Bloom</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A talented acrobat and knife-thrower, Catherine is the star performer of Trowa`s circus troupe. At first, she finds Trowa somewhat creepy, but she eventually warms up to her clown comrade and ultimately comes to think of him as a surrogate little brother.</description>
<picture>72966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2222" picture="25843.jpg">Suzuki Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2867" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Doctor J</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The engineer and creator of Wing Gundam and Heero`s mentor, he is an expert in the field of beam weaponry. His distinguishing features include mechanical-looking goggles and a cybernetic right arm. Quirky but affable, Doctor J is immensely proud of Heero`s abilities and encourages the young man to choose his own fate, including protecting Darlian and rejecting Operation Meteor. It was J who chose Heero`s codename, which he thinks is highly appropriate.</description>
<picture>72977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2868" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<name>Professor G</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The engineer and creator of Deathscythe, as well as co-creator of the spaceship Peacemillion and Duo`s mentor. He is distinguished by his long nose, mushroom-shaped hair and a long scar on his cheek. Sardonic and, like Doctor J, rather eccentric, he tends to describe Deathscythe as "the ultimate work of art", perhaps due to his specialization in stealth systems. A member of the Sweeper group, he was impressed by Duo cracking his security codes and offered to train him as a Gundam pilot.</description>
<picture>72979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3135" picture="24120.jpg">Fujimoto Yuzuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2869" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<name>Doktor S</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The engineer and creator of Heavyarms. Distinguished by his prosthetic nose and spiked gray hair. He was opposed to Operation Meteor, but Heavyarms` assigned pilot, Trowa Barton was prepared to double cross S to his father Dekim.</description>
<picture>72980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3223" picture="88844.jpg">Ootaki Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2870" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<name>H Kyouju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The engineer and creator of Sandrock and Quatre`s mentor. He is rather fat, with a receding hairline and a thin, dark mustache that stands straight out at each end. A worker at MO-III, he originally met Quatre when the young heir`s shuttle was hijacked by the Maganac Corps. After learning of the youth`s strength and resolve, he ended up taking a job as Quatre`s tutor while borrowing Winner family resources to build Sandrock.</description>
<picture>72988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27206" picture="73948.jpg">Taguchi Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38039" type="appears in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>Roushi O</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roushi O is the engineer and creator of Shenlong and Wufei`s mentor. Of imposing stature and spear-bald, the powerful and athletic Roushi O is an expert in many forms of martial arts, a skill he brings to the mobile suits he creates.</description>
<picture>72668.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38048" type="appears in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>OZ-06MS Leo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>OZ-06MS Leo is a mass produced general purpose mobile suit in the After Colony timeline. The unit is featured in Mobile Suit Gundam Wing.</description>
<picture>72758.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38054" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-23">
<rating votes="1">2.31</rating>
<name>Abdul</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Abdul is the second in command of the Maganac Corps in Mobile Suit Gundam Wing. He always wears a pair of small black sunglasses. His custom suit has very large and unique shoulder pads that contain powerful thruster engines and uses a long-range cannon that mounts over the left arm.</description>
<picture>72816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38055" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>Akhmad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akhmad is the 3rd in command of the Maganac Corps in the series Mobile Suit Gundam Wing. While he is quieter than many of his comrades, he is still just as good a pilot. He is a little shorter than Abdul and Auda, but wears a bushy mustache. His Maganac suit utilizes a considerable amount of extra armor including heavier shoulder and skirt armor.</description>
<picture>72836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38056" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>Auda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Auda is a member of the Maganac Corps in Mobile Suit Gundam Wing. He pilots what is perhaps the most unique of the Maganac mobile suits, utilizing a massive left arm with a powerful claw designed to severely damage enemy mobile suits in close range combat.</description>
<picture>72837.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38057" type="appears in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>OZ-12SMS Taurus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>OZ-12SMS Taurus is a mass produced space-combat mobile suit in the After Colony time-line. It is featured in Mobile Suit Gundam Wing, Mobile Suit Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz OVA/movie, and several related mangas. The mobile suit was designed by Hajime Katoki.</description>
<picture>72840.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38058" type="appears in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="7">5.13</rating>
<name>Hilde Schbeiker</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hilde Schbeiker is a fictional character from the Anime series Mobile Suit Gundam Wing.</description>
<picture>72842.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38061" type="appears in" update="2011-10-24">
<name>OZ-02MD Virgo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>OZ-02MD Virgo (aka Virgo) is a mass produced A.I. controlled ground mobile suit in the After Colony time-line. It is featured in Mobile Suit Gundam Wing.</description>
<picture>72880.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38062" type="appears in" update="2011-10-24">
<name>WF-02MD Virgo II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>WF-02MD (OZ-03MD) Virgo II (aka Virgo II) is a mass produced A.I. controlled space mobile suit and successor unit to the OZ-02MD Virgo in the After Colony time-line. It is featured in Mobile Suit Gundam Wing.</description>
<picture>72881.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38064" type="appears in" update="2011-10-24">
<name>Libra</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Libra was a giant space battleship commissioned and built by OZ and designed by the five scientists who created the Gundams. In form, Libra resembles five geometric diamonds, four of which are connected to a corner of the fifth in the center. Its name is derived from the Zodiac constellation Libra.</description>
<picture>72888.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39042" type="appears in" update="2011-11-26">
<name>Danchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77621.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39139" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<rating votes="8">6.84</rating>
<name>XXXG-00W0 Wing Gundam-0</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77782.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39140" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>XXXG-01D2 Gundam Deathscythe Hell</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77783.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39141" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>XXXG-01H2 Gundam Heavyarms Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77784.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39142" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>XXXG-01SR2 Gundam Sandrock Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77785.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39143" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>XXXG-01S2 Altron Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77786.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39144" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>OZ-00MS2B Tallgeese III</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77787.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39145" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>MMS-01 Serpent</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77788.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39146" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-29">
<rating votes="6">5.72</rating>
<name>Mariemaia Khushrenada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young child, Mariemaia is apparently the daughter of Leia Barton and Treize Khushrenada, conceived during the meeting between the two on Colony X-18999 (as detailed in the Episode Zero manga). Supposedly dying at an early age, Mariemaia later resurfaced as the figurehead of the Mariemaia Army, which largely consisted of soldiers who had been loyal to Treize. Thanks to her grandfather Dekim`s grooming, she was fully prepared to ravage the Earth and take her place as the World Sovereign, believing this to be what her father, Treize, would have wanted. She continued believing this until Relena slapped some sense into her-- literally. When Lady Une explained to the young girl that Dekim`s goals were not the same as Treize`s, Mariemaia realized her mistake and jumped in front of Relena to save her from being killed by Mariemaia`s enraged grandfather, resulting in Mariemaia being shot through the spine. She was given medical attention, and is later shown (in a wheelchair, though later appearances show her to have healed) visiting her father`s grave with Lady Une.</description>
<picture>77789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39147" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>Dekim Barton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Once one of Heero Yuy`s top aides, Dekim was present when the colonial leader was assassinated. From that moment on, he began plotting his revenge. However, even after he killed Odin Lowe (the man who shot Yuy), Dekim was not satisfied; he was convinced that the only way to make things equal after the decades of colonial oppression was for the colonies to take over the Earth Sphere, with the Barton family as the ruling family. To that end, he tracked down five of the engineers who had created the Tallgeese and commissioned them to create the Gundams for use with his ultimate plan: Operation Meteor. The original plan entailed dropping colonies onto Earth at strategic locations, and using the Gundams to take control in the ensuing chaos. For Dekim, the scientists and their young pilots didn`t agree with this plan, and stole the Gundams, using them instead to fight for the colonies` independence without resorting to genocide. Infuriated, Dekim began working out a new version of Operation Meteor. Using the Serpent mobile suit left behind by OZ, and the fact that his daughter Leia supposedly had a child with Treize Khushrenada, Dekim launched another Operation Meteor on Christmas Eve AC 196. However, his plan began to crumble once again, thanks to the intervention of the Gundam pilots (and later the common people themselves). Attempting to kill Relena Darlian, Dekim shot Mariemaia when she ran in front of Relena to protect her, then was himself shot in the head and killed by one of his soldiers, who immediately apologized to Treize for betraying his vision.</description>
<picture>77791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3281" picture="154160.jpg">Yoda Eisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39346" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Long Shirin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The head of the Long Clan and formal leader of colony A02026. His granddaughter Meilan was married to Chang Wufei, making him related to the future Gundam pilot in a way. When Operation Meteor`s true form was revealed, it was planned for A02026 to be the colony dropped on the Earth, an action that Wufei greatly opposed. Before the brash young man could leave, Shirin gave him the clan`s heirloom, a jade statue of their guardian, the two-headed dragon Altron, to sell for supplies. In the series, Wufei returns to the colony after receiving Altron Gundam to rediscover his purpose. When OZ attacked A02026 to root out the Gundam, Shirin activates the colony`s self destruct system to keep his people out of OZ`s hands, and to give Wufei a reminder of what he`s fighting for.</description>
<picture>78043.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39438" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-08">
<name>Trowa Barton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The original Trowa Barton was the spoiled son of Dekim, used to getting anything he wanted. Originally scheduled to be the pilot of the Heavyarms, he was furious when he learned that Doktor S and the other engineers didn`t agree with Operation Meteor. As he prepared to tell his father of their "betrayal", Trowa was shot in the back by a mechanic who feared for his family`s safety on Earth, and died. At that point, a nameless engineer offered to take over for the dead man, and the new Trowa Barton was born. It is known that the original Trowa was apparently willing to tell No-Name about his sister`s daughter, Mariemaia, and how she would be ruling the world after Operation Meteor, but this appears mainly to have been boasting rather than true friendship or closeness. If Mariemaia is truly Treize Khushrenada`s daughter with Leia Barton, it can be assumed that the real Trowa Barton is Mariemaia`s uncle by blood.</description>
<picture>78171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5541" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>1998-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>732801</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-wing-endless-waltz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="9779" update="2010-04-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1998-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9780" update="2010-04-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1998-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116267" update="2010-02-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133987" update="2011-10-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
