<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4968" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Koutetsu Sangokushi</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">钢铁三国志</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">KouSan</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">鋼鉄三国志</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.nasinc.co.jp/jp/koutetsu-sangokushi/</url>
<creators>
<name id="969" type="Animation Work">Picture Magic</name>
<name id="1465" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Natsuko</name>
<name id="5737" type="Chief Direction">Endou Tetsuya</name>
<name id="6054" type="Character Design">Okano Yukio</name>
<name id="6054" type="Chief Animation Direction">Okano Yukio</name>
<name id="6187" type="Direction">Saga Satoshi</name>
<name id="9620" type="Character Design">Hashimoto Kouichi</name>
<name id="9620" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hashimoto Kouichi</name>
<name id="9729" type="Character Design">Tsukamoto Chiyomi</name>
<name id="9729" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tsukamoto Chiyomi</name>
<name id="7098" type="Music">Toriyama Yuuji</name>
</creators>
<description>The Imperial Seal has been passed down through the generations since ancient times. It confers great power unto the warriors that it chooses. This is the story of those warriors.
It is a time of chaos and of civil war. It is a time when great armies clash in titanic battles and great heroes carve their names in history. It is also a time of death and destruction, when the people of the land live in constant fear of the sword. Onto this stage steps the reluctant Rikuson (Lu Xun), whose family had been the guardians of the Imperial Seal up until it was stolen by Sonsaku. At the behest of his mentor Rikuson offers his services to Sonsaku with the intention of confirming the will of the Imperial Seal. However, assassins strike down Sonsaku and the Imperial Seal is lost. So begins, Rikuson`s journey to recover the Imperial Seal and discover his destiny.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="465">2.46</permanent>
<temporary count="478">5.67</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>11741.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7513</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8304</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2162</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4042</identifier>
<identifier>gzcnpt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nasinc.co.jp/jp/koutetsu-sangokushi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kōtetsu_Sangokushi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>鋼鉄三国志</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1152</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327428</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8911</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4399" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>Three Kingdoms</name>
<description>Chinese names to the likes of Liu Bei, Guan Yu, Zhang Fei, Cao Cao, Sun Jian, as well as their allies, enemies and subordinates are used or referenced amongst primary and secondary characters.
The use of these names commonly portray the characters as they were historically as warlords and soldiers from the ancient Chinese novel or as foreshadowing to which characters are destined to be allies or enemies.
Certain characters are often glorified above others in relevance or conflict with the original novel (as to follow historically or just provide entertainment with the use of historical figures and events using fictional scenarios).
The supposed historical novel itself was written in the 14th century by Luo Guanzhong of China and is based upon events in the turbulent years near the end of the Han Dynasty and the Three Kingdoms era of China, starting in 169 and ending in 280.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30147" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<name>Sousou Moutoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3270" picture="30153.jpg">Mitsuya Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30148" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="4">7.36</rating>
<name>Shokatsuryou Koumei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31915" type="main character in" update="2011-05-05">
<name>Rikuson Hakugen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31916" type="main character in" update="2011-05-05">
<name>Ryoutou Kouseki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31917" type="main character in" update="2011-05-05">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Taishiji Shigi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31918" type="main character in" update="2011-05-05">
<name>Ryomou Shimei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31919" type="main character in" update="2011-05-05">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Kannei Kouha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31920" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-05">
<name>Shokatsukin Shiyu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31921" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-05">
<name>Sonken Chuubou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31922" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-05">
<name>Sonsaku Hakufu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31923" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="1">2.26</rating>
<name>Shuuyu Koukin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31924" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-05">
<name>Ryousou Kouketsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31925" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<name>Kouso Genyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31926" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Ryuubi Gentoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31927" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<name>Chouun Shiryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31928" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Chouhi Ekitoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31929" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<name>Roshuku Shikei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31930" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<name>Soujin Shikou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2230" picture="21782.jpg">Iwasaki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31931" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<name>Chouryou Bun`en</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31932" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<name>Choushou Shifu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11009" picture="39517.jpg">Miyazawa Tadashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31933" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Kan`u Unchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31934" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<name>Kougai Koufuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31935" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<name>Shuutai Youhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="71789" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">在野の孔明, 深紅の陸遜を江東に放つ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Koumei who Stands in Opposition, the Freeing of Rikuson the Crimson at Koutou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71901" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彷徨える陸遜, 呉の都に孫権を見出す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rikuson at a Loss, his Discovery of Sonken in Go`s Capital</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71902" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">若き志士ども, 江東の大地に集結す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assemble at Koutou`s lands, young patriots</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71903" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">隻眼の勇者, 戦士の道を凌統に託す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The one-eyed hero entrusts Ryoutou with the principles of a warrior</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72101" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘆きの凌統, 仇敵を求めて咆哮す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A grieving Ryoutou roars in agony as he hunts down a bitter enemy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72102" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鈴の甘寧, 悲しき一矢を戦場に射る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In his sorrow, Kannei of Suzu shoots an arrow into the battlefield</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72103" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">惑いし陸遜, 師との再会に光を見る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A bewildered Rikuson sees the light in a reunion with his teacher</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72104" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">諸葛孔明, 論を以て呉の孫権を動かす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shokatsuryou Koumei inspires Sonken of Go with his idea</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72105" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">若武者集いて, 江東の山河に己を磨く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The young warriors assemble at Koutou`s hills and rivers for training</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72106" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">曹孟徳, 赤き壁を駆りて孫呉へ迫る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sou Moutoku pushes a red wall, drawing near Son Go</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75133" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">呉の六駿, 夜明けの長江に紅く煌く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go`s Six Steeds cause the dawn over Choukou to gleam red</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75134" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">知略と鬼略, 妖しき笛の音湖畔に木霊す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ingenuity and cunning, the sound of the ominous flute reverberates across the lake shore</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75135" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">美周郎, 戦野に立ちて陸遜を導く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bi Shuurou stands upon the battlefield to guide Rikuson</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75136" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">孫呉の慟哭, 六駿鎮魂に揺らめく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The wail of Son Go wavers from repose offered by the Six Steeds</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80386" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">憂いし陸遜, 孫権の微笑に再起を誓す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gloomy Rikuson vows to recover with Sonken`s smile</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80387" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">関羽の咆哮, 陸遜を撃ちて覚悟を迫る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kan`u`s roar strikes Rikuson which forces him to hold determination</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80388" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">草庵の再会, 師弟の深縁益州に交叉す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">reunion at the thatched hut, the deep connection between masted and disciple, wedged together in Ekishuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80389" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">桃園の義兄弟, 蜀の山野にて絆の花を見る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The sworn brothers of the peach garden see the flower of ties in the fields and mountains of Shoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80390" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛き太史慈, 中原の大地に仁王立つ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Courageous Taishiji stands tall on the earth of the Central Plains</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80391" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">呉下の阿蒙, 若き智を用いてその身を起こす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amou of Go rises from obscurity by using his young wisdom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81601" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">江陵の落日, 武人の魂を侵奪す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kouryou`s setting sun seiyes a warrior`s soul</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81602" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">劉備乱心, 凍てつく陰となりて江東を彷徨う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ryuubi goes insane and becomes a frozen shadow, wandering in Koutou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81603" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪原の孫仲謀, 陸遜に従いて故国を脱す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Son Chuubou, in the snowfield, follows Rikuson to escape from his homeland</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81604" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">劉備の落涙, 新たな光明を野に示す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ryuubi`s weeping gives a new light to the field</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81605" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">陸伯言, 紅き星落つ五丈原に舞う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Riku Hakugen dances on Gojougen where red stars are falling</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97262" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">深紅の魂, 生ける志士どもを走らす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crimson Soul, Dispatch the Living Patriot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkou no Tamashii, Ikeru Shishi-domo o Hashirasu</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
