<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5016" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>1991-11-21</startdate>
<enddate>1991-12-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Eiyuu Gaiden Mozaicka</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">えいゆうがいでんモザイカ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">モザイカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Mozaika</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Mozaicka</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">英雄凱伝モザイカ</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mozaika</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="661" type="Character Design">Shioyama Norio</name>
<name id="661" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shioyama Norio</name>
<name id="2703" type="Music">Wada Kaoru</name>
<name id="661" type="Original Work">Shioyama Norio</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="660" type="Direction">Takahashi Ryousuke</name>
</creators>
<description>From Ryosuke Takahashi and Norio Shioyama, the creative minds behind great animes such as Armored Trooper VOTOMs and Panzer World Galient, comes an epic tale of swords and sorcery!
On the eternal planet of Mozaika, the formerly benevolent King Sazara has been possessed by an evil priest and has begun a bloody path of conquest all across the world! Mozaika`s only hope is the young warrior U-Taruma, son of U-Dante, one of Sazara`s victims.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="73">5.16</permanent>
<temporary count="73">5.66</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238319.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7266</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8855</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3250</identifier>
<identifier>kugloo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>英雄凱伝モザイカ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88542</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2792</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3611" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-12-06">
<name>evil empire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="42258" type="main character in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>U-Taruma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42259" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<name>Moruka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9443" picture="34858.jpg">Kamiyama Takuzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42260" type="appears in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Durahan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3371" picture="24398.jpg">Nakamura Shuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42261" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<name>Kaze</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3371" picture="24398.jpg">Nakamura Shuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42262" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Menoza</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42263" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>King Sazara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4959" picture="28509.jpg">Nakata Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42264" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Karumaharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3298" picture="151659.jpg">Katou Seizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42265" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">9.39</rating>
<name>Dera</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42266" type="appears in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>U-Dante</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3239" picture="225574.jpg">Ito Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42267" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Jeika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42268" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Valkina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42269" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Maisha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83328.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42270" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Ro Tamago</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3059" picture="203228.jpg">Miyauchi Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42271" type="appears in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>Da Zorin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="418" picture="17270.jpg">Hirose Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42272" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="1">9.39</rating>
<name>Ritish</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83332.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="201" picture="17016.jpg">Nagai Ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="67607" update="2010-07-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">封谷の章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Book of the Sealed Valley</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuukoku no Shou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67608" update="2010-07-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔蓋城の章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Book of the Magai Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magaijou no Shou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67609" update="2010-07-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">老卵の章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Book of the Ancient Egg</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rouran no Shou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67610" update="2010-07-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼の章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Book of Demons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oni no Shou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
