<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5023" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-07-04</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Code-E</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Код-Е</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Код-Е</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">代号E</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">CODE-E</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5870" type="Sequel">Mission-E</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9394" approval="14" total="18">Kotoura-san</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="271364">Solid start with a good concept that just fizzled out about halfway through.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="321417">I Liked The Idea behind this Anime BUT in this Anime NO MAJOR HAPPENING Happens, Leaving you Wanting for More,&lt;br /&gt;And The Ending is Also Disappointing (I`m not saying it`s not good but,... Well I just can`t bring myself to like it).</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/code-e/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1477" type="Direction">Katou Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="1785" type="Original Plan">Sakaki Ichirou</name>
<name id="3557" type="Series Composition">Satou Takuya</name>
<name id="1019" type="Work">Nagoya TV Housou</name>
<name id="3191" type="Character Design">Saitou Tetsuhito</name>
<name id="3191" type="Chief Animation Direction">Saitou Tetsuhito</name>
<name id="5742" type="Music">Kano Caoli</name>
<name id="16956" type="Original Work">Sasahara Kaede</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
</creators>
<description>* Original concept and script by http://anidb.net/cr1785 [Sakaki Ichirou].
Twenty years from now, in early summer in Amizawa Village... the 18-year-old http://anidb.net/ch6360 [Ebihara Chinami] emits electrical waves when she becomes distressed. Due to this, she cannot use electronics such as PCs and cellphones very well. Her power is so strong that it nearly crashed the plane her family was on by causing instrument malfunctions. Her power also leads her to transfer schools frequently. As usual, on the first day of school, Chinami is a little nervous, causing her classmates` cellphones to glitch and electronics to react to her.
The more nervous she becomes, the worse the situation gets, so she begins to take notes on where and how badly the electronics react to her. She eventually meets http://anidb.net/ch6361 [Koutarou] from the science club, who is interested in understanding her power; http://anidb.net/ch6363 [Yuma], a classmate and shrine maiden with the same power; and http://anidb.net/ch6362 [Sonomi]. They refer to the power as Type-E.
What they do not know is that a secret organization is after Chinami`s power...
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="885">3.84</permanent>
<temporary count="893">6.42</temporary>
<review count="1">3.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>12068.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7617</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2564</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4002</identifier>
<identifier>ddthdj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/code-e/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Code-E</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>CODE-E</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327718</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9152</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2402" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-09">
<name>archery</name>
<description>Archery is the art, practice, or skill of shooting arrows with the use of a bow, from Latin arcus. A person who participates in archery is typically known as an archer.
While archery has been historically used for hunting, both for food and later, in a use that survives to this day, also as a sport, through most of pre-gunpowder human history its main use was for combat; archers were extremely important in warfare, in open field and siege alike, due to their ability to massively kill enemy armies with literal rains of arrows and to set things aflame with burning arrowheads. Proper easy of burning arrowheads could destroy the morale of an invading infantry division or set the entire defending fortress on fire, while non-burning arrowheads could destroy a large portion of the enemy infantry before it could even enter melee combat. Such was the destruction ability of archers that horse archers were the backbone of the both the Hun and Mongol hordes; the former brought terror to and helped the eventual demise of the Roman Empire, while the latter conquered such a large portion of Eurasia that historians coined the term Pax Mongolica (paralleling the Pax Romana) to describe their empire that at its apex spanned from modern-day Poland to the Middle East to Southern China, Korea and the southern parts of Russia.
With the discovery of gunpowder and the invention of firearms, archery was quickly rendered obsolete in warfare. Early firearms were not good in comparison to good archers, with drawbacks such as a vastly inferior rate of fire and high susceptibility to wet weather; nevertheless, they had longer effective range and, most importantly, required almost no practice to use properly in comparison to the many years that it took to train an archer; indeed, a popular saying used to go that "to make a good archer, one must start with his grandfather". Nevertheless, in the Far East archery is to this day considered an important subject in the studies of martial arts, and some Japanese schools have archery dojos ran by archery clubs. Additionally, archery saw an 18th century reemergence as a recreational activity in the West, becoming relevant as an elite class sport, specially for hunting but also at non-living targets, and eventually also becoming an Olympic competition.</description>
<picurl>145640.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3237" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-16">
<name>test of courage</name>
<description>As part of a summer excursion or festival, an anime with school setting may also have a test of courage (or kimodameshi in Japanese), where the male and female students are paired up (by lottery) to retrieve a "charm" by passing though a "haunted house" or a scary forest at night.
The teachers usually disguise themselves as monsters or ghosts, scaring the students out of their socks.
This seems to be some sort of Japanese "coming of age" ritual, providing a certain level of excitement under controlled and safe circumstances.
Frequently seen in the Festival Episode.</description>
<picurl>38866.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4009" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-20">
<name>unresolved romance</name>
<description>At the end of the series the main character — even though involved in one or more romances — does not choose and thus resolve the situation.
Usually emotionally very disappointing for the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5788" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-03">
<name>experiments</name>
<description>Involves (para-)scientific experiments.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6360" type="main character in" update="2009-04-20">
<rating votes="4">4.52</rating>
<name>Ebihara Chinami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A clumsy 17 year old girl, who likes to read and do gardening. She has a mysterious ability to emit electromagnetic waves from her body when her emotions run high. This ability forces her to be unable to use electronic equipment of any kind. When the story begins, she had recently moved into town, and catches the attention of Kannagi Koutaro, an eccentric genius in her class. As the story progresses, she develops feelings for Kotarou and eventually ends up dating him.</description>
<picture>23664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="602" picture="79633.jpg">Hashimoto Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6361" type="main character in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="2">2.95</rating>
<name>Kannagi Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An absent minded genius in Ebihara Chinami`s class. He is the head and only member in the Science Research club, and can always be found in the club room. At first he notices Ebihara Chinami`s abilities and pressures her to allow him to study them. Eventually through a series of comic misunderstandings he comes to realise that he has feelings for Ebihara Chinami.</description>
<picture>23665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2027" picture="21353.jpg">Nomura Katsuhito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6362" type="main character in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="4">4.52</rating>
<name>Kujou Sonomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kotarou`s childhood friend who is in love with him. She is very jealous of how Kotarou worries about Chinami and often misunderstands the situation. She is also very wealthy and sometimes can be found helping Kotarou with Chinami.</description>
<picture>23666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6363" type="main character in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="5">4.27</rating>
<name>Saihashi Yuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A miko who lives at the shrine. She is a lone wolf who distances herself from others and refrains from making friends. During her free time, she gives massages to the elders in the neighbourhood but refuses their gifts. Like Chinami, she can emit electromagnetic waves. Her power is not as strong as Chinami`s but she can control it better. Yuma looks out for Chinami and warns her of potential danger.</description>
<picture>23667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="613" picture="155849.jpg">Mizuno Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6364" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="8">4.97</rating>
<name>Komatsuna Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keiko Komatsuna sits in the seat in front of Chinami during class. She is Chinami`s first friend after she transferred to the new school.</description>
<picture>23668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="327" picture="17472.jpg">Momoi Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6365" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-20">
<rating votes="4">1.99</rating>
<name>Ebihara Keisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chinami`s father and works at home as a writer. He is often worried about Chinami, especially when it comes to boys.</description>
<picture>23669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2405" picture="23217.jpg">Shioya Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6366" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-20">
<rating votes="4">5.13</rating>
<name>Ebihara Mitsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chinami`s mother and businesswoman.</description>
<picture>23670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6367" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="2">2.01</rating>
<name>Adol Brinberg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A German spy and twin brother of Mils. In Mission-E he seems to hold a grudge against Chinami for what happened at the summer school some years ago. His hair has become much darker and now views all Type-E users as his enemy because of what Chinami did to his sister. Even though he hates Type-E, he appears to be growing feelings for Maori.</description>
<picture>23671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6368" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="5">5.39</rating>
<name>Mils Brinberg</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A German spy and twin sister of Adol. In Mission-E she seems to have become really ill or went into a coma after the summer school incident. Because of this Adol is no longer his cheerful self. Describing her to be alive "just alive". However, after a visit from Maori, she has shown to react but to what extent was never revealed.</description>
<picture>23672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="79654" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">転校生と告白のこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About a Transfer Student and a Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkousei to Kokuhaku no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79655" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">科学と幸せのこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About Science and Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagaku to Shiawase no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79656" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電磁波と研究のこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About Electromagnetic Waves and Research</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Denjiha to Kenkyuu no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79657" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密とバカのこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About a Secret and an Idiot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu to Baka no Koto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80211" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">憂鬱と親子のこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About Feeling Down and Parents and Their Children</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuutsu to Oyako no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80212" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">巫女さんと修行のこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About a Shrine Maiden and Training</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miko-san to Shugyou no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80213" update="2007-08-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">外国人と初恋のこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About Foreigners and a First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gaikokujin to Hatsukoi no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80214" update="2007-08-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">色仕掛けとすれ違いのこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About a Venus Flytrap and Missed Encounters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Irojigake to Surechigai no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80215" update="2007-08-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お見合いと恋敵のこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About a Marriage Meeting and a Rival in Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omiai to Koigataki no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80216" update="2007-08-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えた力と気持ちのこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About a Lost Power and Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Chikara to Kimochi no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81647" update="2007-09-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サマースクールと陰謀のこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About Summer School and a Conspiracy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Summer School to Inbou no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81648" update="2007-09-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">破滅と再生のこと.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About Ruin and Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hametsu to Saisei no Koto.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117331" update="2010-04-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117332" update="2010-04-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
