<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5053" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Lovely Complex</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">LoveCom</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lovely★Complex</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Трогательный комплекс</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Uroczy związek</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Lovely Complex</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Любовен Комплекс</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Комплекс кохання</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">恋爱方程式</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="short">LC</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ラブ★コン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Lovely Complex</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Lovely Complex</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Bezvadná dvojka</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Lovely Complex</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6466" approval="226" total="273">Kimi ni Todoke</anime>
<anime id="5909" approval="160" total="225">Toradora!</anime>
<anime id="7008" approval="85" total="130">Kaichou wa Maid-sama!</anime>
<anime id="9235" approval="70" total="100">Tonari no Kaibutsu-kun</anime>
<anime id="5678" approval="68" total="84">Itazura na Kiss</anime>
<anime id="199" approval="43" total="62">Kareshi Kanojo no Jijou</anime>
<anime id="4441" approval="32" total="42">Bokura ga Ita</anime>
<anime id="1928" approval="18" total="21">The Kabocha Wine</anime>
<anime id="10918" approval="11" total="15">Ore Monogatari!!</anime>
<anime id="10385" approval="7" total="15">Ao Haru Ride</anime>
<anime id="288" approval="4" total="10">Maison Ikkoku</anime>
<anime id="6103" approval="2" total="13">Skip Beat!</anime>
<anime id="10273" approval="2" total="9">Isshuukan Friends.</anime>
<anime id="5584" approval="1" total="6">Special A</anime>
<anime id="356" approval="1" total="4">Marmalade Boy</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="42">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="616461">very nice anime with two well-developed characters overall. it`s fun, heart-warming, not dirty at all, and it actually has a satisfying ending! 

i recommend it even if you only have a small space in your heart for shoujo :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="2975">Great humor, very "human" characters. Very romantic too. Nice for both guys and girls!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="322738">Lots of laughs, tears, and a happy ending.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="307807">Sometimes Risa cried a bit too much but overall very enjoyable. Especially the facial expressions were brilliant^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="353600">Bittersweet!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372933">Best romantic comedy</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="427701">Great story but I felt like the story dragged on a little too much especially since she falls for him in the first few episodes. Personally think it would`ve been better if they found out their love for each other at the end like in Toradora!.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="163105">fabulous!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="254176">I can`t wait for the second ( i hope there will be second )</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="480721">This anime adaptation is very well done, particularly since it offers a very different take and challenges its viewers on where love is found and blossomed.

Are the characters memorable? Probably not.  Is the plot deep? So-so.  Will you regret it if you don`t see it?  Unquestionably.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="657678">One of the most hilarious, fun, beautiful, unique love stories I`ve watched. It will make you laugh till the very last episode, but it is also very moving and cute. I recommend this mainly for shoujo fans, although, I think anyone who gives this anime a shot would enjoy it so much.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="296063">Once you get past the 3rd episode you just can´t stop watching! This has to be on my top 5 anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="457632">What can i say....watch it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="291829">Romance, slapstick, comedy ... and a really great one too ... that`s a must see ;]</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="150410">best school romance ever!!!1oneone</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="385395">watch it,watch it, watch it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="87753">Very. Very funny =)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="143965">Whenever I think of a good romantic anime, Lovely Complex always comes to mind! Simply a must see!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="119972">It`s the best romance comedy I`ve seen so far.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="159752">Best Shoujo Anime/Manga ever. (to me that is but still it`s AWESOME)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="607018">Hilarious!! only because of Risa! Watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="428284">one of my fav anime series. ever.
i laughed my ass off with this!
it is funny, sweet and has a happy ending. perfect match ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="219874">super funny, supper romantic, super touchy</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="500174">This show is awesome. You will definitely fall for it once you`ve watched the 1st episode</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="156965">Very enjoyable..very fun story.. must see!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/lovecom/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7883" type="Character Design">Maniwa Hideaki</name>
<name id="1842" type="Music">Satou Hironosuke</name>
<name id="1978" type="Direction">Uda Kounosuke</name>
<name id="7883" type="Chief Animation Direction">Maniwa Hideaki</name>
<name id="8438" type="Original Work">Nakahara Aya</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shoujo manga by http://anidb.net/cr8438 [Nakahara Aya], serialised in Margaret.
http://anidb.net/ch4321 [Risa] and http://anidb.net/ch4322 [Ootani] are always being laughed at as the comedy duo. Risa, a girl, is taller than the average girl, and Ootani, a boy, is shorter than the average boy. The two are always bickering and even their teacher sees them as a comedy act. But as their friendship develops, so do Risa`s feelings toward Ootani.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5449">7.68</permanent>
<temporary count="5552">8.18</temporary>
<review count="8">8.20</review>
</ratings>
<picture>222361.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7468</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2034</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4030</identifier>
<identifier>oyptka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/lovecom/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Love_Com#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ラブ★コン#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1114</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327229</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8886</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1716</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4584</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/lovecom</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10002</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="464" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-15">
<name>sarcastic</name>
<description>The character frequently uses sharp, bitter, or cutting expressions or remarks. (From Greek sarcasmos, "to tear flesh, gnash the teeth, speak bitterly".)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1283" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-24">
<name>tsukkomi</name>
<description>A tsukkomi is a comedy duo stock character in a traditional Japanese slapstick stand-up comedy style known as manzai. Tsukkomi characters are the smart, reasonable, and down-to-earth half of the unit; their simple-minded counterparts are the http://anidb.net/t1399 [boke] characters. As a result of their boke counterparts` simple mistakes and gross exaggerations, tsukkomi berate and abuse them both verbally and physically; a very common example of tsukkomi physical abuse is a paper fan slap, which is generally accompanied by a sound effect. Their approximate equivalent in Western culture is the comedy role of straight man.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2760" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>basketball</name>
<description>Basketball is Netball for men, the real game that encourages dribbling and other such uncouth behaviour that was sanitised out of the ladies` version. However, it is itself woozy compared to Ulama, as the losing side are seldom publicly sacrificed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3094" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>befriend attack</name>
<description>A befriend attack is a pounce performed by someone in an attempt to hug someone else. This is an exuberant display of affection, often used for comedic effect. Sometimes, the target of such attacks learn to dodge them, usually by simply sidestepping them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4321" type="main character in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="67">7.77</rating>
<name>Koizumi Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main protagonist of Lovely Complex, Risa Koizumi is not your average Japanese high school student. Standing 172cm tall, Risa`s height is well above that of most Japanese girls her age (the average height for a female is 157cm). Ironically, her surname means `little spring`. She and other characters compare her to a giraffe. Risa can be impulsive and strong-willed at times, and is rarely willing to display her softer side.</description>
<picture>20364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4322" type="main character in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="40">6.36</rating>
<name>Ootani Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is very short for a boy, standing 156 cm tall. The average height for a male in Japan is 171cm. Like Koizumi, Ootani`s surname (roughly, "big valley") is a pun on his diminutive stature, and he can be thoughtless and rude; at heart, however, he is kind and a little silly. Ootani is also the star player of the school basketball team.</description>
<picture>20365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2432" picture="126728.jpg">Nagata Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4323" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="28">7.94</rating>
<name>Ishihara Nobuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fashionable and charming, Nobu is Risa`s best friend. She is generally wiser than Risa or Chiharu in the ways of love, and is always ready to offer her advice. She`s mostly the one who sets up all the `alone time` moments with Risa and Ootani, but it usually ends up failing and Risa goes back to her for comfort.</description>
<picture>20366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2433" picture="222921.jpg">Higashi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4324" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="8">6.03</rating>
<name>Nakao Heikichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nobu`s boyfriend. Considerate, sensitive, mild-mannered and easygoing. Nakao is absolutely dedicated to Nobu, and when he is not playing basketball with Ootani, he can usually be found helping with her match-making schemes.</description>
<picture>20367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2434" picture="23211.jpg">Tokuyama Yasuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4325" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="10">6.16</rating>
<name>Tanaka Chiharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Risa`s closest friends, Chiharu has such a shy, demure personality that she fears most boys her own age. Ootani once harboured a crush on her (she resembles Kanzaki, his ex-girlfriend, or vice-versa), but Chiharu instead fell for the gentle Suzuki.</description>
<picture>20368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="428">Kojima Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4326" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="6">3.34</rating>
<name>Suzuki Ryouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiharu`s boyfriend. Suzuki`s cool demeanour is often mistaken for standoffishness, and so he has few friends. Oblivious to Risa`s crush on him, he develops feelings for Chiharu, and eventually asks her out. Like Chiharu, Suzuki is shy and easily embarrassed.</description>
<picture>20369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4327" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="9">4.21</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the ex-girlfriend of Ootani. She looks very similar to Chiharu (or Chiharu to her), which is one the most likely reasons that Ootani had that crush on Chiharu. They started dating in middle-school, and she was the manager for the school basketball team. She broke up with him, leaving him completely heartbroken, because she was in love with someone else.</description>
<picture>20370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4328" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="11">1.52</rating>
<name>Fukagawa Haruka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A handsome, effeminate young man who developed a childhood crush on Risa when she defended him from a gang of bullies. Though he is popular with many of the other girls (dating seven at a time), he says it`s all preparation for when he goes out with Risa, but she always rejects him.</description>
<picture>20371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4329" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="13">4.02</rating>
<name>Kotobuki Seishirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blonde who has a large crush on Ootani, although he is biologically male, stating that God placed him in a wrong body. His given name is Seishirou, but he prefers to be called Seiko as it sounds more feminine.</description>
<picture>20372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2438" picture="156420.jpg">Takimoto Fujiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4330" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="7">6.90</rating>
<name>Umibouzu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A popular rapper. Risa and Ootani are both avid fans of Umibouzu, leading to Nobu`s suggestion that the two are compatible.</description>
<picture>20374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2440" picture="22337.jpg">Smokey Tetsuni</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4331" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="14">5.39</rating>
<name>Maitake Kuniumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Student teacher at Risa and Ootani`s school. Maitake, who prefers the nickname "Maity" or "Mighty", is taller than Risa and extraordinarily good-looking. He bears a resemblance to "Cain-sama", a character in one of Risa`s favorite visual novels, and soon acquires a legion of female fans.</description>
<picture>20375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4332" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="10">3.32</rating>
<name>Yoshioka Mimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ootani`s next door neighbour. She is in love with Ootani, and brings him milk every day so he could reach her height, about the same as Risa`s. Since Ootani does not not have feelings toward her but does have feelings for Risa (who is exactly the same height as Mimi), she becomes jealous of her. She acts accordingly two-faced between them both: acting sweet towards Ootani, yet acting sour to Risa behind his back.</description>
<picture>20376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2439" picture="166338.jpg">Araki Kae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4333" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="7">1.55</rating>
<name>Kohori Kazuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young student who works part time with Risa in Ikebe. He is notably shorter than her, although slightly taller than Otani (158 cm.), and has distinctive black hair with a red streak. Risa soon discovers that he is also an avid Umibouzu fan. He very soon develops feelings for Risa, who admits to herself that she finds him `cute`.</description>
<picture>20377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2013" picture="21316.jpg">Shimowada Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74502" type="appears in" update="2015-04-18">
<name>Ootani no Ane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74503" type="appears in" update="2015-04-18">
<name>Ootani no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9654" picture="49080.jpg">Yanagisawa Michiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="69165" update="2007-03-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71648" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高1の夏! 絶対カレシ, つくったるわ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First High School Summer! I`ll Get A Boyfriend If It Kills Me!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Estate di 1° liceo. Mi troverò un ragazzo a tutti i costi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kou-1 no Natsu! Zettai Kareshi, Tsukuttaru wa!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792783</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71964" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">元カノと三角関係!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Triangle With The Ex?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Triangolo amoroso con la ex!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motokano to Sankaku Kankei!?</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792784</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="72061" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">好きなオトコか, 昔のオトコか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boy You Like? The Boy From Your Past?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il ragazzo che ti piace, o il ragazzo dal passato?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suki na Otoko ka, Mukashi no Otoko ka?</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792786</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="72346" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チュッ! 好きになっちゃいました!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Smooch! I`ve Fallen In Love!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Smack! Sono innamorata!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chu! Suki ni Nacchaimashita!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792788</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="72347" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">禁断の愛をぶっ飛ばせ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blow Away Forbidden Love!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kindan no Ai o Buttobase!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792791</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73161" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙女の一大決心! ラブラブ告白大作戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Young Maiden`s Momentous Decision! Operation Love Confession!!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La scelta più importante! Una confessione d`amore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome no Ichidaikesshin! Lovelove Kokuhaku Daisakusen!!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792793</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73506" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">撃沈! 史上サイテーな告白!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Abandon Ship! The Worst Confession of Love Ever!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekichin! Shijou Saitee na Kokuhaku!!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792795</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73507" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="14">9.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再起不能! 大失恋!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beyond Hope! Big Heartbreak!!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Impossibile riprendersi! Cure infranto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiki Funou! Daishitsuren!!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792797</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="74356" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">起死回生!! めざせ彼女の座!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Back From the Dead! Aim For the Girlfriend Spot!!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Cambio di rotta! Non perdere la speranza!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kishikaisei!! Mezase Kanojo no Za!!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792799</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75103" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">元カノと対決!? 乳だし大作戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Face Off Against the Ex?! Operation Breast Exposure!!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Paure della ex? Metti in mostra le tette!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motokano to Taiketsu!? Chichidashi Daisakusen!!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792801</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75104" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶体絶命! 元カノと復活愛?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Up A Creek Without A Paddle! Back Together With the Ex?!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Situazione disperata! Il ritorno della ex?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettaizetsumei! Motokano to Fukkatsu Ai?!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792803</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75105" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛を取り戻せ! 本命チョコで女を磨く!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reclaim Your Love! Improve Femininity With True Love Chocolate!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai o Torimodose! Honmei Choco de Onna o Migaku!!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792805</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75106" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">発熱! あいつの部屋でファースト・キッス?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fever! First Kiss In His Bedroom?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsunetsu! Aitsu no Heya de First Kiss?</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792807</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="75107" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マイティにキュン死にや!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death By Heartgasm For Maity!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maity ni Kyunjini Ya!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792809</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80225" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危険なオトコ マイティの甘い誘惑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger-Man Maity`s Sweet Seduction</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un ragazzo pericoloso. La dolce tentazione di Maity!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiken na Otoko: Maity no Amai Yuuwaku</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792811</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80366" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マイティの魔法! 変化する恋模様!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maity-Magic! How To Metamorphose Love?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maity no Mahou! Henka Suru Koi Moyou!?</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792813</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80367" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の鉄拳! 受け止めろ, 乙女魂!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Iron Fists of Love! Catch My Female Spirit Ball!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Tekken! Uketomero, Otomedamashii!!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792815</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81077" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">史上最高の誕生日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Best Birthday In History</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il compleanno più bello del mondo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shijou Saikou no Tanjoubi</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792817</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81078" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">急転直下!! 初デートは不運の始まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sudden Collapse!! First Date Begins With a String of Bad Luck</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Crollo improvviso! Primo appuntamento significa guai.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuutenchokka!! Hatsu Date wa Fuun no Hajimari</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792818</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81351" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宣戦布告!! 嫉妬に燃えるデンジャラス美少女!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Declaration of War!! Dangerous Pretty Girl Burning With Jealousy!!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Guerra dichiarata! Una pericolosa bellezza folle di gelosia!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensen Fukoku!! Shitto ni Moeru Dangerous Bishoujo!!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792820</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="81352" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">別れの予感?! リサと大谷が歩む別々の道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Foreboding Break Up?! Risa`s and Otani`s Separate Paths.</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Separazione annunciata? Strade divergenti per Risa e Otani!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakare no Yokan?! Risa to Ootani ga Ayumu Betsubetsu no Michi</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792822</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82806" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大谷からの破局宣言!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Otani Declares A Catastrophic Collapse!!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il catastrofico annuncio di Otani!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ootani kara no Hakyoku Sengen!!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792824</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82810" update="2007-09-17">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">進路はいろいろ!! みんなが抱えるそれぞれの事情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Each Their Own!! Everyone Has Their Own Passion.</title>
<title xml:lang="it">A ciascuno la propria strada!! Ognuno ha le sue ragioni.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinro wa Iroiro!! Minna ga Kakaeru Sorezore no Jijou</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792826</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="83132" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ずっと一緒!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Together Forever!!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sempre insieme!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zutto Issho!!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792827</identifier>
<identifier>lovely-complex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="108341" update="2009-09-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132910" update="2011-09-11">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132911" update="2011-09-11">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132912" update="2011-09-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132913" update="2011-09-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132917" update="2011-09-12">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
