<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5071" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-07-04</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Doujin Work</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Dōjin Wāku</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Додзинси</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">同人work</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">同人工坊</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドージンワーク</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dojin Work</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">โดจินเวิร์ค</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="116" approval="23" total="24">Comic Party</anime>
<anime id="10295" approval="20" total="24">Mangaka-san to Assistant-san to: The Animation</anime>
<anime id="7251" approval="9" total="20">Bakuman.</anime>
<anime id="10619" approval="9" total="10">Denki-gai no Hon`ya-san</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="252455">You should watch this, it!s really funny, I laughed few times. ^^</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20071026063439/http://www.doujin.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="888" type="Animation Work">Remic</name>
<name id="4254" type="Direction">Yatagai Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="7181" type="Music">Yoda Kazuo</name>
<name id="9932" type="Music">Mitome Kazumi</name>
<name id="12674" type="Character Design">Kimishima Ikuchi</name>
<name id="9111" type="Original Work">Hiroyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a 4-koma comedy manga by http://anidb.net/cr9111 [Hiroyuki], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23323 [Manga Time Kirara].
http://anidb.net/ch2637 [Osana Najimi] sets foot into the world of dojin-shi (self-published manga) when she is invited by her classmate, http://anidb.net/ch2638 [Tsuyuri]. At first, she experiences a culture shock, but is also influenced by Tsuyuri and http://anidb.net/ch2642 [Justice], a very popular http://anidb.net/t2476 [dojin author] and her childhood friend. She then announces that she intends to make a killing in the dojin market. Although Najimi is not good at drawing, she is determined. On her long road to success, both fans and rivals appear.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1655">5.24</permanent>
<temporary count="1669">7.03</temporary>
<review count="2">6.74</review>
</ratings>
<picture>12162.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7765</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2166</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4007</identifier>
<identifier>pytriz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20071026063439/http://www.doujin.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dōjin_Work</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドージンワーク</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1181</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327898</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9061</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4207" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>doujin</name>
<description>Doujin is a general Japanese term for a group of people or friends who share an interest, activity, hobbies, or achievement. The word is sometimes translated into English as clique, coterie, society, or circle (e.g., a "sewing circle").
In Japan the term is used to refer to amateur self-published works, including but not limited to manga, novels, fan guides, art collections, music and video games. Some professional artists participate as a way to publish material outside the regular publishing industry.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>68439.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2637" type="main character in" update="2009-01-21">
<rating votes="16">5.52</rating>
<name>Osana Najimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Najimi is an innocent young girl in college who, after losing her job, decides to switch professions and starts attempting to create doujinshi, or fan-made manga. She is inspired after seeing her friend Tsuyuri sell her doujinshi at a comic festival, and after meeting her childhood friend Justice again, who is also a doujin artist. Her doujin circle is called Beauty Love House, and Najimi uses the pseudonym Beauty Love when writing her doujinshi. She gets easily embarrassed when she encounters people seeing her with inappropriate content.</description>
<picture>17997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2638" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-21">
<rating votes="22">7.84</rating>
<name>Tsuyuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsuyuri is a doujin artist, and creates her doujinshi under the name Bloomer Girl. She is the only member of her doujin circle which she named Panty Revolution. Her doujinshi mainly consists of rape manga.</description>
<picture>17998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2639" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-21">
<rating votes="12">5.06</rating>
<name>Kitano Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sora is a little girl that is rarely seen without Justice. She is the youngest main character by far, as Justice, Tsuyuri, and Najimi are all in college and Sora is the only one apparently too young to participate in Justice`s doujinshi browsing.</description>
<picture>18000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2640" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-16">
<rating votes="9">6.35</rating>
<name>Nidou Kaneru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaneru is an office lady in her twenties who enjoys drawing doujinshi as her hobby, but has poor skills in drawing and creating them. Najimi declares her to be a rival after they both fare poorly in sales at the Comic Market. Tsuyuri artificially encourages this rivalry in the belief that it will make Najimi a better artist and author. Kaneru also misinterprets Justice`s and Junichirou`s relationship not as antagonistic over Najimi, but a yaoi love affair.</description>
<picture>18001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="619" picture="18141.jpg">Sakata Ito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2641" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-09">
<rating votes="9">4.51</rating>
<name>Hoshi Junichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Junichirou is a young man around Najimi`s age who she first met in an adult game store while she was buying one such game to help her with drawing her doujinshi. He later became her first customer the first time she was selling her doujinshi, though he was the only customer at that time. Later, when Najimi gets a job at a cosplay restaurant, he appears there every day, eventually making Justice believe that he stalks Najimi due to him showing up so often. He does in fact have a crush on her, and has to persevere against Justice`s antics to get close to her.</description>
<picture>18002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1622" picture="19660.jpg">Hatano Kazutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2642" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-21">
<rating votes="9">5.70</rating>
<name>Justice</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Justice is a popular doujin artist who often sells tens of thousands doujin at a single event, though does not earn much money due to production costs and the low price he sells his doujin for. He is a childhood friend of Najimi. He appears to be highly protective to Najimi, to the point of getting very annoyed when noticing any man getting close to her.</description>
<picture>17999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="79624" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめてのXXX</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her first XXX</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no XXX</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80002" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はだかのお嬢様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Naked Young Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hadaka no Ojou-sama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80242" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私...うれごろ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I...Have Matured...?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atashi... Uregoro?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80435" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おやめください, ご主人様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Please Stop, Master!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oyamekudasai, Goshujin-sama!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80436" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたりでしましょ♥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Do It Together</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari de Shimasho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80437" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先に浴びちゃうね♥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Take a Shower First</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saki ni Abichau ne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80451" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80764" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">素晴らしき哉, BaLaの香り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scent of a Truly Magnificent BaLa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subarashiki kana, BaLa no kaori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80765" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全部見えちゃってる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I can see it all!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenbu Miechatteru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80766" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポロリもあるよ! 同人大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teary Eyes! Doujin Convention</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Porori mo Aru yo! Doujin Taikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80767" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こんなになっちゃった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Look at What It`s Become</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konna ni Nacchatta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81644" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なじみ とんじゃう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Najimi`s Flying Away</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Najimi Tonjau</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81645" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まだまだやりたい, もっとしたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Keep Doing It, I Want to Do It More</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madamada Yaritai, Motto Shitai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112261" update="2009-12-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112262" update="2009-12-26">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
