<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5084" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2007-06-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shining Tears X Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Сияющие Слёзы И Ветер</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Сверкающие Слёзы &amp; Ветер</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shining Tears Cross Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">光明之泪x风</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">stxw</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">シャイニング・ティアーズ・クロス・ウィンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shining Tears X Wind</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8834" type="Same Setting">Shining Hearts: Shiawase no Pan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8480" approval="1" total="8">Guilty Crown</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="469109">&amp;gt;.&amp;gt; ugh terrible series... i regret watching it, cuz it only gets interesting at the end..overall it was cheesy and random character development ... watch at ur own risk..</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://shining-world.jp/tv_tearsXwind/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1178" type="Original Work">Sega</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="2744" type="Direction">Watanabe Hiroshi</name>
<name id="2479" type="Character Design">Ban Yukiko</name>
<name id="7502" type="Character Design">Emori Mariko</name>
<name id="7502" type="Chief Animation Direction">Emori Mariko</name>
<name id="3926" type="Music">Haneoka Kei</name>
<name id="5735" type="Series Composition">Masaki Hiro</name>
<name id="30444" type="Original Plan">Sawada Tsuyoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>Mysterious disappearances are occurring one after the other in Tatsumi Town. http://anidb.net/ch19121 [Kiriya] has a vision from a mysterious beautiful girl with pointy ears. A book talking for an alternative world is found. And http://anidb.net/ch14435 [Mao] searching for her long lost friend, http://anidb.net/ch8718 [Zero], comes to our world. But what she didn`t expect is to find http://anidb.net/ch8719 [Souma] and http://anidb.net/ch8721 [Kureha], and even less, to accidentally take them to her world. Now, Souma and Kureha have to find a way to come back. But other forces are playing their part in the darkness and Souma with Kureha will find that going back is harder than they first anticipated.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1410">2.99</permanent>
<temporary count="1445">6.20</temporary>
<review count="3">5.44</review>
</ratings>
<picture>227088.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7633</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2031</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4008</identifier>
<identifier>ozneai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://shining-world.jp/tv_tearsXwind/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shining_Tears_X_Wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>シャイニング・ティアーズ・クロス・ウィンド</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1157</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327434</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8915</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2802" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-14">
<name>action game</name>
<description>Any game where reflexes are the key to the gameplay, violence is optional.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3611" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-12-06">
<name>evil empire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3696" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-28">
<name>off-model animation</name>
<description>Anime shows tend to most often run on an already tight budget; some have even tighter ones. Thus, over the years it became a norm to invest more time and money into the first and last episode, leaving many episodes in the middle to stand severe budget restrictions. This sometimes results in episodes which particularly stand out due to the drop in artwork or animation quality; bar some basic framework, they often have little in common with the rest of the series.
One clue to upcoming off-model animation is the noticeable addition of many Korean names in the production credits, as farming out more animation to Korean artists is a nearly universal indicator of a production company trying to save money in all possible ways.
This effect is often called yashigani, after the infamous http://anidb.net/e4682 [fourth episode] of http://anidb.net/a403 [Lost Universe], Yashigani Hoburu. Another prominent term describing the same effect is "QUALITY animation", with capital letters meant to show contrast to actual quality. http://anidb.net/a4531 [Yoake Mae yori Ruriiro na: Crescent Love] is another legendarily terrible offender: the TV airing of its http://anidb.net/e63752 [third episode] had a perfectly spherical ball in place of what should be a cabbage; the "cabbage" was so egregious that it became closely associated with the anime itself, to a point the show would henceforth be nicknamed "Cabbage Love" among Western viewers.
One should not confuse the yashigani effect with art shifts that stem from guest staff, changes in main staff, intentional art shifts, and similar effects. Another effect one shouldn`t confuse this one with is the so-called DVD/BD enhancement, which is when a studio scrambles to meet the deadline for a TV airing and airs a half-finished episode but eventually fixes it for a disk release; for example, http://anidb.net/cr792 [Shaft] is particularly infamous for its disk enhancements, to a point it has become known as "Shafting", and they prominently feature intentionally weird character models, but they don`t often leave bad artwork on the disk release. Additionally, it should also not be confused with intentional lack of detail on background plane characters; this effect is instead when even the foreground has art quality shifting over time due to the aforementioned budget restrictions.</description>
<picurl>29532.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4337" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-03-11">
<name>you`re my hidden weapon!</name>
<description>One or more characters (females usually) turn into weapons or release them from their body to be used by their teammate or partner in times of need.
Examples: Himemiya Anthy from Shoujo Kakumei Utena, Soul from Soul Eater, Kureha from Shining x Tears Wind, and Yuzuriha Inori from Guilty Crown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8717" type="main character in" update="2010-06-22">
<rating votes="9">6.77</rating>
<name>Blanc Neige</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Blanc Neige an old friend of Zero and an Ice Sorceress, who lives in an ice house and showers with ice. She is also the princess of Runevale. She is considered a beauty, but is often cold toward others. Souma is able to draw a soul blade with ice and snow properties from her, the Ice Snow Sword Glass-Diamond (氷雪剣 グラスディアマンド, Hyousetsuken Gurasu Diamando).
For unexplained reasons, the remaining members of Weisritter, Dr. Pios, Volg, Cupido and Keiner, do not appear in the anime.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8718" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-23">
<rating votes="4">3.51</rating>
<name>Zero</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zero is Xion, or what is left of his soul. His angelic wings represent the two entities inside his body, the black one resembles Zeroboros, the white one resembles what is left of Xion, but for all causes, Xion no longer exists. It seems he went to Elde to find someone able to replace him as the Guardian of End Earth. He later chooses Souma, and after meeting him between worlds, states that he now `entrusts` the world to him. He was shown to have still possessed the Twin Dragon Rings, but gave Souma one of the rings, telling him to use it to see the true world.
He keeps running from Mao, as some time before, he unwillingly killed Ryuna (she impaled herself upon his sword) in order to destroy Zeroboros, who lived inside her, but instead it possessed him, making him sprout black wings form his back. During that altercation he also killed Lazarus. It was Mao`s calling that made him fight Zeroboros` possession, turning one of the black wings white, thus leaving a piece of Xion`s soul. He later accepted himself as no longer a human, and revived Ryuna and Lazarus using the capsules in the Sea Dragon King Ruins.
He decides to leave the group and is currently watching the world, entrusting Souma with protecting the world in his place.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>28063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8719" type="main character in" update="2010-06-22">
<rating votes="5">4.96</rating>
<name>Akizuki Souma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akizuki Souma is an athletic student who, along with Kureha, was transported to the dream continent, End Earth. At the beginning of the series, Souma has feelings for Kureha, despite knowing that she has feelings for Kiriya; he sometimes gets annoyed at Kiriya for not noticing her feelings for him. He then confesses his affection for her, which apparently is not mutual, shortly before being transported to the other world. After seeing Kureha presumably die, he was able to pull out a legendary sword from Kureha`s body. Souma turns out to be a `Soul Blader`, which is a person that can form a sword from the heart of any person he shares similar emotions with. Unlike Kureha, Souma would rather stay in End Earth, as he believes that it is the right place for him and since he thinks that he could be "together" with Kureha in End Earth. Later, after Souma and Kureha meet up with Kiriya and Seena, he departs from the group, leaving Kiriya and Seena to take care of Kureha, realizing that she did not feel the same way about him and thus decided to no longer use Kureha`s heart as a Soul Blade, since he knew that her heart had feelings for Kiriya. So, he temporarily uses a katana when there are no Soul Blades around for him to use.
When Souma and Kureha were between dimensions, they were greeted by Zero, who entrusted Souma in guarding the world from then on.
After his second meeting with Zero, he receives one of the Twin Dragon Rings, and begins to see the world in a whole new way. His attitude also shifts from a rash and emotional state, to having a calm and understanding demeanor. Souma becomes a sort of mediator, not taking any sides, and travels with Lazarus, Ryuna, Elwyn, and Blanc Neige, in his mission to protect and save the world. After expressing his desire to join Weissritter, he is nominated as its proxy leader. In the end, after seeing Mao`s sad and tearful face, he realizes his true feelings for Mao and her feelings for him. Souma then decides to give up his chance of going back to his own world and decides to stay with Mao and Weissritter.
Out of the rest of the characters, Souma was able to extract the most Soul Blades; having drawn blades from Kureha, Hiruda, Kiriya, who in fact possesses his Holy Grail, and also from all the members of the current Weissritter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8721" type="main character in" update="2010-06-22">
<rating votes="10">8.35</rating>
<name>Kureha Touka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kureha Touka a student who also happens to work at a shrine as a miko, or shinto priestess. Kureha is skilled in the art of archery, or kyuudou. She was transported to End Earth with Souma after they helped Mao defeat a monster. Upon their arrival, she was attacked by monsters and presumably died. Fortunately, she was revealed to be unscathed after Souma pulled out a sword from her body, the Spirit Sword Snow Moon Flower (霊剣 雪月華, Ryouken Setsu Getsu Ka). After Kiriya and Souma`s fight, she joins Kiriya and the other Luminous Knights. Kiriya can also draw a sword from her, the Spirit Sword Blazing Sunlight (霊剣 日輪烈光, Ryouken Nishirin Rekkou).
Kureha has feeling for Kiriya, but she never expresses them to him. In the end, she returns to her own world, together with Kiriya and Seena.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14435" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="6">9.02</rating>
<name>Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mao is a quarter-beast; she has a pair of cat-like ears. She is also the Princess of Bestia. She traveled to Souma`s world looking for Zero. In the process, she accidentally sent Souma and Kureha into her world. She previously saw Xion standing next to the dead bodies of Lazarus and Ryuna. Since Xion flew away before telling her that he has been possessed by Zeroboros, she was left there confused and in shock. This prompted her search for Zero, whom her country of Bestia had placed on the wanted list for murdering a priestess: Ryuna. Though she explains that this makes it easier for her to find him. She is also the true leader of Weissritter. Souma is able to draw a soul blade with fire properties from her, the Beast King Sword Lion King`s Flame Dance (獣王剣 獅子王炎舞, Juuouken Shishiou Enmu). Her particular soul blade becomes Souma`s preferred soul blade. Her feelings for Souma are revealed when she cries when Souma wants to leave, which moves him and he decides to stay with her in End Earth.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19116" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-22">
<rating votes="9">7.63</rating>
<name>Elwyn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elwyn is an old friend of Zero from the Elf race, and is also the princess of Fontina. Elwyn is now traveling with Souma, and had mentioned that she would kill Zero if he abuses his powers. Souma is able to draw a soul blade with lightning properties from her, the Wind Thunder Sword Blitzbringer (風雷剣 ブリッツブリンガー, Kazeraiken Burittsuburingaa).
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19117" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">9.28</rating>
<name>Xecty Ein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Xecty Ein is one of Baelgard`s four guardians, who is an artificial life-form made by Hiruda, using an ancient weapon as base.
She is in fact Killrain`s sister, Celestia, as Hiruda made her body as Xecty using Celestia`s cells, but then she ended up getting infected by the darkness and Hiruda created a dark matter to absorb the forces of darkness, preventing her from further infection.
During a duel with Kiriya, an earthquake causes the two to fall into a cavern. Kiriya talks with Xecty and tells her the importance of hope and believing in your self, forming a close bond with her. Later, during the fight between Kiriya and Saionji, she gets in the middle and is stabbed by Saionji, sacrificing her life in order to stop the war. She explains to him that she did it in order to give hope to the world, and that Kiriya is her hope. Her spirit then joins the wind, as a way to protect both.
She is later revived by one of the pods from the Sea Dragon King Ruins, and joins the Luminous Knights. She also becomes the priestess of Astraea`s Tower of the Wind. Her soul blade is called Sword of Emperors Excelion (剣帝 エクセリオン, Kentei Ekuserion). She also contains Kiriya`s Holy Grail, being drawn from her Kiriya`s Ultimate Soul Blade (究極心剣, Kyuukyoku Shinken).
She decides to stay together with Saionji, Hiruda, and Jin-Crow in Baelgard, to restore the forest back to its former glory.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19118" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-23">
<rating votes="5">5.13</rating>
<name>Seena Kanon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seena Kanon is a student who belongs to the Student Council just like the other characters. She, along with Kiriya, are later transported to End Earth shortly after Kureha and Souma. Upon their arrival, Seena and Kiriya form an independent mercenary group called the Luminous Knights, with Seena as the leader.
She lets Kiriya use her heart as a sword only to allow him to fight, the Gun Sword Blade Cannon (砲剣 ブレイドカノン, Hooken Bureido Kanon).
Seena is also very skilled in fencing. In the end, she returns to her own world, together with Kiriya and Kureha.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19119" type="appears in" update="2010-06-22">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Celestia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19120" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-22">
<rating votes="3">4.03</rating>
<name>Hiruda Reia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiruda Reia is a seemingly innocent and quiet girl, who is devoted to Saionji. She found the book that allows herself and Saionji to be brought into End Earth. Though she wants to follow him, she does not want to be engulfed in darkness, so she develops a dark second personality, one that will do all the things that she does not want to. She becomes one of Baelgard`s four guardians, the Hellfire Alchemist, Hildareia. Her alter ego prefers the darkside, and even betrays Saionji by siding with Killrain after he takes over the dark elven army. She often does experiments on many elves, turning them into mindless soldiers for Baelgard. Her dark soul blade is called Mythical Beast Sword Mysteltain (妖獣剣 ミストルティン, Youjuuken Misutorutin). Destroying the evil personality`s soul blade is the only way to bring back the original Reia Hiruda.
The good personality contains Saionji`s Holy Grail, Saionji`s Ultimate Soul Blade (究極心剣, Kyuukyoku Shinken), which was instrumental in defeating Er Fahren. She decides to stay in End Earth, together with Saionji, Xecty, and Jin-Crow in Baelgard, to restore the forest back to its former glory.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="568" picture="65531.jpg">Sakuma Kumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19121" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-22">
<rating votes="1">2.29</rating>
<name>Kiriya Kaito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiriya Kaito is a quiet and shy student who receives a message from an elven woman from End Earth. When he tells his friends, the group dismisses the message as they believe it to only be a dream. Kiriya is a skilled swordsman; ranging from kendo to fencing. It is said that no one could beat him if he was to fight seriously. The cherry blossom of their college transports him and Seena to End Earth right after Souma and Kureha, taking the entire building as well. He becomes the knight for an independent mercenary group called the `Luminous Knights`, which is started by Seena.
Like Souma, Kiriya is also a Soul Blader, who uses Seena`s "heart" as a sword. Kiriya is completely oblivious to Kureha`s and Seena`s feelings for him, the latter being one of his childhood friends. He later forms a close bond with an elf named Xecty, who is later revealed to be an artificial recreation of the Elven Queen. Until Xecty`s death, he was confident in his mission to have Saionji admit defeat. Since the start of the war, his attitude shifted from his shy and quiet self, to a rash and emotional state, who sees that fighting is the only way to win (the complete opposite to Souma`s change of behavior).
He is later revealed to hold Souma`s Holy Grail, Souma`s Ultimate Soul Blade (究極心剣, Kyuukyoku Shinken). The one who holds his Holy Grail is Xecty.
In the end, he chooses to return to his own world, together with Kureha and Seena.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19122" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">2.23</rating>
<name>Saionji Haruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saionji Haruto is an heir to a rich family and Student Council President. He, along with Hiruda, are transported to End Earth before the other main characters. When he first encounters his old friends in End Earth, he is revealed to be an enemy. He became the Emperor of Baelgard, and goes by the name "Traihard".
Like Souma and Kiriya, he is also a Soul Blader, and chooses to draw swords from Baelgard`s four guardians, which includes Hiruda Reia. Seeing Soul Bladers as "chosen ones", he offers Kiriya and Souma to join him in his crusade. Saionji plans to conquer all of End Earth, under the pretense that he is actually "saving" it from darkness. His plans, however, are thwarted by Killrain`s release of dark energy. After Hiruda reverts back to her normal self, Hiruda attempts to rescue Saionji when he is linked to the dark tower, with his life in danger. It is then that Saionji realizes her true feelings for him, and in return, he seems to develop feelings for her also, resulting in him being able to draw his Holy Grail from her heart.
In the end, he decides to stay in End Earth, together with Hiruda, Xecty and Jin-Crow in Baelgard, to restore the forest back to its former glory.
Saionji is an extremely talented swordsman, he was capable of defeating Kiriya in a duel with normal swords.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19123" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-22">
<rating votes="4">6.01</rating>
<name>Ryuuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuuna acknowledged Zero`s intentions, a priestess of Etwarl Shrine who believes in Souma. Zeroboros lived inside her, so in order to stop him, she committed suicide by throwing herself into Xion`s sword. She was later resurrected by Zero, along with Lazarus. Souma is able to pull a broadsword type soul blade from her called Holy Dragon Sword Heavenly Cloud Bush (聖龍剣 アマノムラクモ, Seiryuuken Amanomurakumo); it has the power to paralyze its enemies with a blinding light.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19124" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-22">
<name>Lazarus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lazarus is a Dragonian tribesman, who swore to protect Souma. He is also a friend to Ryuna, who acknowledged Zero`s intentions. He was killed by Xion when he got possessed by Zeroboros, but was later resurrected by Zero, along with Ryuna. Souma is able to draw an enormous single-bladed sword from him called Holy Dragon Blade Solid Outrage (聖龍刀 逆鱗金剛, Seiryuutou Gekirinkongou).
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="376" picture="53996.jpg">Sonobe Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19125" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-22">
<rating votes="4">4.58</rating>
<name>Houmei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Houmei is the Priestess of Seiran`s Tower of Rain Water. Centuries ago, she tried to destroy the world. Due to that, she was imprisoned in the forbidden lands of Konron. She later joined the `Luminous Knights` as their tactician. Despite her appearance, she is actually 3000 years old.
Note: In the game, she is actually of the same dragon race as http://anidb.net/ch19131 [Hyouun] although doesn`t look like it. An event in the game explains this connection. In the anime, she is referred to as an elf.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19126" type="appears in" update="2010-06-23">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Clalaclan Philias</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clalaclan Philias is the princess and Priestess of Philias` Tower of the Sun.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19127" type="appears in" update="2010-06-23">
<name>Caris Philias</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Caris Philias is the prince of Philias, thus the future king, and Clalaclan`s younger brother. He was victim of a curse by Shumari, which made him very sick, but was later healed by Houmei. In the last episode, he becomes the king of Philias.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2987" picture="23718.jpg">Shouji Umeka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19128" type="appears in" update="2010-06-23">
<name>Raidel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raidel is a priest of Seiran.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50216.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19129" type="appears in" update="2010-06-23">
<name>Shumari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shumari is the chancellor of Seiran who had the appearance of a nine-tailed fox. He was responsible for the assassination of Astraea`s queen and of the curse bestowed upon Caris. He is later killed by Baelgard`s moving fortress `Eisen Sarg`, right before he was to kill Souma.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50217.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="378" picture="46436.jpg">Oota Tetsuharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19130" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-22">
<name>Rouen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rouen is the King of Seiran. Before becoming king, he was the captain of a pirate crew, but his great conviction and good heart made him win the trust of the beastmen. In the last episode, he becomes a captain again, leaving the throne to Hyouun.
Note: In the game, he joins Weissritter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50218.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5057" picture="28861.jpg">Matsuoka Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19131" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-22">
<name>Hyouun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hyouun is one of Seiran`s five generals. He was ordered to watch over Houmei. He is unofficially considered part of the Luminous Knights due to his involvement with Houmei who is revealed to be his older sister. He has fallen in love with human girls, particularly Kureha and Seena, but he has to keep these feelings to himself due to Houmei`s intervention. In the last episode, he becomes the king of Seiran.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50219.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19132" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-22">
<name>Jin-Crow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jin-Crow is a mysterious birdman. Jin-Crow is a friend to Killrain, before the latter was infected by dark energy. He can still be seen at Killrain`s side, but he also searches for a way to help his friend overcome the darkness. He gives Kiriya the location of the ancient weapons, and later escorts Kiriya`s group to Bestia. In the past, he, Killrain, and Leon, Clalaclan`s older brother, swore peace to the countries, but then Shumari`s plot ruined their plans. He decides to become Xecty`s protector. Together with Saionji, Hiruda, and Xecty, they are busy restoring the forest back to its former glory.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50220.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19133" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-22">
<name>Killrain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Killrain is one of Baelgard`s four guardians. Originally a normal and kind elf, until he was infected by the darkness. Though he is the brother of Astraea`s queen, Celestia, he kept Xecty from knowing her true origins. He`s shown to possess immense dark energy, as shown after Xecty`s death, when he released said energy as a powerful blast, which covered nearly all of Liberia in an icy blizzard. His anger prompted him to blame all living souls, and after controlling the dark elven army of Baelgard, he plans to destroy everything. Only after Souma, Kiriya, and Saionji use the combined powers of their Holy Grails, that his soul is liberated. Together with his sister Celestia, he decides to stay behind and be sealed in the other dimension.
His soul blade is called Demon Gun Sword Gallatin (魔砲剣 ガラティン, Mahouken Garatin), a giant sword able to shoot laser beams. Unlike the others, Killrain himself transforms into a giant sword, rather than having the sword drawn from within him.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50221.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19134" type="appears in" update="2010-06-23">
<name>Zeed</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zeed is one of Baelgard`s four guardians. He is also an immortal due to a contract with his demon sword. He is in fact Philias` late prince, Leon, now under the control of his demon sword. His soul blade is called Holy Armor Sword Balmunc (聖鎧剣 バルムンク, Seigaiken Barumunku), and the sword and armor are similar to the ones used by Leon. He was later defeated by Souma, resulting in Leon`s spirit becoming free from the demon sword`s control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19138" type="appears in" update="2010-06-23">
<name>Lassi</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lassi is a strange little fellow who guided Souma and Elwyn through an icy blizzard. He guided the group to Celestia through a secret opening in the forest to the north of Philias. There, he is revealed to be the Spirit King of the Wind. He has an affinity towards elves who can strangely understand him. After Celestia, he joins Xecty in Baelgard, to restore the forest to its former glory.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19139" type="appears in" update="2010-06-23">
<name>Raihi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raihi is one of Seiran`s five generals. A tiger-like warrior, who is a good friend of Hyouun. He is very proud of his skills as a warrior.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50227.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6937" picture="171392.jpg">Imamura Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19140" type="appears in" update="2010-06-23">
<name>Enu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Enu is one of Seiran`s five generals. A bird-like warrior.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50228.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="71754" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">現代×異世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Today x Strange World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gendai x Isekai</title>
<summary>Many people have started disappearing in Tatsumi Town. Soon the disappearances begin to affect Souma Akisuki`s school. While searching for a cause to the disappearances, Souma and Touka Kureha meet a catgirl named Mao, who is from a different world.  After helping her catch beast human from her world, Souma and Kureha are accidentally dragged into the other world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738479</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71759" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心×剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart x Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro x Tsurugi</title>
<summary>Now stuck in the mysterious End Earth, Souma and Kureha meet a wolf man who explains what the sword, that Souma drew from Kureha, is. After fighting more demons, through several villages, with the wolfman. Souma and Kureha decide to  help seal all the demon gates that are letting the demons through, but is there more to it then just sealing the gates?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738481</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71813" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友×恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friend x Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo x Koi</title>
<summary>Unexpectedly facing Kiriya and Seena on the battle field. Souma and Kureha begin to question everything Shumari has told them. Feeling cornered, Shumari takes Kureha and orders a retreat. Now without a Soul Blade, Souma must find a way to rescue Kureha.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738483</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71814" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">使命×仲間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission x Team</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shimei x Nakama</title>
<summary>With Souma still missing, Kiriya and the others receive even more bad news. Learning of a mysterious army in the neutral zone, they decide to investigate. Upon arriving, Kiriya and the others are surprised to find the leader of the mysterious army to be none other then Saionji.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738485</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="71815" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精×妖精</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Elf x Elf</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei x Yousei</title>
<summary>While fighting one of Baelgard`s four guardians, Xecty, Kiriya is trapped in an underground cavern with her. Elsewhere, Souma and his group meet Elwyn, an old friend of Zero`s. Together they stumble upon a lab that turns the contaminated elves  into soldiers. Leading the lab is none other then Hiruda, can Souma fight his friend?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738487</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="72488" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱砂×氷雪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blazing Sand x Freezing Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Netsu Suna x Koori Yuki</title>
<summary>Souma and his group find an igloo in the middle of the desert. Belonging to the ice sorceress Blanc Neige, who turns out to be an old friend of Zero`s. Meanwhile, an out of control Xecty escapes from a Baelgard.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738489</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73493" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風×涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wind x Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze x Namida</title>
<summary>In an attempt to stop the impending battle. Souma calls on Kiriya and Saionji to ask them to stop their battle. His attempt fails as neither one of them will budge. Now with the final battle between the two starting, Souma must make an attempt to stop them once more.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738491</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73494" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白騎士×零</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Knight x Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiro Kishi x Rei</title>
<summary>After the major events in the previous episode, Zero recounts to Souma his past, and how he became the guardian of End Earth. At the same time, Kiriya travels to Valeria, to request the aid of Beastia, and runs into a familiar cat-girl.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738493</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73495" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望×希望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Despair x Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubou x Kibou</title>
<summary>While Mao tries to find a way to enter into Liberia to find Souma, he and Elwin locate Trihart, who entrusts to them "hope."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738495</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73496" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会×絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion x Bonds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai x Kizuna</title>
<summary>Souma is unexpectedly reunited with of all his friends after leading a depressed Kiriya to meet the world`s "hope". Later, Mao and Souma fight together against Zeed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738497</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73685" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">精霊×魔女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spirit x Witch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seirei x Majo</title>
<summary>Lassi guides the group to meet the elf Kiriya but when Xecty is prevented from releasing the tower of wind`s power by Killrain they decide to storm the place and liberate Saionji. Along the way they also restore Hiruda back to normal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738499</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73686" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光×闇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light x Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari x Yami</title>
<summary>After fighting their way towards Saionji, the group is unable to pierce the barrier protecting him. That is until Hiruda arrives. Meanwhile, Killrain is revealed to be possessed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738501</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="73687" update="2017-07-15">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界×心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">World x Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai x Kokoro</title>
<summary>The group are finally able to defeat Er Fahren and liberate Killrain`s soul. After finding a way home Souma decides to stay in End Earth leaving only Kiriya, Seena and Kureha to return to their own world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738503</identifier>
<identifier>shining-tears-x-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125909" update="2010-12-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125910" update="2010-12-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
