<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="509" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>1998-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Akihabara Dennou-gumi</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Akihabara Cyber Team</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Cyber Team in Akihabara</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">アキ電</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">akiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">adg</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アキハバラ電脳組</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Cyberteam in Akihabara</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2731" type="Sequel">Akihabara Dennou-gumi: 2011-nen no Natsuyasumi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="31111">Over all a good series, at the very least I found it entertaining and I`ll re-watch it again at some point in the future. Don`t expect a mind blowing good anime, but good for a watch. Basically good "For Fans" of the Super Power Genre.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/tv_series/w034.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="3569" type="Music">Mitsumune Shinkichi</name>
<name id="4253" type="Animation Character Design">Kishimoto Seiji</name>
<name id="778" type="Animation Work">Ashi Productions</name>
<name id="4372" type="Direction">Fujimoto Yoshitaka</name>
</creators>
<description>A patapi is a cute mechanical creature which is like a cyber pet. It can eat, sleep, play, and even help out its owners with some stuff. When Hibari Hanakoganei receives a patapi from a prince in her dreams, she is thrilled and names it Densuke. When mysterious forces try to steal Densuke, Hibari discovers that Densuke is not just an ordinary patapi. Densuke has magical powers that allows it to transform into a powerful cyber-fighter who looks like Hibari. Hibari`s friends also receive similar patapis, and together they form the Cyber Team in Akihabara.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="182">3.80</permanent>
<temporary count="185">6.12</temporary>
<review count="1">3.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>11167.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1072</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2288</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32</identifier>
<identifier>afmmhk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/tv_series/w034.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Cyber_Team_in_Akihabara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アキハバラ電脳組</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5380</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88866</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="104534" type="appears in" update="2019-07-19">
<name>Hanakoganei Tokijirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1406" picture="18432.jpg">Suzuki Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104535" type="appears in" update="2019-07-19">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Hanakoganei Hinako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104536" type="main character in" update="2019-07-19">
<name>Hanakoganei Hibari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7067" picture="32080.jpg">Shima Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104537" type="main character in" update="2019-07-19">
<name>Sakurajosui Suzume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2032" picture="186151.jpg">Yoshizumi Kozue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104538" type="main character in" update="2019-07-19">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Higashijuujou Tsugumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104539" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-19">
<name>Sengakuji Kamome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104540" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-19">
<name>Ootorii Tsubame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104547" type="appears in" update="2019-07-20">
<name>Nishifudawashi Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104548" type="appears in" update="2019-07-20">
<name>Kitaurawa Uzura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104549" type="appears in" update="2019-07-20">
<name>Hisho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104554" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-21">
<name>Cigogne Raspaile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5074" picture="156840.jpg">Kitagawa Takurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104555" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-21">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Goutokuji Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104556" type="appears in" update="2019-07-21">
<name>Sebastian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34666" picture="129022.jpg">Hashimoto Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104557" type="appears in" update="2019-07-21">
<name>Sakurajosui Suzumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236507.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104558" type="appears in" update="2019-07-21">
<name>Takaido-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104559" type="appears in" update="2019-07-21">
<name>Higashijuujou Shinnosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104560" type="appears in" update="2019-07-21">
<name>Higashijuujou Misako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104561" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-21">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Daikan`yama Hatoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104562" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-21">
<rating votes="2">8.78</rating>
<name>Soshigaya Miyama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104563" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-21">
<name>Ryuugasaki Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104606" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-22">
<name>Sengakuji Shimafukurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104607" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-22">
<name>Ryuugasaki Washiu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104608" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-22">
<name>Christian Rosenkreuz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104609" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-22">
<name>Shiro no Ouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5596" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仮面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5597" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奈落</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naraku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5598" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Newborn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5599" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニマ・ムンデイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anima Mundi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anima Mundi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5600" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂の城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Castle of Sand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suna no Shiro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5601" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">失楽園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Garden Without Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitsu Rakuen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5602" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祭壇都市</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Altar City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saidan Toshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5603" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今ひとたびの幻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Current Illusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ima Hitotabi no Maboroshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5604" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">召還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Recall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoukan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5605" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">羽ひらくとき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When the Wings Spread</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hane Hiraku Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8996" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ディーヴァ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Diva</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Diva</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8997" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い流星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Shooting Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Ryuusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8998" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホムンクルス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homunculus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Homunculus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9000" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デスクロウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death Crow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Death Crow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9001" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コカトリス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cockatrice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cockatrice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9002" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つばめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsubame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9004" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">去りにし日々の光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Going After the Daily Light</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sari nishi Hibi no Hikari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9005" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒いディーヴァ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Diva</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Diva</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9006" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">五人目...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fifth Member...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goninme...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9007" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い靴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Shoes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Kutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9008" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦アキハバラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle of Akihabara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen Akihabara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9009" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白い王子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Prince</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Ouji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9010" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9011" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビリケン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Billiken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Billiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9012" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Trip Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9013" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Birth</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Birth</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95857" update="2008-12-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95858" update="2008-12-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95859" update="2008-12-25">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95860" update="2008-12-25">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119049" update="2011-07-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Outtakes</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
