<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5107" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-07-19</startdate>
<enddate>2008-07-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gake no Ue no Ponyo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ponyo On A Cliff</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Ponyo - Das große Abenteuer am Meer</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Ponyo das verzauberte Goldfischmädchen</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Рыбка Поньо на утёсе</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Ponyo na klifie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">崖の上のポニョ</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">崖上的波妞</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ponyo on the Cliff by the Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Ponyo - Das grosse Abenteuer am Meer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ponyo sur la falaise</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Ponyo sulla scogliera</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Ponyo en el Acantilado</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Рыбка Поньо на утесе</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Ponyo</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Ponyo på klippan vid havet</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Ponyo à Beira-Mar</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Ponyo: Uma Amizade que Veio do Mar</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Ponyo z útesu nad mořem</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="official">Ponyo på klippen ved havet</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="official">Ponyo on the Cliff by the Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Ponyo rantakalliolla</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">פוניו על הצוק ליד הים</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Ponyo ant uolos prie jūros</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Küçük Deniz Kızı Ponyo</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Ponyo mäe otsas</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">崖上的波兒</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Ponyo y el secreto de la Sirenita</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="303" approval="55" total="65">Tonari no Totoro</anime>
<anime id="679" approval="19" total="33">Neko no Ongaeshi</anime>
<anime id="5303" approval="10" total="11">Chonnyonyeouu Yeouubi</anime>
<anime id="12738" approval="8" total="10">Yoake Tsugeru Lu no Uta</anime>
<anime id="5056" approval="5" total="9">Kappa no Coo to Natsuyasumi</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="9">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="610329">That so kawaii!!!!!!!! Watch it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="507045">I was lucky enough to find this on someone`s top ten movie list a couple of years ago, I had never heard of it at the time.

It`s easy to get swept away by Ponyo`s journey and lost in the fantasy of this movie.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="314759">ponyo, ponyo~</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="2975">Miyazaki is back. Way better than the Moving Castle.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="548718">I`m just here to say "screw you rating".
There is no way this film is worse than Arrietty or Howl, or On Poppy Hill.
For me, it sits in front of Kiki, and before Laputa (probably, I`m not about to seriously work it all out).

I highly recommend as a film for young kids and those with young kids.

Side note: excellently dubbed by Disney.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="721720">This is another great anime by studio ghibli, and it is appropriate for all ages. I highly endorse this movie, though I do question the parenting of the mother (watch it you will understand.)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ghibli.jp/ponyo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="40" type="Direction">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
<name id="729" type="Work">Studio Ghibli</name>
<name id="40" type="Original Work">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
<name id="1947" type="Music">Hisaishi Joe</name>
<name id="11846" type="Work">Hoshino Kouji</name>
</creators>
<description>A young boy, http://anidb.net/ch12312 [Sousuke], befriends a strange looking goldfish whom he names http://anidb.net/ch12311 [Ponyo]. Unbeknownst to Sousuke, Ponyo is a magic fish who has decided that she wants to live with Sousuke and the other humans. Unfortunately, Ponyo`s decision to give up her underwater life creates a crack in an ancient magic spell, and places the world in danger. Together, Sousuke and Ponyo must set things right.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3431">6.96</permanent>
<temporary count="3448">7.56</temporary>
<review count="3">6.55</review>
</ratings>
<picture>83816.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7814</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2890</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4028</identifier>
<identifier>xrkldx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ghibli.jp/ponyo/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ponyo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>崖の上のポニョ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1864</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327529</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9575</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1155" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-28">
<name>mermaid</name>
<description>A creature that is half-human (usually the upper body) and half-fish (usually the lower body). A male mermaid is called merman (but they can appear under many different names). Since mermaids are often confused with Sirens in media, they may posses special abilities akin to Sirens such as enchanting voice (on the other hand Sirens are often being portrayed as mermaids). Some mermaids might be able to transform their whole body into human (which is not surprising since mermaids are often associated with the "want to become human" theme) and that should not disqualify them from getting this tag.</description>
<picurl>209970.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2875" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>ecology</name>
<description>Nature and ecology are a central theme of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3394" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>environmentalism</name>
<description>Environmental protection is a practice of protecting the natural environment on individual, organizational or governmental levels, for the benefit of both the natural environment and humans. Due to the pressures of population and technology, the biophysical environment is being degraded, sometimes permanently. This has been recognized, and governments have begun placing restraints on activities that cause environmental degradation. Since the 1960s, activity of environmental movements has created awareness of the various environmental issues.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3931" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-27">
<name>magical realism</name>
<description>Magical realism is fiction that portrays magical or unreal elements as a natural part in an otherwise realistic or mundane environment, in particular when a highly detailed, realistic setting is invaded by something too strange to believe. Magical realism is often associated with Latin American literature, particularly authors including Gabriel García Márquez and Isabel Allende.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4626" parentid="3394" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-18">
<name>nature strikes back</name>
<description>Humanity continues to pollute and waste the land. Until at some point (usually in the future), nature "has had it" and devises a way to countermand this dire situation. This cleansing of the Earth may well take out humanity, though.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5276" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-25">
<name>typhoon</name>
<description>A typhoon is a mature tropical cyclone that develops in the north-western part of the Pacific Ocean between 180° and 100°E. This region is referred to as the north-west Pacific basin. Identical phenomena in the eastern north Pacific are called hurricanes, with tropical cyclones moving into the western Pacific re-designated as typhoons.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6350" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-21">
<name>Oofuji Noburou Award</name>
<description>The Oofuji Noburou Award is an animation award given to a group or individual at the Mainichi Film Awards to recognise animation excellence. It is named after Japanese animator http://anidb.net/cr5602 [Oofuji Noburou].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="12310" type="main character in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="8">5.50</rating>
<name>Fujimoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10038" picture="37269.jpg">Tokoro George</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12311" type="main character in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="9">8.56</rating>
<name>Ponyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10033" picture="2686.gif">Nara Yuria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12312" type="main character in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="8">8.30</rating>
<name>Sousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10034" picture="37265.jpg">Doi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12313" type="main character in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="14">8.33</rating>
<name>Lisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10035" picture="40460.jpg">Yamaguchi Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12314" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="4">2.21</rating>
<name>Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10036" picture="37267.jpg">Nagashima Kazushige</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12315" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="5">1.87</rating>
<name>Kumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10040" picture="37275.jpg">Hiraoka Eimi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12316" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="5">5.42</rating>
<name>Toki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37259.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10039" picture="37273.jpg">Yoshiyuki Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12317" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="6">5.40</rating>
<name>Yoshie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9343" picture="206321.jpg">Naraoka Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12318" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="4">3.21</rating>
<name>Ponyo no Imouto-tachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8167" picture="37271.jpg">Yano Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12319" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="6">4.54</rating>
<name>Granmammare</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37263.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10037" picture="37268.jpg">Amami Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76103" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-28">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9359" picture="34571.jpg">Oohashi Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="92170" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (15sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92171" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2008-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
