<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5131" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-10-26</startdate>
<enddate>2008-08-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Soukou Kihei Votoms: Pailsen Files</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Armored Trooper Votoms: Pailsen Files</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Zırhlı Piyade Votoms: Pailsen Dosyaları</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">装甲骑兵波多姆兹PAILSEN FILES</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">装甲騎兵ボトムズ ペールゼン・ファイルズ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1698" type="Sequel">Soukou Kihei Votoms</anime>
<anime id="4842" type="Prequel">Soukou Kihei Votoms: Red Shoulder Document - Yabou no Roots</anime>
<anime id="6722" type="Summary">Soukou Kihei Votoms: Pailsen Files - Gekijouban</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="216997">Very good story, mecha design and good CG animation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="307198">The new series in the old style. I recommend to everyone.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.votoms.net/pailsen/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1292" type="Animation Work">The Answer Studio</name>
<name id="661" type="Character Design">Shioyama Norio</name>
<name id="5134" type="Series Composition">Yoshikawa Souji</name>
<name id="660" type="Original Work">Takahashi Ryousuke</name>
<name id="660" type="Direction">Takahashi Ryousuke</name>
<name id="7860" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takeuchi Kazuyoshi</name>
<name id="5283" type="Music">Inui Hiroki</name>
<name id="8304" type="Music">Maejima Yasuaki</name>
</creators>
<description>OVA release from anime series "Armored Trooper Votoms" utilizing the latest in 3D CG animation. Created by the original staff of the series, with an all new story about the end of the 100 year war.
Source: cdjapan</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="442">6.75</permanent>
<temporary count="443">7.32</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221871.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7891</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3256</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3887</identifier>
<identifier>uwnboo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.votoms.net/pailsen/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Armored_Trooper_Votoms:_Pailsen_Files</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>装甲騎兵ボトムズ_ペールゼン・ファイルズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1880</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327826</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9045</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4021" parentid="36" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-08">
<name>evil military</name>
<description>The military is depicted as being of a nefarious nature in this anime. Be it through the heartlessness that their soldiers convey, or the ruthless killing of innocents, the military in this anime is not to be messed with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15676" type="main character in" update="2018-12-04">
<rating votes="168">8.80</rating>
<name>Chirico Cuvie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As the central character around which Votoms revolves, Chirico Cuvie is haunted by two pasts—one he cannot remember and another he cannot forget. He has no memory of his life prior to his 10th year, in which he lived on the planet Sunsa with adoptive parents who found him in a refugee center and were studying his unusual healing abilities—until they were killed in the first of many enemy invasions. Chirico witnessed their deaths, and survived burns that would have killed an ordinary human. But over the subsequent years, he proved himself to be far from ordinary.
Enlisting in the Melkian army as an Armored Trooper pilot, Chirico distinguished himself in many battles against the http://anidb.net/ch90340 [Balarant] and was transferred at age 16 to the elite http://anidb.net/ch90343 [Red Shoulder Battalion]. There, he was scrutinized by the commanding officer, Colonel Yoran Peruzen. Peruzen had been watching Chirico for many years, and had become convinced that Chirico`s miraculous recuperative powers made him immortal; a supreme survivor. After nearly ending Peruzen`s life, Chirico was thrown into the final battle of Sunsa. He wasn`t supposed to survive it, but he did. This was the battle that brought the Hundred Years War to an end, and the Red Shoulder Battalion was disbanded soon after.
In the last ditch effort to rid himself of Chirico, Peruzen transferred him to General http://anidb.net/ch89503 [Albert Killy]`s rogue unit for the raid on Lido. Killy`s men were instructed to kill Chirico during the operation, but Chirico`s unusual abilities made him more difficult to eliminate than anyone could guess. Caught up in events completely beyond his control, however, Chirico became a renegade - haunted both by Killy`s agents and the Melkian army.
Waiting only to uncover the lies and conspiracies that surround him, Chirico makes his way across the galaxy to find his destiny. His incredible stamina and resourcefulness are the result of his unknown heritage. When this truth is uncovered, nothing will ever be the same again.
Source: Geocities</description>
<picture>227433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81265" type="appears in" update="2016-03-26">
<rating votes="5">8.33</rating>
<name>ATM-09-ST Scopedog</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>184577.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="90329" type="appears in" update="2017-07-08">
<rating votes="2">6.51</rating>
<name>B-ATM-03 Fatty</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>204916.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="90330" type="appears in" update="2017-07-08">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>ATH-06-WP Diving Beetle</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>204917.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="90355" type="appears in" update="2017-07-09">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>ATH-14-ST Standing Tortoise</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>204943.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="90356" type="appears in" update="2017-07-09">
<name>B-ATM-04 Chabby</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>204945.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="84492" update="2007-10-20">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">2.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84698" update="2007-10-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渡河作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">River Crossing Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toka Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84699" update="2007-10-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガレアデ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Galeade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gareade</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84700" update="2007-10-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死の谷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Valley of Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi no Tani</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84701" update="2007-10-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">分隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Squad</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Buntai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88436" update="2008-02-28">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異能</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Abnormal Skills</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sogeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88437" update="2008-02-28">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">尋問</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Interrogation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinmon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90479" update="2008-05-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冷獄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frozen Prison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiyagoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90480" update="2008-05-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狙撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shooting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sogeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91484" update="2008-06-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モナド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monad</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91485" update="2008-06-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不死の部隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Immortal Unit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushi no Butai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91486" update="2008-06-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦略動議</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Motion Tactics</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senryaku Dougi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91487" update="2008-06-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダウン・バースト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Down Burst</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Down Burst</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
