<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5145" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shakugan no Shana Second</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Shana Second</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Burning Eyes Shana 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Burning Eyes Shana II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Shana of the Burning Eyes 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Shana of the Burning Eyes II</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Жгучий взор Сяны (второй сезон)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Ognistooka Shana II</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Shana dos Olhos Ardentes II</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">SHANA Liepsnojančios Akys 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shakugan no Shana II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shakugan no Shana 2</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Вогняноока Шана ІІ</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">灼眼的夏娜 第二季</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Shakugan II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SHANA2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SnS 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SHANA II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SHANA 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SnS II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Shakugan 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">灼眼のシャナII[Second]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shakugan no Shana Second</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">작안의 샤나 2기</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8483" type="Sequel">Shakugan no Shana Final</anime>
<anime id="3408" type="Prequel">Shakugan no Shana</anime>
<anime id="6757" type="Side Story">Shakugan no Shana S</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="20">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="480768">What I said about the first season stands!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="156816">Really good series, sure its more fillerish than the 1st, but once the action gets going, it really gets going.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="423301">Provides a sense of power or strength for girls, but not in a "girly" way. I would say this is a meaningful anime and I liked it very much. Indeed, it NEEDS a third season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="445819">If you didn`t like the tangled web of the romance sub-plot that started in the first season, you might want to skip through some episodes in the first half (I also want to add that normally I love romance shows).  I can understand some romance between the two main characters, as it seems natural given their situation.  The first season was bearable, but the second seems like two different shows mashed up into one.

I essentially got through the first few eps got the gist of what was going on, skipped to a nice little 2 ep back story arc, then skipped on to the end of episode 14 where everything started to pick up and got really good.  

The other episodes in the first half just felt like filler... the last half was great... I`m recommending solely based on the last half.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="123017">REALLY great. just the ending is a bit.. not much of an ending. hopfully there will be a third season!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="79565">There is something about this series which I absolutely like.  The adventure, the action, and the relationships will keep you craving more.  I hope there is a 3rd season because the first two are great.  I really hope people support and buy the series when it is available in North America.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="321417">I`m a Fan of This Series (Most Interesting First Male Character(His Magical Potential);&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and Well let`s say i`m sharpening my fangs for 3rd Season.&lt;br /&gt;</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.shakugan.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2120" type="Direction">Watanabe Takashi</name>
<name id="5805" type="Original Work">Takahashi Yashichirou</name>
<name id="4255" type="Character Design">Ootsuka Mai</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="2702" type="Series Composition">Kobayashi Yasuko</name>
<name id="11182" type="Chief Animation Direction">Imoto Yuki</name>
<name id="3744" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujii Masahiro</name>
<name id="4255" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ootsuka Mai</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the novel by http://anidb.net/cr5805 [Takahashi Yashichirou].
http://anidb.net/ch26 [Shana] and http://anidb.net/ch1246 [Alastor] — the Lord of the Crimson Realm — continue to do battle with the Guze no Tomogaras, who are trying to steal the Power of Existence from mortals. In the last battle, http://anidb.net/ch1220 [Yuuji] is revealed to be a mystes, a torch with nearly unlimited Power of Existence. Since the Tomogaras want to capture Yuuji and use him to upset the balance of the Realm, Shana resolves to protect Yuuji. Yuuji then vows to join Shana in her fight.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5627">6.31</permanent>
<temporary count="5695">7.61</temporary>
<review count="4">6.78</review>
</ratings>
<picture>7810.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7847</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20378</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20376</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20377</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14957</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2787</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3956</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4031</identifier>
<identifier>scoeyt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.shakugan.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>灼眼のシャナ_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1222</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>328701</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9473</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-25">
<name>contractor</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3981" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-27">
<name>ninja maid</name>
<description>This is an old tag for anime which had characters that were maids and also ninjas, or at least able to use ninjutsu. The tag will be removed once all maids in question are properly tagged. See also the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninja,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninja and maid] and the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninjutsu,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninjutsu and maid].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5988" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>living with the villain</name>
<description>Both, hero and villain have their secret identities. They live next door, go to the same school, work at the same place or even are best friends. But little do they know that in another part of their life they are the worst enemies. And yet they just do not recognize each other when they are out of their costumes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="26" type="main character in" update="2008-12-15">
<rating votes="808">7.69</rating>
<name>Shana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shana is the female lead of the show and a Flame Haze. Initially she is concentrated solely on her duty as a Flame Haze, going as far as to not bearing even a name. She sees Yuuji only as a Torch, an object, marginally interesting because of his status as a Mystes. Yuuji, in his need to humanize her, chose to name her "Shana" after her sword. However, she slowly opens up to Yuuji, coming to think of him as a person, despite being a Torch, and eventually comes to love him. Until she met him, she was only identified by her Flame Haze title "Flame-Haired Burning-Eyed Hunter," or her sword, Nietono no Shana.</description>
<picture>15372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="151">5.64</rating>
<name>Shanatan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shanatan is the chibi version of Shana, who appears in the special episodes.</description>
<picture>14300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="870" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-04-07">
<rating votes="457">3.24</rating>
<name>Index</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Index, also known by her full name, Index Librorum Prohibitorum, is the series` co-heroine, a young nun from Necessarius ("Church of Necessary Evil"), a branch of the Church of England. Her mind has been implanted with the 103,000 magical texts of the Index-Librorum-Prohibitorum as she possess Photographic memory at the cost of her own memories, or so the church authorities say. Her sorcery name is Dedicatus545. She is said to have 15% of memory space left to use in daily activities, which allows her to live normally for less than a year. However, all of this is a lie and are the church`s plan to make her unable to betray, by "maintenance" her once the memory has come to its limit.</description>
<picture>232175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1015" type="main character in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="398">7.75</rating>
<name>Enpatsu Shakugan no Uchite</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Enpatsu Shakugan no Uchite is Shana`s former name, which she got when she became a flame haze. When transforming, her hair and eyes turn crimson red.</description>
<picture>15374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1220" type="main character in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="207">3.74</rating>
<name>Sakai Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuji, the main character of the story, is just an average high school student. However, his world is turned upside down when he discovers that he is already dead and does not have much time before he disappears. Fortunately, Yuuji is a Mystes who contains a treasure known as the Reiji Maigo. Unlike normal torches, the treasure inside him restores his Power of Existence every night at midnight.</description>
<picture>76010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1246" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="122">7.89</rating>
<name>Alastor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alastor is the Lord of the Crimson Realm to whom Shana is bound. He expresses his will through a divine vessel called the Cocytus, which (in Shana`s case) takes the form of a pendant which the picture shows. Alastor is considered to be one of the strongest of all Lords or Denizens; in fact being one of the true Gods of the Crimson Realm. But even so, he tries to keep the Denizens from consuming Power of Existence.</description>
<picture>76003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1302" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="175">4.17</rating>
<name>Yoshida Kazumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazumi is a fifteen-year-old girl and Yuuji`s classmate. She has a crush on him, but is a bit too shy to tell him directly. In the first season, she spends most of her screen time remaining ignorant of Shana`s true nature and her actual relationship with Yuuji. When Shana became her love-rival, she vowed to tell Yuuji her feelings and to let him decide between her and Shana.</description>
<picture>76005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1314" type="appears in" update="2008-12-17">
<rating votes="34">2.82</rating>
<name>Ike Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hayato, otherwise chiefly known as Ike, is a fifteen-year-old high school student and has been Yuuji`s friend since junior high school. He carries the title "Megane-man" ("Glasses Man"), or Four-Eyes in the English version. He is secretly fond of Kazumi Yoshida. However, as Yuuji`s loyal (and best) friend, he is the one who helps her to show her feelings toward Yuuji.</description>
<picture>15680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1322" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="66">8.03</rating>
<name>Sakai Chigusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chigusa is Yuuji`s mother. She can seem gentle but she is strong and very intelligent. Her husband, Kantarou, works outside the country. Chigusa remains ignorant of Shana and Yuuji`s true nature, but becomes a source of good advice for Shana on matters where Alastor can not counsel her. The Crimson Lord himself acknowledges and bows to her wisdom after a phone call between the two of them. Described as a woman who can accept anything, she seems to harbor absolutely no problems with Shana often visiting Yuuji under the pretext of "training".</description>
<picture>76002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="419" picture="17271.jpg">Sakurai Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1330" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="7">6.71</rating>
<name>Sakai Kantarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kentaro is Yuuji`s father. He first made his appearance in the second season of the anime. He usually resides outside Japan, but enjoys making sudden visits to the Sakai household, surprising his family. Despite his skinny figure, his athletic senses are good enough to retaliate a flying kick from Shana without scratch, who was mistaken that he was an enemy.</description>
<picture>75986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1351" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="57">6.95</rating>
<name>Satou Keisaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keisaku, a fifteen-year-old high school student, is Eita`s friend and class-skipping companion. When Margery Daw came to Misaki City, she randomly chose Keisaku and Eita to be her guides to the city. When he and Eita found a Haridan, a magical map to the city that Friagne had been using until his demise, the two often acted as support. Being a member of a wealthy family and independent of his parents, his house becomes a place for Margery to stay.</description>
<picture>76012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1353" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="31">4.67</rating>
<name>Tanaka Eita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eita, a fifteen-year-old high school student, is a well-built classmate of Keisaku`s. When Margery Daw came to Misaki City, she randomly chose him and Keisaku to be her guides to the city. When they found a Haridan, a magical map to the city that Friagne had been using until his demise, the two boys often acted as her support.</description>
<picture>76013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="465" picture="56019.jpg">Kondou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1354" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="51">7.69</rating>
<name>Ogata Matake</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matake is Yuuji`s classmate. She is a strong-willed physically active girl, as well as a bit of a tomboy. She also has feelings for Eita, and worries about his well-being.</description>
<picture>76017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7454" type="appears in" update="2011-10-17">
<rating votes="5">7.09</rating>
<name>Johan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The former Mystes of the Reiji Maigo. While he was an infant, Pheles murdered her father who tried to sacrifice Johan for a useless Power of Unrestraint to gain eternal youth. Pheles fled with Johan from his home and wandered the world together since. As she raised Johan, Pheles had expected his heart to become corrupted in the same manner as his father when she fulfilled his wishes and desires. It seemed by chance that when Johan reached a later age, he asked for one thing that caught Pheles off guard: herself, an indication that Johan had fallen in love with Pheles. Upon the beginnings of the Appointed Couple, the Reiji Maigo was created to ensure eternal life to Johan and Pheles ceased consuming humans. After his rebirth as a Mystes, he trained himself and became a powerful master of Power of Unrestraint, enhanced with his ability to sense the power of existence.</description>
<picture>69808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7650" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="177">7.17</rating>
<name>Margery Daw</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Margery is a tall, "well-endowed" and mature blond Flame Haze with a drinking habit. She uses the book Grimoire, which is the divine vessel through which Marchosias, to whom she is bound, expresses his will. Her main powers focus around chanting spells and turning into a werewolf. She casts spells by chanting an "Improvisational Poem of Slaughter."</description>
<picture>76019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7655" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-22">
<rating votes="88">8.75</rating>
<name>Marcosias</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Crimson Lord to whom Margery Daw is bound. He expresses his will through the divine vessel Grimoire, which takes the form of a book. He talks wildly, makes comments without remorse, and often teases Margery, often earning a retaliatory punch. He does genuinely care about her, however, perhaps not in the form of friendship but as a companion in battle.</description>
<picture>3077.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7797" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="18">4.21</rating>
<name>Marianne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Friagne`s Rinne (servants). Friagne seems to treasure her a bit more than is healthy for him. She usually takes the form of a doll.</description>
<picture>26824.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7801" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="24">5.47</rating>
<name>Friagne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Friagne, also known as "Flame Haze Murderer", takes his name`s meaning as his hobby, "treasure hunter". He is a powerful Tomogara arrayed in robes of untarnishable white.</description>
<picture>26829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8681" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="109">6.01</rating>
<name>Hecate</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hecate is one of the Trinity of the Bal Masqué, entitled as "the Priestess". She also controls the movements of Seireiden, Bal Masqué`s base. A small pale girl with white cape and hat wielding a staff-like Hougu, Trigon, she doesn`t speak much. Sydonay seems to care for her a lot. Bel Peol always mentions her having "eternal existence". Her position is very important with respect to what the Bal Masqué plans to do with Reiji Maigo, since she is the one who can take the power of Reiji Maigo and send it out to everything in Seireiden.
Hecate is a sad, quiet character, who has taken up the habit of prayer - despite having no one to pray to and despite Bel Peol considering it an odd thing to do - and frequently laments that she is "empty". In the light novels, it is implied that Hecate is praying to the Bal Masqué`s god, the Ceremonial Snake of the Festival. In contrast to her counterpart in the anime, the light novels depict Hecate as a cold and feared leader that even the entire Bal Masqué itself fear her. She has hobby of trekking in mountain tops, yet she despises mountain climbers who litter her favorite sites, so she slaughters them on sight. She is extremely skilled in combat using Aster, a Power of Unrestraint which shoots energy beams like meteor shower, and is capable in grappling as well which equals to Shana`s skill. She has a flute that can summon dragons of blue flame body. She also plays this flute when announcing the end of Seireiden`s anchoring.
In the anime, Hecate synchronized with Yuji, allowing her to draw on his sense of self to fill the void inside of her. The purpose of this synchronization was more sinister, however; once midnight struck, the Reiji Maigo attempted to restore the power of existence of its bearer. Since Yuji and Hecate were synchronized at the time, Reiji Maigo started pouring out an infinite amount of power in an attempt to fill Hecate`s capacity which is infinite. She consider the feelings that she gets from synchronizing with others are hers and no longer from their owners, much like a Torch being the remainder of their original human self takes over its identity. She was defeated when Yuji points out that the feelings, memories and sense of self that she is reveling about are not hers but his. When he says that Hecate is just as empty as she was before synchronizing and she cannot possibly fill her sense of self by drawing it from others(i.e.: questioning her "where her unique self"), she is forced to face the void that lies inside of her and screams in horror, lossing control of the synchronization, Seireiden and herself as well as discharging massive amounts of power of existence she stored while synchronized with Yuji which could destroy an entire city requiring Sydonay to save her.</description>
<picture>76023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11976" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="160">8.15</rating>
<name>Wilhelmina Carmel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wilhelmina is a young lady that wears a maid`s uniform all the time. She is bound to Tiamat, whose will resides in the divine vessel Persona, which shifts forms between a headband, and a mask when in battle. During the great war, Persona`s shape was a tiara. Her title`s meaning is like the term for a player (in chess) who can predict moves far ahead.
She is one of the great Flame Haze from the age of the great war, fighting alongside her friend, Mathilde Saint-Omer (the previous "Flame-Haired Burning-Eyed Hunter"). Together, they are like the counterpart of the "Pair of Wings" combination between the Crimson Denizens Merihim and Illuyankas. Her ability is the power to control an infinite number of ribbons which appear from around her. Wilhelmina, who always speaks in an overly formal and polite manner, has nearly no expression. She`s very skillful in many things, like singing and house chores, and is the one who took care of Shana during the girl`s training at Tendoukyuu. Cooking, however, is one of her weaknesses; this was made even more evident in the second season, after her attempts at cooking crashed Chigusa`s kitchen.
Wilhelmina dislikes Yuji as an overprotective mother might dislike her daughter`s boyfriend, and constantly refers to him as "the Mystes", though later on, she occasionally refers to him by his proper name. This is possibly due to Wilhelmina`s own desire to gain Shana`s affections. She has, in the anime, advocated killing him so as to keep the Reiji Maigo out of the hands of the Bal Masqué and had to be stopped from performing the deed herself twice by Shana. In the anime`s second season, Wilhelmina has begun to, more or less, accept Yuji`s presence, if not his influence on Shana, and, on Shana`s request, becomes Yuji`s training partner when Shana is otherwise not available.</description>
<picture>76018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12148" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="18">7.08</rating>
<name>Tiamat</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tiamat is the female Crimson Lord to whom Wilhelmina is bound. She is described by her own Flame Haze as a most unsociable entity; she is taciturn and to the point, saying nothing more than what is necessary, usually in a monotone, betraying no emotion regardless of the situation. In the novels, her lines are almost always written in four kanji letters, with no hiragana or katakana.</description>
<picture>40948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12623" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-17">
<rating votes="19">7.11</rating>
<name>Kaijin Sabrac</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sabrac is a powerful Crimson Lord who was victorious in numerous battles against the Flame Haze. He is literally an assassin, for he is usually seen receiving requests to kill a certain target of interest; his heavily armoured, face-covered, and leather-bandaged outward looks also add to the fact. He likes to make long fancy-talk speeches, and while he is seen dissatisfied many times, it is hard to see him in a wrath. His hobby is collecting bladed weapons from swords to katanas whether they are Treasure Tools or not, and he actively used them in fights. He and Dantalion loathe each other, for the latter transfigured Sabrac`s Treasure blade Hystorix into a blade-spinning drill-like contraption without permission, and the blade`s owner badly insulted the mad scientist for this.
During combat, his first strike is notorious for its insensibility even to the most sensitive Flame Haze nor Denizen, and that it can be cast at an unlimited number of targets with each strike at maximum power. His Power of Unrestraint, the Stigma, causes all wounds he inflicts to increase in size over time. This spell built for battle is fatal for most targets, and even if he/she might be strong, the target`s fate is unsure, and even if have survived, the piling amount of wounds will eventually bring Sabrac his victory.
Sabrac is actually an unbalanced Lord with a ridiculously gigantic body, yet with the range of sight, hearing, and other senses only as much as human. He hides his body by blending into the area he has chosen for battlefield, enabling him to launch a surprise attack without being detected. The humanoid Sabrac that appears after the first strike does possess the very mind of Sabrac, though it is almost invulnerable because it is only a figure created from small part of his body. As such, it can near infinitely endure or recover from any damage.
Hired by Bal Masqué, he hunted down the Engage Link and casted a part of "Psalm of Grand Order" into Reiji Maigo. He was again hired by Bel Peol and went to Misaki City, badly wounding the Flame Hazes by surprise attack and sets another part of the "Psalm" into Yuji. But his arrogance had let Wilhelmina succeed in curing the Stigma, and Yuji to speculate Sabrac`s secret and comes up with a plan to defeat him by ripping the figure along with few city blocks away from the true body, therefore cutting off his power of recovery and his retreat. By the teamwork of Flame Hazes, Sabrac was defeated, but he managed to escape to Seireiden with the power of Gordian Knot. Later, Sabrac is shown speaking with Bel Peol and announcing that he no longer has a reason to have his base at Seireiden.</description>
<picture>69809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13686" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="16">6.85</rating>
<name>Konoe Fumina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The transfer student Fumina Konoe bears an absolute resemblance to Hecate and her growing bond to Yuji has Shana and Yoshida on the edge of uneasiness, which slightly lessens after a study session.
In episode fifteen, it is revealed that Fumina is in fact a faux vessel created by Hecate, who had been sent to primarily keep an eye on the Reiji Maigo and seal the Silver should it attempt to escape. Her secondary purpose is to collect her memories of interacting with Yuji and the others. In the last episode of the second season, it seems that the memories and feelings from Fumina Konoe has given Hecate human feelings, causing her to hesitate to fire at Yuji at the last moment. This in turn, helps Yuji and Shana overcome the Taimei Shihen, leaving a confused Hecate to wonder what has overcome her state of mind. On this episode, she is also shown shedding tears.</description>
<picture>40949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19751" type="appears in" update="2012-04-26">
<rating votes="21">6.52</rating>
<name>Lamis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Guze no Tomogara in the Torch of an old man.</description>
<picture>76024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19752" type="appears in" update="2010-07-18">
<rating votes="5">3.18</rating>
<name>Sorath</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19753" type="appears in" update="2010-07-18">
<rating votes="7">5.13</rating>
<name>Tiriel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32587" type="appears in" update="2011-10-17">
<rating votes="18">5.75</rating>
<name>Pheles</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Once a trickster who toyed with the life of a mad alchemist, Pheles is a lord who fell in love with a human, Johan the alchemist`s son. In order to stay with him forever, they created the most precious treasure in Guze, a Treasure that can grant eternity to the Mystes bearing it: the Reiji Maigo. Due to the Reiji Maigo, she doesn`t need to consume other humans` power of existence; she can get enough to survive from Johan without him being in danger of disappearing. Due to a fight against the Bal Masque`s assassin Sabrac that severely wounded Johan, she sealed her lover into the Reiji Maigo. She was unaware that Sabrac had also placed the Silver into the Hougu simultaneously. The Reiji Maigo was then lost, so now she searches for him everywhere with a Power of Unrestraint "The Wheel of Wind" (Kaze no Tenrin), a guiding beacon that becomes a duplicate of her own when the target is found. Johan commandeers Yuji`s body to persuade her from sacrificing the current Mystes to bring him back and Pheles agrees to her lover`s wish before leaving for parts unknown. Before she left, Pheles gives Yoshida a cross Hougu called the Giralda.
She is friends with Wilhelmina who once she had saved from the trap set by the Denizen Lord Sabrac. She does not appear in the first season of the anime but appears in the second season around the end of episode twelve amid her search for the Reiji Maigo. She tries to free Johan the first time, only to be interrupted by Margery`s berserk rage as well as the coordinated actions of Wilhelmina and Shana. The second time Pheles tried to free Johan from within the Reiji Maigo, she gets impaled by the Silver`s arm, thus unwittingly calling forth Fecor, Konoe, and Hecate.
Pheles has long neon green hair which extends as far as her thighs and has it unbraided. Some of the fringes of her hair sweep up on opposite directions on each side of her face, with others hanging loose. The rest hang loosely on the middle.
Her outfit consists of a tight-fitting suit consisting of a dark brown upper garment which exposes much of her collarbone, a pair of tight trousers and a garment similar to a bolero with black shoulder pads. Much of her outfit is wrapped with lengths of same-coloured cloth, especially in the waist area, and the same goes for the arm region, except for an extra length of cloth that dangles from her elbow. She also wears a dark brown scarf around her neck and a pair of open-finger gloves.
Source: shakugan.wikia</description>
<picture>69807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33170" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="37">6.60</rating>
<name>Bel-Peol</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bel Peol is one of the Trinity of the Bal Masqué, entitled as the "Strategist". She takes the form of a woman with three eyes, but has an eye-patch covering her right eye. A scheming character that would have no qualms in manipulating her unsuspecting subordinates and sending them off to die. Apparently she also has a gift for engendering loyalty in her subordinates, such as Vine, as she is capable of inspiring them to perform obviously dangerous tasks on her behalf. Her strategic skills are balanced by a considerable aptitude for combat.
In the novel, Bel Peol`s catchphrase is "Much things in life don`t come as one pleases". Unlike most Denizens, who live their lives as they will, Bel Peol is exceptional in that fact that she enjoys the obstacles that come against her plans, delighting in the challenges they pose, feeling that it is the overcoming of such obstacles that makes life interesting.</description>
<picture>76022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33171" type="appears in" update="2014-02-22">
<name>Bal Masque</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Bal Masqué is an organization of Denizens who moved into the human world several millennia ago under the Grand Master and the God of Creation, the Sairei no Hebi (｢祭礼の蛇」, "Snake of Festival"). After his defeat by Flame Hazes, it is currently led by three powerful figures called the Trinity. Since then, the Bal Masqué stayed low and became an organization to support Denizens, like Outlaw does with Flame Hazes. Their goal is to accomplish the "Grand Order", of which the details are yet unknown, and the Power of Unrestraint called the "Psalm of Grand Order" and Reiji Maigo, which resides in Yuji, are the keys vital to their plot. The subordinate members of Bal Masqué are largely classified into three types of functions; the combatants called Wanderers, the trackers and scouts called Jaegers, and the messengers called Heralds.</description>
<picture>150591.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="33172" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="21">7.25</rating>
<name>Sydonay</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sydonay is one of the Trinity of the Bal Masqué, entitled as the "General". For some time, he stayed outside of the Organization, because he wanted the freedom to do as he wants, such as serving the Denizens as a bodyguard for his personal hobby. He also appreciates human civilization enough to enjoy smoking cigarettes. However, after finding Reiji Maigo, he has returned to his previous position. He usually looks like a tall, well-built man wearing a pair of sunglasses and dark colored suits, but with great shape-shifting abilities, he can change into various chimeras without the use of spells like other Denizens do. In addition, when he is on duty as the General, he wields a spear-like hougu called the "Shintetu Nyoi" (神鉄如意, "The Divine Metal at Will"), which shifts shape and size at Sydonay`s will. With this weapon in hand, he leads an army of Denizens and Lords, destroying the major Outlaws throughout Europe and China. Sydonay and Margery have fought one another in the past, as Sydonay describes it as a "reunion" during a battle with her. Out of the Trinity, he cares for Hecate the most, coming to her rescue even when in a fight as shown during his battle with Margery as he abandons the battle to save her from the burning flames.</description>
<picture>76021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37825" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-17">
<rating votes="24">4.62</rating>
<name>Dantalion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37826" type="appears in" update="2011-10-17">
<rating votes="14">2.77</rating>
<name>Domino</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="402" picture="17249.jpg">Katou Nanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37828" type="appears in" update="2011-10-17">
<rating votes="10">5.43</rating>
<name>Fecor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37832" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="12">4.82</rating>
<name>Nakamura Kimiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37834" type="appears in" update="2011-10-17">
<rating votes="8">4.43</rating>
<name>Fujita Harumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1444" picture="172066.jpg">Masu Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37841" type="appears in" update="2013-07-15">
<rating votes="30">8.74</rating>
<name>Khamsin Nbh`w</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Khamsin is the Flame Haze contracted to Behemoth. While he is one of the oldest Flame Haze in history, perhaps even thousands of years old, he bears the appearance like a ten-year-old Middle-Eastern boy. Although a Flame Haze, Khamsin`s primary function is not that of defeating Tomogara, but acting as a tuner, dispelling the distortion caused by battles between the Flame Haze and Tomogara. Despite this, Khamsin also has combat capability, and has the ability to create and move stone golem-like creatures and control stones. He is very powerful, but is more famous for his accuracy, or lack thereof, in his attacks. In the anime, Khamsin and Behemoth are collectively labeled `the geezers` by Margery Daw. Tellingly, the once battle-happy Flame Haze expressed some uneasiness and reluctance for the notion that they might join in battle against the Crimson Denizens. He was formerly a prince who had dreamed of becoming a great warrior, but when he became a Flame Haze to fend off the Denizen, he was forgotten by everyone as the price for the contract. He is fatally wounded by explosions caused by the death of the Seeking Researcher in the final stages of the Second Great War and collapses. He is then surrounded by Wilhelmina, Shana, Margey, the remaining three of The Four Gods of Earth as well as Kazumi. After a heartfelt exchange and some final words to his contractor, Behemoth, he passes away from his wounds.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>69696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39182" type="appears in" update="2011-12-01">
<rating votes="8">1.83</rating>
<name>Eastedge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39183" type="appears in" update="2011-12-01">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Quetzalcoatl</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="688" picture="18295.jpg">Tanaka Kan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39185" type="appears in" update="2011-12-01">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Yuri Chvojka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39186" type="appears in" update="2011-12-01">
<name>Valac</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1875" picture="151654.jpg">Yamakawa Kotomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39325" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Vine</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39326" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Zarovee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2577" picture="22573.jpg">Misono Yukihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39327" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Bifrons</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39330" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Mare</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39331" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Kasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6935" picture="77710.jpg">Matsubara Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39332" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Annaberg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40172" type="appears in" update="2014-02-22">
<name>Oomine Satoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40174" type="appears in" update="2014-02-22">
<name>Okada-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="376" picture="53996.jpg">Sonobe Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40181" type="appears in" update="2014-02-23">
<name>Shitsuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4742" picture="54426.jpg">Fukumatsu Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40183" type="appears in" update="2014-02-23">
<name>Kyodai Kyuupii</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40184" type="appears in" update="2014-02-23">
<name>Sasaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="218" picture="17036.jpg">Nakao Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40185" type="appears in" update="2014-02-23">
<name>Ogiwara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40186" type="appears in" update="2014-02-23">
<name>Shikaisha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40187" type="appears in" update="2012-01-03">
<name>Seito Kaichou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43023" type="appears in" update="2012-03-29">
<rating votes="3">3.04</rating>
<name>Sydonay</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="81556" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再びの刻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatabi no Toki</title>
<summary>The second semester has just begun, but Yuji is having a bad case of déjà vu—the whole day seems to be a repeat of events from last semester! Could it be the work of a Denizen?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="82756" update="2007-09-13">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83799" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全ての序章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prelude to Everything</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subete no Joshou</title>
<summary>Wilhelmina wraps Yuji a little too hard in training, but they discover something new about his Power of Existence. Later at school, Shana and Yuji find themselves trapped in the same dream—and Kazumi is their only hope of escape!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84343" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疑惑の転校生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Suspicious Transfer Student</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giwaku no Tenkousei</title>
<summary>A spoiled new student enrolls in Yuji’s class—and she’s a spitting image of a certain memory-absorbing Denizen! Shana draws out another enemy when she goes to great lengths to dispel her suspicions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84480" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="10">2.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">憂いの少女たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dismayed Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Urei no Shoujo-tachi</title>
<summary>Konoe doesn’t seem to want to leave Yuji’s side. When the transfer student starts getting more and more of Yuji’s attention, the other girls can’t help but feel snubbed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84481" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家族の食卓</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Family Dinner Table</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazoku no Shokutaku</title>
<summary>Shana’s so angry with Yuji that she can’t stand being around him. Wilhelmina notices Shana’s down in the mouth, so she decides to change up their evening meal routine—and achieves some oddly tasty results!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84482" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">試練の前夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eve of the Ordeal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiren no Zen`ya</title>
<summary>The gang gets together for a study session at Satou’s place, but a hungover Flame Haze won’t budge from her spot on the couch. When she finally crawls out, she ends up sharing some insight on the ins and outs of jealousy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84605" update="2007-10-22">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">30second Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85035" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">池速人, 栄光の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hayato Ike`s Day of Glory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ike Hayato, Eikou no Hi</title>
<summary>Ike painstakingly plans a group outing at the amusement park with high hopes of a having a romantic moment on the Ferris wheel with his favorite gal. But he forgot to factor in that every ride gives him the urge to lose his lunch!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85086" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去への扉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Door to the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako e no Tobira</title>
<summary>Sato has a burning desire to become a Flame Haze, so he asks Margery Daw to train him. She’s reminded of the last time she agreed to train someone in New York during the Great Depression.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85087" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀しみのマイルストーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sad Milestone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi no Milestone</title>
<summary>Margery continues to share her painful history against a shape-shifting foe and his time-altering accomplice. Yuji has more control of his power of existence than ever before. When he tries a new move, the results defy expectations.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85088" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰ってきた男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man Who Returned</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaette Kita Otoko</title>
<summary>Shana can’t explain Yuji’s silver flame. At school, a festival calls for picking costume couples, and one pair will be famous star-crossed lovers! Kazumi and Shana ask Yuji’s mom for help—and get a love talk from the man of the house!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85572" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束の二人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Promised Pair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku no Futari</title>
<summary>The entire school is bustling with preparations for the upcoming festival. Wilhelmina returns from her research abroad with news that an infamous member of the crimson world will come for something inside Yuji.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85573" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">清秋祭始まる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Clear Autumn Festival Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seishuusai Hajimaru</title>
<summary>While Yuji’s school kicks off the festival with a parade, Wilhelmina and Margery Daw discuss the heavier matters at hand. Shana’s dead set on dropping the “L” word to Yuji on stage, but a big wind blows in the dreaded enemy looking for her lost lover.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85663" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">収束, そして兆し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Convergence, Followed by an Omen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuusoku, Soshite Kizashi</title>
<summary>The school grounds transforms into a supernatural warzone. When Pheles reaches for the object of her desire, Yuji’s silver flame sends Margery Daw into destructive rage!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86636" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の恋人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eternal Lover</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Koibito</title>
<summary>Yuji lends Pheles some of his power from the Midnight Lost Child. After enjoying the last day of the festival with the girls, Pheles takes a moment to thank everyone for allowing her true self to arrive—so she can try once more to take Yuji’s core!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86798" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">守るべきもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Must Be Protected</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamorubeki Mono</title>
<summary>Finally inside the Ball Masque’s forcefield, the three Flame Haze give it their all in a fiery battle to the finish. Shana and Yuji fight side by side to topple the armored giant and retrieve Yuji’s power of existence before he fades away!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86799" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危難の胎動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stirrings of Peril</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinan no Taidou</title>
<summary>The time is nigh for the Ball Masque to reap the Midnight Lost Child for their own sinister plan. Shana and the others struggle against an impenetrable bubble while Yuji battles countless bots inside!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86800" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマス・イヴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas Eve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christmas Eve</title>
<summary>Yuji’s dad returns home to share some shocking news. Then, Shana and Kazumi plan to put Yuji’s true feelings to the test, but just as he arrives at their rendezvous, a horrendous scheme from the Crimson world takes shape.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86801" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="13">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">合わさる力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Combined Strength</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Awasaru Chikara</title>
<summary>Yuji devises a plan to crack Sabrac’s seemingly endless source of power. When his strategy comes together, Shana makes her biggest flame yet to defeat the nearly invincible Denizen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86802" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">茜色の死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scarlet Battle to the Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akaneiro no Shitou</title>
<summary>Sabrac ascends from the wake of Shana’s attack on the Wanderer. Everyone is badly hurt, and a spell worsens their injuries by the minute! Wilhelmina faces the familiar foe alone, but every effort to wrap him fails to leave even a scratch.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86803" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">言えなかったこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Couldn`t Be Said</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ienakatta Koto</title>
<summary>Forced to follow his abductor, Yuji finds himself caught in a conundrum. But when he figures out the odd Denizen’s trap, he takes matters into his own hands.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86804" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">錯綜の悠二</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Complicated Yuuji</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakusou no Yuuji</title>
<summary>Yuji trains feverishly to turn his power into a useful flame. He’s determined to leave the city with Shana—but she senses a faltering in his resolve when his mother falls ill. While he’s walking off harsh words, Yuji’s seized by identical Denizens!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86805" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Separate Paths</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Michi</title>
<summary>Yuji hones his fighting skills in order to protect himself from a foe that once nearly killed Wilhelmina. Then, two friends decide to take separate paths. While one wants to make a mark in the supernatural world, the other will walk away from it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86806" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つきせぬ想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukisenu Omoi</title>
<summary>The festival is over, but after school activities involve making a plan to counter the Ball Masque. Kazumi dwells on her desire to be closer to Yuji and ponders the parting gift Pheles gave her. Will she be strong enough to use it when the time comes?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86807" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚醒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakusei</title>
<summary>The Ball Masque makes their next move right in the middle of Pheles’ attack! Shana and the other Flame Haze take action, but a girl everyone had grown to trust takes a stab at Yuji. His transformation comes as a surprise—especially to Pheles.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="88296" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灼眼のシャナたん びぎんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shakugan no Shana-tan Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakugan no Shana-tan: Begins</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88414" update="2010-06-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90074" update="2010-06-24">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3 (Episode 24)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91278" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灼眼のシャナたん&amp;吉田-近衛史菜の逆襲-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shakugan no Shana-tan &amp; Yoshida - Fumina Konoe Strikes Back</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakugan no Shana-tan &amp; Yoshida: Konoe Fumina no Gyakushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110773" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2009-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灼眼のシャナたん りべんじ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shakugan no Shana-tan Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakugan no Shana-tan: Revenge</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119231" update="2011-11-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119232" update="2011-11-02">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119233" update="2011-11-02">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129261" update="2012-06-16">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリアグネとマリアンヌの なぜなにシャナ! なんでも質問箱! その8 「敖の立像」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friagne and Marianne`s Why, What, Shana! Ask Anything Question Box 8: Statue of Pride</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Friagne to Marianne no Naze Nani Shana! Nandemo Shitsumonbako! Sono 8: Gou no Ritsuzou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129262" update="2011-04-11">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリアグネとマリアンヌの なぜなにシャナ! なんでも質問箱! その7 「"壊刃"サブラク」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friagne and Marianne`s Why, What, Shana! Ask Anything Question Box 7: "Destructive Blade" Sabrac</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Friagne to Marianne no Naze Nani Shana! Nandemo Shitsumonbako! Sono 7: "Kaijin" Sabrac</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129263" update="2012-06-16">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリアグネとマリアンヌの なぜなにシャナ! なんでも質問箱! その6 「ヒラルダ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friagne and Marianne`s Why, What, Shana! Ask Anything Question Box 6: Hiralda</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Friagne to Marianne no Naze Nani Shana! Nandemo Shitsumonbako! Sono 6: Hiralda</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129264" update="2011-04-11">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリアグネとマリアンヌの なぜなにシャナ! なんでも質問箱! その5 「"彩飄"フィレス」 「風の転輪」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friagne and Marianne`s Why, What, Shana! Ask Anything Question Box 5: Saihyou Pheles / Kaze no Tinrin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Friagne to Marianne no Naze Nani Shana! Nandemo Shitsumonbako! Sono 5: Saihyou Pheles / Kaze no Tinrin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129265" update="2012-06-16">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2008-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリアグネとマリアンヌの なぜなにシャナ! なんでも質問箱! その4 「銀」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friagne and Marianne`s Why, What, Shana! Ask Anything Question Box 4: Silver</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Friagne to Marianne no Naze Nani Shana! Nandemo Shitsumonbako! Sono 4: Gin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129266" update="2012-06-16">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2008-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリアグネとマリアンヌの なぜなにシャナ! なんでも質問箱! その3 「アウトロー」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friagne and Marianne`s Why, What, Shana! Ask Anything Question Box 3: Outlaw</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Friagne to Marianne no Naze Nani Shana! Nandemo Shitsumonbako! Sono 3: Outlaw</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129267" update="2011-04-11">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリアグネとマリアンヌの なぜなにシャナ! なんでも質問箱! その2 「戒禁」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friagne and Marianne`s Why, What, Shana! Ask Anything Question Box 2: Kaigin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Friagne to Marianne no Naze Nani Shana! Nandemo Shitsumonbako! Sono 2: Kaigin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129268" update="2011-04-11">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリアグネとマリアンヌの なぜなにシャナ! なんでも質問箱! その1 「メア」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friagne and Marianne`s Why, What, Shana! Ask Anything Question Box 1: Mea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Friagne to Marianne no Naze Nani Shana! Nandemo Shitsumonbako! Sono 1: Mea</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129269" update="2012-06-16">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video - Vol.5 #2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129270" update="2012-06-16">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video - Vol.5 #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129271" update="2011-04-11">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video - Vol.1 #4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129272" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video - Vol.1 #3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129273" update="2011-04-11">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video - Vol.1 #2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129274" update="2011-04-11">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video - Vol.1 #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129275" update="2011-04-11">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo Collection 4 (from Vol.5)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129276" update="2011-04-11">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo Collection 3 (from Vol.1)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129277" update="2011-04-11">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo Collection 2 (from Vol.1)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129278" update="2012-06-16">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo Collection 1 (from Vol.1)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
