<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5147" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-07-04</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kenkou Zenrakei Suieibu Umishou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Umisho High School Naked Swimming Club</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Умисё</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">전라계 수영부 우미쇼</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kenkou Zenrakei Suieibu Umisho</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kenko Zenrakei Suieibu Umisho</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">健康全裸游泳社</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Umisho</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Umishou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">KZSU</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ケンコー全裸系水泳部 ウミショー</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8266" approval="14" total="19">Softenni!</anime>
<anime id="5356" approval="2" total="5">Bamboo Blade</anime>
<anime id="13734" approval="1" total="5">Grand Blue</anime>
<anime id="11683" approval="1" total="4">Amanchu!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="705">A nice sports (swimming) anime with lots of fan-service, comedy and a little bit of ecchi romance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="264691">sometime i cant stand ecchi but this anime seems great and very hilarious. The story flow may be not totally suprising but it gave a good laugh. Two main characters are adorable. worth anime for watching</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.maql.co.jp/special/umisho/index2.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="999" type="Animation Work">Artland</name>
<name id="3172" type="Series Composition">Ikeda Mamiko</name>
<name id="2183" type="Direction">Soutome Kouichirou</name>
<name id="4538" type="Character Design">Nishino Rie</name>
<name id="4538" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishino Rie</name>
<name id="9208" type="Original Work">Hattori Mitsuru</name>
<name id="13721" type="Music">Satou Yasumasa</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr9208 [Hattori Mitsuru], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr17160 [Weekly Shounen Magazine].
Within the Kanagawa prefecture lies the seaside city of Umineko. There, http://anidb.net/ch5390 [Okiura Kaname], a second-year high school student, attends Umineko Shougyou High School (Umishou). He is also the manager of Umishou`s swim team though he himself does not know how to swim. In fact, he is afraid of the water stemming from an incident that occurred some years ago. While he was at the beach, he nearly drowned when a mermaid pulled him under water. He joined the school`s http://anidb.net/ch57857 [swimming club] in order to learn how to swim, but the club is filled with weirdos, who never taught him how to swim.
One day, a floating house arrives at the shores of Umishou bearing two new arrivals. One of these is the cheerful, sunny, happy-go-lucky girl named http://anidb.net/ch5384 [Ninagawa Amuro], a transfer student to Umishou, and the other is her http://anidb.net/ch21349 [father]. Her incredible swimming speed makes her an instant hit with the swimming club, but Kaname is surprised, since she reminds him of the mermaid he saw only once in his early childhood. After her floating house is destroyed during a storm she moves to live at Kaname`s house.
Note: The fictional island, where the series is set, is modeled on the real island of Enoshima in Fujisawa, Kanagawa.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2450">5.78</permanent>
<temporary count="2477">7.37</temporary>
<review count="3">7.27</review>
</ratings>
<picture>134033.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7802</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2602</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4009</identifier>
<identifier>daghek</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.maql.co.jp/special/umisho/index2.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kenkō_Zenrakei_Suieibu_Umishō</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ケンコー全裸系水泳部_ウミショー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1173</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327717</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9083</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1770</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/umisho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>nopan</name>
<description>The character foregoes underwear.</description>
<picurl>162753.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1155" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-28">
<name>mermaid</name>
<description>A creature that is half-human (usually the upper body) and half-fish (usually the lower body). A male mermaid is called merman (but they can appear under many different names). Since mermaids are often confused with Sirens in media, they may posses special abilities akin to Sirens such as enchanting voice (on the other hand Sirens are often being portrayed as mermaids). Some mermaids might be able to transform their whole body into human (which is not surprising since mermaids are often associated with the "want to become human" theme) and that should not disqualify them from getting this tag.</description>
<picurl>209970.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1241" parentid="2881" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-18">
<name>swimming</name>
<description>Swimming is an individual or team sport that involves using arms and legs to move the body through water. Typically, the sport takes place in pools or in open water. Competitive swimming is one of the most popular Olympic sports, with events in butterfly, backstroke, breaststroke, freestyle, and individual medley. In addition to these individual events, swimmers take part in relays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>208479.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1969" parentid="2756" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>mahjong</name>
<description>Mahjong is a tile-based game, which was developed in China during the Qing dynasty. It is commonly played by four players.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>215287.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2756" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>board games</name>
<description>People here play a board game. It can vary from chess and Go, to Monopoly, to Dungeons and Dragons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5384" type="main character in" update="2009-03-25">
<rating votes="26">8.36</rating>
<name>Ninagawa Amuro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Second year student, and a new transfer student from Okinawa at Umishou. Despite her being a dedicated and skilled swimmer, she finds difficulties in performing at competitions due to her not being used to the rules and environment of professional swimming. Among her other uncommon habits, she prefers swimming nude, and has no shame of doing so beside those she got used to, especially Kaname.</description>
<picture>21948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5385" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-25">
<rating votes="18">6.79</rating>
<name>Orizuka Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Third year student, and vice-captain of the swimming team. Just after meeting Amuro, she realises her hidden potential and recruits her to the swimming team, after challenging her to a match and being impressed with her speed in the water.</description>
<picture>21949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5386" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-25">
<rating votes="25">7.31</rating>
<name>Shizuoka Mirei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A second year. Admired by the boys, she is very self-conscious when people stare at her. Although she doesn`t like people looking at her, she likes to look at members of the opposite sex or anything that resembles them. She is a a very skilled swimmer as she almost won the Kantou Tournament in 200 meters the year before the series starts. Her grandfather is the creator of the Shizu Group.</description>
<picture>21950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5387" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-25">
<rating votes="11">2.79</rating>
<name>Ikuta Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A first year student, nicknamed Makio. Too small for her age, she is usually mistaken as a junior high student. Despite being a member of the swimming team, she is still learning how to properly swim by taking lessons from Kaname.</description>
<picture>21951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5388" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-25">
<rating votes="12">4.81</rating>
<name>Kise Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A third year student. A co-founder of Umishou`s swimming club and Orizuka`s childhood friend. Usually tends to bring trouble to those around her. She also makes up stories and lies just to tease others, and to also gain other guys attention.</description>
<picture>21952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5389" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-25">
<rating votes="17">3.71</rating>
<name>Nanako Maaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First year student. A famous swimmer and model who transfers to Umishou in order to get close to Kaname, for whom she has had a crush since childhood. She considers Amuro as a rival and competes with her for Kaname`s attention. She has a noticeable small fang and wears a swimsuit different from the rest of the team.</description>
<picture>21953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5390" type="main character in" update="2009-03-25">
<rating votes="13">5.37</rating>
<name>Okiura Kaname</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Second year student, and the swimming team`s manager. He had a traumatic experience involving a creature he describes as a mermaid during his childhood, and after which he has been afraid of swimming ever since. However this scenario started to change after Amuro`s arrival at Umishou. Always in trouble due to Amuro`s unpredictable behaviour, he usually denies his growing feelings for her.</description>
<picture>21954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="93" picture="142975.jpg">Hanamura Satomi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="303" picture="166016.jpg">Toyonaga Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5391" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-25">
<rating votes="13">2.57</rating>
<name>Ikariya Masa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Team Captain, nicknamed Ikamasa. Third year, muscle-bound, and obsessed with shaving his and other people`s body hair, and with wearing revealing Speedo bikini swim suits. He is in-fact the most annoying character of the swim team, driving most of the characters crazy from his antics. It is stated by Sanae that the only reason he is the captain is because she and Momoko needed three students to start the swim club, and just dragged him in. However, due to her tendency to make up stories this might not be true.</description>
<picture>21955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5392" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-25">
<rating votes="12">1.64</rating>
<name>Takeda Seito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21349" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-04">
<rating votes="9">6.49</rating>
<name>Ninagawa Masashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21366" type="appears in" update="2010-09-05">
<rating votes="3">2.77</rating>
<name>Domon Manabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21372" type="appears in" update="2010-09-05">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Masa no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54535.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21373" type="appears in" update="2010-09-05">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Yasu Chigusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>5033.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21374" type="appears in" update="2010-12-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Tokuda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22" picture="231891.jpg">Uoken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21422" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="2">4.06</rating>
<name>Kaname no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22109" type="appears in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="3">6.36</rating>
<name>Nanjou Karena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22111" type="appears in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="2">4.28</rating>
<name>Naruko Tomoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="69" picture="171155.jpg">Itou Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22112" type="appears in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="2">4.06</rating>
<name>Hara Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30020">Hirai Hanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22215" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Tokorozawa-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22222" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Shinmi Ran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="93" picture="142975.jpg">Hanamura Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22223" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Tobe Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A first or second year, and another, albeit less perverted" member of the swimming club. He wears large glasses and is quite intelligent. His choice of swimsuit, like Ikuta, is a speedo.</description>
<picture>56205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6126" picture="37816.jpg">Hamazoe Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22225" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Tsunumi Isao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33879" picture="93227.jpg">Sakakibara Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22260" type="appears in" update="2010-10-10">
<rating votes="2">6.67</rating>
<name>Shindou Mimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22261" type="appears in" update="2010-10-10">
<rating votes="2">6.67</rating>
<name>Shindou Mayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22262" type="appears in" update="2010-10-10">
<rating votes="2">6.67</rating>
<name>Shindou Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22263" type="appears in" update="2010-10-10">
<rating votes="2">6.67</rating>
<name>Shindou Nagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56259.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36417" type="appears in" update="2013-07-13">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Yoshizawa Yamana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60862.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2504" picture="186210.jpg">Monden Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36424" type="appears in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="3">4.61</rating>
<name>Himekawa Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1681" picture="19773.jpg">Murata Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36425" type="appears in" update="2013-07-13">
<name>Koshiba Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60865.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="93" picture="142975.jpg">Hanamura Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36426" type="appears in" update="2013-07-13">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Nakamura Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Love ramen. Freestyle event is 800M.</description>
<picture>60866.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="90" picture="16698.jpg">Ootani Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36427" type="appears in" update="2013-07-13">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Nagara Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Freestyle.</description>
<picture>60863.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="30020">Hirai Hanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36428" type="appears in" update="2013-07-13">
<name>Oyamada Asami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60864.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36429" type="appears in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Baa-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amuro`s grandmother.</description>
<picture>53013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18591" picture="188707.jpg">Fukushima Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36432" type="appears in" update="2011-09-07">
<name>Ten`in</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shop assistant.</description>
<picture>53071.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29926" picture="79152.jpg">Yamaguchi Kiyohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36474" type="appears in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Doctor Ganaha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A doctor in the infirmary at Kantou tournament.</description>
<picture>53366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29926" picture="79152.jpg">Yamaguchi Kiyohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57857" type="appears in" update="2013-07-11">
<name>Umishou Swimming Club</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The swimming club was formed 2 years before the start of the series by Orizuka Momoko, Kise Sanae, Ikariya Masa and Tokorozawa-sensei. It has a bad reputation, because of the antics of some of its members</description>
<picture>60854.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="57898" type="appears in" update="2013-07-16">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Nara Tomoyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60876.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="78554" update="2009-10-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="3">1.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79013" update="2007-07-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="18">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちゅらうみっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chura Umi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chura Umi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79653" update="2007-07-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">興味.... ある.. かも...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I... Might Be... Interested...</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Eu... posso estar... interessada</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoumi... Aru... Kamo...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80139" update="2007-07-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魅せる!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Show You!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Eu lhe mostrarei!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miseru!!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80204" update="2007-07-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見せてあげるんだから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Going to Show You</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Eu vou mostrar a vocês</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misete Agerun Dakara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80205" update="2007-07-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あたしのもほしい?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do You Want Mine, Too?</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Você quer a minha também?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atashi no mo Hoshii?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80206" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Não!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Me!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80207" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">呪い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Curse</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Maldição</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Noroi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80208" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よ~く見てなさい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take a Good Look</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Tenham boa sorte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoku Mite Nasai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80209" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忘れさせて...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Help Me Forget...</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Ajude-me a esquecer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wasuresasete...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80210" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゅうにゅう?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Breast Massage?</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Massagem nos peitos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyuunyuu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81646" update="2007-09-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まさかの...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Way...</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Será quem...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masaka no...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82743" update="2007-09-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまっおま~♪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oma Oma</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Oma-Oma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oma Oma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83071" update="2007-10-07">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人魚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mermaid</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Sereia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90465" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90466" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
