<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="518" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-02-06</startdate>
<enddate>2003-04-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gunparade March: Aratanaru Kougunka</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gunparade March - The New War Song</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">건퍼레이드 마치 -새로운 행군가-</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">新结行军歌</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GPM</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ガンパレード・マーチ -新たなる行軍歌-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gunparade March</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Gunparade March</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">גאנפארייד</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3465" type="Same Setting">Gunparade Orchestra</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1806" approval="16" total="20">Soukyuu no Fafner: Dead Aggressor</anime>
<anime id="8549" approval="16" total="20">Muv-Luv Alternative: Total Eclipse</anime>
<anime id="416" approval="12" total="19">Blue Gender</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.jcstaff.co.jp/sho-sai/gpm-shokai/gpm-index.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="1450" type="Character Design">Irie Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="4648" type="Direction">Sakurabi Katsushi</name>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="4597" type="Original Work">Sony Computer Entertainment</name>
<name id="7832" type="Chief Animation Direction">Wada Takashi</name>
</creators>
<description>During WW2 a strange new alien, the Genjuu (幻獣), appeared who`s sole purpose is to kill off Humanity. Whenever they appear the Genjuu give off a strange odor that is acid to a human and killed off a lot of the warriors sent to fight it. Flash foward 50 years. http://anidb.net/ch13887 [Hayami Atsushi] is a pilot of the 5121. The number of adults killed off in the war has forced the government to form the High School Defense force, where children of a certain age and skill are fostered in dorms to fight off the aliens. They use new mecha (HWTs) and special anti alien suits made by the Shibamura group. One day they get a new transfer student. A hot shot mecha pilot who seems to be made out of ice and is a pro at killing the Genjuu. She introduces herself as http://anidb.net/ch13888 [Shibamura Mai].
Who is this Mai? Why did she come to the 5121? Why does she hate the Genjuu so much.
Source: Forbin at MIKOMI</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1711">5.54</permanent>
<temporary count="1725">7.30</temporary>
<review count="9">6.07</review>
</ratings>
<picture>132041.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2126</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>266</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1137</identifier>
<identifier>nfnnfr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jcstaff.co.jp/sho-sai/gpm-shokai/gpm-index.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gunparade_March</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ガンパレード・マーチ_〜新たなる行軍歌〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240111</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="569" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-18">
<name>clumsy</name>
<description>A clumsy person is one lacking in coordination, and as such prone to often having accidents such as tripping, bumping into objects, or dropping things. In female characters, this is often thought of as endearing.</description>
<picurl>63355.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2461" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>domestic cat</name>
<description>The cat (Felis catus or Felis silvestris catus), also known as the domestic cat to distinguish it from other felines and felids, is a small, usually furry, domesticated, and carnivorous mammal. Cats are valued by humans for companionship and their ability to hunt vermin and household pests, and are often kept as indoor pets, in which case they are also called housecats; they have been associated with humans for at least 9,500 years and are currently the most popular pet in the world, being found almost everywhere on Earth.
Cats are similar in anatomy to the other felids, with light, strong and flexible bodies, excellent hearing, sense of smell, and near darkness eyesight, quick reflexes, sharp retractable claws, and teeth adapted to killing small prey. They are skilled predators and hunt over 1,000 species for food. Despite being solitary hunters, cats are a social species, with communication means that include pheromones, body language and a variety of vocalizations, such as meowing, purring, trilling, hissing, growling and grunting.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>41283.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2670" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>school festival - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>THIS TAG NEEDS TO BE SPLIT:
into http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=6119&amp;reltb=eptb [school culture festival]
and http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=2665&amp;reltb=eptb [school sports festival]
The obligatory school festival (or cultural fair) with cosplay cafe, haunted house, theatre performance, and food booths cannot be missing in any school setting.
For good measure there may also be an athletics or sports festival in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2802" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-14">
<name>action game</name>
<description>Any game where reflexes are the key to the gameplay, violence is optional.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13885" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-28">
<rating votes="4">6.62</rating>
<name>Mibuya Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12246" picture="41028.jpg">Sakuma Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13887" type="main character in" update="2010-01-28">
<rating votes="4">3.60</rating>
<name>Hayami Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13888" type="main character in" update="2010-01-28">
<rating votes="10">4.13</rating>
<name>Shibamura Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13890" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-28">
<rating votes="2">2.94</rating>
<name>Takigawa Youhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13892" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-28">
<rating votes="2">2.50</rating>
<name>Setoguchi Takayuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13893" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-28">
<rating votes="4">5.64</rating>
<name>Higashihara Nonomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4602" picture="26936.jpg">Yoshida Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52817" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Katou Matsuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the maintenance workers of the 5121 squad, she is a cheerful girl and cares for her team-mates.</description>
<picture>152924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52818" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="3">9.10</rating>
<name>Hara Motoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52819" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Zengyou Tadataka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2192" picture="196332.jpg">Kashii Shouto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52820" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Kurusu Ginga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52821" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Mori Seika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2205" picture="186188.jpg">Hanba Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52822" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Tanabe Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5619" picture="77767.jpg">Maeda Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52823" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Wakamiya Yasumitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52824" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Toosaka Keigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2406" picture="83146.jpg">Kuriyama Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52825" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<name>Uichita Sarasa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3128" picture="24744.jpg">Suzuki Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52826" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<name>Nakamura Mitsuhiro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2603" picture="22591.jpg">Sakurai Toshiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52827" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<name>Sakaue Hisaomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52828" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<name>Iwata Hiromu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="52829" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<name>Araigi Yumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52830" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<name>Tashiro Kaori</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="685" picture="24841.jpg">Takano Urara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52831" type="appears in" update="2013-06-08">
<name>Ishizu Moe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138033.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="52832" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<name>Yoshino Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="458" picture="171388.jpg">Inoue Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52833" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<name>Akane Daisuke</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52834" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<name>5121 Butai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>132041.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="52840" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<name>Shikon (Tanza Gata)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>10392.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="52841" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<name>Shikon (Fukuza Gata)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>10393.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="52842" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<name>Brain</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10394.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="52967" type="appears in" update="2013-02-16">
<name>Miho</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1886" picture="21014.jpg">Inokuchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52968" type="appears in" update="2013-02-16">
<name>Setoguchi no Kanojo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52969" type="appears in" update="2013-02-16">
<name>Mieko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1886" picture="21014.jpg">Inokuchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52970" type="appears in" update="2013-02-16">
<name>Kurogawa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52971" type="appears in" update="2013-02-16">
<name>Shokudou no Oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2729" picture="186723.jpg">Ishimaru Hiroya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5741" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレイバック - The Visitor -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Playback: The Visitor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Playback</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레이백: The Visitor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Playback - The Visitor -</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5855" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝手にしやがれ - Going My Way -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do Whatever You Like: Going My Way</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fais ce que tu veux</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">맘대로 해라: Going My Way</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katte ni shiyagare - Going My Way -</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6084" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サマータイムブルース - Fire Works -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summertime Blues: Fire Works</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Summertimes blues</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">섬머 타임 풀: Fire Works</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Summertime Blues - Fire Works -</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6277" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人でお茶を - Duelist -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Have Tea Together: Duelist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un thé pour deux</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">둘이서 차를: Duelist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari de Ocha o: Duelist</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6395" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">枯葉 - Thursday`s Child -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Withered Leaf: Thursday`s Child</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les feuilles mortes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">마른 잎: Thursday`s child</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kareha - Thursday`s Child -</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6461" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君去りし後 - I Guess Everything Reminds You Of Something -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After You Left: I Guess Everything Reminds You of Something</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Après ton départ</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">너를 잃은 후: I Guess Everything Reminds You Of Something</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi sarishi nochi - I Guess Everything Reminds You Of Something -</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6462" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">長い夜 - In The Forests Of Nights -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Long Night: In the Forests of Nights</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Longue nuit</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">긴 밤: In The Forests Of Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagai yoru - In The Forests Of Nights -</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6940" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四月になれば彼女は - With Your Musket, Fife, And Drum -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In April, She Will: With Your Musket, Fife and Drum</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand vient avril, elle...</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">4월이 되면 그녀는: With Your Musket, Fife, And Drum</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shigatsu ni nareba kanojo wa - With Your Musket, Fife, And Drum -</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6942" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君にこそ心ときめく - A Day In The Life -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Are the One That Makes My Heart Pound: A Day in the Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon cœur ne bat que pour toi</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">너이기에 마음이 두근거려: A Day In The Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi ni koso kokoro tokimeku - A Day In The Life -</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7180" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しみよこんにちは - Once Upon A Dime -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hello Sadness: Once Upon a Dime</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bonjour tristesse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슬픔이여 안녕: Once Upon A Dime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi yo konnichiwa - Once Upon A Dime -</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7525" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">言い出しかねて - A Good Reward For Their Labour -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Couldn`t Bring It Up: A Good Reward for Their Labour</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Impossible à dire</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">말할 수 있고: A Good Reward For Their Labour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iidashi kanete - A Good Reward For Their Labour -</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7526" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならを言う度に - Gun Parade March -</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Every Time I Say Goodbye: Gun Parade March</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À chaque fois que tu me dis au revoir...</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">잘 가를 말할 떄마다: Gun Parade March</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara o Iu Tabi ni: Gun Parade March</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62102" update="2006-09-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Opening -01- Shinjitsu no Tobira</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62103" update="2006-09-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63185" update="2006-09-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Gunparade March Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
