<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5186" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2007-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sketchbook: Full Color`s</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Sketchbook: Full Colour`s</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">素描本 ~full color`s~</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sketchbook</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スケッチブック ~full color`s~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sketchbook: Full Color`s</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2659" approval="41" total="51">Aria the Animation</anime>
<anime id="4743" approval="34" total="35">Hidamari Sketch</anime>
<anime id="5424" approval="29" total="38">Aria the Origination</anime>
<anime id="8234" approval="27" total="30">Tamayura: Hitotose</anime>
<anime id="6574" approval="21" total="24">GA: Geijutsuka Art Design Class</anime>
<anime id="8060" approval="4" total="11">Morita-san wa Mukuchi</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="104619">Is quite enjoyable, it has cute characters (especially Natsumi Aso) and the ED is very good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="224323">Peaceful &amp; catfull ^_^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="325570">Probably the best slice of life anime series out there. Must-see for anybody who claims to be a fan of the genre.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="445502">This might be my all time favorite anime series.  If you like slice of life, this is the best of the best.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="404473">sweet charming slice-of-life from the studio that made ARIA, similarily soothing, relaxing and humorous :)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.mag-garden.co.jp/sketchbook/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="122" type="Series Composition">Okada Mari</name>
<name id="2149" type="Direction">Hiraike Yoshimasa</name>
<name id="754" type="Animation Work">Hal Film Maker</name>
<name id="3672" type="Character Design">Sugimoto Isao</name>
<name id="8968" type="Original Work">Kobako Totan</name>
<name id="3672" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugimoto Isao</name>
<name id="9159" type="Music">Muramatsu Ken</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a 4-koma seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr8968 [Kobako Totan], serialised in Comic Blade.
http://anidb.net/ch4378 [Kajiwara Sora] is a shy girl who enjoys drawing in her sketchbook. She joins the Art Club at her school, and meets many colourful and eccentric people.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1255">6.78</permanent>
<temporary count="1269">7.53</temporary>
<review count="3">8.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>229235.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8031</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6251</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2942</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4050</identifier>
<identifier>zzajgr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/sketch-full/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mag-garden.co.jp/sketchbook/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sketchbook_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スケッチブック_(漫画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1231</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>328864</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9059</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1984</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/sketchbook</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10153</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3804" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-04-08">
<name>beauty in simplicity</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6184" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>autumn</name>
<description>Autumn, interchangeably known as fall in the US and Canada, is one of the four temperate seasons. Autumn marks the transition from summer into winter, in September (Northern Hemisphere) or March (Southern Hemisphere), when the arrival of night becomes noticeably earlier and the temperature cools considerably. One of its main features is the shedding of leaves from deciduous trees.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161967.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4378" type="main character in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="20">7.29</rating>
<name>Kajiwara Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A shy and quiet first year high school student. The show is narrated mostly by her thoughts and observations. She always carries her sketchbook with her.</description>
<picture>20425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4379" type="main character in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="9">6.53</rating>
<name>Asou Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is in the same grade as Sora and was the first to approach her and joined the art club with her. She likes to make and play with hand puppets with which she enacts full-on conversations. She keeps a dog named Kuro.</description>
<picture>20426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="163" picture="25711.jpg">Nakase Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4380" type="main character in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="8">5.87</rating>
<name>Torikai Hazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl with short blond hair who is best friends with Natsumi. She joined the art club just after Sora and Natsumi. She is always on the look out for a bargain and does not like to waste money.</description>
<picture>20427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4381" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="4">4.58</rating>
<name>Kasugano Hiyori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The teacher of the art club and has a distinctive fable for chickens. She also keeps a pet chicken named P-chan that she brings to school with her and often resides on her head. She is pretty childish.</description>
<picture>20428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4382" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="4">7.20</rating>
<name>Kuga Kokage</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the art club that radiates a rather introverted and dark mood. She is a bit short and sports a black ponytail. She likes to add a cartoon representation of her head to her artwork.</description>
<picture>20429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4383" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="5">8.59</rating>
<name>Kurihara Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A short girl in her second year with a preference for insects and nature in general. She is rather knowledgeable about these subjects as well.</description>
<picture>20430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4384" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="5">5.30</rating>
<name>Sasaki Juju</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tall (in comparison to the other female students) member of the art club. She likes to play the guitar and is friends with Nagisa who is in the same class as her.</description>
<picture>20432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="77" picture="30668.jpg">Oumi Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4385" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="2">3.87</rating>
<name>Kamiya Asaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A short girl with a ponytail and an upbeat personality. Likes to pull pranks, especially on Negishi.</description>
<picture>20431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4386" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="2">4.76</rating>
<name>Negishi Daichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A second-year with an anger management problem. However, he is normally friendly and never gets violent.</description>
<picture>20433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4387" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="7">7.57</rating>
<name>Tanabe Ryou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of two members of the art club who practically never leave each other`s side but rarely show up to club activities. They are usually an outlet for weird or unrelated side gags.</description>
<picture>20434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4388" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="6">7.80</rating>
<name>Himuro Fuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of two members of the art club who practically never leave each other`s side but rarely show up to club activities. They are usually an outlet for weird or unrelated side gags.</description>
<picture>20435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4389" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="17">8.42</rating>
<name>Kate</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blond student from Canada. She transfers to the school in the second semester. She is a bit naive often mixes up kanji or uses them inappropriately (for example for foreign words) and on top of that gets taught some false concepts by http://anidb.net/ch4388 [Himuro] and http://anidb.net/ch4387 [Tanabe].</description>
<picture>20436.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4390" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="2">7.08</rating>
<name>Sugyou Ujou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tall male third-year and the president of the art club. He generally acts as the straight man of the club.</description>
<picture>20437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1630" picture="1887.gif">Tasaka Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4391" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="3">6.58</rating>
<name>Ooba Tsukiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A second-year and rarely seen member of the art club, at least in the anime.</description>
<picture>20438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4392" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="2">6.11</rating>
<name>Kajiwara Ao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sora`s younger brother. He is caring and constantly looks out for his rather spacey sister.</description>
<picture>20439.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4393" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="2">6.29</rating>
<name>Mike</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the more dominant stray cats from the neighborhood who becomes the main character in episode five of the anime. She is modeled after the cat of the original artist. She has white fur with large light and dark brown patches.</description>
<picture>20440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4394" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="8">7.78</rating>
<name>Haa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A stray cat with grey and white fur and thick dark grey stripes. She is more or less Mike`s sidekick. She speaks cat-English, and translates for Mike who can only speak cat-Japanese.</description>
<picture>20441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4395" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="2">5.21</rating>
<name>Gure</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A stray turned house-cat with white and grey fur and thin grey stripes and his back and cheeks.</description>
<picture>20442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4396" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="3">6.20</rating>
<name>Kuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cat with a big face and light brown fur. In the cat episodes he speaks in a very old-fashioned way and has a respect-demanding personality. He gets taken in by Asaka.</description>
<picture>20443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4397" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="3">7.40</rating>
<name>Buchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A grey and white Persian cat that belongs to Kate. He wears a red collar with a bell on it and only speaks cat-English, making Haa the only other cat who can understand him.</description>
<picture>20444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1440" picture="23205.jpg">Saiki Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7787" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-12-26">
<rating votes="176">3.89</rating>
<name>Aria Pokoteng</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>President Aria is the Aria Company`s mascot, a male Aqua breed feline (common traits include larger size compared to Earth breeds, and human-level intelligence). He is smart enough to understand human speech. He was an alley cat before taken in by Grandma 20 years ago, and has been the company`s mascot ever since.</description>
<picture>26811.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="74438" type="appears in" update="2015-04-14">
<rating votes="3">7.21</rating>
<name>Negishi Minamo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daichi`s little sister who always carries a camera with her. She`s in her first year of middle school but often gets mistaken for a grade schooler. She`s usually always cheerful, but has a curious habit of speaking in a very direct and spontaneous manner, not pulling any verbal punches.
She eventually joins Sora`s group of friends after they meet again while Sora is on a small drawing trip in the neighborhood, which culminates in Sora borrowing Minamo`s camera for a short while for sketching purposes, and then later draws a sketch of the then-sleeping Minamo. (With 30% cuteness added, at least according to Minamo herself.)
Source: Myanimelist.net</description>
<picture>171872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="82765" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スケッチブックの少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl with the Sketchbook</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sketchbook no Shoujo</title>
<summary>No matter where she goes, Sora takes her sketchbook along. The world is full of beautiful things, and Sora doesn`t want to miss a single one. However, Sora is incredibly shy. She only has a few friends, but each one adds a new color to her world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713501</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82766" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつもの風景</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Scenery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsumo no Fuukei</title>
<summary>Today, Sora decides to leave the house starting with her left foot instead of her right. She`s about to learn that little choices can lead to big changes! Meanwhile, Miss Kasugano has a new Secret Weapon, and it should be arriving any minute now...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713503</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82767" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青の心配</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ao`s Concern</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ao no Shinpai</title>
<summary>It`s the day of the Town Festival, which means music and fireworks! Sora will be going with her friends, and so will her brother Ao. But Ao knows how strange his sister is. He can`t help but wonder... Is she always like that, even around other people?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713505</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82994" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三人だけのスケッチ大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Three-Person Sketching Event</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sannin dake no Sketch Taikai</title>
<summary>This was supposed to be the day of the big Art Club Sketching Event, until the forecast called for rain. But two students still showed up: Nagisa, the girl who`s obsessed with nature; and Sora, who never misses a chance to sketch something new.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713507</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84274" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねこねこの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cat Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nekoneko no Hi</title>
<summary>Have you ever wondered what it`s like to be a cat? This episode follows the everyday adventures of Mike, Ha-san, Kuma and Grey, four cats who just want the basic necessities of life: unspoiled food, fancy collars, and respect from the humans who feed them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713509</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84275" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の想ひ出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Omoide</title>
<summary>Miss Kasugano has made up her mind. The Art Club is going on an overnight trip! There`s just one problem: they don`t have any money. So at the end of summer, she loads the entire class up on a bus, and they take a field trip to... their own school?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713511</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85060" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">9月の日に...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Day in September</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kugatsu no Hi ni...</title>
<summary>There`s a new girl in class! Her name is Kate, and she`s from Canada. Natsumi is chosen to teach her all about Japanese language and culture – but she has her work cut out for her, since the other students start telling Kate all sorts of bizarre fibs.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713513</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85061" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラジカセと少女の二本立て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Radio-Cassette Player and Young Girl Double Feature</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Radicasse to Shoujo no Nihondate</title>
<summary>It`s two stories in one! First, Hazuki`s radio-cassette player is broken. Can the crazy comedy duo Ryo and Fu help? Then, while out on a Sunday walk, Sora runs into a young girl with a camera. For some reason, the girl follows wherever Sora goes...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713515</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85429" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナニかの為に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For the Sake of Something</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanika no Tame ni</title>
<summary>Tests are fast approaching, and everyone`s studying hard in their own way. Sora, Natsumi, Hazuki and Kate are curious: what`s the most efficient way to study? So together, they set off to ask the Art Club upperclassmen for some secret study techniques.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713517</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85430" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出会いの先</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Lies Ahead</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deai no Saki</title>
<summary>The Art Club is holding their Fall Sketching Event... but as usual, Miss Kasugano has no money, so they end up in the school`s backyard. Some students are disappointed, some are enthusiastic, and some end up being chased around by a stray dog...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713519</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85431" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風邪の日と, ねこねこpart3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sick Day and Cat Day Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze no Hi to, Nekoneko Part 3</title>
<summary>Sora has to stay home with a cold, and she misses being with everyone at school. But just as she`s thinking of her friends, her friends are thinking of her, too... Also, Mike and the rest of the cats are desperate to find a way to speak with humans!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713521</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85432" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スケッチブックの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sketchbook Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sketchbook no Hi</title>
<summary>Sora and her friends take a day trip into the big city! The first stop is, of course, the art store. There, they meet a friendly guy who wants to buy a present for his sister, but doesn`t know what to get. Never fear, Kate`s ready to come to his rescue!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713523</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86290" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとりぼっちの美術部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lonely Art Club</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitoribocchi no Bijutsubu</title>
<summary>After a lively afternoon picnic surrounded by cherry trees in full bloom, Sora finds herself alone in an empty Art Club room. But even though no one is with her, she doesn`t feel lonely. Taking brush in hand, Sora finally paints what`s in her heart.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713525</identifier>
<identifier>sketchbook-full-colors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="98381" update="2009-03-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">さあ♪旅のおともにスケッチブック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come, Sketchbook, My Trip Companion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saa Tabi no Otomo ni Sketchbook</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98382" update="2009-03-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">よっ!水着とカニとスケッチブック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yo! Swimsuits and Crab and Sketchbook</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yo! Mizugi to Kani to Sketchbook</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98383" update="2009-03-29">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">よし!みんなで作ろう旅館の晩御飯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Allright! Let`s Make Dinner Together at the Inn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoshi! Minna de Tsukurou Ryokan no Bangohan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98384" update="2009-03-29">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">はぁ~♪みんなそろって, いい湯だな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haa~ Everyone Gather Up, a Wonderful Bath</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haaa Minna Sorotte, Ii Yu Da na</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98385" update="2009-03-29">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひそひそ. 乙女たちの夜はふけて......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whispering. As the Maidens` Night Wears On</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hisohiso. Otome-tachi no Yoru wa Fukete......</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98386" update="2009-03-29">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">あぁ... 海辺のスケッチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ahh... Seashore Sketch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aa... Umibe no Sketch</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124617" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124618" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124619" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124620" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124621" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124622" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124623" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124624" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124625" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124626" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124627" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124628" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124629" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124630" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C26</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2007-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124631" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C25</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124632" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C24</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124633" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C23</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124634" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C22</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124635" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124636" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124637" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124638" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124639" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C17</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124640" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124641" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124642" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124643" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124644" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124645" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124646" update="2010-10-26">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Tanpopo Suisha - Instrumental Version</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
