<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="52" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>2001-04-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Love Hina Haru Special: Kimi Sakura Chiru Nakare!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Love Hina Spring Special: Don`t Let the Blooming Blossoms Wither and Fall!</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Love Hina: especial de primavera</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Любовь и Хина - весенний спецвыпуск</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">С любовью, Хина - весенний спецвыпуск</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">lhss</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">lhs</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ラブひな春スペシャル ~キミサクラチルナカレ!!~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Love Hina Spring Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Love Hina: Spring Special</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Love Hina Spécial - Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Love Hina - Spring Special</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="49" type="Sequel">Love Hina Again</anime>
<anime id="51" type="Prequel">Love Hina Christmas Special: Silent Eve</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="368" approval="3" total="10">Ranma 1/2: Kessen Tougenkyou! Hanayome o Torimodose!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="167701">Maybe not as good as the previous, but again you must see this before watching love hina again.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/lovehina/</url>
<creators>
<name id="860" type="Original Work">Akamatsu Ken</name>
<name id="3333" type="Character Design">Uno Makoto</name>
<name id="1797" type="Direction">Iwasaki Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="6448" type="Music">Iwamoto Masaki</name>
<name id="7254" type="Music">Korenaga Kouichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr860 [Akamatsu Ken], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr17160 [Weekly Shounen Magazine].
The Toudai entrance exams have finally come (again) for http://anidb.net/ch4665 [Keitarou]. With all his confidence he takes the test, but ends up falling asleep and dreaming about http://anidb.net/ch42 [Narusegawa]. Waking up with barely any time to complete the test, Keitarou thinks he will fail and tries to escape from Hinata Inn and forget all the memories with it. By a stroke of luck he meets http://anidb.net/ch4674 [Seta], but ends up on a faraway island with the whole cast looking for him.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5206">5.81</permanent>
<temporary count="5242">7.46</temporary>
<review count="3">3.22</review>
</ratings>
<picture>20842.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>866</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>192</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>244</identifier>
<identifier>dmaays</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/lovehina/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234309</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4560</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="42" type="main character in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="250">7.10</rating>
<name>Narusegawa Naru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Narusegawa Naru bears an extremely fiery temper and a tendency to inflict violent physical punishment (mostly on Keitarou). This 17-year old student and resident of Hinata Inn is described as "one fuse short of a cannon". She is very intelligent, having placed top in the nation on the college practice entrance exams at their cram school. Of all the girls in the Hinata Inn, she is victimized the most by Keitarou`s clumsiness, which often results in her being naked, exposed in some fashion, or lying in very suggestive positions. Eventually, she develops very strong feelings for him, though has great difficulty in admitting these feelings to herself and Keitarou. Like Keitarou, she strives to get into Tokyo University because of a promise she had made to someone.</description>
<picture>20833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4665" type="main character in" update="2019-10-11">
<rating votes="151">4.05</rating>
<name>Urashima Keitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cram school student, and second-year ronin studying to enter Tokyo University (or "Toudai" for short). When Keitarou was a child, he made a promise with a girl based on a story that two people who love each other will live "happily ever after" if they enter Tokyo University. After being kicked out of home for failing to pass the entrance exams on his second attempt, he travels to "Hinata Inn", a Hotel owned by his Grandmother in order to find a place to stay and study. After a misunderstanding, Keitarou discovers the Hotel is now a Girls only Dorm. Keitarou`s Aunt Haruka mistakenly assumes he has already passed the entrance exams and is already studying at Tokyo University, and the residents agree he can stay. When he fails to correct her and is discovered to be lying, he is forced to leave until Haruka announces the Inn now belongs to Keitarou and he is the new landlord.</description>
<picture>239544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4666" type="main character in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="136">6.63</rating>
<name>Maehara Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 13-year old schoolgirl who, after a bad start in which Keitarou, develops a crush on him. Shinobu is a boarder at the Hinata Inn, in room 201. She is quite skilled in both cooking and household chores as she become the cook (Her family once owned a restaurant in town prior to their divorce). Quiet and shy, she is overly caring of other`s feelings and this contributes to her own emotional frailty.</description>
<picture>30421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="634" picture="18161.jpg">Kurata Masayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4667" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="160">7.05</rating>
<name>Aoyama Motoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 15-year old school girl who is extremely serious, athletic, and into kendo. Motoko is also a boarder at the Hinata Inn, in room 302.
She has difficulty dealing with other people, especially males; she finds men to be a distraction that keep her from being able to concentrate fully on her studies and kendo practice. She also dislikes men because her sister left the dojo to marry. Her relationship with Keitarou initially resembles Naru`s relationship with him; he all too often finds himself on the receiving end of various attacks as a result of his frequent mishaps. She eventually mellows out as she becomes used to him and eventually finds herself developing feelings for him, along with a habit of writing trashy romance tales involving the two of them.</description>
<picture>30417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4668" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="140">3.96</rating>
<name>Kaolla Su</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 14-year old foreign transfer student. She is also a boarder at the Hinata Inn, in room 301.
She is from the fictional kingdom of Molmol, supposedly located near the International Date Line, and is the princess of said country. The dot on her forehead seems to have something to do with the 3-eyed symbol of Molmol, though it resembles (indeed, is almost identical to) a bindi dot. She is often dressed in nothing else except her heavily altered school uniform in almost every episode, or some otherwise scant costume. To top her personality, she is above all extremely hyperactive, usually hugging (or, in Keitarou`s case, kicking) someone, trying to eat something, especially bananas and/or Tama-chan, or inventing some potentially dangerous new device.</description>
<picture>30418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1436" picture="18822.jpg">Takagi Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4669" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="140">5.30</rating>
<name>Konno Mitsune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also known as Kitsune, meaning "fox" in Japanese, she is a 19-year old freelance writer (who never seems to write anything). She is frequently drunk and seems to enjoy teasing Keitarou at every opportunity. Kitsune is also a boarder at the Hinata Inn, in room 205. Her nickname is `Kit Fox`
Her nickname comes from a combination of her first and last names, and the fact that she hardly ever fully opens both eyes at the same time (mostly when she is surprised). As a result, she has a perpetually fox-like, vulpine expression. She`s a practical joker and troublemaker; her mission in life seems to be to ensure that things never get too dull or those around her too complacent.</description>
<picture>30420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4670" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-11">
<rating votes="56">6.00</rating>
<name>Urashima Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only child of Urashima Hinata`s eldest daughter, Urashima Yoko; her second daughter was Keitarou`s mother. After the death of Yoko, Hinata adopted her granddaughter. Therefore, Haruka is Keitarou`s legal aunt in addition to being his actual cousin. It was as a teenager that, while working at the inn, she was first called "Aunty Haruka" by her baby cousin Keitarou - the same time that Keitarou first met both Mutsumi and Naru.</description>
<picture>239543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4671" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="121">6.95</rating>
<name>Otohime Mutsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very gentle, very frail, anaemic, clumsy, and softly-spoken 20 year old girl. Despite her poor physical health, she is very resilient and is able to quickly recover from any injury, much like Keitarou. She has a very sweet and generous personality, often sacrificing her own happiness for others. She lives on or near the island of Okinawa and has an affinity for watermelons and turtles. She met Keitarou and Naru while taking some time off for a brief vacation after flunking her entrance exam to Toudai for the third time in a row, just like Keitarou.</description>
<picture>30419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19182" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4672" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-11">
<rating votes="57">3.90</rating>
<name>Sarah McDougall</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 9-year-old American from California and Seta`s adopted daughter. She initially delights in making Keitarou`s life miserable, however, like most of the girls in the story, she eventually warms to him, even if she still calls him a dork.</description>
<picture>239541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4674" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-11">
<rating votes="36">4.59</rating>
<name>Seta Noriyasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Tokyo University graduate and professor who specialises in archaeology, appearing to be a parody of Indiana Jones. Like Keitarou, he was a third-year ronin. He`s clumsy - especially with women, a terrible driver (his arrival often heralded by his van crashing down from the sky), and an exceptionally skilled martial artist, all partly due to his complete lack of self-preservation. Seta spends a good deal of his time travelling the world on one expedition or another. His goal seems to be to find evidence of the ancient turtle civilization that once flourished throughout east Asia.</description>
<picture>239542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4743" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-07-22">
<rating votes="14">4.89</rating>
<name>Akamatsu-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/cr860 [Akamatsu Ken], the Love Hina manga author, makes a few appearences in the Love Hina anime.
http://anidb.net/a35 [Love Hina 14:]
When the Hinata-sou runs out of money everybody has to help earning money and Keitarou ends up as an assistant for a famous mangaka, where it is discovered that the sensei is living in a villa while his assistants are working like slaves.
http://anidb.net/a51 [Love Hina Christmas Special:]
When Shinobu and Kitsune are in in dire need of money to buy train tickets they meet Akamatsu and end up selling doujinshi at the Comiket for him in exchange for money. What would their reaction be if they knew the content.
http://anidb.net/a52 [Love Hina Spring Special:]
Just as Akamatsu-sensei is rejoicing the fact that the series finally ended and is about to go on a trip around the world on his personal luxury liner (which he bought from the money he made from series` sales), the Hinata-sou crew hijacks the ship to set out on their search for Keitarou. But not before making him apologise for giving everybody that much text during the series.</description>
<picture>20869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="860" picture="20873.jpg">Akamatsu Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10157" type="appears in" update="2011-11-23">
<rating votes="13">2.92</rating>
<name>Haitani Masayuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haitani Masayuki is one of Keitaro`s childhood friends, and is (apart from a few physical differences) almost exactly like Shirai. He is taller and enters a university before Shirai or Keitaro.</description>
<picture>77487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10158" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-02">
<rating votes="18">2.57</rating>
<name>Narusegawa Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mei-chan is Naru`s younger sister. Naru describes her as her "half-sister" in manga volumes 11 and 14. On the other hand, in the anime, episode 22, Mei said "My father married her mother." This leads some to speculate that they are step-sisters, although this is never confirmed. She initially tries to get Keitaro and Mutsumi together in the hopes that Naru would return home if Keitaro were taken. She gives up on this when she and Naru clear up a few family misconceptions. Also, in Love Hina Again, she makes a very brief appearance to help all the Hinata residents about Keitaro and Naru`s relationship &amp; help speed it up. She also appears in the last volume of the manga, seen standing off on the side with the rest of the residence of Hinata Inn while Naru is chasing Keitaro down after accidentally undressing her. She also plays a minor role in the Spring Movie.</description>
<picture>30510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13453" type="appears in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="5">3.57</rating>
<name>Shirai Kimiaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirai Kimiaki is one of Keitarou`s friends. He loves to make fun of Keitarou, calling him a failure in girls and academics, but pulls back later on when Keitarou becomes more successful. He almost always appears with Haitani. His main interests are in women, and one of his only upside is some degree of skill in computers. He also seems to have an interest in older woman like Haruka. He is short, and is almost always shown with big round glasses.</description>
<picture>40925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11020" picture="39571.jpg">Miyashita Michio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13454" type="appears in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="8">5.53</rating>
<name>Ichikawa Emi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Motoko`s kouhai at school, she is also her fan and one of the few people who Motoko frequently spends time with.</description>
<picture>40922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11021">Hokimoto Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13455" type="appears in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="7">4.90</rating>
<name>Onoe Kikuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Motoko`s kouhai at school, she is also her fan and one of the few people who Motoko frequently spends time with.</description>
<picture>40924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="94" picture="170799.jpg">Akita Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13456" type="appears in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="10">5.64</rating>
<name>Matsumoto Sachiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Motoko`s kouhai at school, she is also her fan and one of the few people who Motoko frequently spends time with.</description>
<picture>40923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2896" picture="23231.jpg">Maeda Yukie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13457" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="31">5.70</rating>
<name>Onsen Tamago</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nicknamed Tama, he is the turtle given to Keitarou by Mutsumi. Keitarou points out that the turtle is male, but the girls are convinced he is a `she` and so `he` is referred to as `she` throughout the manga. She is an `onsen kame` or hot-springs turtle, and like others of her species, it appears that she can fly. Su, Mutsumi, Seta, and (later in the series) Keitarou appear to have the ability to speak with Tama-chan, and Su occasionally develops the urge to eat her, though sometimes it is just to tease Shinobu (in the manga, it is said on a side note that Su drops this habit in order to wait for Tama-chan to reproduce). She appears in Negima on Chizuru Naba`s apron on the back cover of volume 8, in chapter 85 of volume 10, and in other places as pictures.</description>
<picture>39574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2896" picture="23231.jpg">Maeda Yukie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27930" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="7">5.93</rating>
<name>Nyamo Naamo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nyamo is a resident of the island Pararakelse, where Keitarou finds himself after he runs off because he thought he`d failed the entrance exam. She is working with Seta because Seta knew her grandfather and she wants to continue his work now that he is dead.
Nyamo is physically almost identical to Shinobu - except having darker skin and longer hair - and shares a number of other traits with her as well, including her extreme initial shyness and reluctance to speak. Nyamo and Shinobu quickly become good friends and correspond when apart. In the manga, she`s last seen attending Keitarou`s wedding. Also in the manga, when she visits the Hinata Dorms, she brings with her a pet giant tortoise named Gidget.</description>
<picture>64623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38928" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-21">
<rating votes="1">1.40</rating>
<name>Sakata Kentarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakata Kentarou is an anime-only character who has a crush on Naru.</description>
<picture>77429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38963" type="appears in" update="2011-11-22">
<rating votes="8">6.44</rating>
<name>Akiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taichi Akiko is Shinobu`s classmate.</description>
<picture>77483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19182" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="311" update="2006-01-31">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2001-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120883" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
