<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5210" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-10-10</startdate>
<enddate>2007-12-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Genshiken 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Genshiken TV 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">genshiken2</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Ґеншікен 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">现视研2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">げんしけん2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Genshiken 2: The Society for the Study of Modern Visual Culture</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9934" type="Sequel">Genshiken Nidaime no Roku</anime>
<anime id="4782" type="Prequel">Genshiken (2006)</anime>
<anime id="4513" type="Other">Kujibiki Unbalance (2006)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="443930">A must to see for all Reallife, comedy lovers.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="83424">More of the same from Genshiken. If you liked the first season, 2 is an able successor, although it does seem to play it a little safer with character development and backs off the "Otaku only" jokes. Worth seeing in any case.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="319095">Waiting for another season...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="55">Just as great as the first season!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="71853">It`s good but I`m still a little disappointed they skipped the most interesting arc from the manga.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="301144">Must see. Laugh all the way to the bank.&lt;br /&gt;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="208034">While it can get more serious that the previous installments, it`s still just as entertaining</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="361783">Everything just begins here. Definitely must see if you enjoyed 1st season.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.genshiken.info/</url>
<creators>
<name id="771" type="Work">Arms</name>
<name id="974" type="Original Work">Kio Shimoku</name>
<name id="4233" type="Character Design">Yanagida Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="3465" type="Series Composition">Yokote Michiko</name>
<name id="708" type="Direction">Yoshimoto Kinji</name>
<name id="4233" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yanagida Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="3068" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishibashi Yukiko</name>
<name id="3066" type="Chief Animation Direction">Noguchi Takayuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the same-named seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr974 [Kio Shimoku], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr31447 [Afternoon].
Genshiken is accepted as a participant in the upcoming ComiFes, and http://anidb.net/ch2519 [Sasahara] must adjust to his new role as club president. Meanwhile, http://anidb.net/ch7448 [Ogiue] continues her struggle to fit into this unconventional club.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4310">7.71</permanent>
<temporary count="4341">8.04</temporary>
<review count="2">8.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>12702.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7985</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7882</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2508</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4047</identifier>
<identifier>vtuaai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.genshiken.info/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Genshiken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>げんしけん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1218</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>328705</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/genshiken2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3610" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-12-19">
<name>game references</name>
<description>Be it the sound of a 1-up being grabbed, three golden triangles appearing on someones shirt or a blatant parody portraying a monkey throwing barrels down a poorly constructed facility, this anime contains characteristics dedicated to the remembrance/worship of an actual video game.</description>
<picurl>166123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4207" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>doujin</name>
<description>Doujin is a general Japanese term for a group of people or friends who share an interest, activity, hobbies, or achievement. The word is sometimes translated into English as clique, coterie, society, or circle (e.g., a "sewing circle").
In Japan the term is used to refer to amateur self-published works, including but not limited to manga, novels, fan guides, art collections, music and video games. Some professional artists participate as a way to publish material outside the regular publishing industry.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>68439.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2519" type="main character in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="89">4.89</rating>
<name>Sasahara Kanji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The wishy-washy Sasahara Kanji is a freshman at Suioh University. He joins the Genshiken after a little persuasion from Kousaka Makoto and quickly engulfs himself in the otaku universe</description>
<picture>17825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="610" picture="18093.jpg">Ooyama Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2520" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="88">4.38</rating>
<name>Kousaka Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Makoto is an all-out otaku who joined Genshiken at the same time as Sasahara. He is a happy-go-lucky type who is mostly oblivious to the world around him.
Kousaka and his childhood friend Kasukabe both enroll at the university at the same time and become lovers shortly after the start of the story.</description>
<picture>17826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2521" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="165">8.29</rating>
<name>Madarame Harunobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madarame often tries to play the role of a tough, military otaku but never quite manages to pull it off. Kasukabe often pick on him because of this.
When the original president resigns, Madarame takes over and thus become the second president in the history of Genshiken.</description>
<picture>17827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2522" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="58">5.70</rating>
<name>Tanaka Souichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tanaka is a master of cosplay. He can create any outfit in a week, often in less time if necessary but he never cosplays himself. At conventions he uses the alias Fukurou.
Later in the anime he starts going out with Kanaka Oono</description>
<picture>17828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2523" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="57">3.45</rating>
<name>Kugayama Mitsunori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kugayama is a stuttering, taciturn person. Initially he is the only person in Genshiken who can draw reasonably well but he usually never do more than rough sketches.</description>
<picture>17829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6405" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="13">3.72</rating>
<name>Enomoto Chihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very good natured person who is nicknamed "Happy Fortune" by his friend Mugio. His parents died when he was 10 years old, and since that time he has been living with his seemingly irresponsible older sister. Having fended for himself for quite some time, he is very good with cooking and cleaning. His role in the group is that of the secretary.</description>
<picture>23773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2438" picture="156420.jpg">Takimoto Fujiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6407" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="33">8.69</rating>
<name>Ritsuko Kubel Kettenkrad</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A half-German girl, Ritsuko is the current President of the Student Council, and a childhood friend of Chihiro. Despite their childhood promise (revealed in the anime as a promise that he will marry her if she stops "being a crybaby") and her obvious feelings for him, she works hard to hide these from him throughout the series. She wears a helmet which seems to be a mark of the office she holds. It seems she used to cry a lot, and has been working hard to stop her tears in an attempt to perhaps live up to a promise she made to Chihiro.</description>
<picture>23775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6408" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="14">4.47</rating>
<name>Kamishakujii Renko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A highly-strung, overachieving girl who considers Tokino her arch-enemy. Renko`s history with Tokino goes back to their days in kindergarten: it is revealed that Tokino once took so long in the bathroom that Renko, unable to wait any longer, wet herself. Ever since that time, Renko has made it her personal mission to somehow embarrass and humiliate Tokino in return. Renko has the unusual ability to read an entire book in under a minute—but unfortunately, she can only remember the information she has read for three minutes afterward.</description>
<picture>23776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3133" picture="25830.jpg">Nishihara Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6410" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="17">6.23</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Vice-President and possibly Secretary of the current Student Council. Like Izumi, Kasumi comes from a yakuza family, and lost her parents as a child. She always carries a sword. She is cold and reserved, a ferocious fighter, and she seems to have only allowed one person—Ritsuko—to be truly close to her. She also has a habit of speaking her mind, which at time frightens Risa.</description>
<picture>23778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6412" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="15">5.95</rating>
<name>Yamada Kaoruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Renko`s team, clearly in awe of and devoted to Renko. Her primary job seems to be trying to keep "Renko-sama" calm, but she does not succeed all that often.</description>
<picture>23780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6443" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="792">8.94</rating>
<name>Itoshiki Nozomu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23897.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7108" type="main character in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="200">6.62</rating>
<name>Oono Kanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>American high school, joining the Genshiken at the beginning of the Fall term. Normally soft-spoken and easily embarrassed, Ohno is surprisingly upfront when it comes to one of her two main passions: cosplay. With a nice figure and large bosom, Ohno and her cosplaying (using costumes sewn personally by Tanaka, whom she begins dating) quickly become Genshiken`s main attraction at student fairs. Ohno`s other main passion is yaoi involving muscular, middle-aged, exceedingly bald men. One of the reasons Ohno joins Genshiken in the first place is because only they would accept her fetish. She is also close to Saki, as Saki was the first one to find out about Ohno`s preference for older men.</description>
<picture>138881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7109" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="50">8.25</rating>
<name>Gendai Shikaku Bunka Kenkyuukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>29215.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7448" type="main character in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="144">7.61</rating>
<name>Ogiue Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fifth president of Genshiken and former member of the Manga Society, Ogiue is a girl who seemingly hates otaku, particularly female ones, but is arguably more perverse of a yaoi fan than Ohno. Ogiue`s tastes in yaoi stem from a preference for shounen series, and like Kugayama she is an amateur artist. Despite her harsh attitude, Ogiue is actually easily coerced into doing things to which she initially objects. Ogiue has a tendency to fantasize about and then draw highly sexual homosexual encounters between the men she knows in real life, particularly Sasahara and Madarame. Ogiue has terrible eyesight, normally wears contacts, and speaks a Tohoku dialect when not speaking Japanese formally. Her most distinctive feature is her paintbrush-like hairstyle, and her last resort when losing an argument is to try and jump out of a nearby window.</description>
<picture>26047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9990" type="main character in" update="2010-06-24">
<rating votes="147">5.84</rating>
<name>Kasukabe Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka`s girlfriend. Fashionable, violent, confident, occasionally smokes, and not at all attracted by the sexual charms of cartoon characters, Saki is not an otaku in any sense of the word. She follows Kousaka into Genshiken, and is eventually blackmailed by the first Genshiken chairman into joining the club. Surprisingly, Saki actually saves Genshiken from being shut down on two separate occasions, though her motives have more to do with revenge and guilt than becoming more of an otaku.
Despite being vehemently against otaku activities such as wearing nekomimi (cat-ears) at the start of the series, Saki eventually becomes comfortable with the other club members to the point that she can be considered their close friend (aside from the possible exception of Kuchiki). Saki has a tendency to use nicknames. She calls Sasahara "Sasayan", Kugayama "Kugapii", and Ogiue "Ogichin" by nicknames, and even though she at first refuses to call Kuchiki by his self-appointed nickname ("Kucchi"), Saki starts using that nickname as well.</description>
<picture>30145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33096" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-06">
<rating votes="38">3.02</rating>
<name>Kuchiki Manabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>6347.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48504" type="appears in" update="2012-09-05">
<rating votes="11">5.53</rating>
<name>Susanna Hopkins</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ohno`s American friend.</description>
<picture>93561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48505" type="appears in" update="2012-09-05">
<rating votes="5">5.68</rating>
<name>Angela Burton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ohno`s American friend.</description>
<picture>93562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56482" type="appears in" update="2013-08-18">
<rating votes="4">3.66</rating>
<name>Asada Naoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56483" type="appears in" update="2014-10-05">
<rating votes="5">2.83</rating>
<name>Yabusaki Kumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the girls in the Manga Society at the time Ogiue attempted to join, she seems to harbor strong feelings of resentment towards Ogiue. Criticizing Ogiue for slipping into her Tohoku dialect when she doesn`t speak formally, Yabusaki herself speaks in a highly pronounced Kansai dialect, which she says scares those from Kantou. When Ogiue is rejected as a vendor for the next ComiFes, Yabusaki (grudgingly) invites her to become a guest artist in her own circle`s doujinshi. Though she appears only towards the end of the manga, she shows up much earlier in the anime, in episode 3 of season 2.</description>
<picture>153078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1436" picture="18822.jpg">Takagi Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59009" type="appears in" update="2013-08-18">
<name>Nakajima Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59010" type="appears in" update="2013-08-18">
<name>Shigeta Mina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60305" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Haraguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60306" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<name>Takayanagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="438" picture="25479.jpg">Yanagisawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60308" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Kitagawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60328" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<name>Saibouzu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60329" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<name>Menma</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="38719" picture="55185.jpg">Kitahara Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60331" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<name>Ihato Kouji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60332" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<name>Katou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katou is a mysterious girl in the manga society, who always wears her hair over her face. At some point, she takes an interest in becoming friends with Ogiue, and sets out to do just that in spite of her fellow members` dislike of the girl. In reality, she is quite good looking, but few seem to know this because of the way she conceals her features.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="218" picture="17036.jpg">Nakao Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60333" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<name>Onodera Ryuuji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60334" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<name>Kaoru</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4741" picture="45560.jpg">Konno Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60337" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<name>Kazamatsuri Neko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="82570" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="17">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新会長のココロザシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Chairman`s Ambition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Kaichou no Kokorozashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83008" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">会議はモメル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Discord at the Meeting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaigi wa Momeru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83009" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アツい夏の一日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Hot Summer`s Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atsui Natsu no Ichinichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83010" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デキテンデスカ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Are You an Item?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dekiten Desuka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83011" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マダラメ総ウケ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Madarame: Total Uke</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madarame Sou Uke</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83012" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">趣味のモンダイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Question of Tastes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shumi no Mondai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83013" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒業症候群</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduation Syndrome</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sotsugyou Shoukougun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83014" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こすけん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cos-ken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kosu-ken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83015" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シューカツはいつも雨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Always Rains on the Job Hunt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuukatsu wa Itsumo Ame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83016" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オタク・フロムUSA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Otaku from the USA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otaku from USA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85783" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リアル・ハードコア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Real Hard-Core</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Real Hardcore</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85798" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その先にあるもの...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Lies Ahead...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Saki ni Aru Mono...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117038" update="2010-03-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<rating votes="5">1.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ramen Angel Pretty Menma 2 - The Two Ramen Angels - Delivery Edition</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122413" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122414" update="2014-04-16">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122415" update="2015-06-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122416" update="2015-06-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131801" update="2011-07-10">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131802" update="2011-07-10">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154013" update="2014-04-16">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154014" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154015" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154016" update="2015-06-14">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
