<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="524" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>1978-11-07</startdate>
<enddate>1979-12-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Captain Future</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Captain Future</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Капитан Фьючер</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">CF</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">キャプテンフューチャー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Adventures of Captain Future</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Captain Future</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Capitaine Flam</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Capitan Futuro</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Capitán Futuro</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">فارس الفضاء</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1849" type="Side Story">Captain Future Karei Naru Taiyoukei Race</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/captain_future/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1009" type="Unknown Relation">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="1833" type="Chief Direction">Katsumata Tomoharu</name>
<name id="4479" type="Music">Oono Yuuji</name>
<name id="5109" type="Character Design">Noda Takuo</name>
<name id="10093" type="Original Work">Edmond Hamilton</name>
</creators>
<description>Curtis Newton, aka Captain Future, is an orphan. His parents died in their artificial satellite while he was an infant. His father was a scientist, who has abandoned Earth for the satellite to dedicate his life to science along with his ageing friend the genius Dr. Simon Wright. Wright senses his death, and decides to implant his brain in a mechanical container. They both manufactured a superior robot and an android. Captain Future dedicates his life to fight evil along with his three men, the brain, android, and robot.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="199">5.26</permanent>
<temporary count="200">6.74</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>2248.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1237</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2561</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>421</identifier>
<identifier>mcgyus</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/captain_future/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-video.co.jp/BD/captainfuture.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Captain_Future</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>キャプテンフューチャー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4312</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235371</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>384</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>267</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="9372" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙帝王あらわる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Space-Emperor of Terror</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Rückverwandlung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`empereur de l`espace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu Teiou Arawaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9373" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天翔ける砦の奇蹟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miracle of the Soaring Fortress</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kampf der Planeten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Prisonniers sur Mégara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amagakeru Toride no Kiseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9374" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遥かなり50億年の旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Journey of 5 Billion Years</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un voyage de cinq millions d`années</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Horukanari 50 Oku Nen no Tabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9375" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の海の牢獄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prison in the Sea of Flames</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Jagd auf den mächtigen Schatten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La prison de la mer de feu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Umi no Rougoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9376" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衛星ヌーンの決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown at the Satellite Noon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille finale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eisei Noon no Kessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9377" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SOS1億年前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SOS 1 billion years ago</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Reise in die Vergangenheit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Départ pour le passé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SOS 1 Oku Nen Mae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9378" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">太陽系創世記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Solar System Genesis</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Fünf Milliarden Jahre zurück</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La naissance du système solaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiyoukei Souseiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9379" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖なる星クウムの謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Riddle of the Holy Star Koom</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Geheimnis des Sterns Koom</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Planète inconnue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seinaru Hoshi Koom no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9380" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">破壊王(レッカー)の陰謀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The conspiracy of the Wrecker</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Plan des Wrecker</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le complot de Wrackar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wrecker no Inbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9381" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">破壊王(レッカー)の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Riddle of Wrecker</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret de Wrackar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wrecker no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9382" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦慄の海悪魔(シーデビル)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The horrible Sea-Devil</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Seelentransplantation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les créatures aquatiques</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senritsu no Sea Devil</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9383" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海底の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Underwater-Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Unterwasserfalle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Prisonnier sous la mer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitei no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9384" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">惑星に空気がなくなるとき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When the atmosphere of the planet disappears</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Luft- und Wasserknappheit auf dem Planeten Laguna</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète qui se meurt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakusei ni Kuuki ga Naku Naru Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9385" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえる惑星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ressurected Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`arme absolue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Wakusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9386" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲劇の暗黒星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The tragic Dark Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gefangen auf dem grünen Planeten Kol</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le créateur universel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Higeki no Ankokusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9387" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">見張りのおきて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Watcher</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Rettung der Quelle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La loi ancestrale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mihari no Okite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9399" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻影の惑星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Planet of Phantoms</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Letzter Drehort: Magischer Mond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète aux mirages</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gensei no Wakusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9400" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪獣狩人(ビブルハンター)は語る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monster Hunter talks</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine Fata Morgana verschwindet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chasseur de Mordicus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Biburu Hunter wa Kataru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9401" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">英雄カフールの謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of Hero Kaful</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kafoul, le héros</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eiyuu Kaful no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9402" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">放たれた最終兵器(スーパーウエポン)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The set-free Ultimate Weapon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les cendres sacrées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanatareta Super Weapon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9403" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャプテンフューチャー死す!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Captain Future dies!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein falscher Captain stirbt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mort du Capitaine Flam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Captain Future Shisu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9404" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀河に眠る神秘の石</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The mystery stone that sleeps in the galaxy</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Weltraumzirkus und die geheimnisvollen Steine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sorcier de la galaxie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginga ni Nemuru Shinpi no Ishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9405" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルルスの正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The True Colors of Alulus</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alulus, ein Wesen aus der vierten Dimension</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lumière sur les luxoides</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alulus no Shoutai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9406" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不死帝王の挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge of the Immortality-Emperor</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Verdächtiger verschwindet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi de l`empereur de l`immortalité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushi Teiou no Chousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9407" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">未知のミクロ宇宙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The undiscovered Micocosmos</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Abenteuer im Mikrokosmos</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sauvetage d`un micro-univers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michi no Micro Uchuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9408" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">星くずのスペースマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Stardust Spaceman</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mort d`un héros</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi Kuzu no Spaceman</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9409" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">彗星の支配者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Governor of the Comet</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Überraschungen beim Elektrolichtfest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le maître de la Comète</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suisei no Shihaisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9410" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀河サーカスの死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deathmatch at the Milkyway-Circus!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Unter Zirkuskünstlern</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sous le plus grand chapiteau de l`univers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginga Circus no Shitou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9411" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀河からの大脱走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Escape from the Milkyway</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Flucht aus der Milchstraße</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Escapade hors de la galaxie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinga kara no Dai Dassou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9412" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">渦巻く墓標</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whirling Gravestones</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sonnensystem in Gefahr</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cimetière de l`espace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uzumaku Bohyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9413" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">透明惑星の幻人間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Phantoms of the transparent Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le fantôme de la planète transparente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toumei Wakusei no Maboroshi Ningen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9414" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">生と死の幻影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantoms of Life and Death</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Quelle des ewigen Frühlings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Terreur dans la vallée des champignons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sei to Shi no Gen`ei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9415" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不死密売シンジケート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Immortality-Smuggling Syndicate</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Maschinenstadt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les pourvoyeurs d`immortalité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushi Mitsubai Syndicate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9416" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">吼える大氷流</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Howling Eternal Current</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abenteuer in der Eiswüste</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays glacé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoeru Daihyouryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9417" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゼロからの出発</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Start from Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wer wagt, gewinnt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Impossible exploit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zero kara no Shuppatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9418" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙遺跡の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of the Space-Ruins</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Weltraumruinen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère des ruines de l`espace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu Iseki no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9419" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">囚人船ハイジャックさる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prisonership being hijacked!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Raumschiff wird gekapert</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La révolte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuujin Fune Hijack Saru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9420" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">半獣人の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of the Semi-Monster-Race</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bei den Tiermenschen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère des hommes animaux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Han Juujin no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9421" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">グラッグ奪回作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rescue-Mission "Grag"</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Suche nach Grag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au secours de Grag</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Grag Dakkai Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9422" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻の星, 幻の文明</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Illusionary Star, Illusionary Civilization</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fin des illusions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi no Hoshi, Maboroshi no Bunmei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9423" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャプテンフューチャー募集!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Captain Future Recruiting!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schauspieler gesucht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La doublure du Capitaine Flam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Captain Future Boshuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9424" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪夢の世界・四次元</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Universe of Nightmare - Four Dimensions</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cauchemar en quatre dimensions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akumu no Sekai - Yojigen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9425" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえれ伝説の英雄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resurrect the Legendary Hero</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hilferuf vom Planeten Tarust</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sauvetage de la planète Tarust</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaere Densetsu no Eiyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9426" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えた宇宙船・彗星王の陰謀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The disappeared Spaceships - The conspiracy of the comet king</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Raumschiffe verschwunden!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De mystérieuses disparitions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Uchuusen - Suisei Ou no Inbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9427" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖のスペース・ロケーション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Horrible Space Location</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Film oder Diamanten?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tournage au fond des mers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu no Space Location</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9428" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死都の対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown at the City of Death</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Höhle des Lebens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La grande bataille</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi To no Taiketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9429" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の都の決闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle in the Capital of Eternity</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat dans la capitale éternelle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no To no Kettou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9430" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗闇族のすむ地底</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dark Tribe from the Depth of the Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Flug in die fünfte Dimension</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vallée des murmures</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurayami Zoku no Sumu Chitei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9431" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">惑星ただ一人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet - Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der unsichtbare Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Capitaine Flam fend l`espace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakusei Tada Hitori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9432" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウル・クォルンの挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The challenge of Ul Quorn</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kuolons Herausforderung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi de Kahlone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ul Quorn no Chousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9433" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとりぼっちの地獄刑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell-Penalty - Solitude</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der legendäre Held Fatul</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le châtiment de l`âme abjecte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitoribocchi no Jigoku Kei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9434" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">光と闇の彼方へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the other side of Light and Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au-delà des ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari to Yami no Kanata e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29782" update="2010-10-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1978-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29783" update="2010-10-22">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1978-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120229" update="2010-10-22">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120230" update="2010-10-22">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124451" update="2010-10-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1979-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
