<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5246" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-07-27</startdate>
<enddate>2007-10-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tokyo Majin Gakuen Kenpuchou Tou Dai Ni Maku</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">tokyo majin 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">東京魔人學園剣風帖 龖(トウ) 第弐幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tokyo Majin - Second Act</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Tokyo Majin 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4799" type="Prequel">Tokyo Majin Gakuen Kenpuchou Tou</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="341694">Yeah, for fans who liked the first series. The second series maintans the same animation and great fighting scenes, although the first series does them much better. The second series suffers from way too much storyline all over the place. Plus too many characters you don`t really care about or are given a chance to know more about aside from a few of the main characters.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="255817">thaaaaaaaanks</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="6797" type="Character Design">Nakai Jun</name>
<name id="6797" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakai Jun</name>
<name id="1543" type="Series Composition">Nemoto Toshizou</name>
<name id="5571" type="Direction">Ishihira Shinji</name>
<name id="2500" type="Music">Negishi Takayuki</name>
<name id="40029" type="Original Work">Imai Shuuhou</name>
</creators>
<description>This time in the beginning the brave fighters have to fight against a dark assassination organisation made for killing. The organisation is known as the `Dancing Swords` they gather up people with good fighting skills and awaken power just like Hiyuu`s and everyones in order to assassinate others only making those who live above the law doing evil as their targets. Hiyuu, Aoi, Kyoichi, Sakurai and Daigo are attacked by these fighters from the organisation and have to fight against them...
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="859">5.18</permanent>
<temporary count="880">7.08</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>160540.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8209</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2683</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4046</identifier>
<identifier>kosevk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tokyo_Majin_Gakuen_Kenpuchou_Tou#Anime_Episodes</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>東京魔人學園剣風帖</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1188</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327822</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8769</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4596" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="30">8.17</rating>
<name>Hiyuu Tatsuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious boy who transfers to Magami High School in his senior year. He is often shown as being very silent and carefree, but he actually has more insight on the people around him. He usually hangs out with Kyouichi and helps him fight gangsters from other schools, giving him the status of the fifth most delinquent student in Magami High School`s history. Tatsuma is probably the only one in the group who is close to Kyouichi and would often calmly tease and irritate him.</description>
<picture>20675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4597" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="18">6.73</rating>
<name>Houraiji Kyouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A well-known delinquent at Magami High and boss of a gang, who always carries around a bokutou. He often gets into fights with gangsters from other schools. When he first encounters Tatsuma, they engage in a fierce fight, which turns out to have been just a way of getting to know each other.</description>
<picture>20676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1999" picture="21304.jpg">Kawanabe Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4598" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="13">5.18</rating>
<name>Misato Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl from a rich family and the President of Magami High School`s Student Council. Aoi is a sensitive person and gets very upset when she is unable to help someone. Years ago she was unable to save her friend from a fire; this gave her a strong desire to protect people. There is a scar, which she received during the fire, on her lower back, though only Tatsuma knows about it. Aoi seems to harbour feelings for Tatsuma.</description>
<picture>20677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4599" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="15">4.92</rating>
<name>Sakurai Komaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain of the Kyuudou Club and Aoi`s best friend. She is quick to defend Aoi when Kyouichi says mean things about her. Unlike Aoi, Komaki is aggressive towards people who get in the way or harm those she cares about.</description>
<picture>20678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4600" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="9">4.63</rating>
<name>Daigo Yuuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of Magami High School`s Wrestling Club and an excellent cook. Yuuya also happens to have a crush on Komaki and he is constantly seen cooking big meals for her.</description>
<picture>20679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21" picture="170939.jpg">Taira Katsui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4601" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="9">3.64</rating>
<name>Touno Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Newspaper club, whom Kyouichi labels a stalker. Goes by the nickname "Anko". A curious and determined girl, Kyouko is always out to get the scoop on Tatsuma and his group`s actions. Sensing that the main characters may be hiding something, she tails them and saw them using their "powers".</description>
<picture>20680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1927" picture="21136.jpg">Narita Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4602" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="8">3.96</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Hisui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Owner of an antiques shop who has business dealings with the Misato family. He is very loyal to Aoi and often calls her Aoi-sama. Hisui seems to have been close to Aoi since the two were little. He received a charm bracelet from her when they were younger, which he now holds in a pouch around his neck. He also promised that he would always protect her no matter what.</description>
<picture>20681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2001" picture="228614.jpg">Sekiguchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4603" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="9">7.33</rating>
<name>Umon Raito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The vocalist of the rock band CROW. He has the ability to manipulate lightning and electricity, as well as the ability to use a form of spell casting (accompanied by chanting and symbols).</description>
<picture>20682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4604" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="7">5.06</rating>
<name>Inugami Morihito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teacher at Magami High School; also Kyoko`s homeroom teacher. He is often seen feeding rabbits in hutches in the school compound. He is not much of teacher since he never attends meetings. He seems to know about the actual events that are happening around the city.</description>
<picture>20683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1441" picture="18827.jpg">Tsuboi Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4605" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="11">7.24</rating>
<name>Maria Alucard</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuma, Kyouichi and Aoi`s homeroom teacher. She can be very childish as a teacher, often screaming at the students and throwing stuff at them. She is often annoyed by Kyouichi, who calls her Maria-chan and always comes up with excuses to skip class. Though her attitude doesn`t show it, she cares deeply for the safety of her students. She rides a motorcycle to school everyday and often speaks in English.</description>
<picture>20684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1888" picture="228611.jpg">Masuda Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4606" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="7">4.10</rating>
<name>Kozunu Tendou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man with superhuman abilities, who is able to transform humans into ogres and demons. Images of when his mother hung herself still haunts him to this day.</description>
<picture>20685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2002" picture="21307.jpg">Katsu Anri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4607" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="11">4.31</rating>
<name>Mary Claire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious young girl with the ability to manipulate fire. She is always by Kozunu`s side. Apparently she was sent by her master Yagyuu to observe him and act as a messenger for her master. Kozune commented that she is a doll that obeys to her master.</description>
<picture>20686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4608" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="8">4.17</rating>
<name>Oribe Yukino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of two shrine maidens that are friends of Komaki. She, along with Hinano, appears to dislike men; she becomes very angry at Kyouichi when he first meets them.</description>
<picture>20687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2005" picture="188512.jpg">Yamazaki Michiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4609" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="10">3.43</rating>
<name>Oribe Hinano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second of two shrine maidens that are friends of Komaki. She appears to be very shy around men; she hides behind Yukino when Kyouichi first meets them.</description>
<picture>20688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="80749" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第壱夜 拳武編「拳武十二神将」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Twelve Generals of the Martial Fist</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Dwunastu generałów Wojowniczej Pięści</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenbu Juunijinshou</title>
<summary>A powerful new threat emerges when a violent and bold group of masked assailants attacks Tatsuma and his friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80920" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第弐夜 拳武編「煉獄する咆哮」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Purgatorial Howl</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Oczyszczający skowyt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rengokusuru Houkou</title>
<summary>While some of the gang hears details about the infamous Martial Fists, the rest of the team is learning about their new enemies the hard way - engaged in amazingly fierce battle!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80921" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第参夜 拳武編「心から変わろう」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Change Ourselves from the Inside</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Zmieniajmy się od wewnątrz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro kara Kawarou</title>
<summary>As Daigo and Kyouichi deal with strange events in the present, scenes from the past reveal painful moments that shaped them into the young men they’ve become.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80922" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第四夜 拳武編「拳は命を奪わない」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fist Does Not Take Lives</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Pięść nie odbiera życia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ken wa Inochi o Ubawanai</title>
<summary>Kyouichi raises his new blade against Ukon. As the rest of the gang takes on swarms of mystical enemies, Tatsuma’s reality is turned upside down by shocking revelations regarding his past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80923" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第伍夜 拳武編「護る拳」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Protecting Fist</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Pięść, która chroni</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamoru Ken</title>
<summary>As the group tries to identify the one responsible for the recent madness, Tatsuma once again comes face to face with Marie - and she wants him dead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80924" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第六夜 宿星編 白虎之章「聖夜は微笑まない」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Story of Byakko: A Mirthless Christmas Eve</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Historia Byakko: Wigilia bez radości</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiya wa Hohoemanai</title>
<summary>During the season of giving, Tatsuma is stunned beyond comprehension to find those closest to him brutally taken away by a murderous fiend known as Chaos.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80925" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第七夜 宿星編 玄武之章「渦王須」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Story of Genbu: Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Historia Genbu: Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chaos</title>
<summary>With pain and madness in the winter air, Tatsuma must decide what kind of man he truly is when he gets his hands on the psychotic killer known as Chaos.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80926" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第八夜 宿星編 朱雀之章「滅日」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Story of Suzaku: Destruction Day</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Historia Suzaku: Dzień zagłady</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Metsunichi</title>
<summary>Tatsuma’s friends are worried he’s spending too much time trying to help Ryuuji. But bigger concerns are on the horizon - an evil like no other is about to strike.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80927" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第九夜 宿星編 青竜之章「集う宿星」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Story of Seiryu: Gathering Stars of Fate</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Historia Seiryu: Zgromadzenie Gwiazd Losu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsudou Shukusei</title>
<summary>The world is in serious danger as Yagyu delivers death to many in an incredibly brutal battle. Unless Tatsuma’s team reaches unimaginable levels of power, the situation is truly hopeless.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80928" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第拾夜 宿星編 黄龍之章「散らない桜」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Story of the Golden Dragon: Cherry Blossoms That Do Not Fall</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Historia Złotego Smoka: Płatki wiśni, które nie opadną</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiranai Sakura</title>
<summary>The citizens of Tokyo come together to rebuild, and the wounded begin to heal. The gang reflects on all that was lost and ponders the mysterious fate of Tatsuma.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80929" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第拾壱夜 番外編「歩め子らよ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Walk Onward, Children</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Dodatek: Naprzód, dzieci</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayume Kora yo</title>
<summary>A glimpse into the past reveals the friendships and struggles along the path undertaken by Tatsuma and his powerful friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80930" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第拾弐夜 番外編「ありがとう」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Romeo &amp; Juliet</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Dodatek: Dziękujemy wam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arigatou</title>
<summary>Happy memories: Sometimes even those who fight to keep Tokyo safe from evil get a chance to live as normal high school kids.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
