<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5252" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kidou Senshi Gundam 00</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gundam Double O</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mobile Suit Gundam Double O</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gundam Double Oh</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Подвижен Костюм Гъндам 00</title>
<title xml:lang="no" type="synonym">Gundam dobbelt null</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Мобилен Костюм Гъндам 00</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kidou Senshi Gandamu Daburuou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mobile Suit Gundam 00 Season 1</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">機動戰士鋼彈OO</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">機動戰士高達00</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">机动战士高达00</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">G00</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">G00 S1</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="short">كاندام 00</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gundam 00</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="short">Ґандам 00</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機動戦士ガンダム00</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam 00</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam 00</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam 00</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">기동전사 건담 더블오</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">โมบิลสูทกันดั้ม ดับเบิ้ลโอ</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">機動戰士00</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5903" type="Sequel">Kidou Senshi Gundam 00 (2008)</anime>
<anime id="7183" type="Summary">Kidou Senshi Gundam 00 Special Edition I: Celestial Being</anime>
<anime id="715" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Gundam</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9568" approval="10" total="18">Kakumeiki Valvrave</anime>
<anime id="4521" approval="4" total="12">Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch</anime>
<anime id="17" approval="2" total="3">Fullmetal Panic!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="37">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="489452">This was the most awesome anime from mecha class in my opinion,</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="52476">Awesome Gundam series, one of the best.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="68044">If your a Gundam fan you will not want to miss watching this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="738147">Not the best Gundam series but it`s pretty good towards the end. The series started off pretty dull and you will feel pretty pointless, then it starts picking up after the 10th episode when stuffs start to make a little more sense and the characters have more characteristics. It took me the third attempt to get pass the 1st episode which I felt is very badly done, and I still feel so. If you could endure the first half of the series, it will be quite rewarding. Opening and Ending songs doesn`t help at all in making the series better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="284821">This series was amazing from start to finish. Glad to see the main characters not win all the time! I`m looking forward to them kicking butt in the 2nd season though. ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="203171">IMO the best Gundam of all (so far)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="419868">Great story, some of the best characters out there</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="188928">While Gundam 00 (S1) is not a bad series, it is dragged down by the lack of strife in the first half. This makes the characters seem shallow and uninteresting, alongside the plot overall. 
However, towards the end of the series the story picks up, delivering potent punch that makes up for the earlier faults and actually makes you care about the characters. A punch potent enough to make you want to watch the second season as well.
Overall, not the best Gundam series around but definitely worth watching.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="271366">If you`re a mecha fan, esp. a Gundam fan, definitely check out this series. It`s one of the best. ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="225190">above average gundam</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="40053">One of the best gundam series.&lt;br /&gt;Not only for gundam fans, the storyline is interesting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="332327">OMG!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="275599">EPIC!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="403799">Empieza bien y termina mejor. Tiene bastante trama y la accion esta muy cuidada y bien realizada No deve perdersela.&lt;br /&gt;Begins good and ends better. It Have drama and the accion its well done and realized. Its a must.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="263262">Just watch it lol.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="232807">This is good, believe me,,,,</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="82793">must watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="23892">Yes!!! I love Nina! :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="5242">its a Must see for sure!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="305044">If you dont hate mecha, Gundam 00 is an absolute must see. One of the best series around.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="47554">Just awesome, simply awesome.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gundam00.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="130" type="Direction">Mizushima Seiji</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="1572" type="Series Composition">Kuroda Yousuke</name>
<name id="951" type="Character Design">Kouga Yun</name>
<name id="105" type="Character Design">Chiba Michinori</name>
</creators>
<description>By 2307 AD, fossil fuels had already long become virtually exhausted. Humankind spent several decades on wars around the little that remained of such fuels and on constructing a large-scale system to draw in solar power from orbit, with an orbital ring, power microwaving technology, and three orbital elevators. In order to construct such a gigantic, resource-intensive system, however, most relevant countries had consolidated into three major power blocks: the http://anidb.net/ch8593 [World Economic Union], centered around the United States of America; the http://anidb.net/ch8594 [Advanced European Union], centered around the European Union; and the http://anidb.net/ch8592 [Human Reform League], centered around Russia, India and China. As only these power blocs and their allies had participated in the construction of the solar power system, only they were entitled to its benefits; with fossil fuels nearing extinction, countries with economies based on them, such as those from the Middle East, became progressively poorer.
Meanwhile, these three superpowers continued to intervene militarily where they see fit, terrorism was still rampant, and peace was a faraway dream for many people. Even in the 24th century, humankind was far from unified. And even though humans insisted in not learning about the horrors of war and did not make a point of pursuing peace, they still intended to venture away from the Earth, with colonies having been built and nanomachines already allowing for decent life conditions even during prolonged periods in space.
In this still disgracefully conflict-ridden world, a private paramilitary organization unveils its existence, announcing its intention to bring forth the eradication of war and conflict through force of arms. This organization, called http://anidb.net/ch2214 [Celestial Being], possesses its own mobile suits, the Gundams, which are much more powerful than those in the hands of any military in the world, and proceeds to using them to intervene in conflicts in order to stop them by force. Their actions quickly divide public opinion, and governments and other groups begin to act by taking their existence into consideration, but will they manage to bring peace to the world? Beyond the question of how the world will reply immediately, what is going to happen in the future as a result of their actions?
— written by Hinoe</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5049">7.76</permanent>
<temporary count="5147">8.23</temporary>
<review count="10">7.63</review>
</ratings>
<picture>7475.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8190</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2581</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4058</identifier>
<identifier>kvhsht</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gundam00.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mobile_Suit_Gundam_00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>機動戦士ガンダム00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1213</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>328140</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9075</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1286" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-28">
<name>megalomaniac</name>
<description>Megalomania is a psychopathological condition characterized by delusional fantasies of power, relevance, and omnipotence, and by inflated self-esteem.&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>70559.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2835" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Africa</name>
<description>The world`s second-largest continent and the birthplace of the human species, Africa is a place of a huge diversity, with deserts and savannas, with famine and precious stones, with cultural and economical riches of all kinds. Throughout history, Africa has been the cradle of empires and has been ruled by foreign powers, and as of the early 21st century sees swift changes and economic boom going side by side with inhuman levels of poverty.</description>
<picurl>126530.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3529" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>space elevator</name>
<description>A needle-like structure placed on the equator of a planet connecting the surface with a low planetary orbit in about 200-300km height (it may even reach out into a geostationary orbit). Very efficient way to move mass "out of" a planet`s gravity well — much more efficient than e.g. chemical rockets.
Alas it is not yet possible to build a space elevator, because all know materials would be crushed under their own weight. There is a faint hope that carbon-based nano-tubes may be a usable material in the future though.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3580" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-05">
<name>cliffhanger ending</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4667" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-20">
<name>hard science fiction</name>
<description>Hard science fiction is a category of http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] characterised by an emphasis on scientific accuracy, technical detail, or both. The term is not defined precisely, and is often seen as an approximate way of describing works. Stories revolving around scientific and technical consistency were written as early as 1860s and 1870s; http://anidb.net/cr5973 [Jules Verne] is generally considered the creator of the genre. Although not always accurate in his scientific depictions, and though Verne himself denied writing as a scientist or seriously predicting machines and technology of the future, the attention to detail in his work became an inspiration for many future scientists and explorers.
Nowadays, the term http://anidb.net/t7086 [soft science fiction] is also often used to refer to science fiction stories which lack scientific focus or rigorous adherence to known science; the categorization "hard science fiction" thus represents a position on a broad continuum ranging from "softer" to "harder". There is a degree of flexibility in how far from "real science" a story can stray before it leaves the realm of hard science fiction; some authors scrupulously avoid such technology as faster-than-light travel, while others accept such notions but focus on realistically depicting the worlds that such a technology might make possible. In this view, a story`s scientific "hardness" is less a matter of the absolute accuracy of the science content than of the rigour and consistency with which the various ideas and possibilities are worked out. Furthermore, later discoveries do not necessarily invalidate the label of hard science fiction; the designation remains valid even when a crucial plot element is later discovered to be incorrect.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5820" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-29">
<name>combat butler -- DO NOT ADD -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is meant to be deleted. Please DO NOT add it to further anime. Please tag the relevant characters "butler" and whatever combat- or martial arts-related tag is appropriate. For the already tagged anime, please tag the relevant characters, and then remove this tag from the related anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5872" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>bad luck</name>
<description>You are living a blessed life far from any troubles. Your sister is a famous reporter, you have a good looking girlfriend and you excel in your studies aiming to be a scientist. Your future is looking bright. But reality is, fate hates you. Your sister is killed, your girlfriend breaks up with you after being crippled in a terrorist attack and finally you end up as a pizza delivery boy.
And just when you thought it can`t get worse, it does. Your former girlfriend turns into a Darth Vader knock-off, tries to impose her world view on others by force and is out there to kill you. Yes, your life does truly suck.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5971" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>red ones go faster</name>
<description>Red things just seem to go faster. In fiction, make something red and you can almost guarantee it`ll move quicker, as if the colour itself reduces drag, lowers inertia and increases forward momentum. A visual shorthand for getting the point across that an object is zippy.
Truth in Television: Red apparently promotes adrenalin release and feelings of excitement or intensity, which can certainly give the appearance that a red object is moving faster, as well as possibly encourage the drivers of red vehicles to push the envelope more. Also, the Doppler Effect makes things red-shifted if they`re moving away from you at a high speed (read: significant fraction of the speed of light). Don`t expect there to be any evolutionary basis for this, however, as it`s unlikely any human would ever get to see it with the naked eye. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="595" type="main character in" update="2014-02-13">
<rating votes="274">6.52</rating>
<name>Setsuna F Seiei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Gundam Meister who pilots the http://anidb.net/ch2212 [Gundam Exia]. He was born in the wartorn Republic of Krugis, where he fought as a child soldier and was saved by the intervention of http://anidb.net/ch2420 [a mysterious Gundam]. After this experience he went on to join the private armed organization http://anidb.net/ch2214 [Celestial Being] under the alias Setsuna F Seiei. He is a quiet and reserved young man who keeps his emotions to himself, but his actions are sometimes impulsive and unpredictable.</description>
<picture>39594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2193" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="121">4.42</rating>
<name>Marina Ismail</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The princess royal of the Kingdom of Azadistan, a struggling nation in the Middle East. Marina has been installed as a sovereign in order to save her country, which has exhausted its fossil fuels and now seeks to join the solar power network operated by the world`s great powers.</description>
<picture>56628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2194" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="143">8.06</rating>
<name>Feldt Grace</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the combat operators aboard the Celestial Being mothership Ptolemaios. Despite her youth, she is very knowledgeable when it comes to mechanics, but she communicates poorly with other people. Her fellow combat operator Christina Sierra plays the role of a big sister to the awkward Feldt.</description>
<picture>39592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2195" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="110">7.16</rating>
<name>Sumeragi Lee Noriega</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The tactical forecaster of the Celestial Being mothership Ptolemaios. Although Sumeragi is not the captain, she is effectively in charge of the ship, and is responsible for drafting mission plans and giving orders in response to the changing battle situation. Her light-hearted attitude contrasts with the heavy responsibility of her position.</description>
<picture>39602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="449" picture="17341.jpg">Honna Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2196" type="main character in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="114">8.22</rating>
<name>Lockon Stratos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Gundam Meister who pilots the Gundam Dynames. Lockon is a superb marksman, and as the oldest of the Gundam Meisters he serves as their unofficial team leader. With his good humor and caring personality, he often plays the role of a big brother to his younger comrades, particularly the quiet and serious Setsuna. He operates his Gundam with the assistance of a Haro robot whose control support enables Lockon to concentrate on his shooting.</description>
<picture>39585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2197" type="main character in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="162">6.19</rating>
<name>Allelujah Haptism</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Gundam Meister who pilots the transformable Gundam Kyrios. Allelujah was raised under the supervision of the Human Reform League, and later went on to join the private armed organization Celestial Being. His personality is normally calm and gentle, and he is reluctant to take lives even when the mission demands it. However, there is another side to his character...</description>
<picture>39586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2198" type="main character in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="150">5.24</rating>
<name>Tieria Erde</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Gundam Meister who pilots the heavily armed Gundam Virtue. His origins, his personal history, and even his age are a complete mystery, but he appears to be an androgynously handsome young man around the age of sixteen. He is ruthlessly loyal to Veda, the entity that controls Celestial Being, and tolerates no deviation from its plans by his unreliable comrades.</description>
<picture>39587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2199" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="10">5.45</rating>
<name>Lichtendahl Tsery</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The helmsman of the Celestial Being mothership Ptolemaios. Lichtendahl is cheerful and talkative, and Christina Sierra occasionally reprimands him for chatting during missions. He also goes by the nickname "Lichty."</description>
<picture>39611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="450" picture="17342.jpg">Azuma Masataka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2200" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="52">6.53</rating>
<name>Lasse Aeon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The gunner of the Celestial Being mothership Ptolemaios. Since the ship has virtually no armament, Lasse normally provides backup to helmsman Lichtendahl Tsery instead. He is distinguished by his cynical and fatalistic attitude.</description>
<picture>39601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2201" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="25">6.85</rating>
<name>Christina Sierra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the combat operators aboard the Celestial Being mothership Ptolemaios, who relay orders to the Gundam Meisters during their missions. Christina was recruited by Celestial Being due to her advanced programming skills. She has a friendly personality, but carries out her duties with professional efficiency.</description>
<picture>39610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="452" picture="41417.jpg">Satou Arise</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2202" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="87">2.79</rating>
<name>Wang Liu Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An agent of the private armed organisation Celestial Being. Wang Liu-Mei is a well-known celebrity with many connections in the world of high finance, and she uses her position to gather intelligence and support the Ptolemaios crewmembers.</description>
<picture>39590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2203" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="27">4.56</rating>
<name>Hong Long</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An agent of the private armed organisation Celestial Being. Hong Long accompanies Wang Liu-Mei everywhere she goes, serving as her retainer and bodyguard.</description>
<picture>39589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="169" picture="16976.jpg">Takahashi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2204" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="55">2.96</rating>
<name>Ribbons Almark</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious young man who always accompanies Alejandro Corner.</description>
<picture>39600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32833" picture="17354.jpg">Sougetsu Noboru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2205" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="15">2.84</rating>
<name>Alejandro Corner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A United Nations ambassador from one of the Union member nations. Alejandro also serves as a Celestial Being observer, but the precise nature of his relationship to the organisation remains unclear.</description>
<picture>39609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2206" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="17">4.15</rating>
<name>Aeolia Schenberg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The legendary inventor who founded the private armed organisation Celestial Being. Two hundred years ago, he proposed the basic theory of the solar power generation system and predicted the development of the machines now known as mobile suits. He has now reappeared in the form of a video address announcing the objectives of Celestial Being.</description>
<picture>39618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="456" picture="17358.jpg">Ootsuka Chikao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2207" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="110">5.60</rating>
<name>Soma Peries</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Human Reform League mobile suit pilot with the rank of 2nd Lieutenant. A product of the Super-Human Institute Labs, Soma was born and bred to become a perfect soldier, and she is designated as "Super-Soldier Number 1." Her body has been modified to adapt to space, and enhancements have been made to her nervous system. She expresses little emotion, whether because of brain alterations or simply due to her unnatural upbringing.</description>
<picture>39599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="457" picture="61775.jpg">Ogasawara Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2208" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="59">7.00</rating>
<name>Sergei Smirnov</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Human Reform League mobile suit commander known as the "Wild Bear of Russia." Sergei is a veteran soldier who earned his reputation in the Solar Power Wars, and now holds the rank of Lieutenant Colonel. Despite his long years of service, he prefers to stay on the front lines, and he often enters the battlefield in a mobile suit in order to observe the enemy with his own eyes.</description>
<picture>39597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2209" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="68">5.53</rating>
<name>Patrick Colasour</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An ace mobile suit pilot with the AEU military. Chosen to demonstrate the new AEU Enact mobile suit, Patrick is the first person to face a Gundam in battle. He is rash and overconfident, and although he boasts of his victories in two thousand mock battles he is hopelessly outmatched by the power of the Gundams.</description>
<picture>39598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2210" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="72">6.56</rating>
<name>Graham Aker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An ace pilot of the Union armed forces who holds the rank of 1st Lieutenant. Initially assigned to the elite MSWAD unit, Graham becomes fascinated with the Gundams after he witnesses the first appearance of the Gundam Exia, and is soon transferred to the Union`s anti-Gundam investigative taskforce. His superb piloting skills enable him to transform his Union Flag mobile suit in mid-air, a manoeuvre known as the "Graham Special."</description>
<picture>39603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2211" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="49">3.09</rating>
<name>Billy Katagiri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A scientist with the Union armed forces. Initially assigned to MSWAD as a technical advisor, he helps Graham investigate the mysteries of the Gundams, and is transferred along with him to the Union`s anti-Gundam investigative taskforce.</description>
<picture>39584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2212" type="appears in" update="2010-12-28">
<rating votes="33">5.82</rating>
<name>GN-001 Gundam Exia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>One of the Gundam mobile suits possessed by Celestial Being. Like the other Gundams, the Exia is equipped with a GN Drive, a so-called "solar reactor" that provides it with almost limitless energy. The GN particles generated by this drive also give the Gundams remarkable mobility and stealth capabilities, and allow them to carry powerful beam weapons. The Exia is intended mainly for close combat, and it can be equipped with seven different swords for different kinds of mission, including a huge GN Sword and two GN Blades whose cutting edges are enveloped in GN particles. Its long-range weaponry is limited to the rifle mode of the GN Sword and the small GN Vulcans installed in its forearms.</description>
<picture>27771.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2213" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="7">7.58</rating>
<name>GN-002 Gundam Dynames</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>One of the Gundam mobile suits possessed by Celestial Being. Like the other Gundams, the Dynames is equipped with a GN Drive that gives it almost limitless energy and remarkable mobility. The Dynames is designed for long-range shooting, and its main weapon is a powerful GN Sniper Rifle that can destroy enemy machines from outside their sensor range. Its head changes into a sniper mode to reveal a special camera eye for precision shooting, and its cockpit is equipped with a dedicated targeting scope. The Dynames can also be outfitted with devices such as GN Beam Pistols and protective GN Shields, depending on the mission requirements.</description>
<picture>27648.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2214" type="appears in" update="2009-06-21">
<rating votes="30">5.38</rating>
<name>Celestial Being</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Celestial Being is a private paramilitary force founded by the scientist Aeolia Schenberg. It pursues the complete eradication of armed conflict mainly through the deployment of the revolutionary Gundam units, as well as other mobile units in aggressive, sometimes indiscriminate armed intervention. It acts upon the advisory of the artificial intelligence Veda, and its preferred mode of operation resembles guerilla or maneuver warfare. As of the initiation of its publicly visible activities in 2307, Schenberg appeared in a taped worldwide broadcast announcing the organization`s existence and intentions. Many people of Earth began a love/hate-like relationship with Celestial Being, though everyone does not desire war. Some people, like Marina Ismail of Azadistan, believe that they create only more conflict by intervening.</description>
<picture>17372.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2216" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="80">6.53</rating>
<name>Shirin Bakhtiar</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marina Ismail`s aide and advisor. Although Shirin has considerable political skill, she cannot participate openly in government since the customs of the Kingdom of Azadistan forbid the involvement of women in politics. Because of this, her advice to Marina is edged with bitterness.</description>
<picture>39605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2217" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-23">
<rating votes="76">3.02</rating>
<name>Ali Al-Saachez</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mercenary team leader who is currently employed by a PMC (Private Military Company) in the Republic of Moralia. Ali is a veteran soldier and an expert mobile suit pilot, and he appears to have played a role in Setsuna F Seiei`s past career as a child soldier.</description>
<picture>45077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2218" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="78">7.59</rating>
<name>Kati Mannequin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An AEU operations commander with the rank of Colonel. Kati is placed in command of Patrick`s mobile suit team during the joint military exercise in the Taklamakan Desert. She is a strict and professional officer, and immediately clashes with the infamous ace pilot she has been assigned to supervise.</description>
<picture>39582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2219" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="6">3.97</rating>
<name>Ralph Eifman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A scientist with the Union armed forces. Professor Eifman was Billy Katagiri`s teacher in graduate school, and is reunited with his former student when he is assigned to the Union`s anti-Gundam investigative taskforce. He personally customizes Graham Aker`s Union Flag to suit the unique performance requirements of its pilot.</description>
<picture>39608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2220" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="3">3.31</rating>
<name>Howard Mason</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Union Flag pilot with the rank of Warrant Officer. Howard is assigned to the anti-Gundam investigative taskforce at Graham Aker`s request, and helps him in his pursuit of the Gundams.</description>
<picture>39607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="169" picture="16976.jpg">Takahashi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2221" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="4">3.91</rating>
<name>Daryl Dodge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Union Flag pilot with the rank of Master Sergeant. Daryl is assigned to the anti-Gundam investigative taskforce at Graham Aker`s request, and helps him in his pursuit of the Gundams. While not as skilled a pilot as Howard Mason, he has plenty of fighting spirit.</description>
<picture>39606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="292" picture="68967.jpg">Nishi Rintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2222" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="3">3.31</rating>
<name>Joshua Edwards</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Union Flag pilot who is assigned to the elite anti-Gundam unit known as the Over Flags. He has a past history with Over Flags commander Graham Aker, and the two pilots have a strong sense of rivalry.</description>
<picture>17390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4741" picture="45560.jpg">Konno Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2223" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="6">3.31</rating>
<name>Ming</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Human Reform League mobile suit pilot with the rank of 1st Lieutenant. Ming serves as deputy commander of Sergei Smirnov`s mobile suit team, assisting Sergei during fleet battles and piloting a Tieren in combat.</description>
<picture>17391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2224" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="51">6.49</rating>
<name>Ian Vashti</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Celestial Being`s chief mechanic. Ian is responsible for developing new weapons and equipment for the Gundams, such as the GN Blades used by the Gundam Exia.</description>
<picture>39593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2225" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="3">3.86</rating>
<name>Louise no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Louise`s mother, her name was never mentioned and only referred by her relation to Louise. She comes from Spain to take Louise home because of the war, but the latter insists on staying in Japan. At first she is against her daughter`s relationship with Saji, but later on accepts and grows fond of him, making Louise jealous at one point.</description>
<picture>17395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2226" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="97">1.21</rating>
<name>Saji Crossroad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A pushover by nature, Saji dreams of going into space, which has developed his ambition to become a space engineer.</description>
<picture>39581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2227" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="119">2.10</rating>
<name>Louise Halevy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Louise Halevy is the daughter of Barry Halevy, the leader of a fossil fuel export regulation watchdog group. Because of her family`s wealthy lifestyle, she possess somewhat of a selfish behaviour and often demands people to get what she wants. A year before the event of the anime series, both she and her father were protected by Celestial Being when a terrorist organisation are planning to target Louise`s father for assassination. This was Setsuna F Seiei`s first task since joining the organization to prevent the assassination of Barry Halevy and protecting his daughter. Although Louise and her father were protected by Setsuna, they have never met each other face-to-face, until a year later she was introduced to him by Saji Crossroad.</description>
<picture>39596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2228" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="18">4.57</rating>
<name>Kinue Crossroad</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saji`s older sister. Pursues Celestial Being during the course of working in the media. Dislikes Louise. She and her brother Saji were orphaned prior to the start of the series. Kinue seemed obsessed over Aeolia Schenberg, believing that Celestial Being had motives other than ending warfare and that researching Schenberg is the key to discovering those motives.</description>
<picture>39613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2229" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="77">2.50</rating>
<name>Nena Trinity</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nena Trinity is the youngest of the three siblings. Outwardly presenting herself as being a cheerful young girl, she habitually smiles and makes the peace sign with her fingers. Nena seems to feel a sense of enjoyment when undertaking destructive missions, indicating a possible sociopathy. In addition to her erratic behaviour, Nena claims to be attracted to "wild" men, even going so far as to forcefully kiss Setsuna F Seiei upon hearing that he is the pilot of the GN-001 Gundam Exia.</description>
<picture>39588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2230" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="13">2.79</rating>
<name>Johann Trinity</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oldest of the three siblings, Johann pilots the Gundam Throne Eins. Undertaking the mission to eradicate the world`s strife, he began armed interventions alongside Michael and Nena. He is a calm person who faithfully handles his given mission while he commands his problematic brother and sister. His rational and cool-headed demeanour provides a subtle contrast to his fiery and stubborn younger siblings. An excellent marksman, he handles the firing of the GN Mega Launcher equipped on the Gundam Throne Eins.</description>
<picture>39614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2231" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="13">1.42</rating>
<name>Michael Trinity</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An impulsive young man, Michael immediately bares his fangs at people who oppose him, brandishing his trademark knife when feeling enraged or intimidated. Similar to his personality, he favours brutal tactics for mobile suit combat and specialises in attacks with the Gundam Throne Zwei`s all-range weapon, the GN Fangs. Though he feels somewhat protective over his younger sister, Nena, he frequently complains about having to comply to orders from his brother, Johann.</description>
<picture>39615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2233" type="appears in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="56">6.72</rating>
<name>Lockon Stratos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lyle is first introduced as Lockon`s unnamed twin brother early on in season one, where he is shown carrying a bouquet of flowers to place on his family`s grave as his brother watches him from behind a tree. He does not make another appearance for the remainder of the season; however, he is mentioned by name in Lockon`s dying soliloquy, in which Neil remarks that the world of tomorrow would be the world in which Lyle would live in.</description>
<picture>39595.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2236" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="6">3.97</rating>
<name>Massoud Rachmadi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An Imam in Azadistan with strong influence in the conservative factions of the Azadistani Parliament. Known as "Rasa" among the conservative factions, when Marina decided to accept the role of princess, he volunteered to become her opposition in order to contain the conservatives from getting radical and violent. His sudden abduction by Ali`s forces had touched off a coup d`état with radical elements of the Azadistani army leading it against Marina and the rest of her reformist-leading government.
He was later tracked down and rescued by Setsuna, Lockon and Hong Long, and returned to make a joint statement with Marina, which temporary quelled the rebellion. It is revealed by Marina in the fourth episode of the second season that he died by unknown means during the gap between season one and two.</description>
<picture>17405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4742" picture="54426.jpg">Fukumatsu Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2416" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="4">6.99</rating>
<name>GN-003 Gundam Kyrios</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>One of the Gundam mobile suits possessed by Celestial Being. Like the other Gundams, the Kyrios is equipped with a GN Drive that gives it almost limitless energy and remarkable mobility. This transformable mobile suit can change into a flight form for high-speed hit and run attacks, and a variety of weapons containers can be attached to the tail of its flight form to suit the mission. In both its flight form and its mobile suit form, the Kyrios far surpasses the transformable mobile suits used by the Union and the AEU. Its GN Shield can also function as a claw and houses a lethal hidden weapon.</description>
<picture>27644.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2417" type="appears in" update="2009-06-09">
<rating votes="4">7.93</rating>
<name>GN-004 Gundam Nadleeh</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The hidden form of the Gundam Virtue. This Gundam is revealed when the Virtue discards its armour, and is distinguished by the long red cords on its head that supply GN particles to the armour parts. The Nadleeh retains the GN Beam Sabers stored inside the knee armour of the Virtue, and it can use the Virtue`s GN Cannons as handheld weapons, but a special GN Beam Rifle and GN Shield have also been prepared for its use. Its pilot Tieria Erde is forced to reveal the Nadleeh ahead of schedule, and it possesses secret capabilities that have yet to be demonstrated.</description>
<picture>17672.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2418" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="4">4.99</rating>
<name>GN-005 Gundam Virtue</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>One of the Gundam mobile suits possessed by Celestial Being. Like the other Gundams, the Virtue is equipped with a GN Drive that gives it almost limitless energy. This heavily armed Gundam is equipped with a powerful GN Bazooka and movable GN Cannons, and can protect itself by generating a GN Field barrier. Its mobility is low compared to the other Gundams, but the Virtue`s tremendous firepower is highly effective in fleet battles and attacks on enemy bases. As its weapons and field generators consume large amounts of energy, the Virtue must often pause to replenish its supply of GN particles.</description>
<picture>17673.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2420" type="appears in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="16">7.62</rating>
<name>GN-000 0 Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The first Gundam mobile suit developed by Celestial Being. Six years earlier, the 0 Gundam appeared before the child soldier who now calls himself Setsuna F Seiei. Virtually nothing is known about this mysterious machine, and its current whereabouts are unclear.</description>
<picture>17674.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8490" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="5">6.53</rating>
<name>GN-003 Gundam Kyrios</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>While in an fighter configuration, Kyrios duals as a jet fighter/bomber. During missions that requires fast hit-and-run tactics the tail unit can fire missiles to either destroy incoming aerial units or specific ground targets. It also carries bombs within the "underbelly" of the tail unit. Because of Kyrios` GN Drives, the fighter is capable of carrying weight that no mobile suit can transport. Thus the tail unit can only be utilized by Kyrios. Without the "tail unit" and its weapon compliments, Kyrios resorts to dog fighting, using its GN Submachine Gun.</description>
<picture>27643.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8494" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="4">8.76</rating>
<name>AEU-09Y812 AEU Enact Ali Al-Saachez Custom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A tuned-up, improved prototype of the Enact for the PMC`s Ali Al-Saachez. The blade rifle appears from the tip of the large sonic blade. Increasing the amount of fixed armaments, the sonic blade is built into the arm.
This Mobile Suit can dock in a Mobile Armor called Agrissa, an old model used in the 5th Solar Wars, but was destroyed by Gundam Drei.
This unit has a slight modification to its fuselage to allow it to operate the plasma field of the Agrissa. Along with the modification it was repainted to match the color scheme from blue to red.
This unit was later abandoned by Ali after he stole the Gundam Throne Zwei.</description>
<picture>27650.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8495" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="4">6.99</rating>
<name>GNW-001 Gundam Throne Eins</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The weapons and capabilities of Throne Eins have a strong resemblance to that of Gundam Dynames. Throne Eins primarily uses rapid firing to engage enemy units. Eins would often fire the GN Rifle for short-to-mid range attacks and firing the GN Launcher for mid-to-long range attacks. While similar to Dynames, a long range tactical mobile suit, the isn`t considered a sniper. Eins most powerful feature is the GN Mega Launcher, it has high GN particle requirement(s). Since Eins doesn`t have unlimited supply of GN particles, Eins is largely dependent to Throne Drei for transferring compressed GN particles for its most devastating attack. Similar to Virtue`s GN Bazooka, the GN Mega Launcher fires high yield destructive beam; the beam is a narrow beam for high precision destruction. While using the GN Mega Launcher, Eins`s GN Rifle is linked with the GN Mega Launcher and Throne Drei, this is an exposed weakness in between charge and firing should the Thrones encounter formidable resistance.</description>
<picture>27651.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8496" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="4">6.99</rating>
<name>GNW-002 Gundam Throne Zwei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Throne Zwei is a melee combat mobile suit that uses its GN Fangs as an offensive guile. When engaging mass amount of units, the GN Fangs would be used to cause distractiong so the Throne Zwei could take advantage of the situation by shooting and/or cutting through enemy suits with its GN Buster Sword. Six GN Fangs are often used and a pair are reserved, but should all of them be destroyed; the pilot is forced into melee combat. While the suit is designed for melee combat (reflective of Micheal`s combat style), its combat potential is dramatically reduced when engaging opponents without its GN Fangs, the same applies for high speed combat.</description>
<picture>27653.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8497" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="8">6.99</rating>
<name>GNW-003 Gundam Throne Drei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Throne Drei`s GN drive disperses red wing-like GN particles similar to green particles emitted by the first Gundam Meister team. Its GN stealth field, which deploys huge pairs of wing GN particles over a wide range, is a powerful ability possessed only by this unit. Its GN shield pod can internally store various missiles, back-up beam sabers and other such equipment that meets tactical needs. Throne Drei is a supplier of GN particles, its able to attach itself to Throne Eins to enhance its beam. Drei can disperse GN particle from its stealth field emitter to defend itself from enemy projectile. It has a customized dock for Neena`s Haro.</description>
<picture>27654.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8502" type="appears in" update="2010-07-06">
<rating votes="2">7.25</rating>
<name>CBS-70 Ptolemaios</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Ptolemaios is the mothership for the Gundams of the Celestial Being. Structurally it has four separate docking bays, each with its own catapult to independently launch GN-001 - GN 005. As its main purpose is for the deployment of the Gundams, the ship itself is not armed.
The Ptolemaios relies on the GN Drives of the Gundams for main power generation. A special connector in each of the docking bays allows the ship to connect to the GN Drive housed within the Gundams to draw power from them. When all four Gundams are launched from the ship, the amount of energy available to the ship is severely limited.
The ship was destroyed by a joint attack of Alejandro`s mobile armor and GN-X`s of the UN Forces.</description>
<picture>27659.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8572" type="appears in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="4">4.99</rating>
<name>Trinity Mothership</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Known only as the mothership to Team Trinity, it is a remote mobile suit space carrier meant for the Throne Meisters to use while on space missions. The ship is later utilized by Wang Liu Mei when she travels in space.</description>
<picture>27773.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8592" type="appears in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="4">2.55</rating>
<name>Jinrui Kakushin Renmei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>he Human Reform League is one of the three major world powers in 2307 AD. Its territories include the Eurasian part of Russia, China, India, some countries of South Asia, the Korean Peninsula,Taiwan, Southeast Asia and Papua New Guinea. They own the orbital elevator off the coast of Australia.</description>
<picture>27807.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8593" type="appears in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="4">3.23</rating>
<name>Sekai Keizai Rengou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The World Economic Union, usually abbreviated as the Union, is one of the three major world powers in 2307 Anno Domini. It is comprised of the nations and states of the North and South American continents, Australia, and Japan. It controls the orbital elevator located in South America.
The Union is the developer of the mobile suit SVMS-01 Union Flag.
The military branch of the Union is known as the MSWAD.</description>
<picture>27808.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8594" type="appears in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="4">3.23</rating>
<name>Shin Europa Kyoudoutai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Advanced European Union ("AEU" for short) is one of the three major world powers in 2307 AD. While in name it`s the European Union, in reality it also controls the African continent, including having military presence there and owning the orbital elevator in Africa.
As of 2307 AD, the AEU`s orbital elevator is still not completed but in operational status. However, it has developed a new type of mobile suit capable of drawing energy from the orbital elevator, starting with the AEU Enact. The new MS technology is part of AEU`s new military expansionism objective.</description>
<picture>27811.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9127" type="appears in" update="2018-10-04">
<rating votes="170">4.75</rating>
<name>Haro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haro is the mechanical mascot of the Gundam science fiction anime metaseries, and is the only character that appears in more than one timeline.
The original Haro is a little robot companion built by the main character Amuro Ray. It is a cute testament to Amuro`s exceptional talent for machines. Haro`s features include a limited range of speech, and the ability to hover (in environments with atmosphere and low gravity) by flapping its ear-like appendage coverings. Haro can usually be found rolling behind Amuro`s next door neighbor Frau Bow. The ability to detect brain waves is also one of Haro`s functions; in one of the episodes, Haro actually claimed that the brain wave of Amuro was lowered/different.
In Zeta Gundam, a mass-produced Mk-II version of Haro ends up in the hands of that series` main protagonist Kamille Bidan, who initially suspects it to be the original. He repairs the robot, only to have it constantly address him as Amuro.
During the events of Char`s Counterattack, Amuro gives a "third-generation" Haro to Hathaway, the son of his captain Bright Noa.
Haro continues to permeate the Gundam franchise, having appeared in Gundam SEED as Lacus Clyne`s multi-colored horde of simple-speech robot pets, built for her by Athrun Zala. These Haros are roughly 1/4 the size of their Universal Century counterparts and are similar in function, however a few possess certain abilities such as unlocking doors. Lacus`s favorite Haro is a pink machine that she refers to as "Pink-Chan" (often translated as "Mr. Pink" or "Pinky"). Another notable Haro in Lacus`s collection is "Navy-Chan", a navy blue robot on which she paints a mustache bearing a distinct resemblance the facial ornament of the ∀ Gundam of the CC (正歴 Seireki) calendar system. The rest of Lacus` Haros have been seen in yellow, orange, blue, green, and black. The parody comic Mobile Suit Gundam SEED Club Yonkoma states that Athrun has built a total of 35 Haros for Lacus.
In Mobile Suit Gundam 00, Celestial Being had produced unknown numbers of Haros as an assistant of daily maintenance works. Currently at least 6 unique Haros have appeared in the animation production. The Haros in the series took much more maintenance and combat role than any other series` counterpart, usually seeing them operating with various machines, including mobile weapons.</description>
<picture>28615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="457" picture="61775.jpg">Ogasawara Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13477" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="3">5.36</rating>
<name>Joyce Moreno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joyce Moreno is the Ptolemaios doctor and longtime friend of fellow crewmate Ian Vashti from before both joined Celestial Being. Fifteen years earlier, he was a member of Doctors without Borders and began referring to himself as "JB Moreno."
He is killed when the Alvatore fires upon the Ptolemaios and destroys the medical bay.</description>
<picture>39617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13478" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="20">5.90</rating>
<name>Regene Regetta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An Innovator who is the genetic twin of Tieria Erde. Although he works closely with Ribbons Almark, the two do not always see eye to eye. As a result, Regene often acts of his own will to complete the plan Aeolia intended, from meeting with Tieria to leaking Veda`s location to Wang Liu Meis.
However, Ribbons was a step ahead of Regene and had Ali Al-Saachez kill him when he attempted to kill Ribbons. However, Regene`s consciousness lived long enough to see Tieria use the codes he gave him in their meeting to lock Ribbons out of Veda.</description>
<picture>39619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26020" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="4">6.99</rating>
<name>GN-001+GNR-001E GN Armor Type-E</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>61437.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26021" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="4">6.99</rating>
<name>GN-002+GNR-001D GN Armor Type-D</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>61438.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26022" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="8">7.93</rating>
<name>GNX-603T GN-X</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>61439.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26023" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="4">3.23</rating>
<name>GNMA-XCVII Alvatore</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>61440.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26024" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="4">6.99</rating>
<name>GNMS-XCVII Alvaaron</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>61441.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26026" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="4">6.99</rating>
<name>AEU-MA07013 Agrissa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>61443.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26027" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="4">4.99</rating>
<name>MSJ-06IIC Tieren High Mobility Type</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>61445.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26028" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="4">4.99</rating>
<name>MSJ-06II-SP Tieren Taozi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>61446.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26029" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="4">7.93</rating>
<name>SVMS-01X Union Flag Custom II [GN Flag]</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>61447.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26144" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="6">5.99</rating>
<name>MSJ-06III-A Tieren All Region Type</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>61547.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="52403" type="appears in" update="2013-01-27">
<name>Allelujah Haptism (Shounen Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="603" picture="223012.jpg">Jou Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52404" type="appears in" update="2013-01-27">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Setsuna F Seiei (Shounen Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11153" picture="188722.jpg">Nishigaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52405" type="appears in" update="2013-01-27">
<name>Laguna Harvey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Laguna Harvey is the president of Linear Train Industries; his company is contracted for operations and maintenance over the orbital elevators. In secret, he`s a member of Celestial Being. He`s one of the few people in the world with influence and the vast resources to provide Celestial Being with resources for their operations without giving attention to the world authorities.
Source: Gundam Wikia</description>
<picture>131408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4742" picture="54426.jpg">Fukumatsu Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="75075" update="2007-06-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2007-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79928" update="2007-10-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission 0</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80218" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2007-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80219" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2007-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81308" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2007-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82476" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソレスタルビーイング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Celestial Being</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celestial Being</title>
<title xml:lang="th">Celestial Beings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Celestial Being</title>
<summary>At a military testing ground near its orbital elevator, the AEU is conducting a demonstration of its new Enact mobile suit. Among the audience are ace pilot Graham Aker and engineer Billy Katagiri of the Union forces.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731933</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="82798" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83123" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83631" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84088" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84109" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガンダムマイスター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gundam Meisters</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gundam Meister</title>
<title xml:lang="th">Gundam Meister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gundam Meister</title>
<summary>As the world reacts with confusion to Celestial Being`s announcement, the Gundam Meisters prepare for a second mission which will clarify their intentions. While Allelujah and Tieria descend from space, Setsuna and Lockon make contact with the Celestial Being agent Wang Liu-Mei, and all four Gundam Meisters then join forces for an armed intervention on the island of Ceylon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731935</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84110" update="2010-11-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84111" update="2010-11-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84322" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変わる世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Changing World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un monde en mutation</title>
<title xml:lang="th">โลกที่เปลี่ยนไป</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaru Sekai</title>
<summary>The Union ace pilot Graham Aker confronts Setsuna as he leaves Ceylon. Graham`s Union Flag mobile suit proves to be no match for Setsuna`s Gundam, but he returns from battle to learn that he and Billy Katagiri have been reassigned to a new anti-Gundam investigative taskforce.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731937</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84323" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対外折衝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">International Negotiation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Diplomatie extérieure</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การเจรจาระดับชาติ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taigai Sesshou</title>
<summary>The Human Reform League holds a memorial service for the soldiers whose lives were lost in the recent interventions, and reaffirms its opposition to Celestial Being. Sergei Smirnov is placed in command of a new team whose mission is to eliminate the Gundams.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731939</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84324" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">限界離脱領域</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape Limit Zone</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Désorbitation imminente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genkai Ridatsu Ryouiki</title>
<summary>Princess Marina leaves Azadistan and begins a worldwide diplomatic tour to seek help for her impoverished nation. Meanwhile, Kinue Crossroad`s younger brother Saji travels into space via the Human Reform League`s orbital elevator for an educational study tour.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731941</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84899" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">セブンソード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seven Swords</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les sept épées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seven Swords</title>
<summary>Celestial Being`s activities have reduced the level of conflict in the world, but there are some who do not welcome this change. Among them is the southern European nation of Moralia, whose economy is based on the arms industry and on private military companies (PMCs).
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731943</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84908" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">報われぬ魂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unrewarded Souls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Consciences tourmentées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukuwareru Tamashii</title>
<summary>During Celestial Being`s intervention in Moralia, Setsuna has been reunited with a figure from his past. His opponent is the mercenary soldier Ali al-Saachez, the same man who once trained Setsuna as a child soldier. Recklessly, Setsuna opens his Gundam`s cockpit to confirm his enemy`s identity.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731945</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="84909" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無差別報復</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Indiscriminate Retaliation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Représailles aveugles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Musabetsu Houfuku</title>
<summary>An international terror network has begun a campaign of bombing attacks in order to force Celestial Being to halt its armed interventions. While Wang Liu-Mei and Celestial Being`s other agents investigate this network, the Ptolemaios crew watch anxiously from the sidelines, and the Gundam Meisters are placed on standby to respond to new attacks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731947</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85161" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大国の威信</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Honor of a Great Power</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le prestige d`une nation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taikoku no Ishin</title>
<summary>Four months have now passed since Celestial Being began its armed interventions. The initial chaos has subsided, and life goes on. Louise Halevy`s mother visits Tokyo to urge her daughter to come home to Spain, Kinue Crossroad continues her investigation of the mysterious Aeolia Schenberg, and United Nations ambassador Alejandro Corner promises to aid Azadistan by connecting it to the solar power network
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731949</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85162" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガンダム鹵獲(ろかく)作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Gundam Capture</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Capturez le Gundam !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gundam Rokaku Sakusen</title>
<summary>In Earth orbit, Sergei`s mobile suit team continues its attack on the Ptolemaios and the Gundam Meisters. While Setsuna and Lockon defend their mothership, Allelujah and Tieria find themselves caught in the enemy`s trap.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731971</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85567" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アレルヤ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Allelujah</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Allelujah</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Allelujah</title>
<summary>In the aftermath of the orbital battle, the Human Reform League`s scientists realize that one of the Gundam Meisters is actually a former test subject of their own Superhuman Institute. Allelujah, meanwhile, has learned that the institute is still in operation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731973</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85568" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">教義の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Limits of Holy Teachings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aux confins de la doctrine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyougi no Hate ni</title>
<summary>Although Princess Marina has secured assistance from the United Nations for her troubled homeland, the Kingdom of Azadistan is still in turmoil. A dispute over the introduction of solar power has brought the country`s conservative and reformist factions to the brink of civil war.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731975</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="85699" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖者の帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return of the Saint</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour du saint</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การกลับมาของนักบุญ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seija no Kikan</title>
<summary>Setsuna`s actions have prevented a coup d`etat in the Kingdom of Azadistan, but the conservative leader Massoud Rachmadi remains missing, and the situation continues to worsen. In order to find out who is behind the crisis, Setsuna visits the site of the solar antenna facility, where he encounters the Union ace pilot Graham Aker.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731977</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86600" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決意の朝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dawn of Determination</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un matin décisif</title>
<title xml:lang="th">รุ่งอรุณแห่งการตัดสินใจ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketsui no Asa</title>
<summary>The three superpower blocs begin planning a massive joint military exercise which will serve as a challenge to Celestial Being. Although they recognize this as an obvious trap, the Gundam Meisters have no choice but to respond with an armed intervention, and the Ptolemaios crew descend to Earth to supervise this dangerous mission.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731979</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86602" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">折れた翼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Broken Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les ailes brisées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oreta Tsubasa</title>
<summary>The Union, Human Reform League, and AEU begin their joint military exercise in the Taklamakan Desert. A nearby uranium storage facility has been left undefended as bait for terrorists, and when Celestial Being intervenes to defend the facility, the combined armies of the three superpower blocs attack the Gundams with overwhelming force.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731981</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86603" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリニティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trinity</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Trinité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trinity</title>
<summary>On the brink of defeat, the Gundam Meisters have been rescued by the intervention of Celestial Being`s second team. Their rescuers identify themselves as Johann, Michael, and Nena Trinity, the Meisters of the mysterious Gundam Thrones.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731983</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86604" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スローネ強襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assault of the Thrones</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`attaque des Throne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Throne Kyoushuu</title>
<summary>The Ptolemaios crew return to space for a rendezvous with Team Trinity. When they finally meet the new Gundam Meisters face to face, Setsuna and his comrades are disturbed by their attitude and behavior.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731985</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86605" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪意の矛先</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Aim of Evil Intents</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trident maléfique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akui no Hokosaki</title>
<summary>Team Trinity continues its campaign of armed intervention. Unlike Setsuna and his comrades, they are targeting military facilities of all kinds and exterminating everyone on the scene, even civilians.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731987</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="86640" update="2010-11-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86641" update="2010-11-06">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87838" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonds</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Liens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizuna</title>
<summary>Having determined that Team Trinity itself is promoting conflict, Setsuna confronts the Gundam Thrones. Tieria comes to his assistance, and the two Gundam Meisters fight as a team for the first time.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731989</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="87839" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変革の刃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blade of Reformation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épée du changement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henkaku no Yaiba</title>
<summary>A mysterious benefactor has provided the three superpower blocs with a new weapon against the Gundams. Quickly establishing a military alliance, the superpowers organize an elite fighting force under the aegis of the United Nations.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731991</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="88397" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">滅びの道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Path of Destruction</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La voie de la destruction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Horobi no Michi</title>
<summary>The United Nations forces have deployed their new weapon, a mobile suit model known as the GN-X which is powered by a pseudo solar reactor. While Sergei Smirnov and Soma Peries lead a GN-X team in pursuit of the Gundam Thrones, another force made up of Union and AEU pilots attacks the Ptolemaios in space.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731993</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="88403" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="18">9.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トランザム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TRANS-AM</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Trans-Am</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trans-Am</title>
<summary>The United Nations reveals the existence of the GN-X to the world, and announces the launch of a Gundam elimination operation with the code name "Fallen Angels." The operation begins with the renewed pursuit of Team Trinity, who have been forced to abandon their supply base and can now only flee before the enemy`s superior numbers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731995</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="88404" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="22">9.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界を止めて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stop the World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Seuls contre tous</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai o Tomete</title>
<summary>Alejandro Corner and Ribbons Almark have forced their way into the heart of Veda and taken control of Celestial Being`s master computer. But their actions have triggered an unexpected programmed response.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731997</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="88405" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="15">9.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりなき詩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Poem</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le poème sans fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owari naki Uta</title>
<summary>Despite the loss of Lockon, the Ptolemaios crew are united in their determination to keep fighting the United Nations forces. The enemy begins another assault, this time spearheaded by the Alvatore, a giant mobile armor operated by the traitor Alejandro Corner.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731999</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="88406" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="15">9.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">刹那</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Setsuna</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Setsuna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Setsuna</title>
<summary>The Celestial Being mothership Ptolemaios has been destroyed, and most of the Gundams are damaged beyond repair. Yet Setsuna continues his desperate fight against the overwhelming power of Alejandro Corner`s mobile armor and the final weapon hidden within it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>732001</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-00</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212679" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212680" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212681" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212682" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission 4</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
