<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="526" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-01-07</startdate>
<enddate>1998-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bannou Bunka Nekomusume (1998)</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Универсальная современная девушка-кошка</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Cat Girl Nuku Nuku TV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Nuku Nuku</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">万能文化猫娘 (1998)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">All Purpose Cultural Cat Girl Nuku Nuku TV</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">TV נוקו נוקו</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="610" type="Alternative Setting">Bannou Bunka Nekomusume Dash!</anime>
<anime id="167" type="Alternative Setting">Bannou Bunka Nekomusume</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="109" approval="7" total="9">Mahoromatic: Automatic Maiden</anime>
<anime id="12" approval="4" total="10">Chobits</anime>
<anime id="88" approval="4" total="4">Koutetsu Tenshi Kurumi</anime>
<anime id="177" approval="1" total="4">VanDread</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/tv_series/w032.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="778" type="Animation Work">Ashi Productions</name>
<name id="802" type="Unknown Relation">Movic</name>
<name id="1519" type="Series Composition">Yamaguchi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="872" type="Original Work">Takada Yuuzou</name>
<name id="4253" type="Character Design">Kishimoto Seiji</name>
<name id="4372" type="Direction">Fujimoto Yoshitaka</name>
<name id="12514" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kishimoto Seiji</name>
</creators>
<description>After starting out in a new school and meeting her rather zany classmates, http://anidb.net/ch9614 [Nuku Nuku] is forced into fighting the dangerous robots of the Mishima corporation`s inner circle, led by the evil mastermind, Hell Mishima. Their plan? To take over the world, of course!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="412">3.83</permanent>
<temporary count="416">6.27</temporary>
<review count="1">7.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>11169.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>557</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3232</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>375</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38</identifier>
<identifier>xfippy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/tv_series/w032.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>All_Purpose_Cultural_Cat_Girl_Nuku_Nuku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>万能文化猫娘</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>236</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>125541</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1393" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-08">
<name>drill</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2665" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>school sports festival</name>
<description>To show off the students in sports clothing — in ecchi anime the female students in particular — a sports festival (or athletic meet) is quite popular in your typical anime with school setting. Here the protagonists can show their skills in diverse athletic competitions.
Note: This festival may also, though very rarely, take place at a kindergarten or preschool.</description>
<picurl>161025.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2873" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>Valentine`s Day</name>
<description>Valentine`s Day is a festive day celebrated every February 14.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China, Valentine`s Day is one month before http://anidb.net/t3147 [White Day], a celebration unique to those countries.
In the rest of the world:
On Valentine`s Day, both males and females will express their feelings of affection towards their loved ones, by exchanging gifts (such as cards, candies, and chocolates), going on dates, and other signs and actions of affection. Some people also take the opportunity to confess and propose for marriage. In Western countries, it is generally expected of the male to offer gifts to the significant other.
In many countries, friends and co-workers also exchange small gifts to show their friendship towards each other.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China:
On Valentine`s Day, many women feel obliged to give chocolates to all male co-workers, except when the day falls on a Sunday, a holiday. This is known as giri choco (義理チョコ, "obligation chocolate"), with unpopular co-workers receiving only chougiri choco (超義理チョコ, "ultra-obligatory chocolate") cheap chocolate.
This contrasts with honmei choco (本命チョコ, "love chocolate"), chocolate given to a loved one.
Friends, especially girls, may exchange chocolate referred to as tomo choco (友チョコ, "friend chocolate").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>160891.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2886" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>New Year`s Day</name>
<description>It is tradition in Japan to celebrate the new year at a Shinto shrine (hatsumode). The protagonists will offer some money, ring a bell at the end of a thick rope, and then pray for good fortune.
This usually goes along with gorging yourself at the many temporary food stalls, playing various games, and drawing a fortune.
The female characters in the anime will usually dress up in a kimono, to show off their traditional Japanese clothing, while watching the fireworks.</description>
<picurl>161028.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2909" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>karaoke</name>
<description>Obligatory national pastime for students in any anime with school setting. Amateur singing to subtitled music videos.
The word itself is a compound of the Japanese words for "empty orchestra".</description>
<picurl>160894.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>creepy laugh</name>
<description>At least one character in the show inexplicably and repetitively seems to have the urgent need to laugh in a creepy, loud and usually very annoying way.
For male bad guys this seems to be a must, but some of the uppity (rich) female characters use the laugh as part of their condescending attitude as well.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5988" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>living with the villain</name>
<description>Both, hero and villain have their secret identities. They live next door, go to the same school, work at the same place or even are best friends. But little do they know that in another part of their life they are the worst enemies. And yet they just do not recognize each other when they are out of their costumes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9614" type="main character in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="18">8.57</rating>
<name>Nuku Nuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nuku Nuku is a biotech-type android of sorts with the brain (or nervous system as some sources claim) of a cat inserted inside. Nuku Nuku was originally a cat until an incident (differs depending on each series) caused her brain to be transferred into the body of a war robot built by Mishima Industries.
Nuku Nuku lives with Akiko, Kyuusaku and their son, Ryuunosuke, who she considers her family.</description>
<picture>29293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5790" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌクと龍之介! とってもワニな夜だった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku and Ryunosuke - It was a very alligator day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku to Ryuunosuke! Tottemo Wani na Yoru Datta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5791" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌク感動! 二葉ちゃんの初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku is excited - Futaba is excited</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku Kandou! Futaba-chan no Hatsukoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5792" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌク熱唱! 家族対抗歌合戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku`s hot song - Family singing contest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku Nesshou! Kazoku Taikou Utagassen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5793" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌクの料理教室! ノンちゃんラブアタック作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku`s cooking class - Non`s love attack plan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku no Ryouri Kyoushitsu! Non-chan Love Attack Sakusen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5794" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌク対古代遺跡! 伝説の巨神あらわる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku vs. the ancient relic! The legendary giant awakens!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku Kodai Iseki! Densetsu no Kyokan Arawaru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5795" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌク登場! 地球の平和を守り抜け!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku appears! Protect the Earth`s Peace!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku Toujou! Chikyuu no Heiwa o Mamorinuke!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5796" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋するヌクヌク! バレンタインは誰んためン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku Falls in Love! Who`s the Valentine for?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi Suru Nuku Nuku! Valentine wa Dare no Tame ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5797" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌク走る! 大運動会, ああそうかい!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku runs - The Big Field day, oh I get it</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku Hashiru! Dai Undoukai, Aa Sou kai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5798" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌク放浪!? あけまして捨てられました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku Abandoned? Happy New Year, I`ve been thrown out</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku Hourou!? Akemashite Suteraremashita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5799" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌクと宇宙の神秘!謎の生命体ミチミチとの遭遇!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku and the mystics of the universe - The meeting with the mysterious alien Michi Michi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku to Uchuu no Shinpi! Nazo no Seimeitai Michi Michi to no Souguu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5800" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌクよ永遠に! 君の笑顔を忘れない!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku lives on - We won`t forget your smile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku yo Eien ni! Kimi no Egao o Wasurenai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5801" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌク時をこえて! プロポーズは盆踊り!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku passes time - Proposal at the bon dance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku Toki o Koete! Propose wa Bon`odori!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5802" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌク青春日記! 万能文化ミュージカル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku Blue Spring of Youth Diaries - All Purpose Cultural Musical</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku Seishun Nikki! Bannou Bunka Musical!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5803" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌクヌク真夏のバトル! エスパー少女隊の罠!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuku Nuku summer`s battle - A trap by esper girls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuku Nuku Manatsu no Battle! ESPer Shoujo-tai no Wana!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
