<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5264" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>1988-05-25</startdate>
<enddate>1988-11-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Abe George Kattobi Seishun Ki: Shibuya Honky Tonk</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">安部譲二かっとび青春記 渋谷ホンキィトンク</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="5678" type="Direction">Ochiai Masamune</name>
<name id="14778" type="Original Work">Abe George</name>
<name id="54196" type="Original Work">Tanaka Masahito</name>
</creators>
<description>This story is based on one of the famous Japanese writers "George Abe"`s troubled boyhood. Although he was born in wealthy family, he starts keeping company with yakuza...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="12">3.52</permanent>
<temporary count="12">4.58</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>12549.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7443</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17501</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2803</identifier>
<identifier>azdhce</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235606</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2436</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="105939" update="2009-08-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1988-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「極道経済学入門」編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Gokudou Keizaigaku Nyuumon" Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105940" update="2010-10-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1988-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「直也帰国第一戦」編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Naoya Kikoku Daiissen" Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105941" update="2010-10-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1988-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「英国留学・脱線」編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Eikoku Ryuugaku, Dassen" Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105942" update="2009-08-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1988-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「青春極道志願」編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Seishun Gokudou Shigan" Hen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
