<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="530" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1972-12-17</startdate>
<enddate>1972-12-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Panda Kopanda</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Adventure of Panda and Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Panda! Go, Panda!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">パンダコパンダ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Panda! Go Panda!</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Die Abenteuer des kleinen Panda (Teil 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Panda Petit Panda</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Панда большая и маленькая</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Suur panda ja väike panda</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6976" type="Sequel">Panda Kopanda: Amefuri Circus no Maki</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/library/old/movie/data/m_panda1.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="8476" type="Music">Satou Masahiko</name>
<name id="782" type="Work">Tokyo Movie</name>
<name id="40" type="Original Plan">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
<name id="43" type="Direction">Takahata Isao</name>
</creators>
<description>Panda Kopanda (Panda! Go Panda!) is a 30 minute movie made in 1972. Miyazaki created the original idea, the script, the layouts, and did key animation, and Takahata directed the film. The story is about a little girl, Mimiko, who was left alone while her Grandma was away. A 1973 sequel, http://anidb.net/a6976 [Panda Kopanda: Amefuri Saakasu no Maki] (Panda! Go Panda! &amp; the Rainy-day Circus), continues the story and was made by the same people who made the first movie.
Source: nausicaa.net/wiki/Panda!_Go_Panda!
Note: The literal translation of the title Panda Kopanda is "Panda, Baby Panda", but it`s been released in North America as Panda Go Panda.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="403">5.75</permanent>
<temporary count="405">6.67</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>36251.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2611</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2379</identifier>
<identifier>stbesx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/library/old/movie/data/m_panda1.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>パンダコパンダ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>144198</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m052</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=rnIDK-Jy27o</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="102930" type="main character in" update="2019-05-24">
<name>Mimiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2890" picture="23182.jpg">Sugiyama Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102931" type="main character in" update="2019-05-24">
<name>Papanda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3386" picture="24413.jpg">Kumakura Kazuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102938" type="main character in" update="2019-05-25">
<name>Pan-chan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1828" picture="20727.jpg">Oota Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102950" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-27">
<name>Omawari-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4652" picture="27089.jpg">Yamada Yasuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102958" type="appears in" update="2019-05-28">
<name>Obaa-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20566" picture="206821.jpg">Senou Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102975" type="appears in" update="2019-05-28">
<name>Sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5292" picture="2352.gif">Mine Eken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102989" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-29">
<name>Doubutsuen no Enchou-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32742" picture="233949.jpg">Wada Ayao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103015" type="appears in" update="2019-05-29">
<name>Nana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7641" picture="32436.jpg">Maruyama Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103016" type="appears in" update="2019-05-29">
<name>Kayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21067" picture="54630.jpg">Matsukane Yoneko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103058" type="appears in" update="2019-05-30">
<name>Zakkaya no Ojisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3344" picture="2056.gif">Kaji Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103061" type="appears in" update="2019-05-30">
<name>Ijimekko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3227" picture="24207.jpg">Ichikawa Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103063" type="appears in" update="2019-05-30">
<name>Dai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40229">Yamaoka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103064" type="appears in" update="2019-05-30">
<name>Yaoya no Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234044.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5822" update="2009-09-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1972-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208210" update="2018-09-19">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>72</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Panda Kopanda Storyboard</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
