<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5310" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-08-02</startdate>
<enddate>2008-08-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sky Crawlers</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Небесные Скитальцы</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">زاحفين السماء</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Sukai kurora</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スカイ・クロラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Sky Crawlers</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">The Sky Crawlers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Sky Crawlers: L`armée du ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">The Sky Crawlers - I Cavalieri del Cielo</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">The Sky Crawlers: Eternamente</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Nebeští jezdci</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Égenjárók</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Padangių Klajokliai</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Sky Crawlers</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Los Exploradores del Cielo</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7478" approval="17" total="31">Toaru Hikuushi e no Tsuioku</anime>
<anime id="581" approval="10" total="23">Last Exile</anime>
<anime id="83" approval="7" total="16">Jin-Rou</anime>
<anime id="111" approval="7" total="10">Sentou Yousei Yukikaze</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="14">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="75610">GOOD MOVIE AND WORTH WATCHING, PG-13 and up! not for robot or bunny girl fans though!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="548153">Intriguing movie with very good graphic and few action scenes.
Very interesting, serious drama with some psychologic feel to it. Definitely worth to see!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="178310">Another Masterpiece from Oshii :) Excellent music ane awesome sound !!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="148212">The best movie i`ve seen for a while.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Good CG`s and I like the music.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="764835">Animation is spectacular, would have given it a 10/10 if they did a better job explaining things, one of those anime`s you`ll probably watch a couple times to really understand everything.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="421413">Aerial battles alone were worth watching, altough there are only few, but those alongside with sad story and deep thought combined with music from Kenji Kawai created really unique piece which you should not miss.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="616601">Great work by Mamoru Oshii. I have no words. Spend your time and watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="152796">Great at first watch, even better the second time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="114421">Probably the best Oshii film so far.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://sky.crawlers.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="131" type="Direction">Oshii Mamoru</name>
<name id="3051" type="Character Design">Nishio Tetsuya</name>
<name id="1689" type="Original Work">Mori Hiroshi</name>
<name id="721" type="Work">Production I.G</name>
</creators>
<description>After experiencing several major wars, people have finally obtained peace. However, they are unable to appreciate peace without contemplating war and death from a safe distance. Therefore, they make a show business out of war. In this staged war, those who must fight each other are children called "Killdre". They remain forever young until they die in the sky.
Kannami Yuichi is stationed at Uris, a frontline base in Europe. He has no memories of the past prior to arriving there, but he knows he is a Killdre, and knows how to operate a fighter.
Yuichi`s ability is soon acknowledged and he becomes an ace pilot. Then, he meets a girl, Kusanagi Suito, a commander of the base, who is also a Killdre and used to be an ace pilot as well. Although they are meeting for the first time, they feel as if they had known each other for a long time and soon they become close. However, one day, she asks him a surprising thing: "Can you kill me? Otherwise, we cannot escape from all this."</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2289">6.23</permanent>
<temporary count="2302">7.30</temporary>
<review count="10">6.37</review>
</ratings>
<picture>133579.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8269</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3089</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4068</identifier>
<identifier>xwvwvo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/sky-crawlers/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://sky.crawlers.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Sky_Crawlers_(film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スカイ・クロラシリーズ#.E6.98.A0.E7.94.BB</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1712</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>328359</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9199</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-16">
<name>smoker</name>
<description>This character likes to smoke cigarettes, cigars or a pipe.</description>
<picurl>227708.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3421" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-03">
<name>aviation</name>
<description>"These magnificant men in their flying machines"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3974" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>star-crossed lovers</name>
<description>Two lovers — usually teenagers — destined to be kept apart no matter how hard they struggle to be together. It may be fate or just feuding families, or even something as mundane as a few hundred miles, but something will always be in their way. Often, the two can only be together in death. The phrase is astrological in origin, stemming from the belief that the positions of the stars ruled over people`s fates. To describe a relationship as "star-crossed" is to say that it is "thwarted by a malign star", or that the stars are working against the relationship. Shakespeare`s Romeo and Juliet is the most famous example of this archetype but it dates back at least as far as the ancient Greeks.
"From forth the fatal loins of these two foes, / a pair of star-cross`d lovers, take their life."
- Romeo and Juliet, prologue</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="40038" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-24">
<name>Naofumi Tokino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29880" picture="78922.jpg">Tanihara Shousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80403" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-24">
<name>Fuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4897" picture="67088.jpg">Andou Mabuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80404" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-24">
<name>Mitsuya Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23356" picture="63011.jpg">Kuriyama Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80405" type="main character in" update="2016-08-24">
<name>Kannami Yuuhichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44958" picture="10349.jpeg">Kase Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80406" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-24">
<name>Yudagawa Aizu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80407" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-24">
<name>Sasakura Towa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80408" type="appears in" update="2016-08-24">
<name>Shinoda Uroyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2233" picture="21784.jpg">Takewaka Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80409" type="main character in" update="2016-08-24">
<name>Kusanagi Suito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40610" picture="159217.jpg">Kikuchi Rinko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80410" type="appears in" update="2016-08-24">
<name>Kusanagi Mizuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8935" picture="239412.jpg">Yamaguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="89882" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (30 sec.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89883" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (60 sec.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90395" update="2008-04-28">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (134 sec.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91791" update="2008-07-05">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (5 min.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95663" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>125</length>
<airdate>2008-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95897" update="2009-02-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2008-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">映画監督 押井守のメッセージ ~新作密着ドキュメント~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Documentary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eiga Kantoku Oshii Mamoru no Message: Shinsaku Micchaku Document</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97448" update="2009-03-18">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2007-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメギガ スペシャル とことん! 押井守 「押井監督 新作「スカイ・クロラ The Sky Crawlers」を語る」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sky Crawlers Interview</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime Giga Special Tokoton! Oshii Shu (Oshii Kantoku Shinsaku (The Sky Crawlers) o Kataru)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102065" update="2009-05-09">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making Of</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111268" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="6">O4</epno>
<length>35</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Sound Design and Animation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111269" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="6">O3</epno>
<length>35</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Animation Research</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
