<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5314" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-10-08</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Juushin Enbu: Hero Tales</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Jyushin Enbu: Hero Tales</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">兽神演武</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hero tales</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">獣神演武 - HERO TALES -</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hero Tales</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">التحدي الكبير</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6284" approval="3" total="7">Sengoku Basara</anime>
<anime id="239" approval="1" total="7">Naruto</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.jyushin.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="968" type="Animation Work">Studio Flag</name>
<name id="1130" type="Financial Production">Square Enix</name>
<name id="1007" type="Character Design">Arakawa Hiromu</name>
<name id="683" type="Series Composition">Sekijima Mayori</name>
<name id="1868" type="Direction">Sekita Osamu</name>
<name id="5754" type="Music">Terashima Tamiya</name>
<name id="9247" type="Chief Animation Direction">Aisaka Naoki</name>
</creators>
<description>Set in a time of chaos, seven heroes of the Stars, the Hokushintenkun, rise up to lead the people. Two of the seven, the Nitenshinson, the Hagun and the Tonrou, are never supposed to exist at the same time, but fate has decided otherwise. Taito, chosen as the Hagun, now must rise up to defeat the Tonrou, as the fate of the Stars destined it to be.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="741">4.31</permanent>
<temporary count="761">6.79</temporary>
<review count="1">3.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>12661.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8281</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2772</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4067</identifier>
<identifier>ruodqq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jyushin.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hero_Tales</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>獣神演武_-HERO_TALES-#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>328672</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9204</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4149" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>non-blood-related siblings -- DO NOT USE -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be deleted. Please add char-char relations of the "is family of" type with the http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Content:Characters#is_family_of [appropriate relation comment] to the relevant characters and remove the tag from the corresponding anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="81255" update="2007-08-14">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82487" update="2007-12-30">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82990" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">破軍吼ゆる刻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alkaid Roars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hagun Kouyuru Koku</title>
<summary>When their village temple is burned to the ground by cutthroat invaders, siblings Taito and Laila are thrust into the middle of a celestial struggle to obtain the power of a sacred sword.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="82991" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">武曲の宿業(さだめ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Karma of Mizar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takeshi Kyoku no Shukugou (Sadame)</title>
<summary>Tales of a destiny written in the stars are overshadowed by Taito’s ferocious desire for a rematch with Keiro. While the young warrior plots his quest for vengeance, Ryuko tries to teach him to control his newfound power.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="82992" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">操気の契り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pledge of Energy Manipulation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misaoki no Chigiri</title>
<summary>Taito’s training with Ryuko continues as the travelers stop for rest in a town where a torrential downpour turns an outlawed religious symbol into a harbinger of death.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="82993" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">五神闘士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Divine Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gotentoushi</title>
<summary>Laila gains an admirer when the heroic travelers fight to bring order to a town ruled by villains. This mysterious newcomer is deadly with a bow and arrow, but he fights on the wrong side of destiny.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84356" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">病みし帝国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ailing Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yamishi Teikoku</title>
<summary>Keiro appears to be plotting against the empire, and the traveling heroes tangle with bandits on behalf of some starving orphans. During the unexpected skirmish, Taito learns the value of teamwork.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85058" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅き英傑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Champion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akaki Eiketsu</title>
<summary>Hosei feels ignored when his master takes a special interest in training Taito, so the young archer picks a fight with a gang of bandits who refuse to die - no matter how many times he kills them!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85059" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しみの禄存</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sorrowful Phecda</title>
<summary>Hosei’s rash behavior causes his master to become an undead servant of evil. With his new friends’ lives on the line, will he be able to obey her chilling final order?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85364" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">北辰紀記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tale of the Big Dipper</title>
<summary>Lord Keiro continues his march of destruction across the peaceful countryside. Meanwhile, Taito grows increasingly stronger, and Ryuko agonizes over his destiny.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85365" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤独なる皇帝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lonely Emperor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodokunaru Koutei</title>
<summary>Spurred by delusions of grandeur, Taito infiltrates the royal palace, determined to teach the emperor how to run a country - or claim the throne for himself!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85366" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帝都にさす影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadow on the Imperial Capital</title>
<summary>Upon reaching the capital, Taito is eager to seek revenge for his fallen comrades. Ryuko fails to convince the young Alkaid that he cannot defeat Keiro, but perhaps a pretty girl will have better luck.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85367" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渓谷に木霊するは...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Echoes in the Gorge</title>
<summary>Sensing Hosei’s pain over the loss of his master, the heroes embark on a mission to lift his spirits. While Taito and Ryuko try their luck as hunters, Laila collects mushrooms in an attempt to conjure up something edible.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85678" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月下の煌き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Glimmer in the Moonlight</title>
<summary>Ryuko seeks the council of his elders as he struggles to determine his role in the prophesized battle, and Chouka makes an aggressive attempt to eliminate Taito.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86528" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二天神尊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Celestial Deities</title>
<summary>When Taito and Keiro meet again on the field of battle, Ryuko must decide whether he will fight alongside his friend - or his father!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86735" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">貪狼神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dubhe God</title>
<summary>Having fallen under the control of his father’s rapidly-expanding influence, Ryuko is powerless to stop his own body from launching a murderous attack against Taito.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86736" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走せし宿業</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Karma Out of Control</title>
<summary>When Ryuko objects to his father’s use of zombie foot soldiers to slaughter innocent citizens, he ends up behind bars. On the other side of the empire, Taito rallies his fellow heroes for one final battle!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86737" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Clash</title>
<summary>Taito’s encounter with Lord Keiro proves that the young Alkaid has grown in power since their first meeting. In the aftermath of their clash, Keiro displays the true depths of his depravity.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86738" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">帝都錯綜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Imperial Capital in Confusion</title>
<summary>The empire undergoes frightening changes after Keiro stakes his claim to the throne. When the former emperor is imprisoned, Taito and company must act quickly to save him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86739" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲憤の白衣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Commoner Infuriated</title>
<summary>Shimei lures Taito into the clutches of Lord Keiro. The Alkaid is ready for a fight, but his counterpart is unwilling, instead choosing to reveal the secrets of his own dark past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86740" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">動乱の幕開け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Turmoil Begins</title>
<summary>Kyo proposes a daring - and deadly - plan to overthrow Keiro, and Rinmei is shocked to learn the full extent of Ryuko’s heartless betrayal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86741" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わかたれし星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stars Divided</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakatareshi Hoshi</title>
<summary>Lord Keiro gains even more power after his daughter’s marriage to the Emperor is made official. Elsewhere, Taito and company cross paths with an old friend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86742" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">蓮通寺炎上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lian Tong Temple Ablaze</title>
<summary>After setting fire to Taito’s city, Chouka’s ninjas take a wise man hostage, but the true threat is a powerful, all-seeing demon who’s out to harm someone close to the Alkaid.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86743" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父子の絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Father-Son Bond</title>
<summary>Upon their triumphant homecoming, Taito and his new friends dazzle the crowd with a martial arts exhibition. Later, the young Alkaid learns the truth about his ancestry.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86744" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天(あま)食む貪狼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dubhe, Devourer of the Heavens</title>
<summary>A festival celebrating the emperor’s engagement is marred by an unexpected eclipse, and Taito continues his mission to restore peace to the empire - one fight at a time!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86745" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">破軍の道標</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alkaid`s Guidepost</title>
<summary>Koyo sends Taito into the forest to rediscover his missing star power, but the mission takes a dire turn when Laila wanders away from camp in search of her brother.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86746" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闘牙回頭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dou Ya Changes Course</title>
<summary>Devastated by the loss of Ryuko, Taito angrily rejects his cosmic destiny. When the young warrior becomes insufferable, Koyo teaches him a painful lesson in humility.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="89079" update="2017-09-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">演武の果て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of the Tale</title>
<summary>Lord Keiro’s grotesque appetite for power turned him into a bloodthirsty monster. Only Taito can stop him, but he’ll need to draw strength from his friends to survive the final showdown!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
