<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5352" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-12-22</startdate>
<enddate>2007-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Bleach: The DiamondDust Rebellion Mou Hitotsu no Hyourinmaru</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">BLEACH The DiamondDust Rebellion Another Hyourinmaru</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">BLEACH The Movie: The DiamondDust Rebellion Another Hyourinmaru</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Белина: Бунтът на диамантения пясък</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Bleach Movie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 BLEACH The DiamondDust Rebellion もう一つの氷輪丸</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bleach the Movie 2: The Diamond Dust Rebellion</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Bleach the diamondDust rebellion</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Bleach - A Gyémántpor lázadás</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2369" type="Parent Story">Bleach</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372636">Best of the two first Bleachmovies in my opinion. A clear story that moves on in a steady pace, nice to focus on Hitsugaya(fanservice no doubt but whatev). Must see for any fan of the series.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/bleach/2007/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
<name id="979" type="Original Work">Kubo Taito</name>
<name id="4566" type="Direction">Abe Noriyuki</name>
<name id="5806" type="Character Design">Kudou Masashi</name>
</creators>
<description>When an artifact known as the "King`s Seal" is stolen during transport from Soul Society, http://anidb.net/ch8354 [Hitsugaya Toushirou] is assigned to retrieve it. Toushirou goes missing after a battle with the thieves, leading Seireitei to suspect him of treachery. They order his immediate capture and execution. Unwilling to believe him capable of such a crime, Ichigo, Rangiku, Rukia, and Renji set out to find Toushirou and clear his name. Meanwhile, Toushirou is still searching for the thieves, and stumbles upon a dark secret involving a shinigami long since dead.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3552">5.38</permanent>
<temporary count="3593">7.17</temporary>
<review count="2">5.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>226373.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8369</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2889</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4125</identifier>
<identifier>cnglrv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/bleach/2007/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Bleach:_The_DiamondDust_Rebellion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版BLEACH_The_DiamondDust_Rebellion_もう一つの氷輪丸</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>491</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>328679</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9294</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2069" type="main character in" update="2013-05-11">
<rating votes="1320">6.46</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Ichigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurosaki Ichigo was raised by his father together with his two sisters after the traumatic experience of losing his mother. One day, minding his own business, he meets Rukia, the Shinigami, who needs his help. While protecting his family they find out about his supernatural abilities and thus a still-living - substitute - Shinigami is born....</description>
<picture>136529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3720" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-23">
<rating votes="577">6.24</rating>
<name>Kuchiki Rukia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sarcastic Soul Reaper who is assigned hollow extermination duties in Ichigo`s hometown. Though her physical appearance is that of a teenage girl, in reality she is around 150 years old. At the opening of the story, Rukia is forced to transfer her powers to Ichigo and assume a temporary lifestyle as a regular human. She registers at the local high school and takes up residence in Ichigo`s closet, while teaching him how to be a substitute Soul Reaper in her place.</description>
<picture>19580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3721" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-15">
<rating votes="312">5.10</rating>
<name>Inoue Orihime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A long-time classmate of Ichigo, linked to him by mutual friend Tatsuki Arisawa. She is effectively an orphan, as when she was 3, her older brother Sora left their abusive parents` home with Orihime and raised her on his own, later on, when Orihime was in middle school he died in a car accident. Though initially devoid of spiritual powers, she develops spiritual awareness early in the plot and later obtains one of the strongest powers in the Bleach universe.
Which is practically a power of the gods: being able to literally reject happened things and making them undone.</description>
<picture>19581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3722" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-23">
<rating votes="121">4.66</rating>
<name>Sado Yasutora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Better known as Chad, is one of Ichigo`s friends at school. He is a biracial Japanese/Mexican student who towers over his classmates. Despite his imposing appearance he is quite meek, and refuses to fight unless it is for the sake of another. Chad does not have awareness of ghosts at first, but this changes when he witnesses a group of children being attacked by a hollow. He discovers a unique ability that strengthens and armours his right arm, enabling him to fight hollows.</description>
<picture>19582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3723" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-23">
<rating votes="135">5.02</rating>
<name>Ishida Uryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Quincy, descendant of a line of priest-like hollow-hunting archers who were historical enemies of the Soul Reapers. He bears a deep grudge against all Soul Reapers, including Ichigo, and is an early antagonist in the series.</description>
<picture>19583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3725" type="appears in" update="2009-02-23">
<rating votes="86">6.75</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Isshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The father of the Kurosaki family. He is initially portrayed as a silly, fight-loving father who takes a keen interest in what his children are doing. He shows them affection either offensively or with an all-too-happy tone, which elicits comical reactions from his kids, usually in the form of a kick.</description>
<picture>19585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7197" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="237">8.02</rating>
<name>Kyouraku Shunsui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyouraku is a laid back and flamboyant man, evident in his style of dress and general attitude and he is rarely seen without a smile on his lips. He wears a straw hat and a shoulder drapped pink flowered haori over his captain`s uniform, that is rose pink on the inside, and he has a thin lined facial hair around his mouth and on his cheeks and chin. Although his haori and obi sash are cheap, his pinwheel hairpins are very expensive.</description>
<picture>54975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7623" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="652">8.93</rating>
<name>Zaraki Kenpachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zaraki Kenpachi is the wild and bloodthirsty captain of soul society`s Eleventh Squad. He cares little for the politics of soul society or its fate, but is happy as long as he gets to fight. He is a tall muscular shinigami with an enormous amount of spiritual energy. Though he is a monster in battle and attacks his foe relentlessly, he often purposely holds back in fights in order to prolong his enjoyment. Kenpachi`s zanpakutou has no name and no apparent abilities; it is also incredibly worn and battered from its long battle history.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>54847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7629" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="461">7.66</rating>
<name>Kuchiki Byakuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuchiki Byakuya is the 28th head of the noble Kuchiki clan, one of the four great noble families in Soul Society. As such, Byakuya acts in an aristocratic manner — he seems always serene and apathetic towards other people, even when he is actually deeply conflicted. He is also extremely calm, even in battle, and is very seldom surprised by even the most drastic of actions. Ironically, when he was younger, he was quick to anger and very hotheaded, as noted by his grandfather, http://anidb.net/ch9327 [Kuchiki Ginrei]; similar to the the way http://anidb.net/ch2069 [Ichigo] and http://anidb.net/ch8722 [Renji] are now.
Byakuya strongly believes in law and order. As the head of one of the great noble families and as a captain in the http://anidb.net/ch9291 [Gotei 13], he always works hard for a peaceful society. He thinks that if someone in his position doesn`t follow the rules as a good example, then no one will follow them. He believes that to maintain the order, all law-breakers must be punished, even if that goes against his own wishes. Despite his icy and regal manner, Byakuya cares for and protects those important to him, even referring to http://anidb.net/ch3720 [Rukia] as his "pride".
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picture>54978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7799" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="297">8.73</rating>
<name>Urahara Kisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urahara Kisuke is the owner of the http://anidb.net/ch9439 [Urahara Shop], specialising in shinigami merchandise.</description>
<picture>54819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8354" type="main character in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="413">7.52</rating>
<name>Hitsugaya Toushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hitsugaya Toushirou is the captain of the 10th division. He is also the youngest captain. His zanpakutou is called Hyourinmaru, an ice dragon. His bankai is called Daiguren Hyourinmaru.</description>
<picture>54897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8722" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="251">5.05</rating>
<name>Abarai Renji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Abarai Renji is the rough and ready vice captain of the sixth squad. He is already strong, but aims to improve even further in order to surpass his captain, http://anidb.net/ch7629 [Kuchiki Byakuya]. He is particularly weak at using kidou in battle, but he makes up for it in pure determination. He is a bit dense at times but he has a good heart and wants to protect his friends, especially http://anidb.net/ch3720 [Rukia], who is his childhood friend. His zanpakutou is http://anidb.net/ch10815 [Zabimaru], a wild animal-type katana.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>54893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9290" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="120">6.19</rating>
<name>Komamura Sajin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Komamura Sajin is the captain of the seventh squad. He is unique amongst the other captains, as he is the only one who is part animal. Despite his stern, canine-like appearance, Komamura is a kind soul with an incredible sense of justice. He has a strong moral code and is fiercely loyal, particularly towards http://anidb.net/ch9307 [Genryuusai Yamamoto] whom he holds in high regard after he allowed him into the thirteen protection squads. His zanpakutou is named http://anidb.net/ch10810 [Tenken].
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>54976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9291" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="1">5.88</rating>
<name>Gotei Juusan Tai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The 13 Protection Squads.</description>
<picture>29262.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9307" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="147">7.57</rating>
<name>Yamamoto-Genryuusai Shigekuni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamamoto-Genryuusai Shigekuni is the captain commander of the thirteen protection squadrons and leader of the first company. Though he may appear to be little more than a frail elderly man, Yamamoto is the most powerful shinigami in Soul Society. He commands the utmost respect from his subordinates and manages to remain calm throughout any emergencies, taking control of each situation with ease. His zanpakutou is the fiery Ryuujin Jakka.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>54994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="385" picture="215702.jpg">Tsukada Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9308" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="36">3.56</rating>
<name>Sasakibe Choujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sasakibe Choujirou works underneath http://anidb.net/ch9307 [Genryuusai Yamamoto] as vice-captain of the first protection squad. He has a large interest in Western culture and likes to make tea from his own grown tealeaves. Sasakibe`s zanpakutou is named http://anidb.net/ch10821 [Gonryoumaru].
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>28822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9309" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="272">7.58</rating>
<name>Soi Fon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54993.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9310" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="71">1.37</rating>
<name>Oomaeda Marechiyo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28824.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2192" picture="196332.jpg">Kashii Shouto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9311" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="313">8.11</rating>
<name>Shihouin Yoruichi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shihouin Yoruichi is not an employee at the Urahara Shop in any official capacity. She is an old friend of owner Urahara Kisuke, and so uses it as a place of residence when she is not abroad. Her natural form is that of a dark brown-skinned woman with deep violet hair, though she can transform into a black cat at will. This form gives her a deep voice, which leads many characters to initially believe she is a male and thus call her "Mr. Yoruichi". Yoruichi is very easy-going despite her previous history; she insists that Soi Fon not use formalities when speaking to her, and she doesn`t feel uncomfortable appearing naked in front of Ichigo Kurosaki. She tends to avoid combat, and will not engage an enemy unless her allies will lose without her intervention. When first introduced, she helps Ichigo and his friends infiltrate Soul Society. As the series progress, it is revealed that Yoruichi is former captain of the 2nd Division, head of the noble Shihouin clan, and Commander in Chief of the Secret Mobile Corps and therefore she is very knowledgeable of the Soul Society`s history due to her background as a leader of one of the four high ranking noble families. A citation from Urahara Kisuke when he explained to Sarugaki Hiyori, any squad in the Gotei 13 who have The Secret Mobile Corps under their control (usually 2nd Squad), it will be an imaginable formidable military force in the Soul Society. As Yoruichi was the leader of the Secret Mobile Corps and also a squad captain herself during the pendulum period and also a leader of a high ranking noble house, thus it has made her position in the Soul Society was one of the most intimidating and respected. A century before the start of the series, she abandoned her captain position by helping Urahara, Tsukabishi Tessai, and the visoreds escape to the human world. Series creator Tite Kubo identifies Yoruichi as one of his two favorite female characters in the series (along with Rangiku Matsumoto), citing that he "has a lot of fun drawing her and creating stories with her".
Yoruichi is very skilled in all Soul Reaper tactical combat and the use of flash steps (瞬歩, shunpo), a high speed movement ability. While the ability is not unique and common for any competent Soul Reaper, her speed is almost unmatched leading to be known as the Goddess of Flash (瞬神, shunshin, English Anime: "Flash Master"). Yoruichi is also very skilled with "Flash Release" (瞬閧, shunkou), an advance combat technique that combines hand-to-hand combat and kidou abilities. The use of shunko allows the user to fight bare-handed against an opponent`s weapon without being injured. She has never been seen wielding a zanpakutou in the current or gaiden storyline, though is shown carrying a kodachi-like blade during flashbacks, she has also been shown using gauntlets and sabatons during her latest fight against Aizen.</description>
<picture>54985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9312" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="41">8.42</rating>
<name>Shihouin Yoruichi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54990.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9314" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="52">5.38</rating>
<name>Kira Izuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9316" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="94">7.53</rating>
<name>Unohana Retsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Unohana Retsu is in charge of the fourth protection squad. As the weakest of the thirteen divisions, Unohana`s team is in charge of medical care for the other shinigami. She has the temperament of a traditional Japanese woman and is gentle, soft-spoken and polite, though she is rumoured to have a fearsome side should you cross or annoy her. Her zanpakutou is named http://anidb.net/ch10919 [Minazuki].
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>28833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9317" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="64">5.55</rating>
<name>Kotetsu Isane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kotetsu Isane is http://anidb.net/ch9316 [Unohana]`s vice-captain in division four of the thirteen protection squads. She is fairly quiet and polite, and while she doesn`t have as much patience as her captain, Isane looks up to Unohana as a role model. Her zanpakutou is named Itegumo.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>28834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9319" type="appears in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="14">2.68</rating>
<name>Iemura Yasochika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28837.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9320" type="appears in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="23">3.79</rating>
<name>Yamada Hanatarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28838.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9329" type="appears in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="38">4.40</rating>
<name>Iba Tetsuzaemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28847.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9332" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="64">6.42</rating>
<name>Ise Nanao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ise Nanao is the vice-captain of the eighth protection squad. Unlike her carefree captain, http://anidb.net/ch7197 [Kyouraku], Nanao is very serious and she often has to keep her superior in check. She also has to deflect Kyouraku`s attempted flirtations and teasing, usually by hitting him with something or scolding him.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>2286.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9335" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="120">6.63</rating>
<name>Hisagi Shuuhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The 69 tattoo on his face resembles the (much bigger) tattoo of Muguruma Kensei, the Shinigami (now Vizard) who once rescued him and his friends from a hollow. Kensei`s tattoo is in the middle of his upper body, below the chest-muscles.</description>
<picture>54898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9342" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-27">
<rating votes="280">6.73</rating>
<name>Matsumoto Rangiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsumoto Rangiku is the busty vice-captain of Soul Society`s tenth protection squad. She is quite energetic and likes to have fun, especially if it involves a bottle of sake. Despite having a completely contrasting personality to her captain, http://anidb.net/ch8354 [Hitsugaya], Matsumoto bounces off well against her superior. When in battle, she fights with her zanpakutou, http://anidb.net/ch10805 [Haineko], which has the ability to turn into ash, surrounding the enemy to attack them.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>79577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4956" picture="28490.jpg">Matsutani Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9344" type="appears in" update="2009-07-04">
<rating votes="193">7.42</rating>
<name>Kusajishi Yachiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vice Captain of the 11th Division in the Goutei 13.</description>
<picture>30550.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9345" type="appears in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="118">7.09</rating>
<name>Madarame Ikkaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madarame Ikkaku is a typical member of the eleventh squad; he is loud, abrasive and itching for a battle. Much like http://anidb.net/ch7623 [Kenpachi], Ikkaku sees fighting as truly enjoyable and has a strong sense of honour insisting that all bouts should be one on one and to the death. Though he is a formidable opponent, Ikkaku is often teased within the division for his baldness, which has given him somewhat of a complex about it. Ikkaku`s zanpakutou is http://anidb.net/ch10804 [Hoozukimaru], which transforms into a double-ended spear when in its Shikai form.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>54834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9346" type="appears in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="117">3.17</rating>
<name>Ayasegawa Yumichika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayasegawa Yumichika is the exceedingly vain fifth seat of the eleventh protection squad. He is obsessed with beauty and reserves a burning hatred for anything he deems ugly. Despite his narcissistic ways, Yumichika is actually a very strong fighter and particularly loyal to his friends. His zanpakutou is named http://anidb.net/ch10813 [Ruri-iro Kujaku], though Yumichika calls it by the name of Fuji Kujaku.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>54878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9348" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="148">7.26</rating>
<name>Kurotsuchi Mayuri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>After having spent several years in the "Maggot`s Nest" (a place where people are put when they`re thought to be dangerous), Mayuri`s being freed by Urahara Kisuke for the purpose of being his lieutenant in his newly developed "Technology Research Bureau", which will give him a great deal of "fun" in the future.</description>
<picture>54831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9349" type="appears in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="108">6.17</rating>
<name>Kurotsuchi Nemu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurotsuchi Nemu is the vice-captain of the twelfth squad; she is also the artificially created daughter of http://anidb.net/ch9348 [Kurotsuchi Mayuri]. She shows no emotion whatsoever and is extremely shy, often not saying anything at all. Though her "father" doesn`t seem to care about her whatsoever, Nemu remains extremely loyal and will follow his orders implicitly.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>28875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9351" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="125">6.81</rating>
<name>Ukitake Juushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9355" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="10">3.01</rating>
<name>Kotsubaki Sentarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28880.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9356" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="22">5.76</rating>
<name>Kotetsu Kiyone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9394" type="appears in" update="2011-07-13">
<rating votes="73">4.95</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Yuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichigo`s little sister.
She`s kind hearted and likes to cook. After the mother`s death, she probably sees herself as some kind of replacement - at least in the kitchen.</description>
<picture>28923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5080" picture="2292.gif">Sena Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9395" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="77">6.27</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Karin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9462" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-11">
<rating votes="53">7.65</rating>
<name>Zangetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9762" type="appears in" update="2009-06-21">
<rating votes="136">7.62</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Ichigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10115" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="14">7.45</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Masaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10245" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-08">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Kusaka Soujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10246" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-08">
<rating votes="1">7.25</rating>
<name>Yang</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3158.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10247" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-08">
<rating votes="3">6.43</rating>
<name>Ying</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3159.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10811" type="appears in" update="2009-07-29">
<rating votes="20">6.14</rating>
<name>Hyourinmaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Personification of Hitsugaya Toushirou`s Zanpakutou.</description>
<picture>32223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5057" picture="28861.jpg">Matsuoka Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="81541" update="2007-08-30">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88258" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2007-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
