<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5356" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2008-04-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bamboo Blade</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Бамбуковое лезвие</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">להב מבמבוק</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Kiếm tre</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Меч от бамбук</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Бамбуковий клинок</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">竹剑少女</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">バンブーブレード</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bamboo Blade</title>
<title xml:lang="sk" type="official">Bambusová čepeľ</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5147" approval="2" total="5">Kenkou Zenrakei Suieibu Umishou</anime>
<anime id="106" approval="1" total="12">Azumanga Daiou The Animation (2002)</anime>
<anime id="8371" approval="1" total="4">Rou Kyuu Bu!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="26">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="724513">This show is not trying to imitate or copy any other comedies or sports shows, it`s doing its own thing. There is no 1 protagonist, instead there is a sizable cast of highly likable characters. Bamboo Blade feels fresh and unique. I did not expect it to be this good!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="446193">While kendo itself isn`t a large interest to the American demographic, Bamboo Blade uses kendo to tell a story of determination, inspiration and adult-hood, with distinguished character, a light soundtrack, and a strong yet innocent plot.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="604679">suitable for a younger audience</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="138921">Funny, good series !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="220563">very goooooooood</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="105643">A nice slow paced watch with a good story and comedy to keep you laughing during he entire duration</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="392345">Judging by the tags and the rating, I did not expect too much from this series.
I still decided to watch it, because of the many seiyuus it had in common with Clannad which is my favorite anime series by far, and I did not get disappointed.

The rating does not make it justice, and though the big selling point of this series is of course the comedy, it has a bit of it all: drama, slice of life and great character development.
Highly recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="66502">Very soft, i liked to watch this series just to relax. Nothing bad to say about it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="74461">has a sport anime feel but the characters are colorful; and enjoyable kendo tournaments</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="147458">Highly recommended - plenty of humour and character development</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="238012">very cool anime.. even went and get one of those bokken.. i hope i spell it correctly.. &lt;br /&gt;anyways.. you`ll enjoy it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="101469">Check this one out if you want to learn the basics on kendo, it`s no kenshin, more of a down to earth, slice-of-life theme. Most characters could use a little depth, but the professor will more than make up for it, you can`t help but laugh at his attempts to make money off the club</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="673908">Maybe the first or second time I write a recommendation, even though I`ve watched 10,000+ episodes myself. This show just have one of the best ever combination out there.

- Your usual "cutesy" HS club anime, but it`s among the good ones
- Good sport aspect, especially since they pick Kendo which is almost nonexistent in anime as main sport theme. Albeit rare, this anime just shows that Kendo itself is good in an anime format (because not every sport does).
- Every moment is just enjoyable. Even if there`s a little frustrating thing, it may become a big relieve in the later episodes.
- Great characters. I`m fond of the MCs combination, every of them often serves a good purpose in every episode (not plot-wise though, but overall stuffs) which is an important aspect.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="242256">Really solid anime. Great characters, quirky, likeable, heroic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Great fun to watch and really pulls you in and makes you want to keep watching.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.bambooblade.jp/pc/</url>
<creators>
<name id="910" type="Animation Work">AIC A.S.T.A</name>
<name id="15686" type="Chief Direction">Igarashi Tatsuya</name>
<name id="6276" type="Direction">Saitou Hisashi</name>
<name id="20976" type="Original Work">Totsuka Masahiro</name>
<name id="20191" type="Original Work">Igarashi Aguri</name>
<name id="28642" type="Character Design">Futayanagi Yukitomo</name>
<name id="35507" type="Music">Senba Kiyohiko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr20976 [Totsuka Masahiro], illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr20191 [Igarashi Aguri] and serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23601 [Young Gangan].
http://anidb.net/ch4232 [Ishida Toraji], aka Kojirou, is the Kendo instructor at Muro`e High School. He is totally broke, and has agreed to send his team to a competition against his http://anidb.net/ch15576 [senpai]`s team. If his all-female team can win the competition, he will have free meals for a year! But, the problem is that Kojirou seems unable to find five, gifted girls to form the dream team — and time is running out...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3744">6.58</permanent>
<temporary count="3778">7.69</temporary>
<review count="6">6.72</review>
</ratings>
<picture>51308.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8455</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2986</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4077</identifier>
<identifier>qhalfh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bambooblade.jp/pc/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Bamboo_Blade</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BAMBOO_BLADE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1242</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329019</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9343</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/bambooblade</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="659" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-17">
<name>dojo</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1645" parentid="2751" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>kendo</name>
<description>Kendo, or kendou in Japanese, is a popular sport from Japan. It consists of swordplay with one or two http://anidb.net/t1817 [shinai], a two-handed bamboo sword which may also be held with one hand only, while wearing armour.</description>
<picurl>163593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1783" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>immature</name>
<description>Marked by or indicating a lack of maturity</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2384" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-22">
<name>prodigy</name>
<description>Character is very good at everything he/she does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3094" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>befriend attack</name>
<description>A befriend attack is a pounce performed by someone in an attempt to hug someone else. This is an exuberant display of affection, often used for comedic effect. Sometimes, the target of such attacks learn to dodge them, usually by simply sidestepping them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3824" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-05">
<name>sentai</name>
<description>In Japanese, sentai is a military unit, and may be translated as "squadron", "task force", "group" or "wing". In the anime fandom, however, it usually refers to the Super Sentai Series, a long-running superhero team franchise of http://anidb.net/t5000 [tokusatsu] shows featuring live action characters and colorful special effects, and other similar shows. A prominent characteristic of such shows is that the colour- and elemental-coded heroes, usually numbering around five or more, fight to save the world from the evil that terrorizes the area, which may even span the entire universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4226" type="main character in" update="2009-03-03">
<rating votes="94">8.21</rating>
<name>Kawazoe Tamaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite being a kendo prodigy, she does not see it as a hobby, but rather just as a chore honed at her home, which happens to be a kendo dojo led by her father. She refuses to join the school`s Kendo Club because she thinks it is unnecessary, but temporarily becomes a member in order to fight off a bully. She despises injustice due to her overdeveloped sense of righteousness and fair play inspired from watching tokusatsu (her favourite being Blade Braver, a show within a show) as a child. She remains a big anime and tokusatsu fan despite her age. At first she is very shy and unsociable, but after holding a part-time job at Miyako`s acquaintance`s store she begins to overcome her shyness and open up to her teammates more often. Kirino and Sayako (and for that matter, most girls in the story) find her very cute, often putting Tamaki`s hair up in ponytails or making her fight in kendo matches just because they want to see her fight. She knows Yuuji before the series`s beginning, and has been called "Tama-chan" by him since their childhood (although she does not like the nickname very much, since it makes her seem childish).</description>
<picture>20247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4227" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-03">
<rating votes="37">8.63</rating>
<name>Chiba Kirino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of the kendo club. Energetic and enthusiastic, she dreams of leading the team to the nationals. Her family owns a deli named "Chiba Deli". Kirino is very happy that Kojirou has finally begun to put more effort into training his kendo team, but she is oblivious to the real reason that her teacher has suddenly begun to train the team so enthusiastically. She is proud that she is the captain of the kendo club and is more responsible than she appears (such as picking up the shinai when the other members leave them lying around on the floor). Kirino seems to find Tamaki quite adorable, as she and Sayako will often treat Tamaki as a "little sister" type. Despite that, however, she has great confidence in Tamaki. She is described as being the heart of the group by Kojirou.</description>
<picture>20248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4228" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-03">
<rating votes="20">7.00</rating>
<name>Kuwahara Sayako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A second year high school student who is described as being random and spontaneous, often changing her interests and goals. During her first year, she joins the Kendo Club, but would sometimes disappear for short periods of time, claiming to quit. She and Kirino have known each other since elementary school, and Kirino often calls her "Saya". She is one of the tallest members on the team, which others poke fun at by "mistakenly" calling her a boy.</description>
<picture>20249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4229" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-03">
<rating votes="27">7.25</rating>
<name>Miyazaki Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced as a very pretty and friendly girl and to the surprise of many, the girlfriend of Danjuurou. However, in reality, she possesses a very dark and sadistic personality, but hides it in order to be together with Danjuurou.</description>
<picture>20250.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4230" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-03">
<rating votes="19">4.04</rating>
<name>Azuma Satori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Very talented in kendo and the second strongest in the club, behind Tamaki. However, she is very bad with her studies despite her diligence, which is why she decided to quit kendo after middle school--in order to concentrate on her studies. It is revealed her glasses are fake; she thought she would get smarter by wearing them. Because she is rather naïve, she is tricked by Miyako Miyazaki into joining the club, thinking that Kendo will help her improve her studies. Satori is comically clumsy, as demonstrated in the ending sequences and some of the previews in the anime.</description>
<picture>20251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4231" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-03">
<rating votes="8">4.42</rating>
<name>Nakata Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A kind, cheerful, and helpful first year student who joins the Kendo Club. He was a member of his junior high school`s kendo club and had also attended the Kawazoe Dojo. He had reached the top eight in the prefectural games during junior high. He is almost on par with Tamaki in skill, and he has defeated Satori Azuma once. He also possesses considerable academic skill as he scored fourth out of all the Freshman on the regional exams.</description>
<picture>20252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4232" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="12">5.02</rating>
<name>Ishida Toraji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also known as "Kojirou", he is the kendo instructor, and also a teacher of politics and economics, at Muroe High School. He is perpetually impoverished and lives from paycheck to paycheck, often taking handouts of food from his students. He is offered the chance of a lifetime from an old senpai — a year`s supply of sushi if his female kendo team can beat his senpai`s in a practice tournament. This inspires Kojirou to put an effort into training his team, much to the delight of his most dedicated student, Kirino Chiba. The only person who knows the real reason for Kojirou`s inspiration is Yuuji Nakata, who calls him "pathetic".</description>
<picture>20253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4233" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="10">1.70</rating>
<name>Eiga Danjuurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also known as Dan-kun, Danjuurou Eiga is a round and plain-faced first year who joins the Kendo Club with Yuuji. He originally wanted to join the Ping Pong Club, but there was no such club in the school. He shocks Yuuji and Kojirou when he brings his pretty girlfriend Miyako to join the club. While he finds the basic training to be "boring" (possibly because he wants to impress Miyako), he is rather proficient in scorekeeping.</description>
<picture>20254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5419" type="appears in" update="2011-10-28">
<rating votes="5">7.05</rating>
<name>Odajima Reimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Odajima Reimi attended the same middle school as Miyako, and became obsessed with her when she beat up http://anidb.net/ch37269 [a boy] who Reimi had a crush on, but who liked Miyako. Since finding out that Miyako joined the kendo club, she follows her to every tournament, taking countless pictures and recording videos of her (abusing her position as a photography club member). Miyako is very disturbed by her stalking, and has lost a few matches due to being distracted by her.</description>
<picture>22048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15573" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-04">
<rating votes="8">8.08</rating>
<name>Suzuki Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In the anime, Rin Suzuki is a second year student at Shugyoku High School. She is Tamaki Kawazoe`s friend and rival. By using the ascension stance she became the first person to beat Tamaki. In their rematch, she was happy to see that Tamaki had gotten stronger because it makes Rin more determined to win.
Like Tamaki, she is a fan of the Blade Braver anime, but unlike Tamaki, she`s primarily a fan of one of the show`s antagonists, Shinaider. She travelled with the Ozawa Swords and Company Association as they choreographed and filmed fight scenes for the Cosmo 13 / Blade Bravers movie. When stuntman Fujimura got hurt on set, she stepped in his role as Shinai-Girl, making Tamaki take her place as the High School Girl.
She has not appeared in the manga, but Touryou Academy`s Kendo Club`s coach, Teramoto, mentions "Suzuki from Kanto" as a someone who could be selected as one of the "Nine Kendo Beauties," someone who could be a rival for Ura Sakaki.</description>
<picture>44196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15574" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<rating votes="3">6.55</rating>
<name>Andou Yuuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuri Andou, the first second-year student on the team, is a girl who seems to zone out most of the time and seems not to care much about winning, but her looks can deceive others greatly. She is rather skilled at kendo and is quite sadistic, like Miyako Miyazaki of Muroe High. Another trait of hers that resembles Miyako`s is Yuuri`s tendency to turn "black" and let some of her true nature show through, which always manages to induce fear in everyone, including her own teammates. (Unlike Miyako, however, Yuuri also tends to openly badmouth her teammates, particularly Akemi Asakawa, when they do something that displeases her.) When Yuuri is showing her crueler side she is surrounded by a rather eerie black aura that looks rather similar to, if not exactly like, Miyako`s "black" aura. Yuuri also tends to resort to using nasty methods to win (such as tripping people with her foot, stepping on her opponents` feet, and "harassing" her opponent by showing her "black" aura) and then deny that she has cheated in a falsely sweet manner, much to the chagrin of the other members of her kendo team, who are already rather frustrated with her apparent lack of team spirit. Apparently Yuuri has a bit of a sweet tooth, as she once cost her team precious time at a practice match with Muroe High by making them stop at a café so she could "charge" her brain with sugar. She apparently does not function well in the morning. Another one of Yuuri`s disturbing traits , seen in episode 15, is her ability to sleep with her eyes open. This freaks Tamaki out when she wakes up next to her while at Training Camp. Occasionally she is seen reading a book during important moments (such as kendo matches or team member assignments), a habit that only emphasizes her complete lack of desire to win.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>44199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2137" picture="224299.jpg">Omimura Mayuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15575" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="2">6.44</rating>
<name>Harada Konatsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konatsu Harada, the first third-year student on the team, is the shortest of the five members of the team Kenzaburo chose, and also the shyest. She is rather skilled in kendo as Kenzaburo once remarks that she has a 2-dan rank, is "self-motivated", and comes to practice every day. She is very quiet and can be flustered by some of the things her team, particularly her teacher, does (as shown in one episode of the anime). Konatsu is one of the strongest members on the team, second only to Karen Nishiyama. During a practice match with Muroe High Konatsu was beaten by Tamaki Kawazoe.</description>
<picture>44200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15576" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="2">1.93</rating>
<name>Ishibashi Kenzaburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kenzaburou Ishibashi is Kojirou`s old senpai and the kendo coach from Machido High School. He was beaten by Kojirou during a kendo meet long ago in their high school years and seems to hold a grudge against him for that, even if it does not seem apparent. Kenzaburou is also jealous of Kojirou`s team, particularly because he has Tamaki Kawazoe, a freshman of Muroe High who beat two of his kendo team members in a practice duel one time. Kenzaburou is a more dedicated teacher than Kojirou, but like his kohai he trains his kendo team only for his own personal gain.</description>
<picture>44201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15577" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<name>Kiyomura Ono</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29921" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>Kyoutou-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The vice principal of Muroe Highschool. He is seen in episode one when he falls out the school`s third floor window. Tamaki saved his life by quickly grabbing a broom nearby and hitting him back up through the window he fell out of. He lends Tamaki his glasses, which she uses under the guise of Bureiba.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>61883.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4726" picture="54694.jpg">Kawamoto Kunihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29923" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Kukkyou Joshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="428">Kojima Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29924" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="9">6.61</rating>
<name>Yoshikawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satori`s homeroom teacher, Yoshikawa becomes involved in Muroe`s kendo club out of concern for Satori`s well-being. When Satori shows that she is capable of balancing kendo with school work, Yoshikawa continues to support the kendo club. She and Kojirou become friends and frequently chat when they are both in the staff room. She is skilled at playing video games. When Kojirou leaves the kendo club, Yoshikawa is requested by the club to become their advisor, which she agrees to do so until she goes on maternity leave. The father of her baby is Kenzaburou, Kojirou`s upperclassman.</description>
<picture>67707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10854" picture="38961.jpg">Sasaki Hinako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29925" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Iwasa Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makoto is one of the new freshman members of the kendo club, who turns out to be Iwasa`s little brother. He is patient, polite and cool-headed, unlike his brother who is a delinquent. Makoto is a total beginner when it comes to kendo. He was impressed when he observed Tamaki doing kendo, which makes him more motivated to join the kendo club. Makoto`s kendo gear was given to him by his brother.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>62657.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="408" picture="17255.jpg">Fujita Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29926" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Toyama Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinobu wants to join clubs, such as the ping-pong club, lacrosse club, sepak takraw etc., but none of the clubs she likes exist. So in the end, she joins her friend, Makoto, in joining the kendo club. She is impatient and ill-mannered, but her attitude is better than her brother`s. Her mother gave her her brother`s gear.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>67708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29927" type="appears in" update="2011-10-28">
<name>Iwasa Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iwasa is http://anidb.net/ch29928 [Toyama]`s friend and fellow Kendo Club member, who also ditches practice. Nothing much is known about this character, and he has not been seen with a shinai before in the anime. In the anime it appears that both he and Toyama have dropped kendo, as they no longer come by. Both he and Toyama are delinquents (they fought two other students when provoked in a video game arcade and destroyed two machines) and have resigned kendo despite their fondness of it. In the closing credits of the final episode of the anime, he is shown to be on the soccer team with Toyama.
Wikipedia</description>
<picture>67848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="185" picture="228625.jpg">Ishigami Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29928" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Toyama Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toyama is the school bully and formerly a member of the Kendo Club. He often ditches kendo practice and had caused all the previous club members to quit (with the exception of Kirino and Sayako) by pretending to "teach" them techniques, which was just him constantly hitting them with his shinai. Miyako attempts to teach him and Iwasa a lesson one time, but fails to do so when Sayako crashes into her. It appears that neither Toyama nor Iwasa come to kendo anymore. It is also shown in episodes twenty-two and twenty-three that he and Iwasa are delinquents, as they fought two other students when provoked in a video game arcade and destroyed two machines--an act that almost led to the kendo club`s suspension. Although he and Iwasa terrorized the kendo club during their brief time in the club, Toyama actually feels that he is not as strong as he appears, as shown in episode twenty-four of the anime. Eventually both he and Iwasa decide to resign from the club to save it from suspension, even though they both do not hate kendo. Its implied that`s he`s afraid of Tamaki due to her strength after easily losing to her. In the closing credits of the anime`s final episodes, it is shown that he has joined the soccer team with Iwasa, and he is verbally fighting with an opposing player.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>67854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29929" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="3">7.02</rating>
<name>Yokoo Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yokoo Maya, the second third-year student on the team, is a competitive and tall girl with more team spirit than anyone else in her team. Maya is a bit of a tomboy and tends to speak in a rather aggressive and foul-mouthed manner, calling her teammates "twits" and "dumbasses" when they do not take kendo seriously. However, she will stick up for her teammates when Yuuri says cruel things about them (or rather, Akemi), as shown in two episodes of the anime. Apparently she also seems to have a rather large appetite that causes her to eat so much that she ends up with a severe stomachache later on. Tamaki beat Maya during the last round of the practice match with Muroe High, much to the latter`s displeasure and shock.</description>
<picture>67709.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12673" picture="151697.jpg">Yazawa Kiyomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29930" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="2">6.44</rating>
<name>Nishiyama Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karen Nishiyama, the third third-year student on the team, is incredibly skilled at kendo, but tends to shake when nervous. When she is cornered in a kendo match she instinctively switches to the offensive, thus effectively beating her opponent. Because of her instinct of going on offense when in trouble Karen is the strongest on her kendo team. Even though she is extremely skilled at kendo, she does not like the idea of fighting an opponent that she does not know in real life, and she will attempt to run away when she is nervous.</description>
<picture>67711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6849" picture="186209.jpg">Mori Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29931" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Asakawa Akemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asakawa Akemi, the second second-year student on the team, is probably the most undedicated out of all the members of her team, as she seems only to care about her boyfriend to the point where she will ditch kendo club for her boyfriend. When she encounters a problem with her boyfriend she will not do her best and will only go on the defense; however, when her boyfriend makes up with her she will immediately start pouring out all of her effort, making her a rather formidable opponent. Apparently none of her teammates save for Kenzaburou have any real concern for her, as they simply let her constant ditchings slide (even if she is ditching from a kendo match). Kenzaburou, however, is appalled with her habit of constantly ditching kendo just to meet up with her boyfriend and her lack of effort when she is upset. It is revealed in one episode of the anime that Akemi possesses "excellent footwork".
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>67712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29154" picture="70393.jpg">Kondou Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29932" type="appears in" update="2011-10-28">
<name>Hayashi Tadaaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hayashi Tadaaki is the coach for the http://anidb.net/ch37969 [Seimei High School] kendo team. He is extremely strict with his students, and verbally and physically punishes them when they lose a match, even if it is against a stronger opponent. His tough training regimen often causes students to quit the kendo team, although he does not regret this, and considers quitters to be weak. After the practice with Muroe High, however, he seems to be willing to take it just a little bit easier on his wards.</description>
<picture>67713.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="544" picture="238510.jpg">Ogawa Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29933" type="appears in" update="2011-10-28">
<rating votes="2">7.19</rating>
<name>Ogawa Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ogawa Mei is a freshman on the Seimei High School kendo team. She joined the team to be with her friends, although all of them eventually quit, until she was the very last freshman girl left on the team. This discouraged her, and she desired to quit the kendo team after the practice with Muroe High, but was convinced otherwise after getting fired up practicing with Tamaki.
Wikipedia</description>
<picture>67714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29934" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Nozomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="428">Kojima Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29935" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<rating votes="2">6.52</rating>
<name>Suzushiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3182" picture="55949.jpg">Sakata Kayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29936" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Kawaguchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17203" picture="46531.jpg">Fujiha Aika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29937" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Nomura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3202" picture="24193.jpg">Nakamura Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29938" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Takahashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1876" picture="66007.jpg">Asakura Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29939" type="appears in" update="2011-10-26">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Konishi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konishi is the general of the Toujou High School team. She is the leader of the kendo team that has a reputation for winning matches through cheating. During the preliminary tournament, her schoolmates locked Tamaki in a shed after tricking her into coming to the parking lot to meet up with her father. There, Konishi got her out and led her to a trap where she injured her ankle after tripping over a bunch of tennis balls that were carefully placed. She was beaten by an enraged Tamaki in her match after receiving a throat strike, but the match was forfeited when Toraji pulled Tamaki out due to her injury. In the closing credits of the anime`s final episode, it appears that she has gotten a haircut, and was scolding her classmates, presumably for attempting to cheat again. This suggests that she no longer resorts to cheating to win.</description>
<picture>67715.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29940" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<rating votes="2">6.16</rating>
<name>Aoki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="238" picture="49561.jpg">Mizusawa Fumie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29941" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Satou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="618" picture="223541.jpg">Okajima Tae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29942" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Iguchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2505" picture="141583.jpg">Makiguchi Mayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29943" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Toraji no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toraji`s father is seen briefly in the anime when he forces his son to work at the family store during his visit. He is a tough man and a hard worker.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>62150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29944" type="appears in" update="2015-02-25">
<name>Toraji no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toraji`s mother frequently sends packages of faddish health foods to her son. However, the food is usually insufficient nourishment for the poor Toraji, or of minimal use. She is shown briefly in the anime and forces her son to work at the store when he comes over to visit.</description>
<picture>62142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="364" picture="202614.jpg">Han Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29945" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>Tamaki no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamaki`s unnamed father is the head of the Kawazoe dojo. He encouraged Tamaki to take up kendo at a very young age, and is therefore responsible for her amazing skill in kendo. Tamaki`s father is possibly in his mid-50`s as he keeps saying "I`m at an age where I can`t even understand Tama-chan anymore" in one episode of the anime. That said, he is in practice a kind, loving, considerate and doting father who merely lacks articulate skills and confidence to express his affections for Tamaki. He constantly worries every time Tamaki brings up Yuuji, mistakenly believing that he and Tamaki are seeing each other, to the point he spies on them at training camp to make sure nothing is happening and constantly frowning or making an angry face whenever Yuuji`s name is brought up.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>61828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3102" picture="24178.jpg">Chou Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29946" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Kawazoe Tsubaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamaki`s mother, who died when Tamaki was very young. Tamaki has only a few memories of her mother, but greatly respects her and remembers that her mother was amazingly talented at kendo. She seemed to have been fond of the high stance, and Tamaki becomes distracted whenever an opponent uses it against her.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>62109.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29947" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kirino no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirino`s mother helps run the family`s deli. She collapses from exhaustion in the middle of the series, which causes Kirino to become distressed and more withdrawn, although her seriousness improved her skills in kendo. In the middle of a match, however, her brother yelled out to her that their mother was all right, in which she immediately lost focus--and the match.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>62484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28669" picture="62483.jpg">Hirano Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29948" type="appears in" update="2013-11-12">
<rating votes="2">6.16</rating>
<name>Miyako no Ane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyazaki Miyako`s older sister. She is so terrible at cooking, that even when totally exhausted Miyako prefer to cook herself.</description>
<picture>61887.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6849" picture="186209.jpg">Mori Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29950" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>Sayako no Otouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61885.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12673" picture="151697.jpg">Yazawa Kiyomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29951" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Sakaguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakaguchi is the owner of the kendo equipment shop that Kojirou takes his kendo team to for purchasing equipment. While Sakaguchi`s kendo skills are only seen in a series of flashbacks in the anime, it is apparent that he is incredibly skilled at kendo, strong enough to make all of the members of Kojirou`s team complain about him. He has a fondness for mochi, although Kojirou`s kendo team tends to eat all of Sakaguchi`s mochi during their visits to his shop. He is also, as Kojirou puts it, "very competitive".
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>61865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1998" picture="21301.jpg">Nagasako Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29953" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<rating votes="1">5.47</rating>
<name>Moo Moo House Tenchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29954" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>Nobu-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3696" picture="224842.jpg">Kitazawa Riki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29955" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>Neko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Considered to be the mascot character of Bamboo Blade, the Cat appears in every episode in the background or even seen interacting with the other characters. In Episode 25, two characters mention that the Gray cat that appears in the episode is a rare cat that only appears every 25 episodes.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>61827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29956" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Suginokouji Takachiho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67717.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29957" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="3">1.85</rating>
<name>Carrie Nishikawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An anime-only character, Carrie is an American girl raised in Japan with a loud and pushy attitude. She becomes Miyako`s rival for Dan`s affections since Carrie finds that he resembles her pet armadillo, Anderson. After seeing a samurai movie as a child, she has always wanted to fight with two swords. As such, she is a strong opponent capable of using the two-sword style of kendo, despite high school competitions prohibiting the use of the two sword technique. Because Carrie has considerably more experience than the novice Miyako, Miyako trains especially hard to defeat Carrie. In the 25th episode, she finally defeats Carrie in a match, and later goes on to defeat her again with Carrie using the two-sword style.</description>
<picture>67718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29958" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Narita Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62610.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37250" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>Takasugi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takasugi is in the same class as http://anidb.net/ch29928 [Toyama] and has the same model of mobile phone as him. Takasugi accidentally took Toyama`s phone home, and returned it (only to be beaten up).</description>
<picture>61826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17211" picture="170199.jpg">Takanohashi Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37251" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>Death Armour</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Death Armour is the antagonist in the in-anime anime Chouken Sentai Blade Braver.</description>
<picture>61831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37255" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>Doruchiru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37256" type="appears in" update="2015-02-21">
<name>Reimi Mama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A woman http://anidb.net/ch4232 [Kojirou] bumped into and argued at a supermarket with during episode 9. She happens to be the neighbour of the superintendent of Muroe Koukou, where Kojirou is employed.
She also happens to be the mother of http://anidb.net/ch5419 [Reimi], as shown in episode 10.</description>
<picture>61913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37257" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>Ten`in</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A supermarket employee unfortunate enough to have to deal with http://anidb.net/ch4232 [Kojirou] and http://anidb.net/ch37256 [a woman]`s quarrelling.</description>
<picture>61940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37268" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Dansei Kyaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An angry customer blaming http://anidb.net/ch29944 [Toraji`s Mother] that they no longer sell banana flavoured milk.</description>
<picture>62155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37269" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Matsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2840" picture="22915.jpg">Suzuki Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37270" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Suugaku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37276" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Sugimoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37278" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Toujou Koukou Komon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28669" picture="62483.jpg">Hirano Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37280" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Bike Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gave http://anidb.net/ch5419 [Reimi] a ride to the tournament.</description>
<picture>62517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2840" picture="22915.jpg">Suzuki Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37281" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Teraji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62574.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37283" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Cosmo One</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10400" picture="215975.jpg">Ogawa Teruaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37284" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Shinaider</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="417" picture="24695.jpg">Hori Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37285" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Ozawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5057" picture="28861.jpg">Matsuoka Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37286" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Fujimura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37287" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<name>Kantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The director that is shooting the new Blade Braver movie.</description>
<picture>62646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5977" picture="30601.jpg">Omoro Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37969" type="appears in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>Seimei Koutougakkou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>72077.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37970" type="appears in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>Shiritsu Machido Koutougakkou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>72080.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38130" type="appears in" update="2011-10-26">
<name>Toujou Koukou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="38195" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-10-28">
<name>Taniguchi Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cameo appearance by Taniguchi Gorou as himself.</description>
<picture>74631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1" picture="44996.jpg">Taniguchi Gorou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="82768" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竹ぼうきと正義の味方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Bamboo Broom &amp; a Champion of Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takebouki to Seigi no Mikata</title>
<summary>Toraji "Kojirou" Ishida, the coach of the Muroe High kendo club, makes a bet with his senpai, Kenzaburou Ishibashi, the coach of the Machido High kendo club, on a practice match between both schools, but the fighters must be five girls, no boys. Toraji`s victory would mean he could eat all he wants at Ishibashi`s father`s sushi restaurant for a full year. Toraji desperately needs to find more talented female kendo students because he only has the team captain in his club, Kirino Chiba. With only a month remaining before his team`s match with Ishibashi`s team, he meets an extremely talented freshman, Tamaki Kawazoe.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="82769" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブレードブレイバーとお弁当</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blade Bravers and Boxed Lunch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blade Braver to Obentou</title>
<summary>Tamaki`s motivation is presented in the form of her TV superhero, Blade Braver. Miyako Miyazaki, Yuuji Nakata, Danjuurou Eiga join the club. Tamaki`s relationship with the other club members develop when they start having lunch together and sharing their boxed lunches. Her everyday boxed lunch, however, consisted of a single umeboshi (pickled ume fruit) and rice, which she constantly made in honor of her parents, and couldn`t share with the others. She start making "shareable" boxed lunches at the end of the episode, even though she feels she`s disrespecting her parents a little.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84154" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラックとブルー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black and Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Black to Blue</title>
<summary>The club members go shopping for protective gear. After trying on their protective gear, Kojirou nicknames Tamaki "Red", the leader of the kendo club`s female team, Kirino is nicknamed "Yellow", and Miyako is nicknamed "Pink". The fourth female member of the kendo club, Sayako Kuwahara nicknamed "Blue", is revealed, and has a painful first encounter with Miyako`s "Black" personality. Kojirou will nickname the last female club member "Green".
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84259" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">室江高と町戸高</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Muroe High &amp; Machido High</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Muroekou to Machidokou</title>
<summary>The day of the match arrives, however, due to the unique personalities of its members, the Machido High kendo club is awfully delayed. The real match starts very late in the episode, and the episode ends with the Machido High club members awed by Tamaki`s ability, after scoring a point in the first battle.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84260" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">川添珠姫と遅刻の武礼葉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tamaki Kawazoe and the Tardy Bureiba</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawazoe Tamaki to Chikoku no Bureiba</title>
<summary>After Tamaki`s match, which ended in a victory for her, the other matches take place while she prepares to participate in the last match too. At the end, the Muroe High kendo club ends winning with three wins, one loss, and one tie against the Machido High kendo club. Therefore, Ishibashi challenges Tamaki to a match, impressed of how a girl of her age with such a great talent is in a kendo club like that.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84362" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピンクとブルー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pink and Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pink to Blue</title>
<summary>Miyako learns that the girl she had thrown in the lake the previous day was actually her senpai in the club, this leads her, in her "Pink" personality (different from her "Black" personality), to awkwardly try to hide her identity from Sayako to avoid any confrontations. She starts to enjoy more of the club`s activities, even though being forced to train from early in the morning, because of the opportunities kendo give to harm others legally. She is eventually convinced by Toraji to apologize and befriends Sayako.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85062" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寿司とメンチカツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sushi and Mince Meat Cutlets</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sushi to Mince Cutlet</title>
<summary>This episode picks up at the end of the previous one, starting with Ishibashi revealing that he knew the fifth fighter, Bureiba, was actually Tamaki. His challenge to Tamaki is accepted and so their match starts. Ishibashi goes all out on Tamaki, and they both score a point, but in the third round, Ishibashi starts out in upper-level posture, rather than the normal middle-level posture. This forces Tamaki to have a flashback of her mother in the same position. Ishibashi leaves the match as a tie, and then goes out to a sushi dinner with Toraji. However, this is when Toraji finds out that Ishibashi`s father has given his restaurant away, making their bet void.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85063" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タマちゃんとアルバイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tama and Part-time Work</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tama-chan to Arbeit</title>
<summary>Tamaki sees an anime package on TV that she wants, but later finds out that she does not have enough money for it. At the kendo dojo, Tamaki overhears Miyako on the phone talking about how she could not work part-time that day. Tamaki approaches her and inquires about it. Miyako then asks Tamaki to work part time there, to which Tamaki agrees to. Tamaki`s father at first disagrees with Tamaki getting a job, mostly because the school does not allow students to work part time jobs, but then accepts because he thinks that Tamaki is growing up, and also thinks she will use the money to buy him a gift for his upcoming birthday.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85399" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東の事情とメイの事情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Azuma`s Circumstances and Mei`s Circumstances</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Azuma no Jijou to Mei no Jijou</title>
<summary>This episode dedicates to Satori Azuma from Muroe High School and Mei Ogawa from Seimei High School. Mei joined the Seimei High kendo club to get along with her friends, but many of her friends quit the club as they couldn`t take the teacher`s strict training. They gear up for the practice match with the Muroe High kendo club. However, she had set her mind to quit after the practice match. Toraji found out that Azuma didn`t want to join the kendo club as her results in examinations were bad. Not because she wasn`t able to do it, but she made careless mistakes. Nevertheless, Kirino drags her to the practice match. The episode concludes with the Muroe High kendo club training against the Seimei High kendo club.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85400" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメーションとドリーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Animation and Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Animation to Dream</title>
<summary>Miyako reveals to the other kendo club members that Reimi has been harassing her because during middle school she refused to go out with the captain of the men`s football team, whom Reimi had already been rejected by. Try as she might, Kirino is unable to remember the name of the potential fifth female member who`s studying at Muroe High School. Yuuji suggests that Kirino should call her friend up and ask for her name again, which she does. Armed with the name Satori Azuma, Kirino and Sayako begin to search for her.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85401" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宮崎都の憂鬱と初大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miyako Miyazaki`s Melancholy and the First Tournament</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miyazaki Miyako no Yuuutsu to Hatsu Taikai</title>
<summary>Toraji meets with his parents, and helps his mom working at a store. He receives his paycheck. Tamaki finishes up her job and receives her paycheck as well. The Muroe High kendo club enters the high school tournament. Only Tamaki did well enough to win. Miyako meets her middle school classmate, Reimi Otajima, who has a crush on her. Reimi is the customer that Tamaki met. Miyako as such became troubled and couldn`t concentrate on her match. It was revealed that Reimi used to harass Miyako when they were in middle school. The episode ends off with Toraji discussing about a fifth member with Kirino.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85402" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コジローと運命の分岐点</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kojiro and the Crossroads of Fate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kojirou to Unmei no Bunkiten</title>
<summary>Tamaki nears the end of her part time-job filling in for Miyako, while the other club member are practicing at the kendo dojo. Tamaki`s father still ponders if Tamaki will buy him a gift for his birthday. Toraji has bad luck when he goes shopping for food. He encounters a woman, also shopping for food, who causes him to lose his temper. This leads to him to the possibility of being unemployed at the kendo dojo. The only way to prevent unemployment is to improve the skills of the kendo club members and compete in the upcoming tournament. At Tamaki last time at her part-job, a mysterious customer arrives.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85675" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先生たちと生徒たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teachers and Students</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensei-tachi to Seito-tachi</title>
<summary>The Muroe High kendo club won all their matches against the Seimei High kendo club in the practice match. Azuma, upon seeing Tamaki`s strong kendo skills become motivated and took part in the practice match. Before that, Tamaki had a match with Azuma. Despite Azuma losing, she was impressed and therefore became motivated. Mei, from Seimei High School, who originally wanted to quit, decided to stay on, as she was impressed by Tamaki`s skills. The episode end off when Tadaaki Hayashi, the Seimei High kendo club`s teacher, competed with Toraji, the Muroe High kendo club`s teacher, having Hayashi winning the match.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86312" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さとりんの決意ともぎゅもぎゅ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Satorin`s Resolve and Nomming</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satorin no Ketsui to Mogyumogyu</title>
<summary>Kirino and Sayako continue their attempts to persuade Azuma to join the kendo club. Their attempts end only in tears. As they run through and around the school, Miyako hears their mobile lamentation and springs into action. She offers an excuse that she has cleaning duties, then sweetly dumps said duties onto her classmates. Alternating between a good friend, salesperson and snake cornering a frog she attempts to win over Azuma. Miyako`s tactics eventually convince Azuma (and later her parents) to join the kendo club with the expectation/condition that it will lead to improved grades. With the kendo club set with five girls, while Yuuji and Eiga are excluded from participation, a training camp is announced. Due to a lack of funds, this intensive training will take place on the school grounds. Tamaki`s father is perturbed especially when Tamaki confirms Yuuji will be there.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86313" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初合宿と初銭湯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Training Camp and First Public Bath</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsugasshuku to Hatsusentou</title>
<summary>It`s training camp at the Muroe High kendo club, jointly with the Machido High kendo club that they had a practice match with. Tamaki`s father sneaks around worried about the boys while the group cleans up the pool, fights over who gets to train with Tamaki, and takes a break at the bathhouse. After that, they have to deal with one of them sneaking away, pillow fights, Sayako`s guitar, and even getting freaked out by the sleeping habits of their fellow students. The episode wraps up with Tama and Kirino, the latter who can`t help but stay up and hold her bamboo sword a bit longer. Camp ends and everyone returns home, but for Kirino, something more than a warm welcome awaits.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86679" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">"それから"と"これから"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"Since Then" and "From Here on Out"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Sorekara" to "Korekara"</title>
<summary>It is a new year and several months have passed since the national kendo competition. Rin invites Tamaki to see the Blade Bravers movie in a movie theater. Back at the kendo dojo, two freshmen show up to join the Muroe High kendo club. The members one by one appear trying to convince them to join the club only to perform sideshow tricks leaving the freshmen unimpressed. The Muroe High kendo club later have a sparring match which causes the freshmen to become enthusiastic about joining the kendo club. It is later revealed that these two new kendo club members, Shinobu Toyama and Makoto Iwasa, are the siblings of the previous members that quit. Toraji returns to school having settled the problem with the woman, which he encountered at the store, that forced him to leave. At the very end of the episode Tamaki encounters a long purple haired woman with blue eyes, hinting that Bamboo Blade may have another season to come.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86680" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">剣道とそれがもたらすもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kendo and What It Brings About</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kendou to Sore ga Motarasu Mono</title>
<summary>The Muroe High kendo club goes to a national kendo competition and meets with many of their former opponents. Miyako, having watched footage of her previous kendo match filmed by Reimi in an effort to improve her kendo skills, manages to beat Carrie, the latter of which calls the former out for a match of their own and is beaten again. Tamaki fights Rin again and wins by using the thrust attack. Toraji, on the other hand, has emptied out his apartment, and in the last few minutes of the episode is shown getting on Nobu`s motorcycle and going to a different place, presumably his new home.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86681" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">剣と道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sword and the Way</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ken to Michi</title>
<summary>Kirino attempts and fails to prevent Tamaki from resigning from the Muroe High kendo club, the latter already having decided to give up. Neither she nor Miyako decide to attend the Muroe High kendo club, and nobody knows of Miyako`s whereabouts. Eventually even Kirino decides not to attend, and the only members left are Azuma, Yuuji, Eiga, and Sayako. Azuma manages to convince Miyako to keep up with kendo, while Sayako dissuades Kirino from quitting kendo. Yuuji comforts Tamaki, telling her that losing is not as bad as she thinks, and Tamaki decides to learn upper-level posture to help improve her kendo skills. Eventually she decides to come back to kendo club, and the members are reunited.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86682" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘘と沈黙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lies and Silence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uso to Chinmoku</title>
<summary>The principal of the school tells Toraji that the Muroe High kendo club will be disbanded because of club members engaging in suspicious or risky activities. It turns to be Toyama and Iwasa`s fault. They, ironically, have stopped attending Muroe High kendo club but have not turned in any resignation forms. Kirino and Sayako are distraught when Toraji reveals the news to them, and they protest the principal`s decision, calling it unfair. Meanwhile, Miyako has an emotional breakdown over her failure in the competition and, surprisingly, refuses Eiga`s comfort. Tamaki, also unhappy over losing the competition, quits the Muroe High kendo club, much to Kirino`s dismay.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86683" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敗者と勝者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Winners and Losers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haisha to Shousha</title>
<summary>The Muroe High kendo club goes to the Kanto High kendo tournament. Miyako shows her improvement in practice, but fails to defeat Carrie in the tournament. The Muroe High kendo club makes it to the third round, where Tamaki is finally defeated by Rin, and Muroe is pushed out of the tournament. Meanwhile, Toyama and Iwasa, two former members of the Muroe High kendo club, are caught fighting in a video game arcade and destroying two machines.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86684" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">川添珠姫と鈴木凛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tamaki Kawazoe and Rin Suzuki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawazoe Tamaki to Suzuki Rin</title>
<summary>Tamaki and Rin witness a scene for the Blade Bravers movie. They stay up late comparing whether Blade Braver or Shinaider is the better character. In the morning Tamaki and Rin, along with the production crew, go on location to film the new Blade Bravers movie, where an incident gets both of them the replacement roles in the new film. The rest of the Muroe High kendo club members either practice or take the day off doing what they want. The episode concludes with Toraji returning from his business trip.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86685" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブレイバーとシナイダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Braver and Shinaider</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Braver to Shinaider</title>
<summary>Toraji gives the Muroe High kendo club a vacation, since he has a business trip to schedule. Yuuji invites Tamaki to go to an amusement park that`s hosting a Blade Braver play. At the venue, She meets a girl called Rin Suzuki, a fan of Braver`s rival, Shinaider. They enter a quiz game show to win The Blade Bravers plush dolls. Unfortunately, Rin wins the plush dolls, in a tie-breaker round. However, Rin gives up all the plush dolls, except the Shinaider plush doll, to Tamaki.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86686" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルマジロとセンザンコウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Armadillo and the Pangolin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Armadillo to Senzankou</title>
<summary>Toraji takes Tamaki to the hospital while the other members of the Muroe High kendo club practice matches with each other. However, Miyako`s sword breaks, so Miyako and Eiga go shopping for a new bamboo sword at the kendo store. Tamaki meets Ishibashi at the hospital, while Miyako and Eiga meet Carrie Nishikawa, an expatriate living in Japan, who falls in love with Eiga at first sight. Ishibashi, taking Tamaki back to her house, tells her she must understand what it is like to lose a match. At the kendo store, Miyako challenges Carrie to a kendo match at the kendo dojo. Miyako notices that Carrie uses a double-sword technique, giving Carrie an advantage. Miyako loses the match, expectedly. As Carrie departs, she informs Miyako that she will return again.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86687" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大会とその後の室江高</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tournament and Muroe High After That</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taikai to Sonogo no Muroekou</title>
<summary>Toraji and Tamaki have a little talk and wounds are tended to. Since Tamaki and Konishi were both badly injured from their match, Kirino, from the Muroe High kendo club, and Aoki, from the Tozyo High kendo club, participate in a representative match. The tournament ends, with at a loss, due to Kirino`s lack of motivation and focus caused by her mother feeling better. The Muroe High kendo club is back at the kendo dojo as usual, with Sayako off somewhere and Tamaki all right.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86688" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光と陰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light and Shadow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari to Kage</title>
<summary>The tournament continues, with Tamaki seemingly in trouble with the other team`s treacherous plots. Konishi, a girl from the Tozyo High kendo club, purposely causes Tamaki to trip over tennis balls, inflicting an injury on her foot. Meanwhile, Azuma encounters a little bit of stomach troubles, ending her match in a tie, and Miyako is continuously haunted by Reimi`s face, ending her match in a loss. Sayako does her duty to relieve Kirino`s burden, and Kirino does her part as the team`s captain. When Tamaki steps up, she has a little payback in store for Konishi.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86689" update="2013-11-17">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キリノの欠席と予選大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kirino`s Absence and the Preliminary Tournament</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirino no Kesseki to Yosen Taikai</title>
<summary>The Muroe High kendo club faces against the Tozyo High kendo club. Kirino is worried by home troubles while the rest of the team worries about her, however. Sayako, sharing a deep connection with Kirino, is prepared to step up for the win and ease Kirino`s burden. Despite these troubles, however, Kirino seems even more focused than ever, gaining her a win in her match against her opponent. Meanwhile, Tamaki is pulled into a deceitful web by a few girls from the Tozyo High kendo club.
Source: Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="88183" update="2013-09-12">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふぁんふ~ふふぇ~ふぉ スペース★アズマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funfuufufefo Space Azma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88243" update="2013-09-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88363" update="2013-09-12">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふぁんふ~ふふぇ~ふぉ さやの疾走の失踪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funfuufufefo Saya no Shissou no Shissou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108248" update="2013-09-13">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154036" update="2013-09-13">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154037" update="2013-09-12">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154038" update="2013-09-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">番宣スポットコレクション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV-Spot Collection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bansen Spot Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154039" update="2013-09-12">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふぁんふ~ふふぇ~ふぉ 特別篇 その②</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funfuufufefo Tokubetsu Hen Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154040" update="2013-09-12">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2008-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふぁんふ~ふふぇ~ふぉ 特別篇 その①</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funfuufufefo Tokubetsu Hen Sono 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154042" update="2013-09-13">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Clip: Only Track</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154043" update="2013-09-13">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154044" update="2013-09-13">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154045" update="2013-09-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154046" update="2013-09-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154047" update="2013-09-13">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Blade Braver Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154048" update="2013-09-13">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Blade Braver Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196894" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">バンブーブレード: CM「ふぁんふ~ふふぇ~ふぉ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bamboo Blade: CM Fanfu-Fufe-Fo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bamboo Blade: CM "Fun Fu Fufe Fuo"</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
