<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5373" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2008-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch R2</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Код Гиас: Восставший Лелуш R2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Código Geass: Lelouch da Rebelião R2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Código Geass R2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Code Geass: Lelouch da Rebelião R2</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Kodas Geass: Leloušio sukilimas R2</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Code Geass: Lelouch`un Başkaldırısı R2</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Code Geass: Cuộc khởi nghĩa của Lelouch R2</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Код Геас: Бунтът на Люлюш 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Code Geass R2</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Код Ґіас: Повстання Лелуша</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">叛逆的鲁鲁修 R2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">CG R2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">cg2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Code Geass 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">geass2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">R2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">cgr2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">コードギアス 反逆のルルーシュ R2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">Code Geass 反叛的魯路修 R2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Code Geass: Lelouch of the Rebellion R2</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Code Geass: Lelouch of the Rebellion R2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Code Geass R2</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Code Geass R2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">코드기어스 반역의 를르슈 R2</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">โค้ด กีอัส ภาคการปฏิวัติของลูลูช R2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">Code Geass 反叛的鲁鲁修 R2</title>
<title xml:lang="mn" type="official">Код Гиасс: Лелоүшийн Бослого Р2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4521" type="Prequel">Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch</anime>
<anime id="8914" type="Alternative Setting">Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch - Nunnally in Wonderland</anime>
<anime id="12567" type="Alternative Setting">Gekijou Soushuuhen Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch</anime>
<anime id="7127" type="Summary">Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch R2 Special Edition - Zero Requiem</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5903" approval="8" total="18">Kidou Senshi Gundam 00 (2008)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="177">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="289891">This was the biggest waste of my time. The anime is an attempt to create a smart ass story plot which failed miserably. The main character is an obnoxious feminine looking aristocrat who tries to psychoanalyze everything and everyone. When an author who does not have a slightest idea about topic and tries to improvise this is the kind of nonsense he creates. DO NOT WASTE YOUR TIME.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="17776">Very dramatic and eventful, starting very promisingly but only to descend into a complete farce, dealing only in cheap sensationalism and cowardly cop-outs time and time again. Recommendable only to viewers of the first season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="276626">ALL HAIL LELOUCHE!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="638942">Definitely action packed. Problem is story has full of holes. Must not use your brain too much and just let the story go otherwise u will feel like "oh come on really?" And be turned off.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="561489">Must see for all.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="287993">I have mixed feelings about this anime. I loved the first season which is just brilliant. But this 2nd season has a poor storyline : a mix of action, fan service and incredible reversals. The whole season is based on these successive surprises effects.
But still, I could hardly stand the one week wait between each episode. So I think you should watch this season if you liked the first one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="258993">Amazing</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="447748">Buena secuela aunque no mejor que la anterior</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="316063">the best anime ever</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="131441">Well lot to say about it , i like the twisted part of it and the conspiracy in every direction ... i saw it because it is recommended to me and the idea was its like "death note" i will tell you its note but its good watch and you will enjoy it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="345948">The best freaking end ever! They anounced a new season which is not directly related to the story, but I doubt it will be as nearly as good as those two.
My favourite anime...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="460841">If one can say season 1 stayed on ground and earthly, then this season 2 went up high and soaring.
The English contents of S1 are better, but still an exceptionally the best Anime of it`s year. Or even beyond.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372933">Highly recommended</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="212661">For an anime that tries to do everything genre-wise.  It sure does it well.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="289742">good direction</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="19040">good continuation of the first season</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="182192">After watching up to episode 5 the plot seems o be taking off really well.  Definitely recommend this to anyone who has seen season 1.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="175892">Best  tactical anime very, has a great story and surprises the watcher every time :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="304057">The best anime ever, you must see this</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="78194">You just can`t miss this anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="347030">Same reason as the first season &amp;lt;3&lt;br /&gt;Story plot is totally unexpected and caught me off guard</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="348479">You will regret it if you dont watch the best ever anime in the history of anime!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="249432">TOO GOOD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="352524">MUST WATCH ! One of best storyline I`ve ever seen in the history of anime and whatsoever else ! You might as well jump off a bridge if you call it boring :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="121129">Its Orgasmic!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="172977">A masterpiece</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="298033">Very cool anime, good looking, with lots of plottwists</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="173182">Very good story and animation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="68948">Never has an anime moved my emotions as much as Geass R2.&lt;br /&gt;I would recommend everyone watch this anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="87917">EPIC MASTERPIECE</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="367836">I consider this show to be the closest to perfect.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="420280">I dare to say it`s even better than S1!
Sublime ending to a great story!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="430077">The best of the best. EVERYTHING is amazing. I believe i`ve nothing else to say to describe this true piece of art.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="375849">This series is so awesome,that it`s impossible to tell exactly why is it that great. First - character development done really good. Second - the story takes such turns,that you could never expect to see! Animation is on the highest level and seiyuu have done a great job at voicing their characters. Definitely a must see!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="314141">wow wow wow</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="482981">Jumped in my "top 3". The whole series had a great impact on me, it challenges one`s thought. The ending, the last episode left me astounded and choking with surprise.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="439927">Best anime I`ve ever seen... It`s a must.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="299048">It`s everything!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="509507">A must see for every anime fan out there. If you like awesome protagonists and great plot then you will like this. The epicness in this anime is definetly over 9000.
At first, I was reluctant whether to watch it or not due to it being mecha (im not particularly fond of mecha) however it become one of my favorite anime of all time.
PS: The awesomeness starts after episode 5</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="433878">Great story with a fitting ending.
Every action taken by the main character results in a consequence, unpleasant ones by the most part, but that`s part of this show`s appeal. Zero`s world is a harsh and lonely one.
Worth watching without a doubt.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="400353">MUST SEE</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="573488">MUST SEE!
Amazing plot, amazing characters, amazing end, amazing.. whatever, everything it`s amazing!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="445819">Total masterpiece... the end was exactly how it needed to be and was perfect, some unanswered questions  pertaining to certain subjects but with what was being dealt with that`s also how it should be.

The first and second season are both perfect and should be an absolute must see on anyone list.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="521116">WOW, this anime was MINDBLOWING, from start till end, it was full of so much hard decisions, twists and turns. Just incredible, everybody that loves to be on the edge of his seat from start right to the very end, should watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="232629">Epic, master piece, legendary, amazing, excelent, blah blah blah...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh, and C.C. is &amp;lt;3</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="576556">As some other people I had hard time deciding if I should watch it because I`m not a fan of the mecha genre but now I`m happy I`ve done it :). 
Code Geass has some annoying characters and some times you can find some plot holes (as in any other work) but if you can get past them you will be rewarded a lot by this anime. It has one of the greatest endings I have ever seen and I`ve seen a lot.
So if you are wondering if you should watch this anime just do it you won`t regret it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="545305">Its a masterpiece, definitely one of the best out there. A nice combination of everything plus a story with a definite conclusion. I`ve already watched it more than 3 times but it is still fun to watch. A word of advice though, don`t watch it right after Death Note. You`ll enjoy it much more this way.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="578744">first season was a masterpiece the best anime and this season is even better than the first and the ending ohh the ending...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="415527">This is for sure the most intelligent series EVER MADE! The first one was great but this one is OUT OF THIS WORLD!!!

You just HAVE to watch it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="301144">One of the best storylines possible, i definitely didnt see the end coming. The Best, must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="755022">Simply great sequel to already great R1.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="229284">MASTER OF SUPREMACY, IT`S REALLY A PITY IT`S OVER!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="218519">Must see.  Second season guaranteed to be EPIC.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="91057">great plot, great animation. it`s code geass, what`s not to like?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="66009">best show in this season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="301597">If you watched the first season, you should know wat I`m talking `about. Thought everything ended that way? Naw...It`s just a begining XD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="129689">really good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="259124">This is one of the best series ever ! You just need to see it ! Masterpiece !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="305044">Absolute masterpiece. 11/10.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="212177">Perfect plot, plot turns, character developement...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="21975">A good story... very good</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="141099">One of the best anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="300347">One of the best animes I have ever seen.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="235999">the right word would be epic&lt;br /&gt;intelligent, clever, sustentative&lt;br /&gt;its like deathnote with mechas&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;everything is better with mechas :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="180353">It is overrated for a reason, now go watch one of the best anime in the world! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All hail Lelouch!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="288344">All things is perfect!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="147924">The storyline is amazing!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="94701">One of the best anime ever!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="276876">must see... just must see))</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="306442">Brilliant!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="354503">Best ever watch it it`s an order :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="313872">Watch it, love it, recommend it!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="232400">this anime is the BEST ONE OUT THERE!!!!!! Must see isn`t even worth it. If u haven`t seen this, then u have not lived.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="383828">Best in its category.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="354280">An excellent continuation of a great series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="396363">All Hail Lelouch!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="223888">goooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooood</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="190028">The anime has a high level of intrigue and battles are fought with intelegience, tactics and logics as much as strong arms. The ever-twisting plot lines, and the even more twisted characters make this anime a worth watch, this combined with the very well made art, animation and plot make this anime a must-see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="373701">The hero Lelouch is just so epic ! Prepare yourself to have your innocent mind changed to a devil one. :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="433672">Much more better than first season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="134012">If you saw the first you must see this as well,if you didnt than you must see the first :P</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="318940">The first season was a killer, but this knoks out EVERYTHING off the charts. Perfect animation, perfect sound, amazingly deep storyline, incredible ending.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="92752">Masterpiece. The first Anime I have rated 10 / 10 (and I have seen close to 150)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="386693">Best...series...ever!!! 100%</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="429965">for me, i can say, one of the best anime i`ve ever seen! excellent fights, excellent plot, one of the best endings i`ve seen in my life! i totally recommend it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="586959">Just as amazing as the first the ending is what makes it a masterpiece</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="474803">This is one of those must watch anime. its a masterpiece, no other word can explain it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="108395">Not many 2nd season is far greater than an epic 1st season ... Must see!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="408512">My favorite anime ever. Terrific storyline.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="361412">Bets ending in an anime, probably will stay like that. Loses some atmosphere from the first part though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="464550">as good as the first sequel!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="484961">I just finished watching the whole Code Geass series and I must say out of the many anime series I`ve watched, this is by far my favourite! The characters and plot are well thought out and I especially love the character design. Plus the ending will completely blow your mind away!!!!! Any anime fan MUST see this series!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="480622">Code Geass is the best of All the Anime.
No time is wasted on the story. Efficient use of time. Well planned story.

Lelouch is the master all behind the protagonist that accidentally create chaos and tragedy. At first look to this type of mecha robotic it`s doesn`t attract me, but whenever I follow up to the story, it bring a lot of shock and surprise. It did give me wonder about the overall story, and made me feel to watch it over. Truly, no other anime could match this anime. If and only if you could understand the anime, you`ll think it`s great. Otherwise you`ll need to watch it repeatedly.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.geass.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1" type="Direction">Taniguchi Gorou</name>
<name id="665" type="Character Design">Kimura Takahiro</name>
<name id="1857" type="Series Composition">Ookouchi Ichirou</name>
<name id="9182" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakou Yukie</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
<name id="1824" type="Music">Kuroishi Hitomi</name>
<name id="1652" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakada Eiji</name>
<name id="1655" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakatani Seiichi</name>
<name id="2256" type="Chief Animation Direction">Chiba Yuriko</name>
<name id="665" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kimura Takahiro</name>
</creators>
<description>It`s been one year since the failure of the Black Rebellion and the supposed death of http://anidb.net/ch1697 [Zero]. Britannia has assigned Area 11 a correctional education status, where Elevens are made an example of by brute force, to try to prevent any future uprisings and suppress rebellious thoughts. Unsuspecting high school student http://anidb.net/ch103 [Lelouch], oblivious to his rebellious past as Zero, stumbles upon a scheme on his life and the life of a mysterious woman known as http://anidb.net/ch45 [C.C.], who reveals to him his forgotten purpose and his true self. Destroying his assailants and declaring himself Zero once again, Lelouch sets out to finish what he started.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="13185">8.98</permanent>
<temporary count="13607">8.80</temporary>
<review count="17">7.60</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221572.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9173</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18881</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>8728</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2904</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5163</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>9591</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4014</identifier>
<identifier>xdqvbg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.geass.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Code_Geass</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>コードギアス_反逆のルルーシュ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1343</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330074</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9853</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2008/codegeass_r2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10514</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B06ZY3XKMD</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-25">
<name>contractor</name>
</tag>
<tag id="904" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-18">
<name>eccentric</name>
<description>Because normal people are no fun.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-08">
<name>ambitious</name>
<description>having a strong desire for success or achievement; wanting power, money, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1291" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-01">
<name>aristocrat</name>
<description>An aristocrat or noble is a member of the aristocracy or nobility, an upper class in feudal societies. Nobles may or may not hold any specific nobility title. For simplicity`s sake, royalty should also be considered nobility.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2756" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>board games</name>
<description>People here play a board game. It can vary from chess and Go, to Monopoly, to Dungeons and Dragons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2917" parentid="2756" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>chess</name>
<description>Chess is a game for two players. It is played on a square board, made of 64 smaller squares, with eight squares on each side. Each player starts with sixteen pieces (eight pawns, two each of knights, bishops, and rooks, and one king and queen). One player`s pieces are a light color, he is called "White", and the other player`s pieces are a dark color, he is called "Black".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2945" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-03-03">
<name>Japan centre of the world</name>
<description>A crisis is about to hit the Earth, but only Japan can resolve the world-wide threat. Thus the story revolves around the happenings in Japan, almost exclusively — the rest of the world and all other nations are irrelevant secondary cast for the most part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3088" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-31">
<name>manipulation</name>
<description>When someone else is pulling the strings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3245" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-05">
<name>strategy</name>
<description>Instead of blindly running into a battle or trap, at least one of the protagonists devises a clever strategy to significantly improve the odds of victory.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3295" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>world domination</name>
<description>"Gee, Brain, what do you want to do tonight?"
"The same thing we do every night, Pinky: try to take over the world!"
A main objective for one of the characters is absolute control of not just one country, but a whole planet!</description>
<picurl>38878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3611" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-12-06">
<name>evil empire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3958" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>coup d`etat</name>
<description>A coup d`état (/ˌkuːdeɪˈtɑː/; French: blow of state; plural: coups d`état), also known as a coup, a putsch, or an overthrow, is the sudden and illegal seizure of a government, usually instigated by a small group of the existing state establishment to depose the established government and replace it with a new ruling body. A coup d`état is considered successful when the usurpers establish their dominance. If a coup fails, a civil war may ensue.</description>
<picurl>10266.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3981" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-27">
<name>ninja maid</name>
<description>This is an old tag for anime which had characters that were maids and also ninjas, or at least able to use ninjutsu. The tag will be removed once all maids in question are properly tagged. See also the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninja,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninja and maid] and the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninjutsu,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninjutsu and maid].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4308" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-26">
<name>delayed death</name>
<description>The Final Battle has begun. The two opponents square off, and one of them hits the other with a series of mighty blows that would fell a mountain. But what`s this? Nothing seems to be happening! That`s when your opponent tells you that You Are Already Dead, right before your head explodes, your body separates in two, or you disintegrate into a fine mist. If you`re unlucky, only one of those happens. Sometimes, you may also discover that you were Made of Explodium.
A common trope in martial arts series, this involves some form of Finishing Move that does not take effect immediately. When used with martial arts, it may involve Pressure Point attacks or some form of Ki Attacks. Assassins may use Universal Poison to achieve a similar effect. In video games, Damage Over Time abilities often have this effect.
When used with swords there are a number of common variations, often shown with a Diagonal Cut. In sword duels, the two sides charge each other and attack. There will be a pause as the two pose, then one (or both) will fall down. Another one is for a Master Swordsman to perform a series of lightning-fast slashes, and then slowly and dramatically sheath their sword (with an audible *click*) before their attacks take effect.
This trope is not necessarily limited to martial arts, either. In more modern settings, gunshot wounds can often have this effect, since getting shot typically feels like getting punched hard and it is not uncommon for victims to take some time to realize it. This can be exploited for dramatic effect in war movies, where fatally wounded soldiers wander the battlefield before succumbing.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4851" parentid="4340" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>group suicide</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4933" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-26">
<name>loyalty</name>
<description>Loyalty is faithfulness or a devotion to a person, country, group, or cause.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5407" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-30">
<name>Pacific Ocean</name>
<description>The Pacific Ocean is the largest of the Earth`s oceanic divisions. It extends from the Arctic in the north to the Southern Ocean (or, depending on definition, to Antarctica) in the south, bounded by Asia and Australia in the west, and the Americas in the east.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192046.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5907" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-26">
<name>origami</name>
<description>Origami (折り紙, from ori meaning "folding", and kami meaning "paper"; kami changes to gami due to rendaku) is the traditional Japanese art of paper folding, which started in the 17th century AD at the latest and was popularized outside of Japan in the mid-1900s. It has since then evolved into a modern art form. The goal of this art is to transform a flat sheet of material into a finished sculpture through folding and sculpting techniques, and as such the use of cuts or glue are not considered to be origami. Paper cutting and gluing is usually considered kirigami.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="45" type="main character in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="1733">8.55</rating>
<name>C.C.</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>C.C. is an immortal girl who outwardly appears to be little more than 16 years old. She becomes Lelouch Lamperouge`s accomplice when he makes a Geass contract with her. She is willful almost to a fault, usually doing whatever she wants regardless of whether or not it inconveniences others, particularly with Lelouch. She also likes to withhold information, usually telling people just enough to leave them wondering. C.C. has a strong penchant for pizza, especially Pizza Hut`s; she constantly orders pizzas to Lelouch`s house using his credit card.</description>
<picture>15902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103" type="main character in" update="2012-07-17">
<rating votes="1943">8.60</rating>
<name>Lelouch Lamperouge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="337" type="main character in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="938">7.91</rating>
<name>Kouzuki Kallen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kallen Stadtfeld is a Britannian-Japanese girl, who believes herself to be a Japanese person at heart and prefers to be known by her birth name, Kouzuki. Her father is Britannian and her mother is an Eleven; her father comes from a prestigious Britannian family, which Kallen benefits from. Her brother, Naoto Kouzuki, with whom she had a deep connection, was a former leader of her resistance cell before his death.
Kallen is a highly-skilled Knightmare Frame pilot, rivaling the abilities of even the Knights of the Round. She is acknowledged as the best pilot of the Black Knights by enemies and allies alike. Her codename, "Q-1," is the Queen`s starting spot in descriptive chess notation. In Lelouch`s assessment of the core members of the Black Knights, her "Combat Ability" score is 100 out of 100, matching that of Kyoshiro Tohdoh; she also has the highest possible "Loyalty" score of 100.
Even when piloting outdated Knightmare Frames such as the Glasgow, Kallen proves to be a dangerous opponent easily defeating numerous Sutherlands, despite the Sutherland being a more advanced Knightmare. With the radiation arm of her Guren Mk-II, Kallen can take down almost any Knightmare Frame in a single attack should they allow her to make physical contact, and later models also have numerous secondary attack modes for mid- and long-range combat. Her Knightmare Frame is also incredibly fast, allowing her to fight on the same level as some of the most advanced Knightmare Frames in the series.
Outside of a Knightmare, Kallen displays superior fighting abilities. She is nimble enough to swat a bee with a single swipe (and cut it in half), and on two occasions she defeats numerous armed men with little trouble. She is also apparently intelligent, since her grades in school are top of the class despite frequent absences.</description>
<picture>14626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="338" type="main character in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="647">2.47</rating>
<name>Kururugi Suzaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>14627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1697" type="main character in" update="2019-09-10">
<rating votes="705">8.84</rating>
<name>Zero</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shortly after gaining the power of Geass from C.C., Lelouch assumes the secret identity Zero, a mysterious, masked revolutionary dressed in a black helmet and cloak. The helmet has a retractable plate over the left eye so Lelouch can use his Geass. In this guise, he forms the Order of the Black Knights, initially composed of the members of Kaname Ohgi`s resistance group. The goal of this vigilante group is a campaign against powerful individuals who oppress the helpless, which he eventually expands into reforming Japan as an independent nation.</description>
<picture>238152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1750" type="main character in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="114">2.22</rating>
<name>Rolo Lamperouge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lelouch`s younger brother and also a student at Ashford Private Academy. However, that is his fake identity. He is actually an assassin who was hired by the Intelligence Service to watch over Lelouch. But he was won over by Lelouch because he felt that Lelouch understood his complicated origins as an assassin. He has the Geass power that stops time.</description>
<picture>16324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1999" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-27">
<rating votes="89">5.62</rating>
<name>Schneizel el Britannia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Schneizel el Britannia is the Second Prince of the Holy Britannian Empire and the Prime Minister of Britannia. He is one of the primary antagonists of the series and a strategist on par with Lelouch, as he is the only person whom Lelouch was unable to beat in chess as a child. Schneizel is ruthless and cold as a strategist, willing to sacrifice lives without a second thought to achieve his ends, but he is also very charismatic and caring toward his subordinates. He seems to show disdain for force when it is unnecessary, as he negotiates a peace treaty with the Euro Universe despite dominating them in every military engagement.
When Lelouch becomes Britannia`s 99th Emperor, Schneizel, alongside the Black Knights and other soldiers opposing Lelouch, confront him. Upon Schneizel`s defeat, Lelouch uses his Geass on him to make him follow Zero`s orders, having anticipated that Suzaku would take on the persona after Lelouch dies.</description>
<picture>16775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="633" picture="33549.jpg">Inoue Norihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2000" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-07">
<rating votes="187">2.78</rating>
<name>Nunnally Lamperouge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nunnally was born Nunnally vi Britannia, daughter of the Emperor of Britannia, Charles zi Britannia, and Marianne vi Britannia. She was 87th in line of succession to the Britannia Throne. When her mother was assassinated, Nunnally was paralysed by bullet wounds, and went blind due to psychological trauma of witnessing the brutal murder of her mother. Lelouch believes that she may be able to see again someday. After the confrontation between Lelouch and the Emperor of Britannia about the murder of their mother, both Lelouch and Nunnally were exiled to Japan as political prisoners.</description>
<picture>16784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2238" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-26">
<rating votes="249">6.20</rating>
<name>Shirley Fenette</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the members of the student council at Ashford Academy. She is also on the swimming team. She shows concern for Lelouch.</description>
<picture>17408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2239" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="191">5.74</rating>
<name>Milly Ashford</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lelouch`s senior and the president of the Ashford Academy student council. She likes to play tricks and cause the student council members trouble, but is really a reliable "older sister" to everyone. Her grandfather is the chairman of the Ashford Academy.</description>
<picture>17410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2242" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="93">6.02</rating>
<name>Rakshata Chawla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rakshata Chawla is an Indian scientist who secretly backed the Kyoto Group before becoming the head of the research and development team of the http://anidb.net/ch2353 [Order of the Black Knights], where she was tasked with developing Japanese Knightmare Frames. She has extensive experience in medical cybernetics. Though she is not fond of speaking of the past, Rakshata is known to have studied at the Imperial Colchester Institute. She is fairly laid back in most situations, usually seen laying on a couch when not actively working, and is never seen without her tobacco pipe. She is visibly enraged, a contrast to her normal demeanor, upon learning that http://anidb.net/ch15098 [Lloyd] and http://anidb.net/ch15096 [Cecile] modified the Guren without her consent. She used to be a colleague of Lloyd`s, but parted ways with him. Upon the formation of the http://anidb.net/ch15673 [United Federation of Nations] and the reorganization of the Order of the Black Knights as its military force, Rakshata is designated as the Chief of Science, a post similar to her previous position within the Order. She reacts to the Black Knights` betrayal of Zero with apathy, being more concerned with the aftermath of the affair. She is captured and imprisoned along with the rest of the Black Knights after the fall of http://anidb.net/ch1999 [Schneizel]. Rakshata is the creator of the http://anidb.net/ch8835 [Guren Mk-II] and of its upgrades, and its most powerful weapon, the so-called "radiation wave", is her original idea. She also developed the Gefjun Disturber, a force field generator that disables all sakuradite-powered technology within its area of effect. In http://anidb.net/a5373 [the second season], Rakshata also creates the http://anidb.net/ch15615 [Shinkirou] for http://anidb.net/ch1697 [Zero]`s personal use.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>17413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="634" picture="18161.jpg">Kurata Masayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2243" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="55">5.83</rating>
<name>Anya Alstreim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anya Alstreim is Knight of Six in the Knights of the Round and pilots the heavy assault Knightmare Frame, Mordred. She is a quiet and introverted person with a mysterious past and has a Britannian emblem tattooed on her left arm. She holds the distinction of being the youngest individual ever appointed to the Knights of the Round at the age of 15. She wants to be remembered, so she maintains a log/blog which she frequently updates with pictures she takes with her camera-phone. As one of the younger members of the Knights of the Round, she is close friends with Kururugi Suzaku and Gino Weinberg. Suzaku`s cat Arthur also takes a liking to her, though the cat seems to be more affectionate to everyone except Suzaku himself.
In the past, she went to stay in the palace as an apprentice for a proper etiquette and witness Marianne`s death at the hands of V.V.. It is also assumed that it was how Lelouch`s photo was in her camera-phone.
Anya maintains a detached attitude in most situations, usually declaring most things to be boring or dull. In battle, her fighting style reflects her heavily-armored Knightmare; she annihilates her enemies with overwhelming force and doesn`t hesitate to kill disabled enemies. However, this detached attitude also gives her a lack of common sense; she had piloted her personal Knightmare Frame just for the sake of capturing Lelouch`s hat to gain extra club budgets, disregarding the fact that she was piloting her Mordred in a non-combat area and had aroused the suspicion of the Knight Police, as well as forgetting the fact that she is to be a couple with Lelouch if she gets his hat.</description>
<picture>17414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2244" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-11">
<rating votes="153">5.72</rating>
<name>Cornelia li Britannia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cornelia li Britannia is the second princess of the Britannia Empire. After Clovis is assassinated, she is appointed as governor of Area 11. She has two loyal confidantes; Andreas Darlton and Gilbert G.P. Guilford. She has an obsession with her younger sister Euphemia.</description>
<picture>17415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2247" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-11-10">
<rating votes="54">5.34</rating>
<name>Li XingKe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An aide-de-camp of the Chinese Federation. He was stationed in Area 11 as an attendant to Gao Hai, one of the High Eunuchs. He has the intelligence that equals Lelouch, and combat skills that match Suzaku.
However, the one thing he lacks is time; Xingke is cursed with a chronic illness, frequently coughing up blood.</description>
<picture>17420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2248" type="appears in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="8">1.21</rating>
<name>Gao Hai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the "High Eunuchs," a group of government officials that substantially rules the Chinese Federation. He was dispatched to Area 11 as consul general. He welcomed the Black Knights in the consulate when he was controlled by Zero`s Geass, but Li Xingke saw this as disloyalty to Tien Zi and had him executed.</description>
<picture>17421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="636" picture="18163.jpg">Sekine Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2250" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="31">3.36</rating>
<name>Tianzi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The young empress of the people of the Chinese Federation. But she holds no actual power; the ones who control state affairs are the High Eunuchs.</description>
<picture>17424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="635" picture="18162.jpg">Matsumoto Tamaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2251" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="11">4.50</rating>
<name>Zhou Xianglin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the aide to Li Xingke. When Xingke is on the battlefield, she commands the troops.</description>
<picture>17425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2252" type="appears in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="5">2.34</rating>
<name>Hong Gu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A soldier who stood with Li Xingke to fight against the High Eunuchs. He has a longstanding quarrel with Xingke.</description>
<picture>17426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2258" type="appears in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="36">3.54</rating>
<name>Arthur</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A stray cat which Third Princess Euphemia befriends after she arrives in Area 11.</description>
<picture>17436.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2261" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="57">4.78</rating>
<name>Shinozaki Sayoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Originally she was a maid working for the Ashford family, taking care of Lelouch and Nunnally.
She participated in the Black Knights behind the scenes as a spy for Diethard. She went missing after the Black Rebellion, but is currently on duty in secret. She is a person of mystery.</description>
<picture>17438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2264" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-07">
<rating votes="201">1.41</rating>
<name>Nina Einstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced as a bookish member of the student council at Ashford Academy. Nina demonstrates an acute xenophobic reaction to Elevens and is initially intimidated by Suzaku when he arrives in the school. She develops an obsessive crush on the Third Princess Euphemia.</description>
<picture>17442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2265" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="85">3.39</rating>
<name>Rivalz Cardemonde</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lelouch`s friend. He takes Lelouch out on his favorite sidecar often.</description>
<picture>17444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2271" type="appears in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="10">4.00</rating>
<name>Kanon Maldini</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A subordinate of Schneizel el Britannia, serving as a political and military adviser.</description>
<picture>17451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="632" picture="18159.jpg">Mito Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2273" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="191">7.36</rating>
<name>Villetta Nu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A dark skinned elite Knightmare Frame pilot and subordinate of Jeremiah Gottwald, though she is more collected than Jeremiah in battle. She is not of noble blood, but supports Jeremiah and the Purist faction as she believes she can earn a title of nobility through them.</description>
<picture>17449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2275" type="appears in" update="2009-01-12">
<rating votes="33">1.58</rating>
<name>Bartley Asprius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A portly and balding Britannian general who commands the Code R research team.</description>
<picture>17455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2279" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="167">6.57</rating>
<name>Jeremiah Gottwald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young officer and one of the "purists" who believe that the Britannian Forces should only consist of Britannians. He pilots the Knightmare Frame, Glasgow.</description>
<picture>17460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2280" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="53">3.64</rating>
<name>Gilbert G.P. Guilford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of Cornelia`s closest subordinates. He is loyal and follows Cornelia`s orders coolly and accurately. His distinctive characteristic is his glasses.</description>
<picture>17461.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="631" picture="25817.jpg">Kouno Yoshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2353" type="appears in" update="2009-01-14">
<rating votes="38">8.36</rating>
<name>Kuro no Kishidan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A revolutionary group started by Zero/Lelouch to overthrow Brittania. It is a group that is said to "protect those without power from those that have it".</description>
<picture>2408.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="8621" type="appears in" update="2010-04-02">
<rating votes="3">6.67</rating>
<name>Knights of the Round</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Knights of the Round are a unit of the twelve most elite Knightmare Frame pilots in the Britannian Empire. They operate outside the normal chain of command of the Britannian Military, and are answerable only to the Emperor himself. They are considered nobility within the Empire, regardless of who or where they might have been before. The Knights each pilot a custom Knightmare Frame named after one of the Knights of the Round Table in Arthurian legend. Each member is given a rank of one to twelve, however, these numerical ranks are largely meaningless as an indicator of authority or skill level except for the Knight of One, who is considered the strongest warrior of the Empire, and has the right to request governance of a colony of his or her choice from the Emperor. Only eight of the twelve seats are filled throughout the course of the series.</description>
<picture>29920.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8636" type="appears in" update="2014-04-03">
<rating votes="148">8.85</rating>
<name>Koutei Lelouch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8835" type="appears in" update="2014-10-17">
<rating votes="4">6.69</rating>
<name>Guren Mk-II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Guren Mk-II is a Knightmare Frame model designed by Indian engineer Rakshata Chawla, manufactured by Japan, and built by the Kyoto House. It is radically different from its Britannian counterparts, and its technology is on par with most seventh generation Knightmare Frames, a fact that is a source of pride for its manufacturers. The later Gekka models were based on the Guren`s technology. Unlike Britannian made Knightmare cockpits, the Guren Mk-II features an unconventional pilot seat shaped in the form of a motorbike seat, and a helm-like outgrowth surrounding its retractable head.
The Guren Mk-II`s main weapon is its silver right hand. The hand stands out from the otherwise red-painted mech, terminating in clawed fingers, and it can extend at the elbow for a surprise attack. Stored within the palm is the Fukushahadou, a powerful microwave radiation emitter. By grabbing onto an enemy Knightmare and activating the emitter, the Guren Mk-II can fry the enemy`s electronics and warp the frame itself, not only rendering the unfortunate machine completely unsalvageable, but often damaging the pilot`s ejection system, usually ensuring that the pilot will perish with his craft. While not designed as such, the Fukushahadou can also function as a shield. It has been shown to block the lances of enemy Knightmares, bullets from Knightmare rifles, and a shell from the Lancelot`s VARIS rifle, though the latter damages the arm on the first attempt. The arm is destroyed in the battle of Tokyo, but is replaced with a slimmer, three-fingered version in the second.</description>
<picture>28207.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8836" type="appears in" update="2014-10-17">
<name>Guren Kashoushiki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>After being defeated in battle by Suzaku Kururugi`s Lancelot Conquista, the Guren Mk-II receives an upgrade in mid-battle through a series of rocket mounted attachments.
This model most obvious change is the addition of a Float System, allowing it to fly, and a Radiant Wave Shielding system. The Float System attachment includes aesthetic changes to the head, adding antennae on the sides. It also gains a new "armor-piercing bombardment-type" Fukushahadou arm which matches the Knightmare`s color scheme, though the forearm is still predominantly silver. The new Fukushahadou arm can fire radiation blasts at long ranges or over wide areas while maintaining its close-range blast. Another addition to Guren`s arsenal is the Gefjun Net, a series of rocket-mounted drones launched from the back of the Guren that release a Gefjun Disturber surge. The Lancelot Conquista had countermeasures preventing complete shutdown when exposed to the Disturber, but even it is still slowed down by the surge.</description>
<picture>28208.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8837" type="appears in" update="2014-10-17">
<rating votes="8">6.96</rating>
<name>Guren Seiten Hakkyokushiki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Guren S.E.I.T.E.N. Eight Elements uses the energy wing system similar to that of the Lancelot Albion, but with four energy "feathers" instead of three. The wings can also serve as cutting weapons. The system allows the Guren to move at blinding speeds, such that it appears to be little more than a purple blur in flight.
Its radiant wave surger arm has gold highlights on the fingers and forearm, and has been upgraded significantly. It can be fired like a Slash Harken, and has a Harken Booster for controlled flight. The arm still functions when launched as such. Its original functions are retained and far more potent: the ordinary radiation burst can block a Hadron Cannon blast with seemingly no effort and the hand can crush energy shielding without the aid of the emitter. It is also capable of firing disk-like radiation projectile. The Guren`s fork knife is also upgraded, having been retrofitted with MVS capability and made about twice as long. Its MVS (which is colored purple as opposed to the usual red) is evidently more potent than normal versions, as it can cut through the Lancelot Conquista`s MVS swords.
The Guren S.E.I.T.E.N. Eight Elements-Type
Additional armor is also present on the knees and ankles. The antennae have been extended and enlarged, making them appear to be giant ears. Its chest is completely different, with the orange part extended further and a pair of green jewels featured prominently on the front. Its namesake comes from its operation system, which is Superlative Extruder Interlocked Technology Exclusive Nexus (S.E.I.T.E.N.) Eight Elements. It also is equipped with two Slash Harkens attached to it`s shoulders.</description>
<picture>28209.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8838" type="appears in" update="2009-06-09">
<rating votes="3">3.50</rating>
<name>Mordred</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Mordred, named after the Knight of the Round Table; is a heavy-artillery Knightmare Frame piloted by Knight of Six, Anya Alstreim. It has an integrated Float System enabling flight. The Mordred exchanges speed for armor, making it highly durable; it is able to take a direct hit from the Gekka`s Katen Yaibatou without even being scratched, whereas any other Knightmare would have been sliced in half. The same cannot be said for the Float System, which can be sheared through with ease. It possesses two sets of Hadron Cannons mounted on each shoulder, which are unfolded and merged into a quad-barrel cannon called the Stark Hadron Cannon, focusing their power into a single blast capable of obliterating an aerial cruiser in a single shot.
The Mordred also possesses miniature proximity missiles, fired from the chest and hips, which leave purple trails behind as they move. Although lacking in close-range weapons, the Mordred`s raw strength allows it to crush other Knightmares with ease.</description>
<picture>28210.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9992" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="66">5.44</rating>
<name>Sumeragi Kaguya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sumeragi Kaguya is the 14-year-old head mistress of the Kyoto House (15 during R2), and a supporter of the Black Knights. Kaguya is Suzaku`s cousin, and met Lelouch and Nunnally during their childhood at the Kururugi Shrine. She is the representative of Sumeragi Concern, a large conglomerate founded by the Sumeragi House. Despite her age and physique, she possesses a strong will and is highly influential amongst the Houses. She is named after Kaguya, the main character of what is considered to be the oldest Japanese folktale.
Kaguya has admired Zero since his debut, and wishes to have his hand in marriage. She claims to be his wife in the second season, though she admits that they are only husband and wife in name. She doesn`t mind him dallying with other women; she claims "a true hero enjoys physical pleasures," and proceeds to suggest that she, Kallen, and C.C. are Zero`s harem, noting their likeness to the Three Court Ladies.</description>
<picture>30147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10629" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-06">
<rating votes="93">4.00</rating>
<name>Charles zi Britannia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Charles zi Britannia, at first only referred to as The Emperor of Britannia (ブリタニア皇帝, Britannia Koutei), born August 4, 1955 a.t.b., is Lelouch`s father and the 98th Emperor of the Holy Britannian Empire as well as one of the main antagonists of the series. He has 108 different consorts. A strong proponent of Social Darwinism, he views equality as an evil that must be dispelled, and to this end he encourages class conflict and military expansionism so as to maintain social evolution and progress. He also suffered a horrific childhood of his family murdering each other for succession, forging a pact with his brother V.V. to create a world without lies. Acquiring allies in Marianne and C.C., Charles created the Sword of Akasha, a weapon designed to facilitate the Ragnarök Connection, remaking the world into a place without lies by killing "God", which is the collective individual unconsciousness of all mankind.
However, when V.V. murdered Marianne and denied his part in her death, Charles was forced to alter the memories of Nunnally before sending her and Lelouch to Japan as political hostages during the sakuradite conflict. Since then, the Emperor focused more on his goals while having his remaining children deal with Britannian matters. Eventually after taking V.V.`s code to become immortal, Charles starts up the final preparations of the Ragnarök connection, revealing the entire truth and that C.C.`s code is the last piece to complete the plan. However, Lelouch sees Charles` ideal world to be nothing more than stagnation that would doom mankind rather than save it, and he uses his Geass to break collective unconsciousness from the connection while having his father dissolve into nothingness. With his last breath, Charles warns Lelouch his rejection of the world he envisioned would only allow Schneizel`s to become a reality.
The Emperor initially possesses a Geass power given to him by V.V. which allows him to suppress memories and create false ones through eye contact. It can also suppress the Geass power of the target, even if it is permanently active. This power, however, is not unbreakable. A victim`s true memories can be supplied by someone else or recalled by extraordinary force of will; doing so will break the Geass and restore any Geass the victim may possess. It can also be broken with a Geass Canceler. During Lelouch`s assault on the Geass Order, he takes on V.V.`s "Code," exchanging his Geass for immortality. The Code mark is situated on his right palm.</description>
<picture>131276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11341" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="69">6.18</rating>
<name>Toudou Kyoushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toudou Kyoushirou is the head of the Black Knights` military operations, and an extremely talented fighter in his own right. He earned the nickname Toudou of Miracles for his singular defeat of the otherwise unstoppable Holy Britannian Empire during the invasion of Japan, remarkably managing this feat without the use of Knightmare Frames. This event would later be known as the Miracle of Itsukushima. He was a childhood instructor to Kururugi Suzaku, and is one of the few Japanese people who understands his ideals. Toudou is often seen bearing a katana at his side.
Toudou is initially a member of the Japan Liberation Front, and resigns himself to death when the organization is wiped out. Zero convinces him to join the Black Knights in order to fulfil the promise of victory created by the Miracle of Itsukushima. Like Kaname, he remains faithful to Zero following his capture during the Black Rebellion, reasoning that Zero must have had a good reason not to inform his troops about his plans. He later leads Black Knight forces in liberation operations throughout the Chinese Federation and the Middle East before being named Chief of Staff of the newly reorganized Black Knights which serve as the national army of the UFN. Asahina`s last transmission about Zero`s massacre helps fuel his doubts about trusting Zero, which influences him when Schneizel reveals Zero`s identity to them. After losing a battle with Suzaku and being gravely wounded, he attempts to go back to the battlefield despite Nagisa Chiba`s pleads, but collapses because of his injuries.
Toudou and the remaining Black Knights are made prisoner and later taken away for public execution along with Schneizel and the U.F.N representatives. When Suzaku assassinates Lelouch as the last part of the Zero Requiem, a shocked Toudou appears to realize what has happened, voicing aloud his confusion. Before he can finish the thought, Kallen asserts that the Zero before them is the real Zero. He is last seen together with Chiba in traditional Japanese attire in a photo of Kaname Oogi`s wedding with Villetta Nu.</description>
<picture>33779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4689" picture="170829.jpg">Takada Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15093" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="80">4.18</rating>
<name>Chiba Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiba Nagisa is the sole female member of the Four Holy Swords. Nagisa is a devoted follower of Tohdoh and is enamored of him. A year after the Black Rebellion, she harbors animosity towards Zero for abandoning them. She survives the final battle but is captured along with all the other Black Knights for a public execution. She is released when Lelouch is killed and is seen together with Tohdoh in traditional Japanese attire in a photo of Kaname Ohgi`s wedding.</description>
<picture>48332.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15094" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="84">2.80</rating>
<name>Ougi Kaname</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ougi Kaname is the leader of the original resistance cell. He took over leadership following the death of Kallen`s older brother, Kouzuki Naoto (紅月ナオト), leaving his teaching job to do so. He is a somewhat reserved individual who lacks self-confidence, often questioning his ability to lead. However, he is also fairly perceptive, recognizing Zero`s intentions to a degree and even deducing some of the things he keeps secret from the organization. Kaname turns over leadership of his resistance cell to Zero after Zero proves himself the more competent and effective commander. When Zero reorganizes the Black Knights, he appoints Ohgi as deputy commander.
Following a battle in which the Japan Liberation Front is all but wiped out, Ohgi finds Villetta Nu left for dead at a ship dock. He nurses her back to health, and lets her live with him when she cannot remember who she is. Though he knows she has seen Zero`s face (Villetta having said so when he recovered her), he cannot bring himself to kill her or use Refrain to recover her memories. Over time, he falls in love with her. During the Black Rebellion, Ohgi is shot by Villetta, who has regained her memories.
Despite being captured in the Black Rebellion, Ohgi maintains his faith in Zero, knowing that Zero alone can liberate Japan. During the opening ceremony for the second Special Administration Region in Japan, he prevents Villetta from being shot. She suspects it is him, but he doesn`t confirm her suspicions and bids her farewell. Later, Villetta arranges a meeting with Ohgi, intending to kill him to erase her links to the Elevens. Ohgi comes knowing full well what she intends to do, and confesses his love for her. Villetta is captured during an altercation with Sayoko and held hostage by Diethard to ensure Ohgi`s loyalty, but is set free shortly after the second battle of Tokyo is cut short. She and Ohgi help convince the leaders of the Black Knights that Schneizel`s claims are valid. However, Ohgi adamantly insists that Japan be freed if they betray Zero, feeling that he couldn`t forgive himself if any less came of it. Diethard notes that it is in Ohgi`s nature to protect, not lead, and considers his new leadership role a "miscast." During the battle against Lelouch, he has Villetta stay on Horai Island, telling her that he was the first to acknowledge Lelouch and that he doesn`t want to get new lives involved, as she is pregnant. He marries Villetta at the end of the series, and is elected Prime Minister of Japan.</description>
<picture>48321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15095" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="75">2.01</rating>
<name>Tamaki Shin`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamaki Shin`ichirou is the leader of the second special squadron of the Black Knights. He is hot-headed, carefree and the self-proclaimed best friend of Zero, quick to cheer others on when not doing the fighting but rash and impulsive when he`s on the front lines. His rashness is shown to border on recklessness, as he orders the execution of the Ashford Academy student council against Zero`s wishes, though extenuating circumstances prevent his orders from being carried out. He pilots a standard Knightmare during battles, but is rather inept at that; his frame is the first to be destroyed by Suzaku`s Lancelot in the first season and in all encounters after that, Tamaki is rather comically dispatched very early in battle, which ends up hurting his pride in the end of the second season (the only time Suzaku needs more than one strike to defeat him).
Tamaki dreams of being a bureaucrat, and states that if he didn`t have his dream to aim for, he would probably have become a Refrain user. He is initially skeptical about Zero, but comes to be one of his most vehement supporters, particularly after the Specially Administrated Zone of Japan fails. Even after being captured and imprisoned for a year following the failed Black Rebellion, he never gives up hope that Zero will rescue them, despite the fact that Zero was reported as dead.
Tamaki seems to be the most critical of C.C.`s involvement in the organization during the first season, due to her lack of an official position, and accuses her of being Zero`s lover. In the second season, this appears to have been lightened into simple back and forth banter. Tamaki also complains about his own lack of an official position in the second season (what happened to his old position is not revealed), wanting to be in charge of finances in some way (Lelouch relieved him of this responsibility early in the first season when he spent much of their money on frivolous dinners for recruiting). With the formation of the United Federation of Nations and the Black Knights` appointment as its unified army, Tamaki is made the Internal Cleaning Supporter. When Lelouch is exposed as Zero, Tamaki takes it the hardest, being the last to accept that Zero could have manipulated them all this time. At the end of the series, Tamaki opens his own bistro alongside Sugiyama, Minami, and Villetta and is last seen standing right next to Ohgi in Ohgi and Villetta`s wedding picture.</description>
<picture>48329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15096" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="153">5.40</rating>
<name>Cecile Croomy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cécile Croomy is Lloyd`s subordinate in Camelot and one of the Lancelot`s developers. She is a capable scientist in her own right, having designed the energy wing system used on the Guren Seiten and the Lancelot Albion. Cécile is a kind-hearted woman and a good friend to Suzaku, often helping him with homework. She also acts as Lloyd`s conscience, not hesitating to scold him or physically punish him for his unintentionally rude remarks or treating Suzaku as a "part". Cécile is a capable Knightmare Frame pilot, managing to single-handedly hold the entire contingent of Black Knights sent to occupy Ashford Academy during the Black Rebellion at bay using a Sutherland modified with equipment from the Lancelot. Prior to joining Lloyd in the military, she studied at the Imperial Colchester Institute.[4] Following Lelouch`s ascension to the throne, she follows Lloyd and Suzaku and willingly accepts Lelouch as the new emperor. A recurring joke is that Cécile is a bad cook, though no one has the heart to tell her; her recipes include onigiri mixed with blueberry jam and sandwiches made with ginger, sugar and wasabi.</description>
<picture>45009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15097" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="98">4.50</rating>
<name>Diethard Ried</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diethard Ried is the head of information, espionage, and public relations for the Black Knights. A graduate of the Imperial Britannia Central University`s Faculty of Law, Diethard is a former producer and member of the press staff at Hi-TV, a Britannian television station. Following the appearance of Zero and the announcement of his goals, Diethard joins the Black Knights, wishing to witness and document Zero`s campaign to overthrow Britannia. Like Kallen Stadtfeld, he shows fierce loyalty to Zero, whom he views as his source of inspiration. He harbors contempt for the Britannian Imperial Family and its supporters, on occasion commenting to Rakshata Chawla that "Britannia is a finished product" and that he would rather take part in creating something new.
Diethard has proven himself to be highly perceptive, easily picking up on the likely outcomes of Zero`s plans. He recognizes immediately that Zero is responsible for the destruction of the Japan Liberation Front`s tanker ship, a fact of which Zero never made the organization aware. However, this same trait also causes him to overreach himself, most evident in his ordering an assassination attempt on Suzaku Kururugi after being instructed otherwise by Zero. When Kallen wonders if he can be trusted, Lelouch replies that Diethard is dedicated to making Zero a god, which makes him predictable and thus easy to control.
Despite possessing some knowledge of who Lelouch is and of his power, Diethard remains loyal. Only when Lelouch is exposed in front of the leaders of the Black Knights does he finally betray him. He claims that he would rather have watched Zero topple Britannia, but will settle for a hero`s death instead. When finding Lelouch proves difficult following his escape, Diethard suggests reporting him as dead, noting that even if Zero came back he would have no credibility without support. He defects to Schneizel following this, deciding that Schneizel and his plans are more interesting than Zero`s. When Schneizel is placed under Lelouch`s control, Diethard flies into a rage, holding Lelouch at gunpoint and claiming that Zero`s story is dead. Schneizel shoots him in the heart before he can pull the trigger. In his dying moments, Diethard asks Lelouch to use his Geass to kill him, to which Lelouch responds that Diethard isn`t worthy of having a Geass order cast upon him.</description>
<picture>48324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15098" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="146">6.08</rating>
<name>Lloyd Asplund</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lloyd Asplund is an earl of the Britannian nobility and the head of the scientific research team Camelot, which is responsible for the development of the elite Knightmare Frame Lancelot. To keep from being reminded of the fragility of human lives and friendship, Lloyd immerses himself in science and comes to view people as nothing more than tools — he regards Suzaku, for example, as a mere component of the machine that he pilots. He has a tendency to mock others and is often rebuked for this behavior by Cécile Croomy, his assistant. Prior to joining the military, he attended the Imperial Colchester Institute.[4] Lloyd`s research organization, Camelot (キャメロット?), is an irregular division of the Britannian Military that has permission from Prince Schneizel to operate outside the command structure and regulations of the regular Britannian armed forces.
Rakshata refers to Lloyd as the Earl of Pudding (プリン伯爵?), as pudding is his favorite food. He is engaged to Milly Ashford in the first season, having agreed to the union mostly in the hope that he might obtain the designs of the Knightmare Frame Ganymede. As such, he is forced into doing nice things for her by Suzaku, though Milly breaks off the engagement after she graduates in order to become more true to herself.
After the second battle of Tokyo, he is confronted by a distraught Nina after she realizes the fatalities caused by her F.L.E.I.J.A. Lloyd tells her that she has to make a choice between saving her heart and morals or discard them for science. When asked by Nina if he had already made that choice, he replies that he never had such a problem due to himself being a sociopath. He willingly joins Lelouch`s new regime, remarking that he and Cécile have become "parts" without ever realizing it. He and Cecile are among the few who know the details of the "Zero Requiem", Lelouch`s plan to unite the world. He expresses an interest in studying Lelouch`s Geass, but he is warned off by Jeremiah. He works with Nina and Cécile to create a countermeasure to F.L.E.I.J.A. and assists Sayoko during the rescue of the hostages on board the Avalon (as ordered by Lelouch). He and Cécile are last seen in Ohgi and Villetta`s wedding picture.</description>
<picture>4166.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15564" type="appears in" update="2014-10-17">
<rating votes="12">7.50</rating>
<name>Lancelot</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Lancelot is the first seventh-generation Knightmare Frame, an experimental prototype developed by Lloyd Asplund. It is the personal Knightmare Frame of the Knight of Seven Kururugi Suzaku.</description>
<picture>44179.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15615" type="appears in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="5">4.48</rating>
<name>Shinkirou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Shinkirou (lit. Mirage) is a unique eighth-generation Knightmare Frame built by Rakshata Chawla for Lelouch`s personal use. It possesses an Absolute Defense Field, which is an array of hexagonal energy fields driven by a Druid System that can be used to erect a powerful barrier with the proper calculations. The Field is strong enough to resist sustained fire from the Mordred`s Stark Hadron Cannon. Weapons include the Structural Phase Transition Cannon, where the Shinkirou releases a prism-like object into which a powerful beam is fired, which refracts it into dozens of deadly pinpoint lasers. It also has a pair of hadron blasters which fire powerful spherical globes of energy which are sufficient to destroy an unprotected Knightmare Frame in a single shot. It is also able to transform into a submarine, which Lelouch uses to secretly leave and return to Ashford Academy using the hidden underwater passageways beneath the school.</description>
<picture>44271.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15617" type="appears in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="10">8.03</rating>
<name>Shinsei Britannia Teikoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Holy Britannian Empire is an imperial monarchy and the most prominent superpower in the Code Geass universe. At the start of the series it controls well over one-third of the world: the entire Western Hemisphere (both American continents) as well as colonies known as "Areas" around the world, such as Japan (Area 11).
This organization entry is intended to cover only people who are part of the Britannian Empire in an official capacity, such as members of the nobility or imperial family or the military.</description>
<picture>44274.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15618" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="24">1.83</rating>
<name>V.V.</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>V.V. is a mysterious boy with blond hair longer than his body. He is the older twin brother of Charles zi Britannia, but looks much younger because he has gained the power of immortality through "Code", like C.C. Also like her, he can grant Geass contracts and gave both his brother and Rolo Lamperouge their Geass abilities, among others in the Geass Order. He succeeds C.C. in becoming leader of the Geass Order, a secret organization that studies and produces Geass users.</description>
<picture>44275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="615" picture="71459.jpg">Tomizawa Kazato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15619" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="4">5.40</rating>
<name>Geass Kyoudou</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Geass Order, also translated as the Geass Cult or Geass Directorate, is a secretive group that studies and produces Geass users. Its last known location is a large underground city, also called the Geass Directorate, which is within the Chinese Federation territory. It is currently under the control of V.V., and so presumably under Britannian influence.</description>
<picture>44277.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15620" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="39">2.51</rating>
<name>Marianne vi Britannia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marianne vi Britannia is the fifth wife of the Emperor of Britannia and the mother of Lelouch and Nunnally, titled the 98th Empress of the Holy Britannian Empire. She is nicknamed "Marianne the Flash" for her piloting skills, having been the test pilot for the Ganymede Knightmare Frame with the support of the Ashford Foundation, which was then a contender in the development of the first Knightmare Frame prototypes. Bismarck Waldstein claims that the only person he had to use his Geass against before Suzaku was Marianne, which shows that she must have been particularly skilled. When Lelouch was a child, she was assassinated within the Aries Palace, purportedly by terrorists, and the culprits were never found. The fact that the impenetrable security of the palace was powerless is what convinced Lelouch that her murder was no random act of terrorism.</description>
<picture>1312.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="628" picture="188442.jpg">Dodo Asako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15621" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="17">2.21</rating>
<name>Bismarck Waldstein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bismarck Waldstein is a man who bears the title of the Knight of One under Charles, the strongest amongst the Knights of the Round. He pilots the Knightmare Frame Galahad, and keeps one of his eyes hidden. Despite his status and combat abilities, he believes that war should be used as a last resort, and also sees strength without restraint as needless violence.</description>
<picture>44281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3290" picture="24305.jpg">Uchida Soumei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15673" type="appears in" update="2010-03-09">
<rating votes="2">6.62</rating>
<name>Chougasshuukoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>After the collapse of the E.U. and the revolt in the Chinese Federation, most of the territories not under the control of the Britannian Empire formed a loose coalition of states to contain Britannian expansion, known as the United Federation of Nations (UFN).
The UFN is composed of forty-seven countries spread across parts of Central and Eastern Europe, Eastern Africa, and the majority of the Asian continent. Decisions are decided by a two-thirds majority vote by the leaders of each country, voting percentage being proportional to population. Member nations have no national armies: all armed forces they may have had are subsumed under the Black Knights, which became the military arm of the Federation.</description>
<picture>44362.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15983" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<rating votes="7">6.80</rating>
<name>Ashford Gakuen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Ashford Academy is a Britannian private academy in Tokyo, owned and operated by the Ashford Foundation. It is attended by Lelouch and Nunnally, who, owing to their mother`s relationship with the Foundation, have been granted free residence in the campus` student club house.</description>
<picture>157647.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16299" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="32">3.08</rating>
<name>Gino Weinberg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gino Weinberg is the Knight of Three, a seventeen year-old Knightmare Frame pilot who comes from a noble family. He has lived a rather sheltered life as his family is very wealthy, and as such displays naïveté with how the world really works. To remedy this, he enrolls in Ashford Academy along with Anya Alstreim. He has a very cheerful personality and friendly demeanor. He pilots the transformable Knightmare Frame Tristan.</description>
<picture>45503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16369" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-04">
<rating votes="11">2.49</rating>
<name>Luciano Bradley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Luciano Bradley is the Knight of Ten, and is known by the sobriquet "the Vampire of Britannia". A violent and confrontational man, he is fond of antagonizing others and attacking without provocation; several of the Knights of the Round appear to dislike him. He shows little care for the lives he ends, be they friend or foe, as long as he can cause destruction. In fact, he fights battles specifically because it allows him to freely kill people in public, even attempting to sacrifice his allies for a fleeting tactical advantage. He claims to be a "homicide genius", and carries a number of large knives which he is adept at throwing. He is fiercely loyal to the Empire, but he does as he pleases most of the time, even around members of the Imperial family. He pilots the Knightmare Frame Percival.</description>
<picture>45675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="484" picture="17476.jpg">Kisaichi Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70692" type="appears in" update="2014-10-17">
<rating votes="2">6.18</rating>
<name>Lancelot Conquista</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Lancelot Conquista is an upgraded version of the Lancelot used by Knight of Seven Kururugi Suzaku. The Conquista is heavily damaged during the second battle of the Tokyo Settlement, after its encounter with the Guren S.E.I.T.E.N. Eight Elements.</description>
<picture>162831.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70693" type="appears in" update="2014-10-17">
<rating votes="2">6.18</rating>
<name>Lancelot Albion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Lancelot Albion is the final version of the Lancelot used by Knight of Seven Kururugi Suzaku.</description>
<picture>162833.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70694" type="appears in" update="2014-10-17">
<rating votes="1">8.62</rating>
<name>Monica Kruszewski</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Monica Kruszewski is a member of the Knights of the Round and is the Knight of Twelve.</description>
<picture>162834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70695" type="appears in" update="2014-10-17">
<rating votes="4">9.65</rating>
<name>Avalon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Avalon is one of the primary flagships used by the Britannian side throughout the series.</description>
<picture>162835.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="86099" update="2008-01-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Special 21 sec. teaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88395" update="2008-02-24">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">TV commercial 30 sec. trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88803" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="64">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔神 が 目覚める 日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day a Demon Awakens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Jour de l`Eveil du Démon</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il giorno in cui si risvegliò il demonio</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O dia em que o demônio acordou</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Diena, Kai Demonas Prabudo</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Şeytanın Uyandığı Gün</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majin ga Mezameru Hi</title>
<summary>It’s a year after the battle between the Black Knights and the Britannian army. Zero is dead, and only a handful of Black Knights remain. But Lelouch is alive with no memory of the last year. Is it a trick or all part of a greater plan?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="89063" update="2008-03-30">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 68 sec. trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89116" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="47">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">日本独立計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plan for Independent Japan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Plan pour un Japon indépendant</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Piano per l`indipendenza del Giappone</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O plano para a independência do Japão</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Japonijos Nepriklausomybės Planas</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Japon Bağımsızlık Planı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nihon Dokuritsu Keikaku</title>
<summary>With his memories back, Lelouch brings Zero to life once more. But there’s a year’s worth of work to rebuild and still many unknown variables. What new advantages will the Britannian army have against them, and is Zero up to the task to face them again?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="89117" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="38">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">囚われの学園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Imprisoned in Campus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En prison à l`Académie</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La presa dell`isituto scolastico</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Prisão Na Academia!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Įkalintoji Akademija</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kampüste Hapis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toraware no Gakuen</title>
<summary>Lelouch tries to get clues about Nunnally’s whereabouts, but no one around him remembers her. To find her, he’ll have to figure out his mysterious new brother, Rolo. But he’ll have to do it while maintaining the guise that his memory hasn’t returned.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="89118" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="37">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆襲の処刑台</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Counterattack at the Gallows</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Contre-attaque sur l`échafaud</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il patibolo del contrattacco</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Contra-ataque no patíbulo</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Kontrataka Per Egzekuciją</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Darağacında Karşı Saldırı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakushuu no Shokeidai</title>
<summary>Lelouch only has a short time to save the imprisoned Black Knights and regain his followers. But he also needs to figure out Rolo and his role in Britannian’s game. Will this boy and his Geass keep Lelouch from bringing back the Black Knights?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="89986" update="2008-04-09">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">15 second commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90061" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="38">8.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナイト オブ ラウンズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Knights of the Round</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Chevaliers de la Table Ronde</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Knight of rounds</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Knights Of Rounds!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Apvaliojo Stalo Riteris</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Knight of Rounds</title>
<summary>Suzaku returns to Ashford Academy to monitor Lelouch, determined to see if the other has regained his memories. Lelouch must take more care around the Britannian soldier. But when Suzaku plays an unexpected card, Lelouch’s guard may fall to pieces.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="90226" update="2010-01-08">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<rating votes="1">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">6 minute preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90500" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="43">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">太平洋 奇襲 作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Surprise Attack over the Pacific</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Guet-Apens au-dessus du Pacifique</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Operazione “Attacco a Sorpresa” sull’Oceano Pacifico</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Plano para um ataque surpresa no Oceano Pacífico</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Ramiojo Vandenyno Pasalos Operacija</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiheiyou Kishuu Sakusen</title>
<summary>Nunnally is set to be the new Viceroy of Area 11, and Lelouch will take every chance to get her back. But the reunion he wants may not go quite as planned. Has Nunnally chosen Suzaku over her beloved brother?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="90670" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="38">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">棄てられた 仮面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Abandoned Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le masque abandonné</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Giù la maschera</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A Máscara Descartada!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Palikta Kaukė</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suterareta Kamen</title>
<summary>When Nunnally reveals her plans on starting the Nippon special zone again, Lelouch realizes that he may no longer be needed at her side. Has Zero’s purpose been lost? Has the time come to drop the mask and stop his game?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="90671" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="36">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">百万のキセキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Million Miracles</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un million de miracles</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un milione di miracoli</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Um Milhão De Milagres!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Milijonas Stebuklų</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyakuman no Kiseki</title>
<summary>Zero agrees to join the Nippon special zone, much to the surprise of the Black Knights. He makes a deal with the Britannian army that will lead to his exile. But exile is the same as running away; has Zero forsaken the Japanese and his plans?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="90673" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="32">8.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">朱禁城の花嫁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Bride in the Vermilion Forbidden City</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une fiancée dans la Cité Interdite</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La sposa della città proibita</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A esposa de Zhu Jin Cheng</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Nuotaka Iš Uždraustojo Miesto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zhu Jin Cheng no Hanayome</title>
<summary>A wedding is set to occur between the empress of the Chinese Federation and the first prince of Britannia. If the Chinese Federation turns on the Black Knights, everything they’ve work towards could come to an end. Will Zero dare to crash a royal wedding?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="90674" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="30">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神虎輝く刻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When Shen Hu Wins Glory</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand brille le Shen Hu</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Quando splende lo Shen Hu</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Quando o Shen Hu brilha</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Šen Hu Šlovė</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shen Hu Kagayaku Toki</title>
<summary>Zero absconds with the empress, taking her out of the Vermilion City. Before he can get far, they are stopped by an unknown Knightmare. The Chinese Federation gains the advantage, taking one of the Black Knights hostage. Can the Knights afford the loss?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91185" update="2008-06-01">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9-10 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91186" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="30">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">想いの力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Power of Passion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La force des sentiments</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La forza dei sentimenti</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O poder dos sentimentos</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Širdžių Galia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoi no Chikara</title>
<summary>The Black Knights continue their fight against the Chinese, but the battle takes a turn for the worse when the Britannians back the Eunuchs. They no longer care about the empress’ wellbeing, meaning Zero may have lost his bargaining chip…and the battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91187" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="31">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラブ アタック!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Attack!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Love attack !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Love attack!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Ataque do amor!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Meilės Ataka!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love Attack!</title>
<summary>The Knights of Round have become students at Ashford Academy right as Lelouch has returned. But he has other worries, like the countless dates his stand-in set up while he was away. Lelouch must take on his next challenge—Cupid Day!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91297" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="47">9.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去 から の 刺客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assassin from the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`assassin venu du passé</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`assassino dal passato</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Assassino do passado</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Žudikas iš Praeities</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako kara no Shikaku</title>
<summary>Jeremiah seeks out Lelouch to end their dance once and for all. With his ability to cancel Lelouch’s Geass power, Jeremiah may be more of a threat than expected. Or will an unexpected connection change their dynamic?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91298" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="35">9.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギアス狩り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Geass Hunt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chasse au Geass</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Caccia al geass</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Caça aos Geass</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Geass`o Medžioklė</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Geass-gari</title>
<summary>With Shirley’s death hanging over him, Lelouch directs his anger towards the Geass power. He makes his first contact with the mysterious V.V. and declares war. Meanwhile, Suzaku plans to take drastic measures to force answers about Lelouch out of Kallen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91926" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="45">9.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">C の 世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cs` World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monde de C</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il mondo di C</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O mundo de C</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">C Pasaulis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">C no Sekai</title>
<summary>Finally, Lelouch comes face to face with his father. Everything he’s planned and schemed has led to this confrontation. But when C.C. shows up, suddenly the truth about his contract and her past change everything he thought he understood.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91927" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="32">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超合集国決議第壱號</title>
<title xml:lang="en">United Federation of Nations Resolution Number One</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Première résolution de la Fédération des Nations Unies</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La prima risoluzione dell’Alleanza degli Stati Uniti</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A 1ª Decisão Da União Federativa Das Nações!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Jungtinių Tautų Federacijos Rezoliucija Nr.1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chougoushuukoku Ketsugi Daiichigou</title>
<summary>The emperor is missing, and Zero takes the chance to ratify the United Federation of Nations. With the 47 nations involved, they will have enough backing to declare war on the Britannian Empire, finally freeing their countries. But nothing is ever so easy…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91928" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="33">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">土 の 味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Taste of Humiliation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De la terre dans la bouche</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il sapore della terra</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Um gosto de terra</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Purvo Skonis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuchi no Aji</title>
<summary>While the war rages on, Lelouch begs for Suzaku’s help in making sure Nunnally will be safe. But with the death of Euphemia and Shirley still heavy in his heart, will Suzaku be able to do this for Zero, the murderer, or is it for Lelouch, his oldest friend?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92148" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="41">9.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二次 トウキョウ 決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Battle Tokyo II</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La deuxième bataille de Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La seconda battaglia decisiva a Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A segunda batalha decisiva de Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Antrasis Žūtbūtinis Tokijo Mūšis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dainiji Tokyo Kessen</title>
<summary>The battle for Tokyo fills the sky. The Black Knights take out the power gaining temporary advantage, but when Suzaku appears, he threatens to use Britannian’s most terrifying weapon: the F.L.E.I.J.A. But to fire such a devastating weapon…is it worth it?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92455" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="39">9.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Betrayal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Trahison</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Tradimento</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Traição</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Išdavystė</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ทรยศ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri</title>
<summary>Nunnally is gone. Lelouch cannot deal with the grief, and as he locks himself away, Prince Schneizel calls a temporary ceasefire to reveal the truth behind Zero to his Black Knights. When they learn of his Geass, will this be the end of the Black Knights?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92457" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="35">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">皇帝失格</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emperor Dismissed</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`empereur démis</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`imperatore estromesso</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Inapto Para Ser Imperador!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Imperatoriaus Klaida</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ปลดจักรพรรดิ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutei Shikkaku</title>
<summary>Lelouch has lost everything and knows the only thing left is to take out his father, the Emperor. But he’s not the only one bent on seeking him out. Suzaku, on Schneizel’s orders, plans to assassinate the Emperor. What awaits the two on Kamine Island?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92458" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="54">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラグナレクの接続</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ragnarok Connection</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La jonction Ragnarök</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La connessione ragnarok</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A conexão do Ragnarok</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Ragnaroko Susijungimas</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การเชื่อมต่อแร็กนาร็อก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ragnarok no Setsuzoku</title>
<summary>Having trapped himself and his father, Lelouch finally demands the truth behind his mother’s death. When Marianne herself appears, everything that Lelouch thought he knew crumbles around him. It’s time to face the truth from the beginning.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92459" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="39">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">皇帝ルルーシュ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emperor Lelouch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lelouch Empereur</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Lelouch l`imperatore</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Imperador Lelouch</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Imperatorius Lelušas</title>
<title xml:lang="th">จักรพรรดิลูลูช</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutei Lelouch</title>
<summary>Lelouch has overtaken the empire, establishing himself as Emperor. He starts by abolishing the aristocracy and announcing Suzaku as the Knight of Zero. Lelouch announces that Britannia will join the U.F.N., but Schneizel makes an unexpected move.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92660" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="35">8.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シュナイゼル の 仮面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Schneizel`s Guise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le masque de Schneizel</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La maschera di Schneizel</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A máscara de Schneizel</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Šnaizelio Kaukė</title>
<title xml:lang="th">หน้ากากของชไนเซล</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Schneizel no Kamen</title>
<summary>Nunnally has declared Lelouch and Suzaku as her enemies. By siding with Schneizel she is allowing the use of the F.L.E.I.J.A., but she has been led to believe the destructive weapon would be used only when necessary. However, Schneizel has other plans
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92661" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="36">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダモクレス の 空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Grip of Damocles</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les cieux sous le Damoclès</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I cieli della Damocles</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O céu de Damocles</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Damoklo Dangus</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ท้องฟ้าแห่งเดโมเครส</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Damocles no Sora</title>
<summary>The Black Knights fight a close battle with Schneizel, neither side giving way. Before the F.L.E.I.J.A.’s can destroy them all, Lelouch must outsmart the brother he has never beaten and face the sister he has spent his life protecting.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92662" update="2019-10-23">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="108">9.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re;</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re;</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Zero Requiem</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Re;</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Re;</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">RE</title>
<title xml:lang="th">Re;</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re;</title>
<summary>Lelouch makes his final move; Zero Requiem takes action.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92897" update="2015-04-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2008-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93202" update="2011-05-25">
<epno type="5">P25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Parody of episode 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96821" update="2015-04-08">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2009-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106460" update="2009-08-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106461" update="2009-08-18">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108661" update="2015-04-08">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108662" update="2015-04-08">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108663" update="2015-04-08">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108664" update="2015-04-08">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108665" update="2015-04-08">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108666" update="2015-04-08">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2009-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108667" update="2015-04-08">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112153" update="2013-10-31">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112154" update="2009-12-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118587" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="3">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Flash "Baba Theater Redux" Short 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118588" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="3">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Flash "Baba Theater Redux" Short 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118589" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Flash "Baba Theater Redux" Short 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118590" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="3">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Flash "Baba Theater Redux" Short 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118591" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="3">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Flash "Baba Theater Redux" Short 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118592" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="3">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Flash "Baba Theater Redux" Short 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118593" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="3">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Flash "Baba Theater Redux" Short 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118594" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="3">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Flash "Baba Theater Redux" Short 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118595" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="3">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Flash "Baba Theater Redux" Short 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118637" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コードギアス 反逆のルルーシュ キセキの誕生日[バースデー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miraculous Birthday</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki no Birthday</title>
<summary>A festival is approaching, and Ashford Academy is busily and peacefully -- or as peacefully as it gets, anyway -- preparing to it. However, terrorists attack and seize control of the school, interrupting the students` activities. Now Lelouch and his friends must thwart the terrorist attack.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="126466" update="2013-10-31">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128488" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BD&amp;DVD発売記念FLASH ~きせきのBABA劇場~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Code Geass: The Miraculous Birthday Omake Flash "Baba Theater Redux" Short</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BD &amp; DVD Hatsubai Kin`en Flash: Kiseki no Baba Gekijou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195717" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S26</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Soubou no Oz Picture Drama 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195718" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Soubou no Oz Picture Drama 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195719" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Soubou no Oz Picture Drama 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195720" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Soubou no Oz Picture Drama 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195721" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Soubou no Oz Picture Drama 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225519" update="2020-01-08">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2015-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 10</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
