<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="540" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>1992-02-03</startdate>
<enddate>1993-01-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hana no Mahou Tsukai Marybell</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Floral Magician Mary Bell</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Flower Witch Marybell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mary Bell</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">花の魔法使いマリーベル</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Wróżka z Krainy Kwiatów</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">مغامرات نغم</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6070" type="Other">Hana no Mahou Tsukai Mary Bell: Phoenix no Kagi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/tv_series/w024.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="8320" type="Music">Ishiguro Takako</name>
<name id="4247" type="Series Composition">Mitsui Hideki</name>
<name id="2088" type="Series Composition">Koyama Takao</name>
<name id="5738" type="Direction">Endou Tetsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>This is a story about a Mary Bell, a little witch with a magical tambourine, and her two friends, Ken and Yuuri. With the help of Mary Bell`s magical power, Ken and Yuuri life is filled with magical adventures and music. And when everytown of SunnyBell is in trouble, Mary Bell with the help of her magical tambourine can transform into a superheroine (or supposedly a heroine...)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="59">4.37</permanent>
<temporary count="59">6.08</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>11580.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1659</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2804</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1113</identifier>
<identifier>rmhzhc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/tv_series/w024.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Floral_Magician_Mary_Bell</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>花の魔法使いマリーベル</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89057</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1050</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="92231" type="main character in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Marybell von Decasse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92232" type="main character in" update="2017-11-08">
<name>Tambourine</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65524.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92236" type="main character in" update="2017-11-08">
<name>Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65525.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92237" type="main character in" update="2017-11-08">
<name>Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92238" type="appears in" update="2017-11-08">
<name>Ribbon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97122" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Vivian</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>221492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97123" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Jito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66395.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97124" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Rose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>221493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97125" type="appears in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Tap</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97126" type="appears in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Takuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="338" picture="17174.jpg">Ono Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97127" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Bongo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3838" picture="25826.jpg">Satou Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97128" type="appears in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Bart</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>221480.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97129" type="appears in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Remi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97130" type="appears in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Bro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66397.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2405" picture="23217.jpg">Shioya Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97131" type="appears in" update="2018-08-04">
<name>Noppo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66396.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2244" picture="52187.jpg">Nagashima Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6007" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こんにちは! 私マリーベル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hi! I`m Mary Bell</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6009" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お隣さんは花嫌い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Neighbor Hates Flowers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6012" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">らく書き天国こんにちは</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hello, Graffiti Paradise!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6015" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">やっぱりケンはパパの子だ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ken Gets His Talent From Papa!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6392" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サニーベルの思い出の木</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tree of Memories in Sunny Bell</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7276" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">50万年目のケンカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Quarrel In The 500,000th Year</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10018" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大好き! ジュリア!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Love You, Julia!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11678" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">はばたけピッチー大空へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly High In The Sky, Peepchee!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12793" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精たちの桜祭り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cherry Festival of Fairies</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15143" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精ハンター・ジート登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fairy Hunter Jito Arrives</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24848" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリーベルのCMコンテスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audition for a TV Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25243" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フラワーハウスの大事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Huge Happening in Flower House</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26328" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">想い出のオモチャはど~こ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where`s My Old Toy?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26537" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボンゴの母の日プレゼント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bongo`s Mother`s Day Gift</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28001" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユーリに恋した王子さま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prince in Love with Yuuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30519" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">うちのパパはゲーム作家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Dad is a Game Producer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35493" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジートのわるだくみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jito`s Evil Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jiito no Warudakumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36061" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボンゴとタップの大航海!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bongo &amp; Tap`s great voyage?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bongo to Tappu no Daikoukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37346" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャンプは楽し!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Camping is fun!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyanpu wa Tanoshi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38016" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友情の一輪車レース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friendship in the Unicycle Race</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuujou no Ichirinsha Race</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38966" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">星の国から来たポーラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paula From the Starland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi no Kuni kara Kita Paula</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39409" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケンの初めてのお使い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ken`s First Try</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ken no Hajimete no Otsukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41579" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷子の迷子の人魚姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stray Mermaid Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maigo no Maigo no Ningyo-hime</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42600" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">またまたジートがやってきた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jito Appears Yet Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matamata Jiito ga Yattekita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44572" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユーリといたずらイルカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yuuri and The Mischievous Dolphin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuri to Itazura Iruka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45692" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">いるかいないかフェニックス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Does the Phoenix Exist or Not?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iru ka Inai ka Fenikkusu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46804" update="2006-03-04">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリーベルの絵本(えほん)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mary Bell`s Drawing Book</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mariiberu no Ehon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47332" update="2006-03-04">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビビアンと子猫(こねこ)のチャチャ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vivian and Chacha, the Kitten</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bibian to Koneko no Chacha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48091" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆうれい屋敷(やしき)の古時計(ふるどけい)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Old Clock in the Haunted Mansion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuureiyashiki no Furudokei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48092" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷(まよ)いの森(もり)のビビアン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vivian in the Forest Maze</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoi no Mori no Bibian</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48093" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フラワードアで大混乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Amazing Flower Doors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flower Door de Daikonran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48094" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">テーブルランプを取り返せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get the Table Lamp Back</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48095" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-09-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリーベルのパパとママ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mary Bell`s Papa and Mama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48096" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">子供になったローズさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rose-san Becomes a Child</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48097" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お菓子の家とおかしな二人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Candy House &amp; A Funny Couple</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48098" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリーベルの月世界旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moon Trip with Mary Bell</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48099" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケンと2本角のユニコーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ken &amp; the Two-Horned Unicorn</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48100" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タンバリンがつかまった!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tambourine Was Captured!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48101" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タンバリン救出大作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tambourine: The Great Rescue Operation!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48102" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コスモスの妖精を捜して</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Search of the Cosmos Fairy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48103" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">誘拐されたビビアン!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vivian is Kidnapped?!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48104" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">がんばれ! 愛のキューピット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go for It! Cupid of Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48105" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪の降る日の願いごと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wish upon the First Snow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48106" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トゲトゲ草パニック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prickly-Prickly Plant Panic</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48107" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジジベルサンタの大騒動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Santa Jiji Bell`s Big Fuss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48108" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議の国のマリーベル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mary Bell in Wonderland</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48109" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">がんばれ! タンバリン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go for it, Tambourine!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48110" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サニーベルの一大事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunny Bell in Big Trouble</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48111" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリーベルと聖なる樹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mary Bell and the Holy Tree</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48112" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢をあなたに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreams for You</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
