<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5406" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-01-09</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ookami to Koushinryou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">spice+wolf</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Spicy Wolf</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">spice&amp;wolf</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Wolf and Spice</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Wilk i Przyprawa</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">תבלין וזאב</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Vilkė ir Prieskoniai</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Aktar ve Kurt</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Kurt ve Baharat</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Вовчиця та спеції</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Вовчиця і спеції</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">狼与香辛料</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">SaW</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">SW</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">S&amp;W</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">otk</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">狼と香辛料</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Spice and Wolf</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Spice and Wolf</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Волчица и пряности</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">늑대와 향신료</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">狼與辛香料</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6465" type="Sequel">Ookami to Koushinryou II: Ookami to Kohakuiro no Yuuutsu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9287" approval="201" total="219">Maoyuu Maou Yuusha</anime>
<anime id="14727" approval="9" total="15">Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen</anime>
<anime id="575" approval="8" total="17">Kino no Tabi: The Beautiful World</anime>
<anime id="1" approval="4" total="17">Seikai no Monshou</anime>
<anime id="12450" approval="3" total="14">Zero kara Hajimeru Mahou no Sho</anime>
<anime id="4563" approval="2" total="59">Death Note</anime>
<anime id="3651" approval="2" total="36">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu</anime>
<anime id="11672" approval="1" total="5">Magi: Sindbad no Bouken (2016)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="67">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="423440">I dont get it. Anime about wolf godness and trade?Booooring(c)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="296539">I disliked this series because of Horo, who is so annoying I had to force myself to watch it, but the last scene of season 1 compensates this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="87307">Just finished watching this amazing anime. Short but sweet. I highly recommend it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="6433">Even though this doesn`t take place in the present and it includes supernatural beings, the best way to describe the flow of this series would be a "slice of life" series as we get to know and see the bond between the antagonists. Great character development.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="626835">One of the best Anime I ever watched.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="354280">A wonderfully original focus on economic events, blended with great characters and animation, make this a great show.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="14283">Very good, yet Special show. Something completely different for a change.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="314759">Sweet short anime with nice music.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="254176">Although the conversations about economical deals were a little boring , i liked it :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="332605">A character-centric show with many little clever twists.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="179096">Very Deep Adventure/Drama about a Wolf Goddess. Each arc is Thrilling but never ends will a cliffhanger. Very Mature anime Not in the Rating sense but in the understanding of it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="257215">A very different sort of Anime. More close to real world and daily life.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="101454">This is a charming show! &lt;br /&gt;The cast is great: a merchant, first obsessed by&lt;br /&gt; financial gain is progressively seduced by the apparently frivolous, sexy deity. &lt;br /&gt;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="308233">Definatly the right choice if you grow tired of your average school romance, shounen what ever anime. It`s fresh, interesting and well worth your time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="345634">Great anime. Not only about economy, but about love.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="471794">By watching this you will understand the true meaning of "storytelling". Recommended with a thumbs up .^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="104528">This is a MUST SEE Anime. It`s powerful yet funny too. Might be slow but it never feels over and it isn`t. A second season is greenlit and we hope for spring of `09</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="82150">Good quick watch, the protagonists are likable characters that make you want to know more about them. The story isn`t AWESOME but it`s good and will keep you begging for more. In all, an good show!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="596844">I really don`t want to spoil anything, but I have to warn you folks! Once you`ve watched season 1, you`ll be watching season 2... only to be seriously annoyed there is no more than that. Absolutely one of the best anime I have watched.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="261604">A must see!  It`s  a wonderful  story</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="208034">The best fantasy anime I`ve seen in a long time</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="432184">Just watch it! Why? Find out yourself and you`ll understand...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="80989">Beautiful love story! ^_^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="41516">Extremely well-written dialogue full of worldly wisdom turns the two leads of this show into one of the most profound and memorable couples in anime medium. Add the smart engrossing plot about the subtleties of medieval trading and you have one of the best anime out there. The only real detriment is that it will leave you longing for more due to its unfinished nature (though reading novels is still an option).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="281180">What you Expect: Wolf`s Rain. What you Get: Macro-Economics. But its a good story. And note to all: This series is based on 8-and-counting light novels. This season is based on the first two.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="181147">Loved this one, wishing for a season 2</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.spicy-wolf.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3673" type="Character Design">Kuroda Kazuya</name>
<name id="3211" type="Direction">Takahashi Takeo</name>
<name id="1558" type="Music">Yoshino Yuuji</name>
<name id="915" type="Animation Work">Imagin</name>
<name id="1432" type="Original Work">Hasekura Isuna</name>
<name id="3673" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kuroda Kazuya</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr1432 [Hasekura Isuna].
http://anidb.net/ch2818 [Kraft Lawrence] (Spice) is a travelling medieval merchant, who finds a 600-year-old pagan harvest deity named http://anidb.net/ch29 [Holo] (Wolf) in his wagon one night. She begins travelling with him, and her wisdom helps increase his profits. But her true nature draws unwanted attention from the church...
Note: The novel series won the Silver Prize in the 12th Dengeki Novel Awards. The story forgoes the traditional sword-&amp;-sorcery adventure element to focus on how people lived and did business in the Middle Ages.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="8920">8.37</permanent>
<temporary count="9029">8.38</temporary>
<review count="10">8.31</review>
</ratings>
<picture>233308.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8537</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2966</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3984</identifier>
<identifier>galvpu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.spicy-wolf.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Spice_and_Wolf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>狼と香辛料</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1310</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329450</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9700</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2100</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1391</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2008/ookami_to_koushinryou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10426</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10852</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B06Y1CFSKV</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3423" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>religious persecution</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3932" parentid="6073" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-11">
<name>older female younger male</name>
<description>This tag indicates that this anime has a male and female lead, and the female is older. If the main cast is greater than two people, then the use of this tag would indicate a romantic relationship between those two.
In case of harems it translates to:
a) majority of the girls are older than the guy
b) the lead girl (or her main rival) is older than the guy</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4202" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-17">
<name>contraband</name>
<description>The anime includes depiction of smuggling or smuggled goods.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4271" parentid="2876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-29">
<name>corrupt church</name>
<description>An official religion (not cult or sect) has become evil or was evil to begin with, and tends to be highly influential with political leaders, to strengthen / enforce the church`s power over the people.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4642" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-08">
<name>economics</name>
<description>Economics is the social science that studies economic activity to gain an understanding of the processes that govern the production, distribution and consumption of goods and services in an economy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29" type="main character in" update="2017-12-29">
<rating votes="2235">9.20</rating>
<name>Holo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Holo is a wolf harvest deity originally from a land in the north known as Yoitsu. She made a promise with men from a town called Pasroe where she would ensure the town would have good wheat harvests year after year. However, as time went on, the townspeople slowly started to forsake Holo and did not rely on her as they once did. As such, Holo escapes from town in Lawrence`s wagon and started traveling with him to see how much the world has changed since she has been in Pasroe. Holo has chosen the form of a girl younger than Lawrence, though she still retains her large white-tipped wolf tail, and ears. Her true form is that of a very large wolf which many people revered and feared.
She refers to herself as the "Wise Wolf of Yoitsu" (ヨイツの賢狼, Yoitsu no Kenrou). She is typically very haughty and self-sufficient, though due to her isolation for hundreds of years in Pasroe, she came to feel very lonely, and sometimes shows a more fragile side of herself. She relies on Lawrence for company as she fears loneliness, which is something that Lawrence is very aware of and tries to comfort her in his own way. Holo is also very aware of the different time spans that she and Lawrence have, as a human lifespan is like a blink of an eye for her kind. Holo is shown to be quite scared of that fact but hides it with jokes. She has a peculiar way of speaking, modeled after that of the oiran high-class courtesans. She is fond of delicious food and alcohol, but especially loves apples. She takes pride in her tail and takes special care of it, constantly combing and maintaining it.</description>
<picture>209420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2818" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="252">8.11</rating>
<name>Kraft Lawrence</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kraft Lawrence, who chiefly goes by his surname, is a twenty-five-year-old travelling peddler who goes from town to town buying and selling various things in order to make a living. When he was twelve, he became an apprentice to a merchant relative, and set out on his own at eighteen. His goal in life is to gather enough money to start his own shop, and he has already been travelling for seven years while gaining experience in the trade. He meets Horo one night and eventually agrees to her travelling with him. She helps him by providing her wisdom which helps to increase his profits and get him out of jams. As the series progresses, both Lawrence and Horo demonstrate a growing affection toward each other.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>42502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2819" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-01">
<rating votes="26">2.69</rating>
<name>Chloe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chloe is an anime-original character. She is a villager of Pasroe and has known Lawrence for a long time. In fact, Lawrence taught her how to be a merchant. Despite still not knowing how she should feel about him, she respects him as her teacher and a good friend. [Spoiler]They later break off their friendship when Chloe allies with the church to capture and kill Holo.[/Spoiler]
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>26967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7874" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-01">
<rating votes="77">7.77</rating>
<name>Nora Arendt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nora makes her first appearance in volume two of the novels. She is a skilled shepherdess from a church-town named Rubinhaigen. Her companion in this profession is a well-trained sheep dog named Enekk. She entrusts Lawrence with a task after they meet.</description>
<picture>26914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14872" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-07">
<rating votes="8">3.50</rating>
<name>Soren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious merchant that Lawrence and Holo meet on their journey when they visit a monastery. He suggests a "get rich quick" scheme to Lawrence involving reminted coins.</description>
<picture>42651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14876" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-07">
<rating votes="11">3.85</rating>
<name>Weiss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend of Lawrence`s who runs a money-exchange business. He has a fondness for women and takes a liking to Holo.</description>
<picture>42652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="277" picture="223606.jpg">Hanawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14877" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-07">
<rating votes="10">5.49</rating>
<name>Liechten Marheit</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The manager of the large Pattio branch of the Milone Company. He is a calm, cool, and collected man who speaks very politely. He agrees to cooperate with Lawrence after hearing his business proposal.</description>
<picture>42654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14878" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-07">
<rating votes="11">3.74</rating>
<name>Jacob Tarantino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The head manager of the Rowen Trading Company in Lubinheigen, of which Lawrence is a member. He is a longtime merchant who considers all the members of Rowen Trading Company to be his children. He has known Lawrence since Lawrence was still learning to become a merchant, and he is the one who gave him the nickname "Kraft".</description>
<picture>42656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14879" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-07">
<rating votes="8">2.09</rating>
<name>Hans Remerio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The head of the Remerio Trading Company in Lubinheigen. Lawrence procures a large quantity of armor goods and visits Remerio, but when he arrives the company entrance is extremely vacant and appears to be in trouble.</description>
<picture>42658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14880" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-07">
<rating votes="9">1.87</rating>
<name>Martin Liebert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is one of the leaders of the Remerio Trading Company. He accompanies Lawrence to the northeast to the city of Ramtora.</description>
<picture>42659.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="86192" update="2007-12-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86193" update="2007-12-29">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86619" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="35">5.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と一張羅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Best Clothes</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и выходной костюм</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i najlepsze ubrania</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Icchoura</title>
<summary>Kraft Lawrence, a 25-year-old traveling merchant, arrives at the town of Pasroe during its harvest festival. In the fields surrounding the village, Lawrence meets a girl claiming to be the legendary wolf deity, Holo. Lawrence, in disbelief, asks her to prove it so the girl returns to her wolf form before disappearing. Back in town, Lawrence meets with a younger girl named Chloe, a former student of his. She asks if she can become Lawrence`s business partner, but he declines, telling her that she is too young to make such a risky move. After leaving the town, Lawrence meets Holo again and learns that she escaped the town so that she can visit her homeland in the north. Lawrence agrees to let her accompany him on his travels.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86624" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="28">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と遠い過去</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Distant Past</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и далекое прошлое</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i odległa przeszłość</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Tooi Kako</title>
<summary>While taking refuge from the rain inside a nearby church, Lawrence and Holo meet a traveling merchant named Zeelen, who tells Lawrence of a plan to trade old silver coins for new ones to make a profit. Holo later tells Lawrence she sensed Zeelen lying, though neither she nor Lawrence know why he lied. The next day, Lawrence agrees to meet with Zeelen in the port city Patzuille to discuss further plans. After departing with Holo, Lawrence recounts how he was attacked by wolves `about eight times` in the forest. Holo defends the wolves` actions and Lawrence flares up in anger. After a lull in the conversation, Lawrence asks Holo if she has ever eaten a human, but she refuses to answer.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86917" update="2017-03-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅の途中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86965" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と商才</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Business Talent</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и деловая хватка</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i sztuka handlu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Shousai</title>
<summary>Lawrence and Holo arrive in Patzuille and prepare to sell fur before meeting with Zeelen. Passing through a street lined with shops, Holo purchases a large quantity of apples which leave a scent on the furs, allowing Lawrence and Holo to sell the furs at a higher price to the Milone Company. That night, Lawrence and Holo meet with Zeelen and finalize their partnership the following day, only later learning the purity in the silver has decreased, contrary to Zeelen`s claims.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="87012" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と無力な相棒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Her Helpless Partner</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и беспомощный компаньон</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i bezsilny partner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Muryoku na Aibou</title>
<summary>Lawrence enlists the help of the Milone Company to counter Zeelen`s scheme. However, men from the Medioh Company, Zeelen`s associates, try to ambush Lawrence and Holo at night. Holo and Lawrence flee to the Milone Company but Holo acts as a diversion so Lawrence can escape to safety. After arriving at safety, Lawrence is told that Milone Company has all the information needed to defeat Zeelen and the Medioh Company`s plan and no longer needs Lawrence. To compound Lawrence`s problems, a letter arrives from Medioh informing him that they know Holo is a wolf and are prepared to hand her over to the church.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="87013" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="21">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と痴話喧嘩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Lovers` Quarrel</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и любовная ссора</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i Kłótnia Kochanków</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Chiwagenka</title>
<summary>After negotiating with the leader of the Milone Company, Lawrence strikes a deal, rescuing Holo with the help of the Milone Company. Once freed, Holo tells Lawrence that Chloe has joined forces with the church and intends to turn Holo over to break away from the past when people depended on the favor of deities like Holo to survive. Noticing Holo`s escape, Chloe and the other church members begin to search for the pair, slowly encircling them.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="87014" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="21">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と無言の別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Silent Farewell</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и прощание без слов</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i Nieme Pożegnanie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Mugon no Wakare</title>
<summary>Holo and Lawrence are slowly surrounded by Chloe and the Medioh Company. A pursuer stabs Lawrence, slowing him and eventually causing him and Holo to become trapped. Chloe tries to convince Lawrence to hand over Holo in exchange for his life, but he refuses. To protect Lawrence, Holo transforms into her wolf form and rampages through their pursuers before disappearing as Lawrence blacks out. He awakens in the Milone Company headquarters, where he is informed that despite the vast profits, there were also vast losses in the coin venture, so there is little money left for him. Lawrence takes his payment in pepper but soon receives a bill for new clothes and apples. After realizing that Holo is still around, Lawrence reunites with her and they agree to continue their travels together.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="87015" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と正しき天秤</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Virtuous Scales</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и точные измерения</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i Uczciwa Równowaga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Tadashiki Tenbin</title>
<summary>Lawrence and Holo travel to the town of Poloson, where Lawrence sells the pepper he received from the Milone Company. During the exchange, Holo reveals that the man buying the pepper is attempting to swindle Lawrence. In exchange for not reporting the swindler, Lawrence receives more profit than he originally expected. While traveling to the church city of Rubenhaigen, Lawrence and Holo talk about future profit from the armor he received from the merchant and the illegality of smuggling gold. They pass a group of travelers who warn them of mercenaries from the north. Continuing on the road, they come across a female shepherd and stop to greet her, though Holo is less than enthusiastic because of the instinctive hostility between shepherds and wolves.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="87016" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="21">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と羊飼いの子羊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Shepherd`s Lamb</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и агнцы</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i Pasterka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Hitsujikai no Kohitsuji</title>
<summary>Just before Lawrence departs, the shepherd, Nora, asks him if he would hire her as an escort to protect the party from wolves. After a conversation with Holo, Lawrence does so and the group heads off towards Rubenhaigen. Upon arrival, Lawrence parts ways with Nora to sell the armor in his cart. As Lawrence passes the initial inspection and pays the tax for the two armor sets, he finds the city government reluctant to receive armor as payment. Lawrence and Holo head to the guild of which he is a member and are greeted warmly inside.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="88467" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と渦巻く陰謀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and the Swirling Plot</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и зловещий заговор</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i Wzrastający Spisek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Uzumaku Inbou</title>
<summary>After Lawrence procures a certificate from the guildmaster, he goes to an armor company to sell his armor. To his horror, he discovers that the armor market has crashed and that he now holds a very large debt and worthless goods. Faced with an ultimatum to pay back the debt in two days or be rendered bankrupt and thus be thrown out of society entirely, Lawrence desperately tries to find merchants willing to lend him money, but each and every one turns him down. He realizes the merchants are unwilling to aid him because of his unmarried relationship with Holo, and, in a fit of rage, takes out his frustration on her. Even after Lawrence tries to apologize to her, Holo tells him that she is heading back to the inn for now.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="88556" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="20">9.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と若僧の群れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and a Group of Youngsters</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и молодая стая</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i Młode Stado</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Wakazou no Mure</title>
<summary>Lawrence sets off to Ramtra with Nora, Holo, and Liebert, a Remerio businessman, to smuggle gold. Halfway through the forest, they are attacked by wolves, but Nora keeps them at bay. Upon arrival at Ramtra, Liebert retrieves a bag full of gold and the group begin their return trip. In the forest, they are surrounded by wolves again, this time led by a young wolf deity. Lawrence tells Nora and Liebert to go ahead. After they leave, Lawrence reluctantly departs as well to let Holo deal with the wolves. He waits for her near the edge of the forest but is attacked, tied up, and left for the wolves by three men from the Remerio Company, who hope to keep all of the profits from the smuggling for themselves.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="88557" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と最大の秘策</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and the Biggest Secret Scheme</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и грандиозная афера</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i Doskonały Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Saidai no Hisaku</title>
<summary>Lawrence scrounges a few coins, but he has nowhere near enough to repay his debts. He attempts to give them to Holo as an apology for his earlier behavior, but she rejects them and chides Lawrence for being too nice and not blaming her for his situation. The next day, the pair goes to Lawrence`s debt collector and proposes gold smuggling to get out of debt. Since the debt collector`s company has already failed and is also pressed for money, Holo drives him into a corner and he agrees with their scheme. Lawrence and Holo later meet with Nora and tell her about their plan to smuggle gold in her sheep`s stomachs, and, after some smooth-talking by Lawrence, she agrees.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="88624" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="21">9.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と新たな旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and a New Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и новое путешествие</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wilk i Nowa Podróż</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Arata na Tabidachi</title>
<summary>Lawrence burns the ropes binding him and reunites with Holo. She refuses to tell him what she did to placate the wolves` wrath, and then chides him again for being too nice and protecting her clothes instead of running away on his own. After being told of Liebert`s betrayal, Holo transforms into her true form. With Lawrence riding on her back, she catches up with their betrayers and Nora, who is still oblivious about the betrayal and their plan to murder her. Holo routs the men but spares Liebert, who reveals that Remerio betrayed them at the very beginning because the gold procured was only one-sixth of the intended profit. Lawrence uses this information to blackmail the president of the Remerio Company, extorting 500 gold coins over a period of ten years. Lawrence does, however, allow them to keep and use the smuggled gold to save the company from bankruptcy. After reassuring Holo of his devotion, Lawrence continues on his journey with her. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="88625" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と幸福の尻尾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and a Tail of Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Волчица и хвост удачи</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Koufuku no Shippo</title>
<summary>While in the town of Patzuille, Lawrence decides to purchase a better set of clothes for Holo. However, Lawrence only has a gold piece, too large denomination to purchase clothes. They return to Weiz, intending to exchange it for silver and agree to meet later at a tavern for drinks. Lawrence uses a "secret technique" to buy clothes for Holo that were once worn by a noble. He first buys cheap blankets at an inflated price to buy the expensive clothes at an extremely cheap price, made even cheaper by Holo`s charm. Though the clothing merchant makes a profit on the blankets, he loses money on the entire deal because of the more expensive clothes.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92378" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92381" update="2009-12-16">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD only Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93935" update="2010-03-06">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD only Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102650" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2 (Episode 12)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112114" update="2009-12-16">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112115" update="2009-12-16">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112116" update="2009-12-16">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112117" update="2009-12-16">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112118" update="2009-12-16">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112119" update="2009-12-16">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112120" update="2009-12-16">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
