<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="542" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>1994-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>1995-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Haou Taikei Ryuu Knight</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lord of Lords Ryu Knight TV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lord of Lords Ryu Knight</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">llrk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">RyuK</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">覇王大系リューナイト</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Adeos le chevalier vaillant</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="616" type="Alternative Setting">Haou Taikei Ryuu Knight: Adeu Legend</anime>
<anime id="2687" type="Character">Haou Taikei Ryuu Knight: Adeu Legend Final</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.sunrise-anime.jp/sunrise-inc/works/detail.php?cid=123</url>
<creators>
<name id="1945" type="Series Composition">Hoshiyama Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="4231" type="Original Work">Itou Takehiko</name>
<name id="3580" type="Direction">Kawase Toshifumi</name>
<name id="3626" type="Music">Ooshima Michiru</name>
<name id="6487" type="Character Design">Soeta Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="6488" type="Music">Kanezaki Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
</creators>
<description>In the fantasy world of Adeus Legend, knights, priests, magicians, ninjas all summon Giant Mechs with ability similar to their class to fight. This is a story about the growth and learning of a young knight. He starts out his adventure with an older knight mentor who has a mysterious past, then saves a princess and her priest companion and goes on a quest to reclaim her kingdom.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="144">4.59</permanent>
<temporary count="146">6.55</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>167407.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>908</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1848</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1051</identifier>
<identifier>umpoyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=123</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Haō_Taikei_Ryū_Knight</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>覇王大系リューナイト</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89013</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1033</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/254</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1994/ryuknight</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="226" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-21">
<name>priest</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3622" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>merchandising show</name>
<description>The bane of the parent`s wallet; this show usually has only a single reason for existence: to advertise the toy line it is based upon to the intended target audience. The variety of toys can range from accessories for girls and boys, to cards and figures or models. Most often the ability of the toys will be exaggerated or invokes magic to work in the anime. The toys`s names will also be continuously repeated in the anime, often accompanied by flashy effects and loud shouting. Combined with an intricate story that typically involves an adventure or a tournament of sorts, it makes for an effective commercial.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="6013" update="2007-05-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺がアデューだ!現われた騎士道ボーイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Adeu! The Chivalry Boy Makes His Appearance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6014" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍者は味方?もう一人いたリュー使い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is the Ninja an Ally? Another Ryu Wielder.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6555" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パッフィー大活躍!魔法使いのお姫さま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paffy Saves the Day! A Mage Princess</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13141" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">騎士道まっしぐらねらわれたリュー使い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Full Speed with the Chivalry! The Targeted Ryu Users!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chasse aux chevaliers Ryus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13239" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めての敗北森の中のすごい奴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Loss! - The Great Guy within the Forest!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le 2e défit d`Adeos</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13316" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アデュー再挑戦!相手は強敵リューチーフ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adeu`s Re-Match! - The Opponent is Ryu Chief!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13432" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">盗まれたリューエルフ村の大災難</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The stolen Ryu! - Big disaster at the elf village</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monstre Stantor</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13681" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵は美少女軍団!大河の前で通せんぼ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Enemy is a group of Beautiful Girls! - The Blockade before the River!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère du lac vert</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14230" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖のダンジョンリューナイトが動けない!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fearsome Dungeon! - Ryu Knight Can`t Move?!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14557" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下宮殿の闘い突破口を切り開け!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle at the underground palace! - Break thru the opening!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15283" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">出現!邪悪の騎士暗黒のリューナイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hes appeared! It`s the Knight of Darkness! - And his Dark Ryu Knight!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15284" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガルデンを倒せ!氷の城の決闘!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defeat Galden! - Decisive Battle at the Castle of Ice!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17546" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死霊がいっぱい切り札はイズミ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lots of Ghosts! The Trump Card is Izumi?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17717" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">出陣リュー侍!武士道一直線!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get into Position, Ryu Samurai! Straight down the road of Bushido!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17842" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会グラチェス炎にかけた友情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We meet again, Gratches! - Friendship bound In flame!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18606" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴブリンが出た!!嘘つきカッツェの大儲け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Goblins Have Shown u!! Lying Katze`s Huge Profit!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18607" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奪われた王国!パッフィー悲しみの帰郷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Stolen Kingdom! Paffy`s Disheartening Return Home!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19416" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パフリシア城奪還!! うなれ!怒りの魔法剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Recapture Phahuricia Castle! - Will yo my command, Magic Sword of Hatred</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22401" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘境への扉雲海の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Door in the Uncharted! Battle in the Sea of Clouds!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22404" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パッフィーを救えイドロの魔の手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Save Paffy! Idoro`s Dark Grasp over Magic!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23587" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オアシスの罠対決!!砂漠の機械城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trap at the Oasis! Showdown Time!! The Desert Machine Fortress!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25019" recap="true" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の美剣士登場その実体は誰だハグ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Appearance of the Mysterious Beautiful Swordsman! Just who is he-hagu!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31817" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死を呼ぶ航海アデュー父との再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Voyage that calls Forth Death. Adeu`s Reunion With his Father!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35915" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">邪竜族降り立つ!! 恐るべき侵略者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Helldragon Tribe Has Landed!! The Fearsome Invaders.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36393" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">見えた!時の神殿聖騎士への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I can see it! The Temple of Time and The Path of a Paladin!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36647" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シュテルの猛攻!! 追い詰められたリューたち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steru`s Fierce Attack!! The Cornered Ryus!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39597" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">できた! 必殺剣 炸裂メテオザッパー!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ve done it! A Perfect Sword Technique, the Explosive Meteor Zapper!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39808" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい仲間 謎のガンマン登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Ally. The Entrance of the Mysterious Gunman!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39809" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">リューを呼ぶ罠! 一千年目の反撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Trap that Invites Ryus! The Counterattack of a Thousand Years!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46138" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">精霊剣を取り戻せ 剣豪 VS 月心!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get back the Spirit Sword. The Sword Master VS Gesshin!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46797" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦え サルトビ! よみがえる闇風伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fight on, Sarutobi! The Rebirth of the Yamikaze Legend!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46984" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃えろサルトビ! 爆裂丸フルパワー!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burn up, Sarutobi! Bakuretsumaru, Full Power!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47530" recap="true" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃のパッフィー! 目覚めろリュー使い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paffy, Shocked! Re-awaken, Ryu Rider!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48090" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">出番だカッツェ! チビッコお宝大作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`re up, Katze! The Kiddy Treasure Hunt!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="55077" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガルデンの悲劇 あばかれた黒衣の騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tragic Galden! The Revealed Past of the Black Knight!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="55078" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者への試練 イズミ, 師匠との対決!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Challenge for the Brave! Izumi Faces Off With His Master!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="55079" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦慄! 新たなる敵 非情のドゥーム兵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Horribly Frightening! A New Enemy! The Heartless Doom Soldier!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61827" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒りのガルデン イドロ, 最後の出撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Malevolent Galden! Idoro`s Final Onslaught!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62046" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">騎士ふたり アデューVSガルデン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Knights! Adeu VS Galden!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62074" recap="true" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">集まれリュー使い! 解けたアースティアの謎!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gather, Ryu Riders! The Unveiled Mysteries of Earth Tear!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63587" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛べ! パラディン 強敵ドゥームを倒せ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly, Paladin! Defeat the Powerful Dooms!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64031" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">グラチェスの決断 エルドギア壊滅!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gratches` Decision. The Destruction of Eldogia!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65853" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">変身! マジドーラ リューウィザード登場!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Transform, Magidora! Welcome in Ryu Wizard!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65854" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">リュー使いの運命 操られたダークナイト!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Destiny of the Ryu Users. The Controlled Dark Knight!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65855" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガルデンの決意 爆裂丸クラスチェンジ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Galden`s Resolve. Bakuretsumaru`s Class Change!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73334" recap="true" update="2007-09-09">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">守れアースティア 勇者達の道のり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect Earth Tear! The Journet the Heroes Partook!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73335" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月心, 最後の賭け! 大地の剣を守れ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gesshin`s Final Gamble! Protect the Earth Blade!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73336" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">白き狼の叫び 灼熱のシャインバラム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Howl of the White Wolf! Blazing Shinebaram!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73337" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">閃光の中の兄妹 デリンガー執念の一撃!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brother and Sister Within the Light! Derringer`s Desperate Shot of a Lifetime!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73338" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">立て! アデュー アースティア最大の危機!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stand up, Adeu! Earth Tear`s Greatest Crisis!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73339" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡の大逆転!? 来たれ, リューの使い手たち!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Miraculous Turn of Events!? Come forth, Ryu Users!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73340" update="2007-05-13">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">輝け! 光速の聖騎士 アデュー, 新たなる旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shine, Paladin! Adeu`s New Journey!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90402" update="2008-04-29">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
