<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5429" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-12-19</startdate>
<enddate>2007-12-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tokyo Marble Chocolate</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Токийский мраморный шоколад</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">도쿄 마블 초컬릿</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">TMC</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Токійський мармуровий шоколад</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">東京マーブルチョコレート</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Tokyo Marble Chocolate</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Tokyo Marble Chocolate</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6466" approval="10" total="20">Kimi ni Todoke</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="246151">Normaly I hate romance genre but with this anime  I did´t feel any disgusting other way I really like it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="240543">Romance/Comedy that will make you laugh all the way through.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="158354">this one is JUST BRILLIANT! How much you can tell in just 25 minutes (in 50 actually :P)! Very funny and touching!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tokyomarble.com/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="721" type="Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="721" type="Original Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="2992" type="Direction">Shiotani Naoyoshi</name>
<name id="9029" type="Character Design">Tanikawa Fumiko</name>
<name id="2992" type="Mini Roba Design">Shiotani Naoyoshi</name>
<name id="16422" type="Music">Yanagawa Takeshi</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch5025 [Chizuru] loves http://anidb.net/ch5026 [Yuudai]; Yuudai loves Chizuru. Yet, neither of them can say it clearly because, not only are they both uncertain about the other`s feelings but, a mutual fear of hurt stemming from failed relationships in their pasts continues a pattern of misunderstandings. So trapped by their insecurities that their relationship is going nowhere, they drift further and further apart. While Chizuru thinks this is the end of the road, Yuudai struggles desperately to overcome his cowardly nature before he loses what is most important to him. There are two sides to every story, every relationship; but can love survive if both sides cannot meet halfway?!
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1259">6.47</permanent>
<temporary count="1262">7.38</temporary>
<review count="2">7.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>39215.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8372</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3088</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4112</identifier>
<identifier>eboepn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/tokyo-marble-chocolate/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tokyomarble.com/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tokyo_Marble_Chocolate</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>東京マーブルチョコレート</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1807</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329248</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9527</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2309" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>insecure</name>
<description>Not confident or assured; uncertain and anxious.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3037" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Skytree</name>
<description>Tokyo Skytree is a broadcasting, restaurant, and observation tower in Sumida, Tokyo, Japan. It became the tallest structure in Japan in 2010 and reached its full height of 634.0 metres in March 2011, making it the tallest tower in the world, displacing the Canton Tower, and the second tallest structure in the world after Burj Khalifa (829.8 m).
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much older http://anidb.net/t3667 [Tokyo Tower].</description>
<picurl>161122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5025" type="main character in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="2">3.47</rating>
<name>Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5026" type="main character in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="3">4.65</rating>
<name>Yuudai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5027" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="2">8.46</rating>
<name>Mini Roba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5028" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="2">8.48</rating>
<name>Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5029" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-15">
<name>Yamada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5030" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-15">
<name>Takada-senpai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2023" picture="21346.jpg">Seamo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5031" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-15">
<name>Takuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5032" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-15">
<name>Shinta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="86928" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マタアイマショウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Meet Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mata Aimashou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86929" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全力少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Full Power Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenryoku Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95884" update="2011-01-31">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2007-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">SEAMO/Mata Aimashou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SEAMO/Mata Aimashou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95885" update="2011-01-31">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2007-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Sukima Switch/Zenryoku Shounen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sukima Switch/Zenryoku Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121375" update="2010-08-21">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinema Edit Version</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
