<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="544" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-01-27</startdate>
<enddate>2000-04-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Oh! Super Milk-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">OH! スーパーミルクチャン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Super Milk-chan Show</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">המופע של מילק צ`אן</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="543" type="Prequel">Super Milk-chan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_2000/tv_049.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="4359" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oomori Takahiro</name>
<name id="3630" type="Character Design">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="23946" type="Original Plan">Tanaka Hideyuki</name>
<name id="23946" type="Direction">Tanaka Hideyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Originally started as short 14 episodes of 4-5 minutes animated series, Super Milk-Chan came back as Oh! Super Milk-Chan. The background story and the characters are still the same with the original series, however, it`s more cynical and funnier with new digital animation element.
Here is the summary from the original Super Milk-Chan:
Milk-chan is a girl who lives in a house stuck on the side of a building with her two sidekicks: Tetsu-ko, a paranoid robot that looks like a bottle and Hanage, a green blob with a mustache. Milk is poor and she can`t pay the rent, so she works for the president as a secret agent.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="132">2.31</permanent>
<temporary count="135">4.92</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>202108.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1020</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1769</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1118</identifier>
<identifier>jdxjjq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_2000/tv_049.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1145</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159787</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="52929" type="main character in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Milk-chan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="34652" picture="128938.jpg">Nakamura Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6011" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクの亡者が街にやって来た の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Evil Spirits Go Marching In</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Mouja ga Machi ni Yattekita no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6243" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクのギバちゃんからダイオキシン の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Giba-chan to Dioxin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Giba-chan kara Dioxin no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8731" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクの負けるな! 墨校ナイン の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Give Up, Sumi High Baseball Team!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Makeruna! Sumi Kou Nine no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11696" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクの遊星からの帰ってきた若大将 の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Return of the Young Master from the Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Yuusei kara no Kaette Kita Wakadaishou no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11697" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクのモチがのびたりちぢんだり の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rice Cakes Stretching and Shrinking</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Mochi ga Nobitari Chijintari no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14616" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクのタワーリング・ホームレス の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Towering Homeless</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Towering Homeless no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17547" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクのタンタンたぬき・平成豚合戦ブーブー の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ra-Ra-Raccoon Dog, Heisei Pig Wars Oink Oink</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Tan-Tan-Tanuki, Heisei Buta Kassen Buubuu no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22432" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクのバーチャルサウンドシステム の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Virtual Sound System</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Virtual Sound System no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24402" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクの金融腐蝕半島 の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Financial Decay Peninsula</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Kin`yuu Fushoku Hantou no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27246" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクのホーホケキョ・死ぬのはどっちだ の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hou Hokekyo, Who`s Going to Die</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Hou Hokekyo, Shinu no wa Docchira Da no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28553" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクのまったりトーク・ゴチになります の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Having a Thick Talk for Dinner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Mattari Talk, Gochi ni Narimasu no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29042" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミルクのさよなら人類: エピソード最後 の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell to Mankind: Last Episode</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Milk no Sayonara Jinrui: Episode Saigo no Maki</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
