<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="545" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>8</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-02-05</startdate>
<enddate>2003-04-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hunter x Hunter: Greed Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Greed Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hunter X Hunter OVA 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">HxH GI</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">HxH OVA 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GI</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ハンターxハンター: Greed Island</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ฮันเตอร์ x ฮันเตอร์ OVA GI</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1427" type="Sequel">Hunter x Hunter: Greed Island Final</anime>
<anime id="173" type="Prequel">Hunter x Hunter: Original Video Animation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8692" approval="8" total="21">Sword Art Online</anime>
<anime id="4324" approval="2" total="3">.hack//Roots</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2"/>
<url>http://www.nippon-animation.co.jp/work/1827/</url>
<creators>
<name id="728" type="Work">Nippon Animation</name>
<name id="836" type="Work">Marvelous Entertainment</name>
<name id="896" type="Work">Pony Canyon</name>
<name id="728" type="Animation Work">Nippon Animation</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="874" type="Original Work">Togashi Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="4336" type="Series Composition">Kishima Nobuaki</name>
<name id="6734" type="Character Design">Tagashira Shinobu</name>
<name id="6892" type="Direction">Yukihiro Matsushita</name>
</creators>
<description>After the conflict with the spiders, http://anidb.net/ch7192 [Gon] and http://anidb.net/ch7273 [Killua] return to the York Shin auction to try their luck with Greed Island. Once inside, Gon and Killua meet up with http://anidb.net/ch10783 [Biscuit], Wing`s old teacher, who helps them train to defeat the monsters and player killers found inside the game.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3950">7.99</permanent>
<temporary count="4004">8.27</temporary>
<review count="2">9.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>144670.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2282</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>138</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1171</identifier>
<identifier>gphyzi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nippon-animation.co.jp/work/1827/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>HUNTER×HUNTER_(1999年のアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240669</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5961</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5981" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-12">
<name>seeking protagonist</name>
<description>The main character has a main objective that is referenced to through the whole series; he is in search of something, or someone
Should it be treasure, friends, money, power or all of the above nothing will stop our lead character in his quest to find his passion</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6191" parentid="2881" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>card games</name>
<description>A card game is any game using playing cards as the primary device with which the game is played, be they traditional or game-specific. Countless card games exist, including families of related games (such as poker). A small number of card games played with traditional decks have formally standardized rules, but most are folk games whose rules vary by region, culture, and person.
Many games that are not generally placed in the family of card games do in fact use cards for some aspect of their gameplay. Similarly, some games that are placed in the card game genre involve a board. The distinction is that the gameplay of a card game primarily depends on the use of the cards by players (the board is simply a guide for scorekeeping or for card placement), while board games (the principal non-card game genre to use cards) generally focus on the players` positions on the board, and use the cards for some secondary purpose.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4976" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="747">9.10</rating>
<name>Hisoka Morow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hisoka is a magician, as well as a serial killer. Hisoka is deceitful, playful, and narcissistic by nature; he acts only according to self-interest. Hisoka combines his magic tricks with violence, and delights in battling against those he considers strong to the point of sexual arousal. In the manga, his sentences within speech balloons typically end with a suit symbol. Hisoka takes an interest in Gon and his friends after encountering them during the Hunter Exam; although he initially is posited as an antagonist due to affinity towards murder, he spends much of the series acting as both an adversary and comrade to Gon.
Nen type: Transmutation
In Hunter`s Character &amp; World Official Databook his height is 187 cm and in manga ch. 377 his height is 190+ cm.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>46438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7192" type="main character in" update="2013-09-01">
<rating votes="500">5.41</rating>
<name>Gon Freecss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gon Freecss is the son of the legendary Hunter Ging Freecss and the protagonist of the series Hunter × Hunter by Yoshihiro Togashi.
Gon was left in the care of his aunt Mito on Whale Island as an infant by his father Ging, and never saw his father since. Holding great disdain for Ging`s constant travels and putting Gon in danger, she forced Ging to give his son up so he could live normally. Mito told him as a child that his parents were deceased, but Gon eventually figured out the truth and chose the path of a Hunter to meet his father once again.</description>
<picture>46413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7273" type="main character in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="672">8.87</rating>
<name>Killua Zaoldyeck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Killua was born as the middle child to a family of renowned assassins, the Zoldyck family. Showing great promise from birth, Killua has already mastered many killing techniques at a tender age, and is set to be one of the best assassins the family has ever produced. Bored and tired of killing, Killua unexpectedly rebelled against his family, injuring both his mother and brother, and ran away to join the Hunter exam. He met Gon during the first portion of the Hunter Exam and became great friends.</description>
<picture>46430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3921" picture="206017.jpg">Mitsuhashi Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7274" type="main character in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="382">7.18</rating>
<name>Kurapika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7275" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="174">5.66</rating>
<name>Leorio Paradinight</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leorio meets Gon just as Gon leaves Whale Island to take the Hunter Exam. Much is unknown about Leorio. What we do know is that he once lost a close friend, Pietro, to a debilitating illness. Leorio feels deeply remorseful about being unable to save his friend, as the illness was entirely curable, but required a surgery he could not afford. Thus, he aspires to become a doctor--one that not only cures the ill of their disease, but also waives the fee for the poor. In this light, his outwardly superficial reason to join the Hunter Exams in the pursuit of great wealth has a more noble justification--the money he gains is used not only to fund for his medical school fees, but also to pay for the medicine and other miscellaneous expenditures when treating those who can`t afford it.</description>
<picture>46435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10783" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="38">7.11</rating>
<name>Biscuit Cluegar</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She first comes into the story in Greed Island. Although she appears to be a little girl, in her true form she is actually a massive and extremely muscular woman several times the size of her preferred form. The only reason she stays in her girl form is because she claims she hates her original form`s appearance. Regardless of which form she is in, Biscuit is very powerful. However, she does receive a tremendous power boost when she transforms to her real appearance. She helps Gon and Killua train while they are at Greed Island, leading them closer to the end of the game. Her goal in the game was to get the gem found only in that game, Blue Planet. She prefers to be called "Bisky." In addition, she was the teacher of Wing, the man whom first taught Nen to Gon and Killua.
[from Wikipedia]</description>
<picture>169210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="188" picture="1804.gif">Kimura Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39390" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-28">
<rating votes="104">6.49</rating>
<name>Feitan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Feitan is one of the original members hailing from Meteor City and currently the de facto leader of the Phantom Troupe. He is attired in what one would expect from a bandit — dark clothes partnered with a skullhead scarf that covers his mouth. He seldom speaks, but when he does, it is full of grammatical errors, giving the impression that he is not speaking in his native tongue. During the Phantom Troupe`s fight with Chimera Ants, Feitan reverts to his native language, which was shown with Chinese characters. After Feitan`s victory over Zazan in Meteor City, he is crowned temporary leader of the Phantom Troupe. Feitan`s movements are incredibly fast, being able to leave afterimages of his body. He wields an umbrella that conceals both a sword and a gun that fires out of the tip.
His Nen ability is called "Pain Packer: Unforgiven" which transforms the injuries he has received from his enemy into an attack. The more pain he receives, the stronger his attack is. Currently, only "Rising Sun: Burnt by the Sun" has been revealed, a miniature sun that burns anyone around him disregarding even allies, as shown by the rest of the Phantom Troupe fleeing from the scene when he uses this ability. Only Feitan is unaffected by the attack, presumably because of the armor that is formed on him. Nen type: Transmutation
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3146" picture="49928.jpg">Hibino Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42396" type="appears in" update="2012-03-19">
<rating votes="11">3.99</rating>
<name>Miluki Zaoldyeck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2342" picture="22096.jpg">Ishizuka Katashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42699" type="appears in" update="2014-11-10">
<rating votes="15">5.55</rating>
<name>Silva Zaoldyeck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Silva is Killua`s father, and a head of Zaoldyeck family. A silent, pensive figure, Killua`s interaction with him seems limited. He allows Killua to go along with Gon on their journey to find his father, but only because he sees it as a crucial step in his development as the future head assassin of the Zaoldyeck family.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>84231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43493" type="appears in" update="2014-11-10">
<rating votes="3">3.40</rating>
<name>Zushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zushi is a young boy who studies Shingen-Ryu Kung fu and Nen under the tutelage of Wing, whom Gon and Killua meet in the Heavens Arena. He is a formidable fighter and a prodigy in his own right, said to have skills only 1 out of 100,000 people have. However, he is quickly surpassed by Gon and Killua, who are said to have skills only 1 out of 10,000,000 people have. According to the results of his water divination, Zushi is a Manipulator.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>85994.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43494" type="appears in" update="2014-11-10">
<rating votes="11">5.00</rating>
<name>Wing</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wing is an assistant master of the Shingen-Ryu style of Kung Fu whose pupil is Zushi. He meets Gon and Killua at the Heavens Arena and eventually teaches them Nen. Although he initially refuses to train the two (even lying to them about the purpose of Nen), he changes his mind when they advance to the 200th floor of Heavens Arena, realizing they could die or be badly injured by the other Nen users. For the next several months he teaches them the basics of Nen, after which he announces they have passed the secret final requirement for being a Hunter. He does however somewhat fear their immense potential. Wing`s teacher was Biscuit Krueger, who incidentally becomes Gon and Killua`s second teacher.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>85995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43495" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="94">8.04</rating>
<name>Chrollo Lucilfer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chrollo Lucilfer is the founder and leader of the Phantom Troupe. He forms the group with six other homeless children in Meteor City in his youth, thereafter leaving it. The Troupe was joined by more members, in accordance with Chrollo`s idea of a group with exactly thirteen members, including himself. He organizes the Phantom Troupe mainly to commit acts of theft, though it is unknown what the group does with the stolen objects. His Nen ability also allows him to directly steal the abilities of other users of Nen. He led the genocide on Kurapika`s clan, the latter thereafter stalking Chrollo and neutralizing his Nen ability as punishment. Nen type: Specialization
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90764.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43497" type="appears in" update="2014-11-11">
<rating votes="3">3.10</rating>
<name>Bonolenov</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bonolenov is covered in bandages and wears boxing gloves. These bandages cover up a large number of holes throughout his body. During the Chimera Ant arc, he was seen fighting with the other members of the Phantom Troupe against the Chimera Ants. His physical power ranks eighth among the Troupe, and he is the thirteenth Troupe member. Bonolenov is a descendant of the Gyudondond, a small wild tribe that was chased out of their lands by development. When males of the Gyudondond tribe reach the age of three, they are circumcised and needles are inserted in various parts of their body. Over time, these needles are replaced with thicker and thicker sticks, and the holes are stabilized with bamboo stalks or stones. Using these holes, Gyudondond males are able to create a variety of sounds. They are called "Bap", the dancing warriors, and fulfill the role of shamans and performers in their tribe. Before combat, they use their bodies to play songs of battle. The Gyudondond believe that the more beautiful a sound that is played, the greater the spirit it can summon. As a member of this clan, Bonolenov possess this as his Nen ability, titled "Batte Le Cantabile".
Nen type: Conjuration
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90753.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43498" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="10">5.79</rating>
<name>Franklin Bordeau</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Franklin is very large, with multiple facial scars similar to that of a Frankenstein. His ability is called "Dual Machine Gun", and is capable of shooting countless bullets composed of Nen from his fingers (which he himself modified). Franklin ranks fourth in physical power among the Troupe, and he is among the original members hailing from Meteor City.
Nen type: Emission
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2057" picture="21394.jpg">Kaneko Yukinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43499" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="3">3.94</rating>
<name>Kortopi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Very little is known about Kortopi. Exceptionally short in stature, he also has a thick and messy mane of hair covering his entire head, obscuring everything except for an occasional glimpse of his left eyeball. He is the weakest in the Troupe in terms of raw physical power. In fact, his Nen abilities so far suggest that he is not involved in combat at all, but rather theft and subterfuge. His Nen ability is called "Gallery Fake: Divine Left Hand, Demonic Right Hand", which allows him to make perfect copies of any object by touching it with his left hand and producing the copy with his right. The size of the object doesn`t matter. He can also make copies of living humans, but they`ll be immobile and lifeless. He`s also able to know the exact location of any copy he has created by touching the original object. The copies vanish after 24 hours have passed.
Nen type: Conjuration
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4813" picture="45576.jpg">Tenjin Umi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43500" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="66">7.30</rating>
<name>Machi Komachine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Machi is incredibly loyal to Chrollo, and is one of the original Phantom Troupe members from Meteor City. Hisoka seems to have an occasional interest in her, although it is hard to see whether it is genuine. Her ability is to form aura into thread, the strength of which is inversely proportional to its length: a thread as long as the diameter of the Earth would be as strong as cotton, but a one meter-long thread can lift a ton. Besides attacking it can be used to track people, but was also shown used to stitch severed limbs back on. Physically, she is the strongest woman in the Troupe and the sixth strongest overall. She also has an extremely keen intuition (the other members of the Troupe say that she has never been wrong about her intuitions).
Nen type: Transmutation
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8085" picture="228456.jpg">Uemura Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43502" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="17">4.86</rating>
<name>Phinks Magcub</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Phinxs uses his hands in battle, which has been shown to be extremely powerful. He is one of the original Phantom Troupe members from Meteor City and wears an Egyptian Pharaoh-like outfit in battle. Phinxs seems to get along best with Feitan, and is almost always seen partnered with him both in and out of combat. His Nen ability is called "Ripper Cyclotron", the strength of which is dependent upon how many times he rotates his arm; the more rotations, the more powerful his attack will be. In terms of physical strength, Phinxs is ranked second among the Troupe members. His name is an anagram for "Sphinx".
Nen type: Enhancement
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34781" picture="234982.jpg">Matsumoto Yoshirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43503" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="21">6.69</rating>
<name>Shalnark Ryuusei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shalnark is member number six of the Phantom Troupe, and from his appearance, he seems to be a normal boy. However, he is one of the most intelligent and quick-thinking members in the group, being highly adept at using computers and information gathering. Shalnark is also a licensed Hunter, so he has access to certain information that could be potentially useful to the Phantom Troupe. His main ability revolves around remotely manipulating the actions of others using his cell phone by sticking a specialized antenna into their bodies. His secondary ability involves applying the antenna upon himself and putting his body on autopilot, resulting in an enhanced state with enough power to devastate most opponents. However, he dislikes this ability because he is subject to immense muscle pain for several days after its use, and as he has no control over the process and retains no memory over what has transpired he can`t derive any pleasure or satisfaction when he uses it to win a fight. Shalnark ranks tenth in physical power among the Troupe.
Nen type: Manipulation
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43504" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="36">7.24</rating>
<name>Shizuku Murasaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizuku is extremely forgetful and can be an airhead at times which, along with her unassuming appearance, can cause opponents to underestimate her combat abilities. Shizuku uses her Nen vacuum "Blinky" ("Deme-chan" in the original Japanese version) in combat, which is able to suck up anything that is not nen created or that she considers living. It is also able to regurgitate the last thing sucked up. She is left-handed, and the twelfth strongest physically out of the thirteen members of the Troupe. Shizuku is member number eight, a replacement for the last member since the Troupe came together. Nen type: Conjuration
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4471" picture="26743.jpg">Bungo Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46848" type="appears in" update="2014-11-11">
<rating votes="6">3.83</rating>
<name>Senritsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Senritsu (Melody) is an Music Hunter and is the kind and understanding member of Neon`s bodyguards. She is always ready to listen to anyone`s confessions and has the gift to make people open up to her. As Leorio notes, she is one of the very few characters who has made Kurapika open up to her. Melody`s physical appearance is in short contrast to her kind soul. Due to effects of the "Sonata of Darkness", a musical piece said to have been written by Satan himself and possibly inspired by the Devil`s Trill Sonata, her body is a short and her face disfigured. However, she was not always like this; she was once a normal person. She was transformed when she and a friend listened to the Sonata of Darkness. It is composed of four parts: piano, violin, flute, and harp, and it is said that whomever listens to it will be greatly cursed. Melody`s goal is to find the sonata and destroy it. Melody has the ability to emit her aura to people to soothe ease fatigue when she plays an instrument. She also has a very sharp sense of hearing and can tell a person`s psychological state just by listening to their heartbeat. For example, she knows when people are lying or when someone has completely lost his/her temper.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3701" picture="25016.jpg">Tarako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49254" type="appears in" update="2012-09-23">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Zepile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3161" picture="69050.jpg">Yamanoi Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51617" type="appears in" update="2012-12-23">
<rating votes="2">3.40</rating>
<name>Puhat</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4554" picture="228453.jpg">Miyano Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51618" type="appears in" update="2014-11-12">
<rating votes="9">5.42</rating>
<name>Tsezguerra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsezguerra is an experienced Money Hunter and 1-Star Hunter. He is hired by Battera to beat Greed Island and also tests the people who want to enter Greed Island in order to earn the 50 Billion prize money. He and his team ally with Gon, Killua, Biscuit, Hisoka and Goreinu to take part in the dodgeball game against Razor. He and his team later engage Genthru`s in a game of chase in order to buy time for Gon to train against Genthru`s "Little Flower" ability and for Killua to heal his injuries.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>129902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38572" picture="143890.jpg">Mizuki Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51619" type="appears in" update="2012-12-23">
<rating votes="9">3.65</rating>
<name>Battera</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12648" picture="172620.jpg">Kibe Kimiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107855" type="appears in" update="2020-01-06">
<name>Biscuit Cluegar</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242822.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6020" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">競売 x 作戦 x 80パーセント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Auction x Plan x 80 Percent</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les enchères X Un plan X Taux de réussite, 80 %</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoubai x Sakusen x 80 percent</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6066" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電気 x オーラ x 必殺技</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Electricity x Aura x Special Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Électricité X Aura X Technique spéciale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Denki x Aura x Hissatsuwaza</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6545" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">錬 x 試練 x それぞれの一歩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ren x Trial x Everyone`s Step</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ren X Le recrutement X Première étape</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ren x Shiren x Sorezore no Ippo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6546" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スタート x 呪文 x 懸賞の街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Start x Spell x Reward Street</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le début X Sort X La ville des défis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Start x Jumon x Kenshou no Machi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7040" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勧誘 x リスト x 最初はグー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invitation x List x Rock, Paper, Scissors!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Recrutement X La liste X Coup de poing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanyuu x List x Saisho wa Guu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7074" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奪る x奪られる x カード地獄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take x Taken x Card Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Voleur X Volés X La carte de l`Enfer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toru x Torareru x Card Jigoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7466" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">山賊 x 怪物 x ビスケット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bandit x Monster x Biscuit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Brigands X Monstres X Biscuit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanzoku x Kaibutsu x Biscuit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7532" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">修行 x 原石 x シザーハンズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Training x Raw Ore x Scissor Hands</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Entraînement X Joyau X L`homme aux mains d′argent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shugyou x Genseki x Scissor Hands</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40877" update="2010-09-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2003-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40878" update="2010-09-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2003-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
