<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5454" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-12-28</startdate>
<enddate>2007-12-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Harukanaru Toki no Naka de 3: Kurenai no Tsuki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">In a Distant Time 3: Crimson Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Vùng đất xa xăm 3: Trăng Đỏ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">遙かなる時空の中で3 紅の月</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2580" type="Same Setting">Haruka Naru Toki no Naka de: Hachiyoushou</anime>
<anime id="7086" type="Other">Harukanaru Toki no Naka de 3: Owarinaki Unmei</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.gamecity.ne.jp/neoromance/tv/haruka/kurenai/</url>
<creators>
<name id="845" type="Animation Work">Yumeta Company</name>
<name id="930" type="Original Work">Koei</name>
<name id="124" type="Direction">Shinohara Toshiya</name>
<name id="4393" type="Music">Hirano Yoshihisa</name>
<name id="5802" type="Character Design">Tsunaki Aki</name>
<name id="5802" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tsunaki Aki</name>
</creators>
<description>One day, Kasuga Nozomi encounters a strange boy at her high school, who sends her across time and space to Kyou, a place in another world that bears a strong resemblance to Kyoto towards the end of the Heian period. There, the Minamoto clan ("Genji"), led by Minamoto no Yoritomo, is at war with the Taira clan ("Heike"), led by Taira no Kiyomori. The Heike hope to defeat the Genji by releasing vengeful spirits to disturb the earth`s natural flow of energy and to terrorize the land. The boy is revealed to be the human form of Hakuryuu, the White Dragon God that protects Kyou, who is weakened by the presence of the vengeful spirits. As the Hakuryuu no Miko (Priestess of the White Dragon God), Nozomi allies herself with the Genji because Hakuryuu cannot send her home until his power is restored...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="129">4.03</permanent>
<temporary count="133">6.40</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>6384.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8724</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4190</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4116</identifier>
<identifier>gdobss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gamecity.ne.jp/neoromance/tv/haruka/kurenai/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>遙かなる時空の中で3_紅の月#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1299</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329337</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9493</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3260</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8036" type="main character in" update="2009-11-09">
<rating votes="6">6.37</rating>
<name>Kasuga Nozomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8037" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-09">
<rating votes="3">8.22</rating>
<name>Arikawa Masaomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8038" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="2">7.95</rating>
<name>Minamoto no Kurou Yoshitsune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8039" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-09">
<name>Hinoe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4665" picture="27220.jpg">Takahashi Naozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8041" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Musashibou Benkei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8042" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-09">
<name>Arikawa Yuzuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8043" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-09">
<rating votes="2">7.61</rating>
<name>Kajiwara Kagetoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8045" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-09">
<name>Taira no Atsumori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8046" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-09">
<name>Ridvan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8047" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-09">
<rating votes="2">5.01</rating>
<name>Kajiwara Saku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12849" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-09">
<name>Hakuryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12850" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-09">
<rating votes="2">5.01</rating>
<name>Houjou Masako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12851" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-09">
<name>Taira no Tomomori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12852" type="main character in" update="2009-11-09">
<name>Taira no Tsunemasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="277" picture="223606.jpg">Hanawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12855" type="appears in" update="2011-03-13">
<name>Taira no Koremori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9687" picture="46695.jpg">Matsuda Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="84704" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2007-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89023" update="2008-04-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2008-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">龍神温泉罰ゲームの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ryuujin Onsen Punishment Game Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuujin Onsen Batsu Game no Maki</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
