<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5473" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-09-29</startdate>
<enddate>2008-02-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ooedo Forty Eight</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">오오에도 48가지 수법</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Oodeo Shijyuuhatte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ooedo Shijuu Hachite</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ooedo Shijuuhatte</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">OED48</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">大江戸四十八手[ふぉうてぃえいと]</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3358" approval="1" total="6">Ihara Saikaku Koushoku Ichidai Otoko</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.mediabank.co.jp/mediabank/product?page=product&amp;banner=1343036990</url>
<creators>
<name id="6172" type="Direction">Awai Shigeki</name>
<name id="877" type="Animation Work">Studio 9 Maiami</name>
</creators>
<description>The action takes place in Ooedo Japan, when geishas and public houses appeared. Back then, girls raised in poor provincial families had little chances to get married successfully. The only opportunity to improve financial and social status for them was to move to Ooedo, the city of wealthy clans, and to become a servant or a geisha - and, perhaps, a lover of a rich feudal. Young and poor http://anidb.net/ch64078 [Oshizu] has chosen this very path.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="124">4.27</permanent>
<temporary count="126">5.69</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>89526.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9333</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5439</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5280</identifier>
<identifier>cffgdk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mediabank.co.jp/mediabank/product?page=product&amp;banner=1343036990</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14538</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="893" parentid="2729" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>dominatrix</name>
<description>A dominatrix is a woman, typically a paid professional, who takes the dominant role in BDSM activities. A dominatrix may be of any sexual orientation, which does not necessarily limit the genders of her submissive partners. The role of a dominatrix may not even involve physical pain toward the submissive; her domination can be verbal, involving humiliating tasks, or servitude. The umbrella term for BDSM activities involving a dominatrix is female dominance, female domination, or simply femdom.
Source: Wikipedia.</description>
<picurl>230370.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2225" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>whipping</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2690" parentid="2641" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Tokugawa period</name>
<description>The anime takes place during a period of Japanese history running from 1603 to 1868.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2905" parentid="2729" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-14">
<name>erotic torture</name>
<description>Erotic torture involves deliberately using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure. Examples include, among others, hot wax on skin, nipple clamps, electricity, extreme verbal and derogatory abuse, forced public exhibition, etc.
This is distinct from the common, non-erotic http://anidb.net/t6730 [torture], which is generally for the purpose of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or to apply coercion to compel action from the victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2920" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>rimming</name>
<description>Rimming is the act of using one`s tongue on the anus or perineum of another person in order to gain and/or give sexual pleasure.</description>
<picurl>165410.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4348" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-04">
<name>wafuku -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be split and deleted. Please tag all relevant characters from the tagged shows with http://anidb.net/t7076 [the appropriate wafuku tags] and then delete this tag from the corresponding anime. Thank you very much.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="64077" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-21">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Ohariko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12400" picture="19665.jpg">Momoi Ichigo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64078" type="main character in" update="2014-04-21">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Oshizu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154686.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64079" type="main character in" update="2014-04-21">
<name>Kounosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154687.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64080" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-21">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Sejima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39409">Kinako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64081" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-21">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Katsura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6023" picture="225099.jpg">Kazane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64082" type="appears in" update="2014-04-21">
<name>Azami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27886" picture="21776.jpg">Ueto Ryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="83094" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2007-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幕の壱 新参女中惑乱始末</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cleaning Up the Newcomer Maid`s Bewilderment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maku no Ichi: Shinzan Jochuu Wakuran Shimatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85384" update="2008-07-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">京女憚り始末</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cleaning Up the Kyoto Woman`s Hindrance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouonna Habakari Shimatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88375" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">傀儡女淫変始末</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cleaning Up the Puppet Woman`s Strange Licentiousness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kugutsume Inhen Shimatsu</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
