<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5479" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1985-10-26</startdate>
<enddate>1985-10-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yousei Florence</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fairy Florence</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">妖精フローレンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">A Journey Through Fairyland</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Фея Флоренс</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="4880" type="Direction">Hata Masami</name>
<name id="5281" type="Original Work">Tsuji Shintarou</name>
<name id="7393" type="Music">Yamamoto Naozumi</name>
</creators>
<description>A gentle and talented boy named http://anidb.net/ch35770 [Michael] played beautiful music on his oboe, and his greatest love was to play for and tend to the flowers in the greenhouse at the school of music where he attended. Unfortunately, his gardening made him constantly late for orchestra practice and resulted in his dismissal from the school. When Michael fell asleep that same night, he was awakened by a dainty Flower Fairy named http://anidb.net/ch35769 [Florence], who would take him on an enchanted journey to a land where flowers came alive, treble notes were mischievous, and adventure beckoned. There, he would soon come to realize that his love of flowers and desire to become a great musician could go hand-in-hand and help him to become focused in life and discover himself.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="78">6.80</permanent>
<temporary count="81">6.60</temporary>
<review count="1">7.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>241849.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1458</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4943</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3088</identifier>
<identifier>pxqajj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>妖精フローレンス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>149580</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4570</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35768" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-19">
<name>Higemusica-sensei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5773" picture="30235.jpg">Kobayashi Asei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35769" type="main character in" update="2013-02-16">
<name>Florence</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28086" picture="170250.jpg">Mariya Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35770" type="main character in" update="2013-02-16">
<name>Michael</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3835" picture="25463.jpg">Ichimura Masachika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35771" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-19">
<name>Musica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="8964" picture="33375.jpg">Nakajima Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35772" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-19">
<name>Laura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="28087">Takami Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="90008" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>1985-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
