<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5524" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>21</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-11-03</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ryuusei no Rockman Tribe</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">流星のロックマン トライブ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4791" type="Prequel">Ryuusei no Rockman</anime>
<anime id="5973" type="Alternative Setting">Irregular Hunter X</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.xebec-inc.co.jp/anime/ryusei2/</url>
<creators>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="6429" type="Series Composition">Araki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="1283" type="Original Plan">Capcom</name>
<name id="682" type="Direction">Kato Takao</name>
<name id="6285" type="Music">Naruse Shuuhei</name>
<name id="8899" type="Character Design">Adachi Shingo</name>
</creators>
<description>The ancient civilization vanished ages ago, and a few of its remnants still exist as myths and legends called UMAs (unidentified lifeforms). The UMAs begin merging with humans in order to search for the treasures of Mu, the powerful ooparts, which will give them the power to revive Mu. After Geo and Omega-Xis encounter several unusual enemies, they meet a professor named Doctor Orihime who sends them on a quest to find the ooparts and stop the UMAs. Using the ooparts, Mega Man is able to take new forms, including Thunder Berserk, Fire Dinosaur, and Green Shinobi. The series premiered November 3, immediately after the original series`s conclusion.
Years ago, Mu , an ancient civilization had vanished. But there were three treasures left behind by the land of Mu, these treasures were called OOParts (Out Of Place Artifacts) bearing the power to give Rockman the forms of "Thunder Berserker", "Green Shinobi", and "Fire Dinasor". It starts with Subaru at a museum finding the first artifact "The Sword of Berserk" releasing an enormous amount of Em Waves. Just after two Denpa Lifeforms attack the museum to take the "Sword of Berserk". War-Rock, unexpectedly, accidentally eats it. Doctor Orihime reveals the information of the OOParts to Subaru, while revealing the names of the Denpa Lifeforms, Yeti Blizzard, Phantom Black, and Burai. In secret Doctor Orihime is a decendent of Mu. Now Rockman, and Harp Note have to face new enemies with new powers.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="88">4.41</permanent>
<temporary count="92">6.41</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>6643.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8865</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3493</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.xebec-inc.co.jp/anime/ryusei2/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>流星のロックマン_トライブ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>895</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329274</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9737</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5818" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-01-21">
<name>out-of-place artefact</name>
<description>Out-of-place artefact (OOPArt) is a term coined by American naturalist and crypto-zoologist Ivan T. Sanderson for an object of historical, archaeological, or palaeontological interest found in a very unusual or seemingly impossible context that could challenge conventional historical chronology.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11473" type="main character in" update="2009-09-09">
<name>Hoshikawa Subaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A gentle but a bit lonely fifth-grade student, he mourns the disappearance of his father, and has neglected school as a result. After being confronted by his classmates who pester him to return to school, he heads to an observing platform where he discovers the fugitive AM-ian Warrock by donning the Visualizer glasses left to him by his father, which allows him to view the EM Wave World. Warrock, having stolen the mysterious Andromeda Key from the FM King, claims to have knowledge of the boy`s missing parent. The two are able to merge together becoming Rockman. Subaru uses this new found power to protect his friends and others from the invading FM-ians.</description>
<picture>34305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11474" type="main character in" update="2009-09-09">
<rating votes="2">5.52</rating>
<name>War-Rock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Warrock is an AM-ian; unlike FM-ians, AM-ians are able to turn humans into EM waves without fusing with them. At first, Warrock has no feelings towards the Earth or its people, including Subaru, with his only concern being the safety of the Andromeda Key. However, he slowly begins to change and care for others.</description>
<picture>34310.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11475" type="main character in" update="2009-09-09">
<name>Rockman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The merged form of Hoshikawa Subaru and Warrock.</description>
<picture>34312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11476" type="main character in" update="2009-11-16">
<rating votes="4">7.14</rating>
<name>Hibiki Misora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hibiki Misora is a popular idol who, like Hoshikawa Subaru, is depressed over the loss of a parent, her mother, which leads them to establish a friendship. In terms of demeanor, Misora is quite the opposite of Subaru: spunky, outspoken, and mischievous.</description>
<picture>34313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11477" type="main character in" update="2009-09-09">
<name>Harp</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harp is an FM-ian who used to work for the Andromeda King and often hides in Misora`s guitar. Her form is a cross between a harp and a note. She is shown to act like a high status old lady, whom gets into arguments with Warrock.</description>
<picture>34317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11478" type="main character in" update="2009-09-09">
<name>Harp Note</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The transformed form of Misora Hibiki and Harp.</description>
<picture>34322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11479" type="main character in" update="2009-09-09">
<rating votes="2">8.38</rating>
<name>Shirogane Luna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirogane Luna is the perky and bossy fifth-grade class president of Kodama Elementary. Openly admits she adores Rockman from the second he saves her.</description>
<picture>34325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11480" type="main character in" update="2009-09-09">
<name>Ushijima Gonta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ushijima Gonta is a gruff bully who attempts to intimidate Subaru into returning to school, but eventually makes amends with him. He is quite a dim witted student who depends on Luna to get him out of trouble, or explaining things to him.</description>
<picture>34327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2071" picture="74324.jpg">Oohata Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11481" type="main character in" update="2009-09-09">
<name>Saishouin Kizamaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saishouin Kizamaro is a nerdy and condescending student who is more or less one of Luna`s flunkies.</description>
<picture>34328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11482" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-09">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Hoshikawa Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hoshikawa Akane is Subaru`s mother. She wishes for Subaru to go back to school, but respects his wishes to stay at home. She has a passion for cooking.</description>
<picture>34331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="188" picture="1804.gif">Kimura Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11589" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-09">
<name>Amachi Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mamoru Amachi is a good friend of Daigo Hoshikawa, Subaru`s father. He`s the head researcher and founder of AMAKEN. Mamoru delivers the news of Daigo`s disappearance to Subaru and his mother, and bestows upon Subaru the Visualizer that was left to him by his father.</description>
<picture>35004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2585" picture="22579.jpg">Tsuchida Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11590" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-09">
<name>Goyoda Heiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heiji Goyoda is an investigator of incidents involving FM-ians and suspects that Subaru, who is often present during the incidents, may be involved. Goyoda makes an incorrect assumption that Rockman is a criminal and often tries (and fails miserably) to arrest him.</description>
<picture>35005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="84726" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムーの遺産</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Heritage of Mu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mu no Isan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84727" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-11-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムーの封印</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seal of Mu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mu no Fuuin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84728" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブライの襲撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bly`s Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bly no Shuugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84729" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">発動, ベルセルクの剣!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call Forth, Sword of Berserk!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsudou, Berserk no Ken!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84897" update="2007-11-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒマナラの雪男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Yeti of Himanara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himanara no Yukiotoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84898" update="2007-11-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒマナラのムー遺跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mu Ruins of Himanara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himanara no Mu Iseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85375" update="2007-11-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハイドとゴースト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hyde and Ghost</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyde to Ghost</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85376" update="2007-11-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">試しの剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sword`s Trial</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tameshi no Ken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85377" update="2007-12-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドッシーの真相</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Truth of Dosshi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dosshi no Shinsou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85685" update="2007-12-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラキオの願い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brachio`s Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Brachio no Negai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86175" update="2007-12-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">潜入! ナンスカ村</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Infiltration! Nansca Village</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sennyuu! Nansca Mura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86176" update="2007-12-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖の神様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Terror of God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu no Kamisama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86179" update="2007-12-27">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">修行でおさる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Curious in Training</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shugyou de Osaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86637" update="2008-01-11">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍者屋敷のオーパーツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oopart of the Ninja Mansion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ninja Yashiki no Oopart</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87791" update="2008-01-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三つ巴, オーパーツ争奪戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Three-way Oopart Struggle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsudomoe, Oopart Soudatsusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87792" update="2008-01-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベラボーな作戦!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Absurd Strategy!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Berabou na Sakusen!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87793" update="2008-01-25">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハイドの策略</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hyde`s Scheme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyde no Sakuryaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88416" update="2008-02-27">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オリヒメの正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Orihime`s True Colors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orihime no Shoutai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88417" update="2008-02-27">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-03-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">無のエンプティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Empty of Naught</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mu no Empty</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88418" update="2008-02-27">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤高の戦士ブライ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lone Soldier, Bly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokou no Senshi Bly</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88419" update="2008-02-27">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-03-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムー大陸の決闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel On the Mu Continent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mu Tairiku no Kettou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
