<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5525" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Duel Masters Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">デュエル・マスターズ ゼロ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5905" type="Sequel">Duel Masters Cross</anime>
<anime id="5537" type="Prequel">Zero Duel Masters</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/contents/zero_duelmasters/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4447" type="Series Composition">Fujita Shinzou</name>
<name id="5681" type="Direction">Suzuki Waruro</name>
<name id="16936" type="Character Design">Itou Hideki</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: The previous season of Zero Duel Masters was set in an alternate universe, so this season`s plot is a continuation of the Duel Masters Charge.
It follows after the duel of Shobu vs. Zakira in which Shobu lost.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="19">2.37</permanent>
<temporary count="20">4.60</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>6662.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11491</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10526</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4010</identifier>
<identifier>nossql</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/contents/zero_duelmasters/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>デュエル・マスターズ_ゼロ#.E3.83.87.E3.83.A5.E3.82.A8.E3.83.AB.E3.83.BB.E3.83.9E.E3.82.B9.E3.82.BF.E3.83.BC.E3.82.BA_.E3.82.BC.E3.83.AD</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>895</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9738</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6191" parentid="2881" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>card games</name>
<description>A card game is any game using playing cards as the primary device with which the game is played, be they traditional or game-specific. Countless card games exist, including families of related games (such as poker). A small number of card games played with traditional decks have formally standardized rules, but most are folk games whose rules vary by region, culture, and person.
Many games that are not generally placed in the family of card games do in fact use cards for some aspect of their gameplay. Similarly, some games that are placed in the card game genre involve a board. The distinction is that the gameplay of a card game primarily depends on the use of the cards by players (the board is simply a guide for scorekeeping or for card placement), while board games (the principal non-card game genre to use cards) generally focus on the players` positions on the board, and use the cards for some secondary purpose.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="37975" type="main character in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>Kirifuda Shoubu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72347.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37976" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-23">
<rating votes="24">7.61</rating>
<name>Tasogare Mimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1488.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="215" picture="151687.jpg">Nakajima Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37977" type="main character in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>Kadoko Rekuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37979" type="main character in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>Hakuou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37989" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>George Kamamoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1904.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37994" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-23">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Kirifuda Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="84730" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強化</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84731" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinigami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84732" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">焦り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aseri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84733" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレのデュエル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Duel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84734" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-11-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">陰謀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84824" update="2007-11-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-11-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">偽者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nisemono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85380" update="2007-11-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">導き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michibiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85381" update="2007-11-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強化! ボルシャック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouka! Bolshack</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85434" update="2007-11-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝利デッキVS黒城デッキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouri Deck vs. Kokujou Deck</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85697" update="2007-12-07">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バロム・エンペラー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ballom Emperor</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86085" update="2007-12-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キング・アルカディアス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">King Alcadeias</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86086" update="2007-12-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">デス・メタル デッキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Death Metal Deck</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86103" update="2007-12-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">白凰VSジュラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakuou vs. Jura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86617" update="2008-01-08">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">白凰の敗北</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakuou no Haiboku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87757" update="2008-01-22">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87758" update="2008-01-22">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87854" update="2008-01-29">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">非情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hijou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88300" update="2008-02-19">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">喪失</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88301" update="2008-02-19">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝舞VSジュラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoubu vs. Jura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88302" update="2008-02-19">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88401" update="2008-02-25">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死神 死す!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinigami: Shisu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88488" update="2008-03-03">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝舞VSオクト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoubu vs. Octo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88636" update="2008-03-11">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-03-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ただひとつのデュエル魂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tada Hitotsu no Duel Tamashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88827" update="2008-03-18">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">武者VSゼロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Musha vs. Zero</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88981" recap="true" update="2019-11-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2008-03-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別篇 魂召喚スペシャル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Hen: Tamashii Shoukan Special!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
