<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5531" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2008-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Blassreiter</title>
<title xml:lang="lv" type="synonym">Bālais Motobraucējs</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブラスレイター</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Blassreiter</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">블라스레이터</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">蒼色騎士</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4906" approval="20" total="32">Darker Than Black: Kuro no Keiyakusha</anime>
<anime id="8480" approval="12" total="20">Guilty Crown</anime>
<anime id="673" approval="3" total="10">Texhnolyze</anime>
<anime id="1551" approval="1" total="3">Boukyaku no Senritsu</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="12">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="339465">Refreshing action anime, with some decent characters</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="286214">Don`t let your first impression fool you, the rest of the series is not as bad as the first episode =P</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="214723">Pretty good anime, the plot starts to shine after 5-7 eps.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="30442">This anime has way too low ranking. It`s really good, and touches heavier topics than the most (like guilt, redemption, faith, angst)...

Maybe that`s why it`s ranked so low...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="436338">both thumbs up, underestimated series rly, must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="399240">i don`t know why people didn`t like it.
it was really good. Action,great animation,and surprisingly good stories.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="446496">Great story, nice animation. I really like it... ^_^</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.blassreiter.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Original Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="2163" type="Character Design">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="2442" type="Series Composition">Urobuchi Gen</name>
<name id="2702" type="Story Composition">Kobayashi Yasuko</name>
<name id="1354" type="Original Work">Nitroplus</name>
<name id="1948" type="Direction">Itano Ichirou</name>
<name id="2163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="1948" type="Series Composition">Itano Ichirou</name>
<name id="20200" type="Music">Hibino Norihiko</name>
</creators>
<description>The story is set in a fictional Germany and centers around the outbreak of biomechanical creatures named Demoniacs, who rise from corpses and attack people mindlessly. The Demoniacs have the ability to merge with most technology including cars and motorcycles, not only gaining control of them but also enhancing their performance greatly. Against them is a group of people known as XAT, Xenogenesis Assault Team, who police these Demoniacs in an attempt to keep the peace and discover the reasons for the Demoniac change. All the while, a number of human-turned-Demoniacs appear. Some use their powers for good whilst others for evil. One will rise above all other Demoniacs to become the Blassreiter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2015">4.32</permanent>
<temporary count="2043">6.68</temporary>
<review count="5">5.46</review>
</ratings>
<picture>9311.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9069</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5539</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3407</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4195</identifier>
<identifier>xuqgdc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/blassreiter/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.blassreiter.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ブラスレイター</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1368</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330246</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10009</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1221" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-28">
<name>scooter</name>
<description>A scooter is a type of motorcycle with a step-through frame and a platform for the rider`s feet.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>218044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1563" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-27">
<name>femme fatale</name>
<description>A Femme fatale (french for "deadly woman") often leads men into compromising, dangerous, and deadly situations. She tries to achieve her hidden purpose by using feminine wiles such as beauty, charm, and sexual allure. Typically, she is exceptionally well-endowed with these qualities. In some situations, she uses lying or coercion rather than charm. She may also be (or imply to be) a victim, caught in a situation from which she cannot escape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1590" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>biker</name>
<description>A person who is skilled at riding a motorcycle/motorbike and does so on a regular basis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1616" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-07">
<name>crippled</name>
<description>A person that is partially or totally unable to use one or more limbs, for example a lame.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1633" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>xenophobia</name>
<description>An intense dislike and/or fear of people from other countries.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1656" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-27">
<name>corrupt</name>
<description>The character is spiritually or morally impure and may accept payment or other benefits for services or material which the recipient is not due, under law.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1719" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-28">
<name>orphan</name>
<description>The character (in common usage: only a child, or the young of an animal) has lost both parents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1994" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-25">
<name>flying</name>
<description>This character has wings, natural or artificial, which enable the character to take flight. Or is in command of some form of levitation (e.g. a witch using a broom to fly).
Not to be confused with "flying planes" or "flying helicopters".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2019" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-16">
<name>suicidal</name>
<description>The character has suicidal tendencies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2047" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-31">
<name>human weapon</name>
<description>This tag applies to weapons that can take up a human-shaped form (Bleach and Soul Eater), artificially created human-like entities (Angeloids from Sora no Oto, Dragoons from ScrappedPrincess) and engineered humans (Chise from Saikano, Saiko Yuki from Silent Möbius).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2697" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-05">
<name>voyeurism</name>
<description>Voyeurism is the sexual interest in or practice of spying on people engaged in intimate behaviors, such as undressing, sexual activity, or other actions usually considered to be of a private nature. The principal characteristic of voyeurism is that the voyeur does not normally interact directly with the subject of his/her interest, who is often unaware of being observed. The essence of voyeurism is the observing but may also involve the making of a secret photograph or video of the subject during an intimate activity. When the interest in a particular subject is obsessive, the behavior may be described as stalking.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2709" parentid="4656" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-30">
<name>netorare</name>
<description>Netorare is what happens when the protagonist gets his wife/girlfriend stolen from him by someone else. It is a sexual fetish designed to cause sexual jealousy by way of having the heroine indulge in sexual activity with someone other than the protagonist.
The intent or reason causing the scenario does not have any bearing as to whether the scenario is netorare or netori; perspective is the only differentiating factor.
Netorare is generally caused by, but not limited to: the stealing party has malicious intent to harm the protagonist, or the wife/girlfriend hopes to improve their relationship by causing the protagonist to be jealous.
Netorare Type A
The heroine is willingly cheating on the protagonist with another guy, and enjoys every second of it. No rape, blackmail, drugs etc. involved; it`s consensual sex from the very beginning.
Netorare Type B
Initially, the heroine is raped, blackmailed, drugged, or otherwise tricked to have sex with someone other than the protagonist. However, she eventually starts enjoying it, and the sex becomes fully consensual in the end.
Netorare Type C
The heroine is raped in front of the protagonist, and he can only helplessly watch it. It`s non-consensual from start to finish.
Note: Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2716 [Netori].</description>
<picurl>150946.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2745" parentid="1773" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>mechanical tentacle</name>
<description>Same as tentacles, but instead of being fleshy-slimy, they`re made of metal or perhaps plastic, doesn`t really matter, as long as they look mechanical.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2811" parentid="2831" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Germany</name>
<description>Germany, officially the Federal Republic of Germany, is a federal parliamentary republic in central-western Europe. It includes 16 constituent states, and has a largely temperate seasonal climate. Germany is the most populous member state of the European Union. Germany`s capital and largest metropolis is Berlin, while its largest conurbation is the Ruhr, with its main centres of Dortmund and Essen.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214345.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2906" parentid="2846" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>nanomachines</name>
<description>The anime features sub-microscopic (nano = 10E-9 = one billionth) machines, machines that float in the bloodstream and affect the human body. They can be used both for good (repairing human cells in situ) or for evil (nano-machine warfare, attacking human cells in situ).</description>
<picurl>183210.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3075" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-27">
<name>nervous breakdown</name>
<description>A character sees his entire world being destroyed around him, and his brain can`t take it anymore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3278" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>deception</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3316" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>despair</name>
<description>Involves characters that may be lost in negatively emotional atmospheres created through feelings of hopelessness and suffering.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3472" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-29">
<name>unusual illness</name>
<description>A character has unusual or unlikely side-effects from an accident or suffers symptoms from ailments that could only exist within the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3589" parentid="4251" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-04">
<name>multiple protagonists - TO BE MOVED TO PARENT OR DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be moved into its parent tag http://anidb.net/t4251 [ensemble cast], or removed entirely. If the tagged entry meets the updated definition of ensemble cast, tag ensemble cast and delete multiple protagonist. If it does not meet the ensemble cast definition, delete this tag and take no further action.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3664" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>futuristic motorcycle</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3826" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-26">
<name>evil laugh</name>
<description>The thing all great evil villains do after saying/doing something evil.
Some notable examples of great evil villains with evil laughs: Dr. Evil, Dr. Horrible, The Joker, Lelouche, Light, and Mickey Mouse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4274" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>hidden agenda</name>
<description>Someone or some organization/government/etc. is misrepresenting themselves by doing/saying one thing while hoping/striving for something else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4277" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>nuclear weapons</name>
<description>A nuclear weapon is an explosive device that derives its destructive force from nuclear reactions, which release vast quantities of energy from relatively small amounts of matter. Nuclear weapons are considered weapons of mass destruction, and their use and control have been a major focus of international relations policy since their debut.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4411" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>uncovering weaknesses in human nature</name>
<description>By actions or dialogues one char will trick, surprise, or otherwise provoke other characters to react - not in the positive light they would like to be seen in - but in the way they (deep down) really are. E.g. a char accidentally speaks his quite despicable thoughts out loud.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4566" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-08">
<name>transforming weapons</name>
<description>This anime features transforming weapons, this can either be cars or household appliances that transform into weapons, such as transformers or weapons that themselves transform into bigger badder shapes to deal more and more damage.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4656" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-06">
<name>infidelity</name>
<description>Infidelity is a violation of a couple`s assumed or stated contract regarding emotional and/or sexual exclusivity, sometimes according to the subjective feeling that one`s partner has violated a set of rules or relationship norms; this violation results in feelings of sexual jealousy and rivalry. What constitutes an act of infidelity is dependent upon the exclusivity expectations within the relationship. In marital relationships, exclusivity expectations are commonly assumed although they are not always met. When they are not met, research has found that psychological damage can occur, including feelings of rage and betrayal, lowering of sexual and personal confidence, and damage to self-image.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4716" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-25">
<name>experimental technology</name>
<description>In generic use, experimental technology has not yet been fully proven in operating. Often only a prototype exists that`s being tested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4753" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>disturbing</name>
<description>Watching the show may cause the viewer to have unpleasant feelings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5466" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-17">
<name>epidemic</name>
<description>A rapid spread or increase of something (e.g. a disease) affecting many persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5732" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-01-21">
<name>evil american</name>
<description>The US plays the evil role. Usually through their actions towards another country while playing the role of the World Police.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5767" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Itano circus</name>
<description>The Itano circus is named after Itano Ichirou, a Japanese animator, and refers to a highly stylized and acrobatic method of depicting aerial combat and dogfights in many anime, particularly the Macross series, where it was utilised by Itano for the first time and was ground-breaking.
The Itano circus is characterized by detailed, fluid shading of the mecha, the close-range acrobatic moves the duelling fighters make in combat, as well as twisting contrails left by fighters and missiles. It is also commonly used in specific reference to an attack where a mecha or spaceship launches a large swarm of missiles with meticulously animated spiralling smoke trails and erratic trajectories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5994" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-25">
<name>kamikaze</name>
<description>Literally means "divine wind" or "god`s wind" in Japanese.
A suicide attacker, specifically the WWII Japanese pilots, that flew their planes into Allied ships and other targets.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6063" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-28">
<name>hallucination</name>
<description>Hallucinations can occur when excessive amount of drugs (normally illegal) are consumed / injected / smoked. A person hallucinating cannot differentiate between reality &amp; falsehoods. Surroundings &amp; environment looks crazy, bright and colourful. Everything seems to be moving.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6330" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-18">
<name>sentient object</name>
<description>A sentient object is what would be an inanimate object, but which has the capacity to think, feel, perceive, analyse, or experience events. Generally, sentient objects have the ability to take decisions and act on them. It is also common for them to be able to move around on their own and simply do things on their own power.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1719" type="appears in" update="2008-12-29">
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<name>Xenogenesis Assault Team</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A Special Police Division formed to combat Demoniacs by the Federal Police with most of their members ride motorcycles. Their headquarters is in a church in Bifröst. It had been disbanded after Wolf had its personnel infected and turned them to Demoniacs. After the events of Blassreiter, the German federal government rebuilds XAT with the new mandate of protecting people who can turn to Blassreiters.</description>
</character>
<character id="18979" type="main character in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="19">7.17</rating>
<name>Joseph Jobson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A lone, mysterious figure who serves as a Demoniac hunter. He is often seen either talking to Elea or whittling a statue of the Virgin Mary and is considered as a good candidate for the role of Blassreiter since his extraordinary sense of self-control allows him to retain his sanity, at the cost of remaining weaker than other more `open-minded` opponents like Xargin or Beatrice. During the course of the story, he causes motorbike star Gerd Frentzen to become paralysed. As a result, he becomes one of XAT`s primary targets (he then becomes known as `Blue` due to his body colour). It was after one of his run-ins with the police forces that he befriends Malek, Amanda`s adopted brother, with whom he shares similar experiences of bullying and social isolation. He is later reunited with the revived Sasha (who now bore white hair and a cybernetic implant in her left eye) and agrees to receiving the Pale Horse physical enhancement program, which will theoretically allow him to develop greater strength at the cost of his own self-control. The experiment later proves successful, turning himself into a berserker-like Blassreiter with red outlines instead of blue ones. But in the berserker state, haunted by illusions, he can`t tell the difference between friend or foe, even attacking Sasha and Amanda. Only Snow was able to bring him to his senses after sustaining heavy injuries. Joseph fights outside Zwölf`s base with Beatrice after the confrontation with Snow. He nearly kills her before Xargin interrupts and defeats him, claiming that the power Joseph had was fake.
In his Demoniac form, Joseph can make use of an energy whip, which he can also turn into a narrow-bladed sword. He uses the GARM motorcycle (masquerading as a Yotsubishi custom model), which he can fuse with once transforming.</description>
<picture>49971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18980" type="main character in" update="2014-02-02">
<rating votes="23">6.59</rating>
<name>Amanda Werner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female officer of XAT. She is Hermann`s partner, and Malek`s adoptive sister. She is hesitant in her orders to kill Blue/Joseph, and after Malek is turned into a Demoniac, attempts to stop XAT from killing him. When almost all XAT officers and civilian personnel were killed or turned to Amalgams, Amanda was one of two human survivors along with Hermann, and the only one to apparently save herself when the helicopter used in their escape was destroyed. She was later admitted into Zwölf and offered a role as an operative, although she accepted only for Malek`s sake, proudly stating that so long someone from XAT lived, XAT itself continued to exist. During the chaos that preceded Xargin`s assault, she stormed Zwölf`s HQ with Hermann and rescued Malek, turning to her aunt for protection and shelter. She stayed there when Joseph went to his doomed fight with Xargin, and in the years later she managed to rebuild XAT, serving as an instructor to the new task force. Following Joseph`s death, after the end of the series, she becomes the new pilot of GARM and thus Elea`s partner.
While Amanda is an ordinary human, she shows a high degree of experience in firearms and melee fights similar to her former colleagues. Also, after the destruction of XAT, she becomes the pilot of her team`s lone remaining Paladin, which is embedded with the names of her deceased friends as a memento of their sacrifice.</description>
<picture>49973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18981" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="5">5.00</rating>
<name>Gerd Frentzen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A famed motorcycle racer with white hair. Due to a Demoniac attack, he was rendered paralysed from the waist down, an event which ended his career as a champion and alienated him from both his team and girlfriend. On the brink of despair he was approached by Beatrice and offered the chance to restore his lost legs, becoming a Demoniac in the process. Initially working the same way as Joseph and hunting down Amalgams he was hailed as a hero and a saviour, but after discovering that his former team manager and his girlfriend had been plotting behind his back, he tried to kill them in a murderous rage and was branded as a monster. With only Hermann and Malek supporting him, he quickly succumbed to his powers and began to see everyone around him as another Amalgam. He fought fiercely with Joseph several times, and during one of these fights, regained his sanity long enough to ask Joseph to kill him if he lost control again, as he had just recently slaughtered his Amalgam-turned girlfriend on broad daylight. When he does lose control again during a race with his friend Hermann Saltza, he manages one last feat of will and drops his guard to allow Joseph to kill him, ending his tormented existence. Later on in the series, both he and Hermann are seen resting together in purgatory.
As a Demoniac, Gerd was exceptionally well-versed in melee combat, fighting with a pair of energy-bladed boomerangs attached to his back or protruding sharp energy blades from his feet, knees or elbows. His armoured form was mostly white, with his helmet being purplish-red.</description>
<picture>49975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18982" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="7">4.72</rating>
<name>Hermann Saltza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amanda`s partner and an officer of XAT, Hermann was a good friend of Gerd Frentzen, having raced with him for a long time. He was known as reckless and more often than not ignored orders, much to his superior`s chagrin and his colleagues` amusement, though he stayed loyal to his duty to hunt down Amalgams. Gerd`s transformation in an Amalgam left him stunned and desperate, and he and Malek were the only ones to defend Gerd even after he started behaving erratically. Seeing Joseph - or Blue as he knew him - killing his friend worsened his condition, fuelling his extreme hatred toward Joseph and blaming him for Gerd`s fate. When Wolf revealed his nature as an Amalgam and took over XAT, Hermann was the only human survivor who escapes along with Amanda by piloting a helicopter that ended up crash-landing soon after he ejected Amanda to safety. Laying on the brink of death, he was saved by Beatrice, who gave him her blood and turned him into an Amalgam. Although following his resurrection he suffered from amnesia and couldn`t remember their encounter. He discovered the truth inside Zwölf HQ, where he fled in a frenzy after stealing the prototype `666 Bike` (a floating platform-motorbike designed for Joseph to use). Pursued by Amanda and initially willing to find and kill Wolf alone as retribution for his dead friends of XAT, he agreed to team-up with her and rescue Malek. he ends up fighting Beatrice soon after, recognizing her as the one responsible not only for his, but for Gerd`s and Malek`s fate as well. He lands a killing blow during their fierce battle, and Beatrice uses her final attack on Malek before dying. Hermann took the hit instead and died soon after in Amanda`s arms.
Hermann`s Demoniac form is that of a red-armoured, demon-horned warrior with spiral motifs on his shoulder pads and head, armed with an enormous two-handed halberd equipped with a retractable chain-linked blade. He makes proficient use of the motorbike stolen from Zwölf, using it as a floating platform for aerial combat.</description>
<picture>49976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18983" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="19">6.73</rating>
<name>Elea</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The A.I. installed in the GARM motorbike, Elea has the appearance of a scantily clothed, dark haired girl with horns on her head. She usually criticize Joseph to no avail, and calls the Demoniacs beautiful.</description>
<picture>49978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18984" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="4">1.56</rating>
<name>Wolf Goering</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The team leader and field commander of XAT. Wolf is an imposing and powerfully built man with dark skin, who is usually very strict and often at odds with Hermann`s rebellious nature. He was wounded during the transportation of Gerd`s infected girlfriend Jil Hoffman, after he fought her with a taser when she awoke as an Amalgam. From then on he began to show strange symptoms of illness that Beatrice confirmed to be signs of him changing into an Amalgam. Seduced and committed to Xargin`s cause, he infected most of his subordinates with his mere presence, hoping they would remain at his side when they turned to Amalgams as well. This showed that, nevertheless, Wolf was still bound by some sort of friendship toward them, as he was distraught after mortally wounded Al and Brad in self-defence. After the destruction of XAT he tried to revive Al, Brad, and Lena with his blood, but succeeded only in reviving Al. He continued to direct his task force from there on, albeit as a human-hunting one. He fought against Amanda and a Demoniac-turned Hermann while counting on Al`s help, but was fooled and killed when Al regained his memories and blew most of his head off. He later appears with the other deceased characters with an apologetic look, asking Amanda for forgiveness.
Wolf`s Demoniac form is an enormous, powerful humanoid with gorilla-like features and a horned head shaped like a skull. Though slower than most Amalgams he`s immensely strong and resilient, using his tank-like armour to fend off most attacks bare-handed. He can also elongate his arms, rocket-punching his enemies with extreme strength.</description>
<picture>49979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18985" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="4">3.25</rating>
<name>Bradley Guildford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the two snipers of XAT, he`s in charge of shooting Amalgams from afar with his anti-tank sniper rifle. A somewhat stoic person, with his hair covering his eyes most of the time, and Lena`s boyfriend back in the days when they served together in the military before joining XAT. He was infected by Wolf and managed to escort Hermann and Amanda to safety at the helipad of XAT`s HQ, but ends up mortally wounded by Lena`s Paladin, which had fused with an Amalgam. He killed her himself, using his powers just enough to allow him to turn his hand into a barrel and shoot her in the head with the same bullet she gave him sometimes before. He is later killed by Wolf. Both he and Lena refuse Wolf`s blood when he tries to revive them, and turn to ash.</description>
<picture>49980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18986" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="8">5.10</rating>
<name>Alvin Lutz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>XAT`s second sniper, Alvin, or Al for short, is somewhat the opposite of Brad, as he appears to be a laid-back and carefree individual. Although he is also much more aggressive. He`s one of the team members protecting Hermann and Amanda while XAT is being destroyed by Wolf, and stays behind them before reaching the helipad to fend off the Amalgams` attacks. Killed by Wolf, he accepts his blood and is revived as a Demoniac, aiding his former leader with complete obedience until he almost kills Amanda and Hermann. When he remembers what was done to him and XAT, he turns on and kills Wolf. He does not reunite with his friends, choosing instead to die alone by blowing his head off with his rifle.
While well versed as a sniper, Al is far more precise and deadly as a sharp-shooting Demoniac. His armour is dark purple and he has curved horns on his head, plus a single yellow eye that occupied most of his face. His rifle was directly linked to his right arm, assuming a bio-mechanical appearance in the process. He has three dog tags around the barrel of his rifle; probably his, Brad`s and Lena`s.</description>
<picture>49981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18987" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="6">3.74</rating>
<name>Mei-Fong Liu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>XAT`s communications and tactical specialist. She usually stays with Wolf in the Fennek armoured vehicle during XAT-led operations in the field. Her true nature is that of a double agent planted by Victor, a cyborg, one of the three Apocalypse Knights, and the pilot of the Scale Rider; a bulky but extremely agile ultra-high altitude fighter-bomber which serves as the other two Knights` transport. She is actually a clone of Victor Stachus` granddaughter, as she was plagued by an extremely short lifespan which would have her dead after a mere 20 years of life. She takes part in the attempt to fend off the nuclear assault launched by the United States and the UN, and dies after ramming the Scale Rider into an unmanned nuclear bomber in Earth`s low orbit.</description>
<picture>49983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18988" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-02">
<rating votes="4">2.00</rating>
<name>Victor Stachus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The director and commander-in-chief of the XAT task force, Victor is actually the true leader of Zwölf having established XAT only as a means to study the Amalgams. He directed the university where Sasha discovered the nanomachines that brought about the creation of Amalgams as bioweapons and was the one who offered their power to Xargin, turning him into his enemy soon after. During the assault on Zwölf HQ he succeeded in deleting any information on the Isis anti-nanomachines from the organization`s mainframe but was confronted and brutally killed by Xargin, who fused Victor with the base servers. He did not die however, instead becoming a sort of A.I. inside Zwölf`s software. He assists Sasha in her attempt to shoot down the barrage of nuclear missiles directed at Germany, and is destroyed in the process.</description>
<picture>49984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18989" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="4">2.27</rating>
<name>Beatrice Grese</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious doctor who works at Clermont Medical Hospital and gives Gerd Frentzen a pill that would cure his paralysis under the condition that he would keep it confidential. Later on, Beatrice also gives Malek a pill as well and even brainwashes Wolf over to her cause. She turns out to be working with Xargin to replace humanity with Demoniacs, which she claims are evolved humans. Beatrice is eventually attacked and wounded by the Apocalypse Knights and ends up disowning Wolf when he loses control of the Demoniacs. During the invasion of Zwölf, she`s severely wounded by Joseph in his Blassreiter form, but is saved by Xargin. She is later left to take care of the Zwölf castle after Xargin leaves. While there, Beatrice finds out that the Isis files are missing and tracks down Amanda and Hermann. She is then confronted by Hermann in the forest and tells him that she`s responsible for what happen to Gerd and Malek. They engage in a fierce battle. Beatrice is eventually defeated by Hermann with the help of Malek.
As a Demoniac, Beatrice takes the form of an armoured female with blades instead of feet and a large net-like skirt made of energy. Only her nose is visible, as her entire head is covered and sports two large horns similar to Xargin`s. While both capable of flight and powerful in melee combat, Beatrice can also blast high-strength beams of energy.</description>
<picture>49985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18990" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="8">1.81</rating>
<name>Malek Werner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amanda Werner`s adopted brother and an ardent fan of Gerd Frentzen. Constantly bullied at his school for being an immigrant, he ended up skipping classes to avoid being discriminated against due to his origins. It is suggested that he already tried to drop out of school prior to the events in the series but had a counsellor help him back on tracks - only to fall victim to the same bullies when he returned. It`s during one of those encounters that he meets Joseph, with whom he shares similar childhood experiences, and takes care of him after he`s wounded during a fight with XAT. Distraught by Gerd`s destroyed reputation and the suicide of his only friend (who suffered from the same bullies` actions), he was approached by Beatrice and offered a pill much in the same way as Gerd, becoming a Demoniac as well. With his new powers, Malek initially believed himself to be a protector of justice allowed to punish the oppressors of the weak in whatever way he saw fit, exacting vengeance against his tormentors by brutally slaughtering them. He was confronted by XAT and fought with Joseph briefly, before being shielded by him and by Amanda as well against Al and Brad`s sniping. Escaping with Joseph into the countryside, he tended to him until Xargin appeared and easily defeated him with such power that he slipped into a catatonic state. He was kept by Zwölf as a research subject, though was eventually rescued by his sister and Hermann. He woke up during Hermann`s fight against Beatrice, and was shielded from a mortal attack once again. He resolves to challenge Xargin a second time, and although he fares better, he was nonetheless weaker and was again beaten easily. Years after Joseph`s death, during the finale, he is shown as a nineteen-year old teenager, clothed in Joseph`s trademark coat and riding a red version of his GRAM motorbike, equipped with an A.I. named Maria.
In his Demoniac form, Malek has odd-shaped yellow armour with satyr-like feet and curved horns on his helmet. While not extremely strong - for Demoniac standards - he shows incredible speed and dexterity, so much so that he leaves after-images of himself when moving. He`s armed with a long energy whip that can be turned into a dual-bladed sword. The whip can also rotate in a spiral-like motion, creating a small combat shield strong enough to easily repel small arms fire.</description>
<picture>49987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18991" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-19">
<rating votes="4">2.30</rating>
<name>Magwald Xargin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The primary antagonist of the series, Magwald Xargin was once an enthusiastic and generous researcher in his university years who tried his best to help the immigrant population, finding it unthinkable that humans wouldn`t help their peers and opposing the racist views that were commonplace in his country. He was Sasha`s lover and a great supporter of her research, though he didn`t know its objectives, believing it to be a revolutionary medical discovery. The extreme acts of intolerance he suffered, from the fire at the church where he met Joseph for the first time to the death of Sasha, drove him to disillusionment and utter despair, and when Victor Strachus bestowed him the power of the Amalgams, to complete madness. Now driven by a Messianic complex, he saw humanity as a hopeless race incapable of anything other than harm and destruction and vowed to exterminate them all himself, replacing them with a much more pure population of Amalgams. He wounded Joseph in the same event that saw him become the enemy of mankind and granted him his blood, turning him into his fiercest foe, and sometime later stumbled upon Beatrice and her dead horse. He resurrected them both and took them in as his right arm and mare respectively. While driven by genocidal ideals, Xargin is very calm, polite, and religious, often reading the Bible or citing prayers. His very appearance reflects his belief of being a saviour, as he`s always bare-footed and clothed in white, with almost feminine facial features. Xargin showed himself rarely, although he beat Malek and Joseph easily when he made his second appearance and took part in the assault of the Zwölf HQ, killing Victor Strachus. He is finally stopped after killing Joseph by being showered with Isis nanomachines, which reduce him and his whole army of Amalgams to ash, which he surprisingly takes in stride as the will of God. In the hologram that was shown at the end of the series he was present in the background, next to Beatrice.
Xargin can be considered the most powerful Amalgam in the entire series. As a Demoniac he appears as a towering, armoured humanoid reminiscent of a king or a warlord, with spiralling horns protruding from his head and four tentacles on his back. He fights with an aptly oversized greatsword, which he wields easily with one hand. Before his final fight with Joseph no one ever wounded him, being impervious to even the most powerful weaponry of the Paladins. His powers were somewhat unique in that he showed a degree of pyrokinesis, the ability to shoot powerful energy blasts, and to heal or even revive living beings.</description>
<picture>49988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24677" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-03">
<rating votes="6">5.87</rating>
<name>Sasha Jobson</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alexandra "Sasha" Jobson is Joseph`s older sister, and a rarity among immigrants in that she graduated from a public university despite her background and origins. Presented as a kind-hearted and cheerful woman, Sasha was loved by both Joseph and Xargin, who was interested by her research in the field of nanomachines, which he thought was for the purpose of aiding the medical community. This however was a lie, as her work was for the military, which was bent on the development of biological weapons. She was beaten to death by racist citizens, and died due to the injuries she suffered. She reappeared years later at Zwölf HQ, revived as a cyborg with much of her body rebuilt, shorter white hair, and a cybernetic green eye which replaced her original left. She also had a number of plugs along the left side of her face and in other parts of her body, such as her neck. Much colder than before, Sasha is one of the Apocalypse Knights and the pilot of the Bow Rider; a powerful energy cannon that doubles as a bipedal white mecha focused on long-range fire support. Plagued by what she had created back when she was human and what her brother had to endure, she sought atonement by means of death, and defends Germany from the impeding nuclear strikes at the end of the series with Mei Feng and Shido. She dies when the Bow Rider overheats and explodes with her still inside it.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>58380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63699" type="appears in" update="2014-02-03">
<name>Igor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A racer who was a part of Gerd`s former team, he was wounded by Gerd after he became the leading pilot of his team and is an arrogant but skilled racer.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>149509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63700" type="appears in" update="2014-02-03">
<name>Matthew Grant</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Former racing team manager of Gerd Frentzen, who turned into a Demoniac after 60 hours of coming in contact with Gerd`s blood. Was killed in his Demoniac form by Joseph. He was having an affair with Jill Hoffmann behind Gerd`s back and came in contact with Gerd`s blood when he stabbed Gerd in defense of Jill.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>149510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4687" picture="27301.jpg">Kinoshita Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63701" type="appears in" update="2014-02-03">
<name>Jill Hoffmann</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gerd Frentzen`s former lover, who ended her relationship with him due to his paralysis and cheated on him behind his back with Matthew Grant. Gerd found out and nearly killed her by strangulaiton. She eventually becomes a Demoniac due to exposure to Matthew`s blood, and is later killed by Gerd.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>149511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="568" picture="65531.jpg">Sakuma Kumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63703" type="appears in" update="2014-02-03">
<name>Johann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Malek Werner`s best and only friend. After being forced to bully Malek, he hung himself out of guilt.</description>
<picture>149525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="238" picture="49561.jpg">Mizusawa Fumie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63724" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="3">3.74</rating>
<name>Lene Rosamunde</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lene "Clavier" Rosamunde was a member of XAT`s Paladin squad - Team 3. She transferred to XAT from the same police unit as Brad and Al, to pursue Brad for which she had feelings. She was the one, who gave Brad his lucky charm bullet, and received same one from him.
While being tortured by Wolf, who tried to convince her and Brad to join him as Amalgams, she asked Brad to return her his lucky charm. Which he did, shooting her to death, and relieving from pain.</description>
<picture>149650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64440" type="appears in" update="2014-02-16">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Snow</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who became an Amalgam after getting infected by Joseph. Joseph saved her in the past and she in turn goes to bring about Joseph to his senses while sustaining heavy injuries in the battle with him. She seems to show some affection for Joseph.
Since she is not seen again afterwards and her hologram is displayed in the final episode, it may be assumed that she died of her injuries.</description>
<picture>150338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64441" type="appears in" update="2014-02-16">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Shidou Kasagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A well-built and imposing man with an air of coldness and a gruff attitude, Shido is of Japanese origins, having left a wife and two children to serve as one of the Apocalypse Knights. He is the pilot of the Sword Rider; a red canine-shaped mecha armed with missile launcher and prehensile, energy-firing claws mounted on extensible cables. Shido is presented as merciless, insulting Amanda and her deceased friends. He does this only to test her resolve however, and leaves clues for her about how to find Malek later on. It was revealed that Shido became a cyborg out of altruism toward his family, as his wife was from Hiroshima and suffered from genetic disease stemming from the atomic bombing of the city. He donated most of his organs to his children so to let them survive, and underwent the process that made him a Knight.
He fights fiercely against Xargin during the assault on Zwölf HQ and is wounded, but survives and takes part in the Knights` attempt to fend off the nuclear strikes against Germany. He manages to destroy the first barrage of missiles while under fire by a formation of F-35 Lightning, and self-destructs an already heavily damaged Sword Rider to destroy the last two missiles, dying in the explosion.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>150339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="88805" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="17">3.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望の始まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prelude to Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubou no Hajimari</title>
<summary>Meet Gerd, the invincible motorcycle-racing champ...whose career is cut short when a rage-filled Demoniac interrupts a race, causing utter destruction. Gerd ends up in a wheelchair never to ride again. Amidst his despair, he is approached by a mysterious woman who claims that she has the means to restore his physical abilities...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>318035</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="89846" update="2011-07-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89948" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">栄誉の対価</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Price of Glory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eiyo no Taika</title>
<summary>After witnessing the Gerd-turned-Amalgam protecting the humans from the threat of another Amalgam, people embrace his comeback as the emergence of a hero. His once-devastated life seems back on the track when one day he receives a voice mail from his ex-girlfriend Jil.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>323364</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="89990" update="2008-04-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89991" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90034" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">感染拡大</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Infection Spreads</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kansen Kakudai</title>
<summary>Amanda suspects a connection between Joseph, the mysterious man witnessed around Gerd, and the Blassreiter that fought with Gerd. She subsequently starts her own investigation. Meanwhile, the XAT witness a sudden change in the condition of the victims that were exposed to the Amalgam`s attack. The victims start to show signs of transforming into an Amalgam themselves.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329998</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90270" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疎まれし者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Disdained</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utomareshi Mono</title>
<summary>Joseph barely escapes from the XAT but is seriously injured. He collapses from exhaustion and his wounds. When he recovers consciousness, he finds himself sheltered in a warehouse containing waste disposal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339844</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90271" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">包囲網</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Under Siege</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Houimou</title>
<summary>One of the XAT members, Herman, has been seeking the Amalgam that appeared at the race circuit. He finds out that the very man he is looking for is Joseph. He searches Joseph out and manages to corner him....
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334351</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90445" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">憎悪の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At the Ends of Hatred</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zouo no Hate ni</title>
<summary>Malek is devastated by Gerd`s death. Joseph is worried about Malek and tries to stay close, remaining within the city. However, a security camera captures his transformation, and subsequently XAT learns his true identity.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349686</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90446" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔を憐れむ歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song that Pities the Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma o Awaremu Uta</title>
<summary>Gerd is tormented by the fact that he has become a beast, and as a result goes wild. He tries to fight against Joseph but is immediately contradicted. Joseph explains that he need not die if he is able to maintain his humanity. Meanwhile, Herman devises a plan to use Malek to stop Gerd.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345720</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90634" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕はもう弱虫じゃない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Weak No Longer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku wa Mou Yowamushi ja Nai</title>
<summary>Malek`s despair drives him beyond the bounds of reason. He transforms right in plain view of his bullies and starts taking his revenge. XAT agents arrive on the scene, but Malek attacks them as well. Joseph tries to persuade Malek but fails. XAT enforcements arrive and start preparing for a full-force attack on Malek.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352566</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90860" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">力の価値, 力の意味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Price and the Meaning of Power</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikara no Kachi, Chikara no Imi</title>
<summary>Amanda berates herself for not being able to look out for Malek. In an effort to save him, she sets out on a search with Herman, apart from XAT operations. Meanwhile, the injured Joseph and Malek take refuge in an abandoned church, where Joseph`s long-standing target of pursuit shows up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358372</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91125" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陰謀の中で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inside the Conspiracy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inbou no Naka de</title>
<summary>Joseph and Malek are taken into custody in a XAT laboratory. Amanda goes against orders to transfer them to a different government agency and starts to analyze Joseph`s data with the aid of Herman and a XAT researcher. There, she comes across a top-secret report code-named "Blassreiter."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>365572</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91386" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黙示録の序奏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prelude to Apocalypse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mokushiroku no Josou</title>
<summary>XAT agents begin to fall ill, one after another. Then one day, in response to a massive emergence of Amalgams in the city, the agents themselves start turning into Amalgams. A fierce battle breaks out within the XAT ranks who have turned into Amalgams and those who have not, when at last, Joseph regains consciousness.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>371852</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91478" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">審判の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Judgment Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinpan no Hi</title>
<summary>Al and Brad start showing subtle signs of Amalgamation, but Amanda and Herman are  unaffected. Amidst the inferno of ex-XAT agent Amalgams running amok, Al and Brad pledge their allegiance as XAT agents to protect Amanda and Herman until they are safely out of XAT grounds.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>383172</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91684" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖者の選択</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Saintly Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seija no Sentaku</title>
<summary>Joseph is now 15 years old. He meets a young doctor who is engaged in support activities for Outsiders such as Joseph. Joseph is touched by the doctor`s belief that normal citizens and Outsiders are both creations of god and thus should be treated equally. Joseph begins assisting  the young doctor`s activities when a group of mindless citizens attacks the doctor and injures him. At the hospital where the doctor is taken in, Joseph meets a woman named Sasha who is the doctor`s friend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>393764</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91685" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠い記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distant Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tooi Kioku</title>
<summary>Amanda takes the injured Joseph to a dilapidated church. There, Amanda learns of Joseph`s past and of his parents who died to protect him. His parents were what ordinary citizens called "Outsiders," a class of people considered inferior. Joseph was brought up by a priest who continuously reasoned with him that however harsh the world is, there must be some meaning to his life. However, reality as an Outsider was far harsher on young Joseph than anyone could ever imagine...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>389118</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92039" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神を讃える千年の騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Millenary Knights of God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami o Tataeru Sennen no Kishi</title>
<summary>Joseph and Amanda are caught and taken to the headquarters of Zwölf, a mysterious institution that meddles in forbidden science. Among its members called Apocalypse Knights are people whom Amanda knows well, and this deeply disturbs her. The Apocalypse Knights manipulate specially developed ultra-weapons and easily take down the horde of Amalgams that had previously given XAT such a hard time. Amanda is more enraged rather than stunned.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>400116</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92121" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
<summary>Amanda questions Sasha, who is still collaborating with Zwölf, the cause of this whole tragedy. However, Sasha is determined to take Zargin down with her own hands, in order to end Joseph’s suffering, and also Zargin’s. Meanwhile, a man dressed as a clergyman is making his way toward Zwölf headquarters. He has lost his memory and does not know why he is still alive, but nonetheless continues to move forward, as if driven by some uncontrollable force.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>405698</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92252" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">獣の咆哮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bellow of the Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kemono no Houkou</title>
<summary>Hermann transforms into an Amalgam and destroys the Zwölf headquarters. He then flees on Triple Six, the newly deployed vehicle. Amanda climbs aboard Paladin and pursues him. Hermann suffers from hallucinations and emotional outbursts, and rejects Amanda. However, Amanda is determined not to give up on him; she does not want to lose another comrade. Meanwhile, Sasha and the Apocalypse Knights begin their attack on the military air base taken over by Wolf and the Demoniacs.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>412754</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92422" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第四の黙示</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fourth Apocalypse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiyon no Mokushi</title>
<summary>Victor is pressured to get the situation under control, and deploys Joseph, whose enhancement procedure has only just been completed. Meanwhile, Amanda and Hermann vow to avenge the deaths of their comrades, and face off against Wolf and his gang of Demoniacs. Substantially outnumbered, Amanda and Hermann are cornered when the enhanced and rampaging Joseph appears on the scene and starts to slaughter the Demoniacs. The massacre continues amidst Joseph’s hallucinatory manifestations of desperation, fear, and resentment.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>414534</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92546" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去からの想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Quondam Affections</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako kara no Omoi</title>
<summary>Joseph continues to slay one Demoniac after another. Wolf escapes from this bedlam, after which Hermann gives chase. Amanda follows suit, but along the way she meets a girl named Snow. Years ago Snow has became an Amalgam after being exposed to Joseph`s blood. Since then she traveled with him, during which course they became emotionally close. Amanda learns of Hermann’s destination from Snow, leaves her to deal with the raging Joseph and heads toward XAT headquarters where Wolf has taken shelter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>414702</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92551" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄泉の軍勢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legion from the Netherworld</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomi no Gunzei</title>
<summary>Upon hearing Snow`s voice, Joseph regains his sanity. He is immediately taken into custody by Zwölf to have his enhancements tuned up once again. Meanwhile, Xargin is heading a battalion of Demoniacs to mount an attack on the Zwölf headquarters. His purpose is to find out whether Joseph, who has the power to enforce submission of the Demoniacs, has awakened or not. Amanda, with her own agenda of retrieving Malek from Zwölf, succeeds in infiltrating the headquarters on the pretense that she has captured Hermann.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>414706</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92915" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼白の騎手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom Rider</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souhaku no Kishu</title>
<summary>Xargin and the Demoniacs attack the Zwölf headquarters, immediately causing complete mayhem. Sasha confronts Xargin, telling him that she has been brought back to life for the purpose of purifying him. Xargin replies that nothing other than terminating the world will serve as purification. Meanwhile, Amanda and Hermann are searching frantically for Malek when Amanda discovers a mysterious message.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>414718</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92959" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かぬ想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drifting Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokanu Omoi</title>
<summary>Amanda escapes from Zwölf headquarters, and takes refuge in an orphanage run by her aunt. There, she is visited by Sasha, who entrusts her with the data of Isis, the last resort to defeat Xargin. However, Beatrice learns of Isis, and heads for the orphanage. In order to protect Amanda and the others, Hermann faces off with Beatrice in a resolute battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>414724</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93064" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">劫火の大地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scorched Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouka no Daichi</title>
<summary>The Zwölf is wiped out, and the governments of other countries make a decision to attack German territories. Mei-Fong and her comrades learn from their own alert system that bombing raids have begun, and try to intercept the missiles utilizing resources of the Apocalypse Knights. Meanwhile, a single figure faces off with Xargin in order to buy time until Isis is completed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>414730</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93120" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束の地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promised Land</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku no Chi</title>
<summary>Joseph continues his final battle with Xargin with the nanomachine Isis injected into his body. The Isis will bring certain doom to Xargin, and to Joseph himself. Meanwhile, in the air and on the ground, Sasha and Mei-Fong desperately try to intercept the new-generation intercontinental ballistic missiles that were launched for the purpose of turning German territory into a smoldering wasteland. However, the ICBMs manage to deflect the interceptions with their state-of-the-art system and edge ever closer to German airspace.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>414742</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125760" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125761" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130415" recap="true" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラスレイター・ナビ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blassreiter Navigator</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blassreiter Navi</title>
<summary>This is a special program which recaps the first eleven episodes of BLASSREITER in approximately 20 minutes.
 
If you have never seen the show, this is a great chance to learn what the story is about. Check out this program, and if you like it, you can go back and watch all the previous episodes. The latest episode is also available online.
 
For fans since from the beginning of the series, this digest will bring you back all the highlights of the first half, so it`s a must-see as well!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>434102</identifier>
<identifier>blassreiter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131817" update="2011-07-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロモーション映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Promotion Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131818" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラスレガイド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blassreiter Guide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blassre Guide</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131819" update="2011-07-11">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vol.8 - Information</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131820" update="2011-07-11">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vol.7 - Information</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131821" update="2011-07-11">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vol.6 - Information</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131822" update="2011-07-11">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vol.5 - Information</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131823" update="2011-07-11">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vol.4 - Information</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131824" update="2011-07-11">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vol.3 - Information</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131825" update="2011-07-11">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vol.2 - Information</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131826" update="2011-07-11">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vol.1 - Information</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
