<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5534" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2008-06-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Amatsuki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">雨夜之月</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Аматсуки</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Амацуки</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Амацуки</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">雨月</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">あまつき</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="145509">The premise in this anime has so much potential. Thirteen episodes is not enough. The end is rushed and left wide open and unresolved.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="276230">Uncomplicated and enjoyable but beware, NO resolution. This watches like one big prolog to the real series which with this setup could be really good. If there is no next season I will regret having watched this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="309568">Short but sweet mint not always be the best but it i still sweet enough for a must see.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://amatsuki.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="1410" type="Series Composition">Furuhashi Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="1410" type="Direction">Furuhashi Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="6734" type="Character Design">Tagashira Shinobu</name>
<name id="27278" type="Original Work">Takayama Shinobu</name>
<name id="2479" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ban Yukiko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the josei manga by http://anidb.net/cr27278 [Takayama Shinobu], serialised in Comic Zero-Sum.
Ordinary high school student, http://anidb.net/ch6172 [Rikugou Tokidoki], has to take supplementary History classes, to boost his failing grade, at a state-of-the-art museum. This museum allows the visitor to use high-tech virtual reality to reconstruct a realistic Edo of the Bakumatsu period. However, once the simulation begins, Tokidoki is attacked by a strange creature. After something happens to his left eye, he realizes that he is not wearing the VR goggles - it is no longer a simulation; he`s trapped in the virtual world and has no way of getting back.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1968">4.79</permanent>
<temporary count="1989">6.98</temporary>
<review count="3">6.10</review>
</ratings>
<picture>7090.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9029</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3359</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4146</identifier>
<identifier>ouuydt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://amatsuki.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Amatsuki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>あまつき</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1353</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330153</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9945</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2125</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2008/amatsuki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="513" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-13">
<name>tengu</name>
<description>They are a class of supernatural creatures found in Japanese folklore, art, theater, and literature. They are one of the best known yōkai (monster-spirits) and are sometimes worshipped as Shinto kami (revered spirits or gods).
Although they take their name from a dog-like Chinese demon (Tiangou), the tengu were originally thought to take the forms of birds of prey, and they are traditionally depicted with both human and avian characteristics.
The earliest tengu were pictured with beaks, but this feature has often been humanized as an unnaturally long nose, which today is practically the tengu`s defining characteristic in the popular imagination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-24">
<name>kitsune</name>
<description>Kitsune is the Japanese word for http://anidb.net/t191 [fox], which are a common subject of Japanese folklore. This term in English specifically refers to kitsune as demon foxes or fox spirits. Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t1814 [foxpersons], a http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin] with fox characteristics.
Stories depict them as intelligent beings and as possessing magical abilities that increase with their age and wisdom. Foremost among these is the ability to assume human form.</description>
<picurl>226225.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2402" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-09">
<name>archery</name>
<description>Archery is the art, practice, or skill of shooting arrows with the use of a bow, from Latin arcus. A person who participates in archery is typically known as an archer.
While archery has been historically used for hunting, both for food and later, in a use that survives to this day, also as a sport, through most of pre-gunpowder human history its main use was for combat; archers were extremely important in warfare, in open field and siege alike, due to their ability to massively kill enemy armies with literal rains of arrows and to set things aflame with burning arrowheads. Proper easy of burning arrowheads could destroy the morale of an invading infantry division or set the entire defending fortress on fire, while non-burning arrowheads could destroy a large portion of the enemy infantry before it could even enter melee combat. Such was the destruction ability of archers that horse archers were the backbone of the both the Hun and Mongol hordes; the former brought terror to and helped the eventual demise of the Roman Empire, while the latter conquered such a large portion of Eurasia that historians coined the term Pax Mongolica (paralleling the Pax Romana) to describe their empire that at its apex spanned from modern-day Poland to the Middle East to Southern China, Korea and the southern parts of Russia.
With the discovery of gunpowder and the invention of firearms, archery was quickly rendered obsolete in warfare. Early firearms were not good in comparison to good archers, with drawbacks such as a vastly inferior rate of fire and high susceptibility to wet weather; nevertheless, they had longer effective range and, most importantly, required almost no practice to use properly in comparison to the many years that it took to train an archer; indeed, a popular saying used to go that "to make a good archer, one must start with his grandfather". Nevertheless, in the Far East archery is to this day considered an important subject in the studies of martial arts, and some Japanese schools have archery dojos ran by archery clubs. Additionally, archery saw an 18th century reemergence as a recreational activity in the West, becoming relevant as an elite class sport, specially for hunting but also at non-living targets, and eventually also becoming an Olympic competition.</description>
<picurl>145640.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2467" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-22">
<name>sword</name>
<description>A sword is a long, edged piece of metal, used as a cutting, thrusting, and clubbing weapon in many civilizations throughout the world. Before firearms became commonplace, and fast enough to render other weapons pointless in the battlefield, they were the main kind of weapon for war and duels alike. A sword fundamentally consists of a blade and a hilt, typically with one or two edges for striking and cutting, and a point for thrusting. That aside, however, they may come in all sorts of designs: the medieval European swords used to be big, heavy weapons that did not actually cut but instead broke the enemy`s bones under their armor; conversely, the Chinese jian sword (called "ken" in Japanese) attempted to exploit the armor`s joints and perforate the enemy`s flesh in those places, but was useless against the armor itself, and did not take the strikes, preferring to redirect them, to this day being considered a highly "circular" weapon and associated to taijiquan; on the other hand, the Japanese katana was a balanced all-purposes weapon that could be used even in an axe-like way, but which a master swordsman could use in many other, more elaborate manners.</description>
<picurl>127113.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2692" parentid="2641" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-10">
<name>Bakumatsu - Meiji Period</name>
<description>"Bakumatsu" (幕末, "Late Tokugawa Shogunate") occurred between 1853 and 1867 during which Japan ended its isolationist foreign policy and modernized from a feudal shogunate to the Meiji government. Bakumatsu represents the final years of the Edo period (when the Tokugawa shogunate ended) and preceded the Meiji era. The primary historical significance of Bakumatsu was the conflict between the pro-imperialist "Ishin Shishi" ("nationalist patriots"), and the shogunate forces, including the elite Shinsengumi ("New Selected Corps").
The Meiji Era (including Meiji Restoration) denotes the 45-year reign of Emperor Meiji, running from 23 October 1868 to 30 July 1912. During this time, Japan started its modernization and rose to world power status.
Be aware that this category should only be assigned to anime that take place in Japan during the years mentioned above, and not to every anime that has samurai in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2884" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>psychoactive drugs</name>
<description>Psychoactive drugs are chemical substances that affect the function of the central nervous system, altering perception, mood or consciousness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3432" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>pacifism</name>
<description>The belief and following of principles stating all and any conflict has a peaceful solution without use of violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6172" type="main character in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="7">4.34</rating>
<name>Rikugou Tokidoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An easygoing high school student who adapts easily to new surroundings. He loses the vision in his left eye to the Nue and Yakou and finds himself trapped in a simulation of the Edo period. Called the "unwritten page" by some in the virtual Edo, as his fate isn`t foretold by Heaven`s Net. The demons that want to protect the world want to make him the new "Teiten" or God of Amatsuki, since he is just as powerful as the current one.</description>
<picture>23403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6173" type="main character in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="6">4.58</rating>
<name>Shinonome Kon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Tokidoki`s high school who is cool-headed and logical, but has a reputation for getting into fights. He was also attacked by the Nue and Yakou, which left him without the sensation in his right arm, and became trapped in Edo as well. He arrived two years before Tokidoki, and acts as Tokidoki`s mentor after his arrival.</description>
<picture>23404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6174" type="main character in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="10">5.82</rating>
<name>Kuchiha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A swordswoman who has a dog deity (inugami) living inside her, and as a result, is despised by humans. She saved Tokidoki from the Nue. At first, she hates optimistic and naive people like Tokidoki, but she warms up to him throughout the course of the series. She usually wears her hair in a long ponytail, and has a big appetite.</description>
<picture>23405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6175" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="8">6.60</rating>
<name>Bonten</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A powerful demon with the ability to read fate. He is one of the four Holy Ones. He has known Ginshu since he was a child.Their first encounter he had tried to kill her, but found out that it was futile (as she had said she was just a decoy for Shinshu). He was very fond of Ginshu (it was mutual) but unlike Ginshu, he did not like to openly admit it and often spoke to her rudely. He spent most of the winter as a child playing with Ginshu in various games. However, their relationship changed drastically after the priestess of the Sakigami shrine severely injured Tsuyukusa. A bloody battle took place, and as Ginshu and Byakuroku killed each other, a deal was made with Heaven, so that Shinshu`s power was transferred to Bonten, and he replaced Byakuroku taking his place as Heaven`s Seat.</description>
<picture>23406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6176" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="4">4.03</rating>
<name>Shamon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In public, a temple priest, but in private, a demon hunter. He is Kuchiha`s foster father.</description>
<picture>23407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6177" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="2">6.99</rating>
<name>Tsuyukusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A kodama who works with Bonten. He resents humans for the death of Byakuroku, but seems to have little trouble befriending them.</description>
<picture>23409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6178" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<name>Utsubushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tengu who serves Bonten. Utsubushi regards Bonten as his `father` as he is in fact a collaboration of spirits Bonten had gathered and given form to.</description>
<picture>23410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6179" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="3">4.98</rating>
<name>Ginshu</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the four Holy Ones and the High Priestess of the Sakigami shrine. Originally believed to have been cursed by the demon Byakuroku, it was later revealed that her spirit was in fact placed within Byakuroku`s body, as an attempt by Bonten to preserve them both (after a battle that would have cost both their lives). Ginshu is actually asexual, but is referred to as a Princess anyway.
It is revealed that Ginshu is actually not the real High Priestess, but a decoy to protect the real High Priestess, Shinshu. She possesses "poison blood" to demons, so when they try to eat her they die.</description>
<picture>23411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6180" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="4">3.02</rating>
<name>Shinshu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ginshu`s younger sister. She can never age and is forever a child, and is actually the real High Priestess and possesses the power of foresight through the use of dreams. She is very innocent and cute, and is very fond of Ginshu.</description>
<picture>23412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6181" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="2">3.03</rating>
<name>Sasaki Tadajirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A government official in charge of demon hunting. He and Shamon are old friends.</description>
<picture>23413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6182" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="4">4.74</rating>
<name>Tsuruume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ginshu`s attendant. She has been loyal to Ginshu since she was a child, and heavily quarreled with Shinshu. It is revealed that she is from a well off family, but has chosen to serve Ginshu.</description>
<picture>23414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6183" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="2">5.36</rating>
<name>Kurotobi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A strange person on the orders of Sasaki to watch Tokidoki. He has a pet demon, a Fire Rat. He also knows how to handle demons.</description>
<picture>23415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6184" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="4">2.60</rating>
<name>Benitobi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6185" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="2">4.39</rating>
<name>Susutake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2219" picture="23794.jpg">Ishino Ryuuzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6186" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="2">3.67</rating>
<name>Byakuroku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An old and powerful snake demon who, at the brink of death after biting into Ginshu`s `poison blood`, became the vessel for Ginshu`s spirit. He raised Bonten and Tsuyukusa.</description>
<picture>23418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6187" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="3">5.96</rating>
<name>Imayou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A kitsune who resents humans for the death of her master. She`s corrupted by the Yakou after killing humans. She is later saved by Tokidoki, and afterwards reverts back to her original form.</description>
<picture>23421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="693" picture="226546.jpg">Igarashi Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6188" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="2">4.39</rating>
<name>Suou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6189" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="3">3.38</rating>
<name>Inugami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6190" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="2">3.67</rating>
<name>Aruji-dono</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6191" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="2">2.50</rating>
<name>Yakou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6192" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-02">
<rating votes="3">2.07</rating>
<name>Ainezu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6193" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="3">1.59</rating>
<name>Nue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23424.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6194" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="3">4.98</rating>
<name>Heihachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend of Tokidoki and Kon. He later becomes friends with Tsuyukusa. He gets teased by Kon for having strange and large eyes. He`s severely injured by Imayou, but is healed and brought to health by Tsuyukusa.</description>
<picture>23408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="88799" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨夜之月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Rainy Evening`s Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame Yoru Kore Tsuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89845" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90084" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狗をよぶ聲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Voice That Calls to Dogs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu o Yobugoe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90257" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">化け物道中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On the Monster`s Road</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakemono Douchuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90332" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬神と姫神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spirit of the Dog and the Sacred Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inugami to Himeka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90375" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暁と目覚め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dawn and Waking</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akatsuki to Mezame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90643" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">澪標</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marks In A Water Channel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miotsukushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90684" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暁降ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Falling Daybreak</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akatsuki Kutachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90849" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">薄暮花が眠る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dusk Flower Is Sleeping</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakubo Hana ga Nemuru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91110" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">春昼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spring Noon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haru Hiru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91197" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして, 日は陰り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And So, the Days Darkened</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Hi wa Kageri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91490" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">木の暗茂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dark and Thick Woods</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ki no Kura Shigeru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91579" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高嶺颪の虎落笛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Winter Winds of the High Peaks Whistles Through the Bamboo Fence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kourei Oroshi no Mogaribue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91580" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">児手柏の両面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Both Sides of the Konotegashiwa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konotegashiwa no Ryoumen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167971" update="2015-04-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167972" update="2015-04-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
