<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5535" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>2008-06-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kurenai</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Курэнай</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">쿠레나이</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">كوريناي</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Kurenai</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Куренай</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kure-nai</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Куренай</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">红</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">紅</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kurenai</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">홍(紅)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7373" type="Sequel">Kurenai (2010)</anime>
<anime id="6322" type="Same Setting">Denpateki na Kanojo</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8211" approval="17" total="36">Usagi Drop</anime>
<anime id="4403" approval="4" total="12">Seirei no Moribito</anime>
<anime id="7248" approval="3" total="10">Sarai-ya Goyou</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="31">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="79753">Personally i watched this because it was related to "Denpa Teki na Kanojo" (AWSOME to watch), but its just another completely different with absolutely no relation. 
Viewer advised this anime has a male character (mature character), who is voiced by a female, actually sounding like a female.
That does not sit right with me...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="179325">I didn`t expect much, but I was so wrong.
It actually was pretty good and enjoyable.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="84039">it`s very fun and has somewhat interesting animation because it mix various types of animation</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="18705">Starts off seeming great -- some nice ideas and interesting characters, unique art style, etc... But as it goes on things get stranger and more irrational, and the main character gets weaker and more annoying. By the end it just made me angry.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="492628">Interesting plot and characters, the bad part is the lack of attention to side characters and there personalities.
It is still decent but the felling that it could have been better will remain.
Still recommended</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="268960">It’s kind caring nature combined with a topic about forced family traditions made it one of my favorite anime. Despite it flaws it was enjoyable to watch!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="278693">Well, let me put it this way- Kurenai is a very amusing way to juxtapose a single-parent male with impudent yet cute girl-child and whatever the dramatic overall storyline in is. The interaction bt/wn the male lead and girl is tongue-in-cheek, as is the girl`s interaction with the women who live next to the male lead. HILARIOUS! PLEASE WATCH!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="47306">Cute, funny, lovable characters, so far a favorite from this season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="254276">10 of 10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="176331">Simply a kickass seinen anime that doesn`t require much effort to enjoy it.  The anime is very lax and easy to sit down and watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="374795">Great show. I wonder how I could`ve missed that one. A must see !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="341304">Exceeded way beyond my expectations. A very original, well animated and written series. Watch it now, you wont regret it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="143965">Definitely recommendable as a must see, must have.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="414904">Awesome series. Awesome character development, awesome voice acting, awesome story. Must see.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.samidareso.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="982" type="Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="1404" type="Original Work">Katayama Kentarou</name>
<name id="1600" type="Series Composition">Matsuo Kou</name>
<name id="1600" type="Direction">Matsuo Kou</name>
<name id="4418" type="Character Design">Ishii Kumi</name>
<name id="4418" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishii Kumi</name>
<name id="9159" type="Music">Muramatsu Ken</name>
<name id="8545" type="Character Design">Fuji Jun</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr1404 [Katayama Kentarou], illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr3723 [Yamamoto Yamato].
The 16-year-old http://anidb.net/ch3634 [Kurenai Shinkurou] is a mediator — a specialist in settling squabbles between people. Despite his youth and easy-going nature, he is a man of some skills when it comes to protecting both his clients and his client`s interests. One day he is assigned as a bodyguard for http://anidb.net/ch3635 [Kuhouin Murasaki], a seven-year-old girl. From how the girl reacts to everyday events, like shopping, it is quite clear to Shinkurou that she must come from a wealthy background, and as it turns out Murasaki`s family is very powerful and dangerous...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4207">6.96</permanent>
<temporary count="4239">7.79</temporary>
<review count="7">7.04</review>
</ratings>
<picture>83853.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8518</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3358</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4160</identifier>
<identifier>uptvfh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.samidareso.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kure-nai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>紅_(小説)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1346</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330183</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9652</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3932" parentid="6073" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-11">
<name>older female younger male</name>
<description>This tag indicates that this anime has a male and female lead, and the female is older. If the main cast is greater than two people, then the use of this tag would indicate a romantic relationship between those two.
In case of harems it translates to:
a) majority of the girls are older than the guy
b) the lead girl (or her main rival) is older than the guy</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4136" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-03-05">
<name>sudden loli companion appearance</name>
<description>The main character meets a preadolescent girl in an unexpected way becoming a friend / partner of the main character.
(The term loli is short for Lolita meaning a girl in preadolescent age. Typical attributes are moe, cute, and innocent.)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4304" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-04-26">
<name>anti-climactic end</name>
<description>The story in this anime and the character development were building up so some special point, and the viewer will probably have been looking forward to this resolution. But the ending was a let-down.
This may have several reasons, e.g. it may simply be "bad" story-telling, or the animation studio ran out of money and had to prematurely end the story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3634" type="main character in" update="2017-07-26">
<rating votes="29">5.16</rating>
<name>Kurenai Shinkurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main protagonist of the series. Despite his looks he is a capable and strong worker who works for Benika doing many types of jobs including being the bodyguard of Murasaki. He is trained in martial arts as well as being physically strong and will take any job for Benika, whom he looks up to.</description>
<picture>65231.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3635" type="main character in" update="2009-05-26">
<rating votes="90">8.41</rating>
<name>Kuhouin Murasaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Murasaki is the seven year old daughter of Souju and Renjo Kuhouin. She is the one being protected by Shinkuro. At first very stubborn and snobbish, she soon lightens up and trusts Shinkuro. She lives with him for protection against her family that has a rule of keeping her in the Inner Sanctuary of their home at all times and never experiencing the outside world until Benika took her.</description>
<picture>25974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3636" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-26">
<rating votes="10">6.75</rating>
<name>Juusawa Benika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Shinkuro`s employer for which he would do anything for out of gratitude for her help when he was young and because he respects her completely. She a calm and collected person who goes with her intuition. On behalf of Murasaki`s mother last wish she took Murasaki out of the Inner Sanctuary and placed her in the care of Shinkuro who she believes is similar to her.</description>
<picture>65237.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3637" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-26">
<rating votes="9">6.64</rating>
<name>Inuzuka Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She works for Benika as one of her subordinates and has a tendency to overstep her bounds with complaints about Shinkuro. She believes that an important job like protecting Murasaki would better be left in more capable and experienced hands.</description>
<picture>65236.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1626" picture="156857.jpg">Ookubo Aiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3638" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-26">
<rating votes="18">7.64</rating>
<name>Murakami Ginko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a friend of Shinkuro`s who also looks up information for him on the Internet to help. She has been his friend for a long time and also seems to have a crush on him as well as she worries about him when he does jobs for Benika. Ginko is jealous whenever Yuuno is around him.</description>
<picture>65233.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1444" picture="172066.jpg">Masu Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3639" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-26">
<rating votes="23">8.41</rating>
<name>Houzuki Yuuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who Shinkuro lived with when he was young and also his sparring partner. She comes from a family that used to be assassins but still practice the martial arts. Her soft demeanour hides the fact that she is a strong fighter. She also seems to have a crush on Shinkuro and likes to spend time with him. Yuuno has a younger sister named Chizuru, who is five. Their grandfather expects Yuuno and Chizuru to carry on the Houzuki family martial arts skills.</description>
<picture>65232.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3640" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-26">
<rating votes="16">5.63</rating>
<name>Mutou Tamaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a university student who lives in the same building as Shinkuro. She can be described as a very flirtatious person, especially towards Shinkuro. She says she is very knowledgeable in the ways of love but doesn`t include her own experiences as she has a hard time keeping a boyfriend. She tends to voluntarily watch Murasaki during the day while Shinkuro is at school.</description>
<picture>65234.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3641" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-26">
<rating votes="22">7.53</rating>
<name>Yamie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is yet another tenant of the building Shinkuro lives in. She always wears black and calls herself a very sinful woman. She likes cats and usually keeps to herself except when it comes to Shinkuro and Tamaki. Her attitude can be considered sarcastic most times.</description>
<picture>65235.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="33" picture="133462.jpg">Kimura Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3642" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-21">
<rating votes="3">2.24</rating>
<name>Kuhouin Renjou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is Murasaki`s father who according to custom had to marry a woman named Kazuko. During her stay she abused Murasaki`s real mother named Souju while taking the role of mother to herself to which she was not accustomed. Renjou in the meantime did nothing even when Souju, the woman he really loved, committed suicide.</description>
<picture>19459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36095" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="8">7.05</rating>
<name>Lin Cheng-Shin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She has no interest in the Kuhouin family matters and only works for them because she desires strong opponents to defeat.
Note: This Lin is completely different character than in the anime 2010 version which is based on the original novel and manga.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>1328.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75116" type="appears in" update="2015-05-11">
<name>Houzuki Housen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Current Head of the Houzuki Family.</description>
<picture>173274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1416" picture="18579.jpg">Ishimori Takkou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75117" type="appears in" update="2015-05-11">
<rating votes="2">3.94</rating>
<name>Houzuki Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41952" picture="166825.jpg">Imagawa Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75127" type="appears in" update="2015-05-11">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Kuhouin Souju</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75128" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-11">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Kuhouin Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75129" type="appears in" update="2015-05-11">
<name>Sofu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3298" picture="151659.jpg">Katou Seizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75130" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Kuhouin Kazuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuhouin Renjou`s legal wife. She is jealous of Renjou`s affection towards Souju and has no qualms about showing it.
Source: Japanese Wikipedia.</description>
<picture>173301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="486" picture="235171.jpg">Koyama Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75131" type="appears in" update="2015-05-11">
<name>Tomoaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinkuro`s classmate.</description>
<picture>173302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10369" picture="38120.jpg">Urata Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75132" type="appears in" update="2015-05-11">
<name>Akio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinkurou`s classmate.</description>
<picture>173303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2069" picture="170535.jpg">Yamaguchi Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75133" type="appears in" update="2015-05-11">
<name>Jochuutou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head Maid.</description>
<picture>173305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="634" picture="18161.jpg">Kurata Masayo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="88798" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Extreme Night</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Noite climática</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Ekstremali Naktis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokuya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89077" update="2008-03-31">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89833" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">溝と流れと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With a Drain and Stream</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Com o escoamento e fluxo</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Tekėti pasroviui...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizo to Nagare to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89892" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">15 second commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90082" update="2008-04-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="18">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">偽者の顔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Face of an Imposter</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A face da fraude</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Apsimetėlio veidas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nisemono no Kao</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90256" update="2008-04-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">才物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clever One</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Pessoa esperta</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Protingas žmogus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saibutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90362" update="2008-04-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">望み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Desejo</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Troškimas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nozomi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90437" update="2008-08-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="23">4.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">貴方の頭上に光が輝くでしょう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Light Probably Shines over Your Head</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A luz sobre você está brilhando</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Šviesa virš tavo galvos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata no Zujou ni Hikari ga Kagayaku Deshou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90647" update="2008-08-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Mulheres</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Moteris</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90723" update="2008-08-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自愛と臆病と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taking Care of One`s Self and Cowardice</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Auto-preservação e covardia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jiai to Okubyou to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90724" update="2008-08-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">貴方と私と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With You and Me</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Você e eu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata to Watashi to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90725" update="2010-12-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90726" update="2010-12-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91104" update="2008-05-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91161" update="2008-05-31">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">慣れの恐怖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreadful Experience</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Medo agudo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nare no Kyoufu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91238" update="2008-06-06">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">われ思う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Think</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Eu acho</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ware Omou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91327" update="2008-08-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">われ存在り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exist</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Eu sou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ware Ari</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
