<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5536" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-03-26</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">School Days: Magical Heart Kokoro-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Шкільні дні: магічне серце☆Кокоро-чан</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">School Days ~マジカルハート☆こころちゃん~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">School Days: Magical Heart Kokoro-chan</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5117" type="Alternative Setting">School Days</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.schooldays-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="794" type="Animation Work">TNK</name>
<name id="1355" type="Original Work">0verflow</name>
<name id="9771" type="Character Design">Gotou Junji</name>
<name id="1540" type="Series Composition">Uezu Makoto</name>
<name id="1539" type="Direction">Motonaga Keitarou</name>
<name id="9771" type="Chief Animation Direction">Gotou Junji</name>
<name id="3347" type="Music">Ookubo Kaoru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Spin-off of the School Days game by http://anidb.net/cr1355 [0verflow].
http://anidb.net/ch2352 [Katsura Kokoro], the little sister of http://anidb.net/ch2345 [Kotonoha], turns into the magical girl http://anidb.net/ch62854 [Magical Heart] out to save the world...
Note: Originally meant as an April Fools` joke in 2007.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1289">2.46</permanent>
<temporary count="1314">5.34</temporary>
<review count="1">6.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>8235.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8921</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3328</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4139</identifier>
<identifier>uvqaqg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.schooldays-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1879</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9632</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2344" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="197">1.31</rating>
<name>Itou Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Itou Makoto is the unlikely protagonist of the series. A generally mannered and composed student in year one of class three, his life becomes complicated when he begins to unfaithfully initiate polyamorous relationships with girls that he is unable to singly commit to.
Though he is initially casual, gregarious and understanding, his addiction to sex overtime corrupts his personality and he instead becomes more apathetic, rash and egotistical towards others, regardless of interpersonal harm or later consequence.
Makoto lives with his divorced mother and has a younger sister Itaru who lives with their father. He is good friends with http://anidb.net/ch2351 [Sawanaga Taisuke] and http://anidb.net/ch2350 [Katou Otome].</description>
<picture>148140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2345" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="123">7.62</rating>
<name>Katsura Kotonoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsura Kotonoha is a gentle and reserved student in year one of class four who is on the student council and serves as one of the most pivotal characters in the story.
A cute and noticeably well-endowed bookworm, she becomes the initial love interest of http://anidb.net/ch2344 [Makoto] early into their second term, and with some effort from http://anidb.net/ch2346 [Saionji Sekai], becomes his girlfriend after she reciprocates her affection for him.
While Kotonoha for the most part is calm and gentle, she has a very delicate conscious, which under stress leads to irrational culpability, delusions and even malice.
She has a younger sister http://anidb.net/ch2352 [Kokoro] and lives with their wealthy mother Manami and father in the fictional area of Haramihama. She is disliked by http://anidb.net/ch2350 [Katou Otome] and is subject to her bullying and duress.</description>
<picture>148141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="618" picture="223541.jpg">Okajima Tae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2346" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-04">
<rating votes="110">4.11</rating>
<name>Saionji Sekai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saionji Sekai is a student in year one of class three who is the antithesis and foil of http://anidb.net/ch2345 [Kotonoha].
A playful and outgoing classmate seated directly next to http://anidb.net/ch2344 [Makoto], she takes a curious interest in him during their first acquaintance, and in every medium of the series, helps to establish his bond with Kotonoha. Though genuinely upbeat, Sekai does occasionally show a more serious side, and when sufficiently frustrated can be loud, selfish, overemotional and even manipulative.
She lives with her mother http://anidb.net/ch41022 [Youko] in the fictional area of Motehara-Sakashita, is part-time employed as a waitress at the family restaurant Radish and is also the best friend of http://anidb.net/ch2347 [Kiyoura Setsuna].</description>
<picture>148142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1528" picture="223648.jpg">Kawaragi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2347" type="appears in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="76">5.45</rating>
<name>Kiyoura Setsuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiyoura Setsuna is a student in year one of class three, who as http://anidb.net/ch2345 [Kotonoha], is on the student council as a class representative.
One of the more inscrutable characters, Setsuna is a keen, focused and habitually tacit girl who tends to have and keep the most level head of her peers when situations go awry.</description>
<picture>148143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4664" picture="234976.jpg">Imoto Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2348" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="35">1.68</rating>
<name>Kuroda Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuroda Hikari is a temperamental and fastidious student in year one of class three, recognisable by her signature squid rings hairstyle.
She initially believes that http://anidb.net/ch2344 [Makoto] and http://anidb.net/ch2346 [Sekai] are dating from the very start, and tends to negatively generalise him; later growing closer to him herself. Though she is actually quite friendly and social, Hikari is the most childish of the cast; sporting an unduly knack for whining and prying into the affairs of others.
Her family owns a confectionery store and café, famous for its lemon custard pie. Hikari is good friends with Sekai and has an unreciprocated crush on http://anidb.net/ch2351 [Sawanaga Taisuke].</description>
<picture>148148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1617" picture="19642.jpg">Tanaka Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2349" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="41">2.17</rating>
<name>Kanroji Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanroji Nanami is a student in year one of class three who is a member of the girl`s basketball team, attending the school on an athletic scholarship.
A mostly interpersonal character, Nanami is a mature and somewhat quiet individual who really never involves herself with the affairs of others and as such remains for the most part unanalysed. She is the only girl of the main cast to have an established boyfriend from the start, a member of the basketball club named Kyoichi; though to her chagrin he is more of a devout otaku.
Nanami is good friends with http://anidb.net/ch2346 [Sekai], who comes from her junior high school, and http://anidb.net/ch2350 [Katou Otome]. Of the entire cast Nanami is the tallest character.</description>
<picture>148149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2350" type="appears in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="51">2.27</rating>
<name>Katou Otome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katou Otome is a direct and headstrong student in year one of class four, who as http://anidb.net/ch2349 [Nanami], is a member of the girl`s basketball team. She is usually authoritative to her peers, tolerates nothing but her way and opinion, and does not generally associate with anyone but her trio of friends http://anidb.net/ch41024 [Obuchi Minami], http://anidb.net/ch41025 [Koizumi Natsumi] and http://anidb.net/ch41023 [Mori Kumi]; who together frequently harass and coerce http://anidb.net/ch2345 [Kotonoha].
Despite her difficult behaviour and personality however, Otome can be particularly tender and shy, especially around http://anidb.net/ch2344 [Makoto], who she has known since junior high school and subsequently developed a crush on.</description>
<picture>148144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="460" picture="17368.jpg">Nagami Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2351" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="55">1.27</rating>
<name>Sawanaga Taisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sawanaga Taisuke is a student in year one of class three.
A spirited, peculiar and rather hopeless romantic, Taisuke is a close friend of http://anidb.net/ch2344 [Makoto] from junior high school who frequently endeavors to forward his otherwise lonely ambitious love life; oblivious to the attraction of http://anidb.net/ch2348 [Hikari].
He takes a strong interest in http://anidb.net/ch2345 [Kotonoha], despite her rejection.</description>
<picture>148150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8994" picture="234982.jpg">Matsumoto Yoshiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2352" type="main character in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="52">5.72</rating>
<name>Katsura Kokoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsura Kokoro is the sweet-natured younger sister of http://anidb.net/ch2345 [Kotonoha]. Unlike her older sibling, Kokoro is peppy, talkative and full of curiosity who is just as teasing as she is apprehensive of Kotonoha.
She has a good friend named http://anidb.net/ch62823 [Uzuki] and affectionately looks up to http://anidb.net/ch2344 [Makoto] as her older brother.
Kokoro lives with Kotonoha and their mother Manami and father.</description>
<picture>148151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2007" picture="76719.jpg">Ashiro Megu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41022" type="appears in" update="2014-01-06">
<rating votes="8">8.28</rating>
<name>Saionji Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saionji Youko is the single mother of http://anidb.net/ch2346 [Saionji Sekai]. She`s a gentle, well-balanced person who often counsels her daughter in love matters (despite occasionally behaving like a teenager herself, thus causing embarrassment for Sekai).
Youko runs the family restaurant "Radish", well-known for their waitresses` cute uniforms; the restaurant staff includes Sekai as well as http://anidb.net/ch2347 [Setsuna]`s mother Mai (who`s doesn`t appear in the anime).</description>
<picture>148181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2007" picture="76719.jpg">Ashiro Megu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41023" type="appears in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="12">2.13</rating>
<name>Mori Kumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mori Kumi is a member of http://anidb.net/ch2350 [Otome]`s gang who frequently perform their mobbing attacks against http://anidb.net/ch2345 [Kotonoha].
Amongst these she`s the most harmless one and stands out for her care-free, hyped-up behavior, most notably in terms of relationships where she is cagey about her boyfriend and frequently teases her friends with insinuations, never actually telling them who her partner actually is.</description>
<picture>80918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38771" picture="145881.jpg">Saita Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41024" type="appears in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="12">1.84</rating>
<name>Obuchi Minami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Obuchi Minami is the gossip girl amongst http://anidb.net/ch2350 [Otome]`s gang: Rumors are her favorite hobby. She also participates actively in the mobbing attacks of the gang against class-rep http://anidb.net/ch2345 [Kotonoha].</description>
<picture>80920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2297" picture="21995.jpg">Kuribayashi Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41025" type="appears in" update="2014-01-05">
<rating votes="12">1.57</rating>
<name>Koizumi Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Koizumi Natsumi is a member of http://anidb.net/ch2350 [Otome]`s gang who are constantly mobbing their classmate http://anidb.net/ch2345 [Kotonoha]. More than others she enjoys tantalizing and manipulating her victim who`s easy to intimidate, and she`s never at a loss of snappish comments and other underhandedness. She takes advantage of Kotonoha`s weakness in order to terrorize her.</description>
<picture>80922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7449" picture="234985.jpg">Furuhara Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62853" type="appears in" update="2014-01-06">
<rating votes="1">1.45</rating>
<name>Magical World</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="618" picture="223541.jpg">Okajima Tae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62854" type="main character in" update="2014-01-06">
<rating votes="1">6.59</rating>
<name>Magical Heart</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2007" picture="76719.jpg">Ashiro Megu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62855" type="appears in" update="2014-01-06">
<rating votes="1">3.79</rating>
<name>Tanaka-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26" picture="170737.jpg">Chijiwa Ryuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62856" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-06">
<rating votes="1">1.45</rating>
<name>Doctor S</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4664" picture="234976.jpg">Imoto Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="88984" update="2008-03-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90095" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90096" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<rating votes="1">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Digest</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90097" update="2008-04-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91793" update="2008-07-06">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TVCM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91828" update="2010-04-01">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">8.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Chain Saw</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91829" update="2008-07-08">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Eye Catcher</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
