<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5538" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2008-10-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">RD Sennou Chousashitsu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Real Drive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Real Drive</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">RD 潜脑调查室</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">RD</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">RD 潜脳調査室</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">RD 잠뇌조사실</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="120055">I liked this overall despite having some issues with it. Its a nice show that can really make you think... just be forewarned that it`ll take some patience to really get into. One of my biggest issues with the show was that it had a tendancy to introduce a lot of complex new concepts and terminology, but I felt it largely left you to figure them out for yourself where it could`ve benefitted from more explanation far too often. Also, while most episodes were decent, some were notably weaker to the extent that I considered dropping the show fairly early on after 2 weaker episodes in a row (7 and 8 ), but I`m glad I persevered because it really picked up after that. If you can look past that, most episodes left you thinking and wanting more, the artwork and animation were nice and clean, and the characters were mostly likeable and well fleshed-out. I say `for fans` because it`s certainly not a show for everyone, but if it sounds at all interesting to you then by all means give it a go.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="76659">If you`re shirow masasume fan, I know you won`t miss it. If not, you still won`t miss it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="339649">Deep and very original story. Intense.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="508260">Definitely the surprise title of 2008.  It seems to mirror the design of Ghost in the Shell, providing a more bright and optimistic view of the near future where technology helps make life better.  Must of the show focuses on an episodic formula focused on the core characters.  But around episode 17, it develops a strong plot that answers many of the underlying questions the series has developed.  If you like stories that develop over time, this is a great show for you.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ntv.co.jp/RD/</url>
<creators>
<name id="871" type="Original Work">Shirou Masamune</name>
<name id="7076" type="Series Composition">Fujisaku Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="4393" type="Music">Hirano Yoshihisa</name>
<name id="721" type="Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="721" type="Original Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="1410" type="Direction">Furuhashi Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="6910" type="Music">Taniuchi Hideki</name>
<name id="12329" type="Character Design">Ueyama Tetsurou</name>
</creators>
<description>In 2061... 50 years after humanity developed the Net Society that depended on information networks despite their security issues.
To improve security, a new network called Meta Real Network — or Metal for short — was developed. Personal memories are reduced to information and placed within protected virtual stand-alone organic cyber enclaves called Bubble Shells Online. The result was a virtual explosion of creative freedom as people felt safe enough to explore instincts and desires on Metal that they would not otherwise explore in real life. This friction between the Metal`s alluring lack of restrictions and the rules-bound reality led to incidents that investigators known as Cyber Divers must handle. http://anidb.net/ch11602 [Haru Masamichi] is one such Cyber Diver.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1616">6.13</permanent>
<temporary count="1636">7.33</temporary>
<review count="3">7.05</review>
</ratings>
<picture>83997.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8941</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3363</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4158</identifier>
<identifier>fyvfgi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ntv.co.jp/RD/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/rd/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.productionig.com/contents/works_sp/62_/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Real_Drive</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>RD_潜脳調査室</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1378</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329470</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9691</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2008/rd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2836" parentid="7082" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Australia</name>
<description>Australia, officially the Commonwealth of Australia, is a sovereign country comprising the mainland of the Australian continent, the island of Tasmania and numerous smaller islands. It is the largest country in Oceania and the world`s sixth-largest country by total area. The neighbouring countries are Papua New Guinea, Indonesia and East Timor to the north; the Solomon Islands and Vanuatu to the north-east; and New Zealand to the south-east. Australia`s capital is Canberra, and its largest city is Sydney.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192049.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2875" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>ecology</name>
<description>Nature and ecology are a central theme of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3394" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>environmentalism</name>
<description>Environmental protection is a practice of protecting the natural environment on individual, organizational or governmental levels, for the benefit of both the natural environment and humans. Due to the pressures of population and technology, the biophysical environment is being degraded, sometimes permanently. This has been recognized, and governments have begun placing restraints on activities that cause environmental degradation. Since the 1960s, activity of environmental movements has created awareness of the various environmental issues.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3569" parentid="1278" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-17">
<name>human-android love</name>
<description>There is a romance going on between a human (often male) and an android (usually female).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4244" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>healthcare and medicine</name>
<description>The anime contains themes related to healthcare, medicine, or the human body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4267" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-31">
<name>underwater diving</name>
<description>Underwater diving is the practice of descending below the water`s surface to interact with the environment. It is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6903 [acrobatic diving]. Please note that this tag is only about underwater diving as a sport; diving for e.g. salvaging shipwreck should be tagged with other, more specific tags.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4626" parentid="3394" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-18">
<name>nature strikes back</name>
<description>Humanity continues to pollute and waste the land. Until at some point (usually in the future), nature "has had it" and devises a way to countermand this dire situation. This cleansing of the Earth may well take out humanity, though.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5769" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>panels that require pausing</name>
<description>Panels that require pausing are image or text panels that interrupt regular animation and flash by so quickly that the viewer cannot recognize the image or read the text fast enough while playing at regular speed; they require pausing the video, or at least viewing it at a lower speed. Given the short screen time these panels are given, they are usually not relevant to the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7082" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-07">
<name>Oceania</name>
<description>Oceania is a geographic region comprising Melanesia, Micronesia, Polynesia and Australasia. Situated in the southeast of the Asia Pacific region, Oceania is the smallest continental grouping in land area and the second smallest in population after Antarctica.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214397.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11602" type="main character in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="2">4.90</rating>
<name>Haru Masamichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist of the series. A diver of "The Metal" and long time friend of Eiichiro Kushima. Masamichi was in a diving accident while testing an early Meta-Real technology and was in a coma for 50 years before awakening as an old man.
- wikipedia</description>
<picture>35133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1816" picture="20691.jpg">Mori Katsuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11603" type="main character in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="7">6.73</rating>
<name>Aoi Minamo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An intern hired by Masamichi Haru and Sister of Souta Aoi. Originally hired to replace Holon during a leave for maintenance, she became a permanent employee after she helped guide Masamichi back from a dive gone wrong. Unlike the other humans and some animals in the story, she does not possess a Cyberbrain augmentation, and requires electronic accessories to access The Metal.
- wikipedia</description>
<picture>35134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2798" picture="22836.jpg">Oki Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11604" type="main character in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="3">8.77</rating>
<name>Aoi Souta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Employee of the EISF and brother of Minamo Aoi.
- wikipedia</description>
<picture>35135.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3930" picture="168241.jpg">Aihashi Aiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11605" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="17">8.94</rating>
<name>Horon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An android who helps Masamichi Haru with daily life in his old age and assists him in his search for the answer in the sea.
- wikipedia</description>
<picture>35136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11606" type="main character in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="2">5.24</rating>
<name>Kushima Eiichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Director of the EISF and friend of Masamichi Haru. While as old as Masamichi, his body has the appearance of a twenty-eight year old man. It was revealed later in the series that Kushima chose to replace his original body with a prosthetic one, allowing him to continue his work beyond the limits allowed by the human body.
- wikipedia</description>
<picture>35137.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14379" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-26">
<rating votes="5">4.77</rating>
<name>Itou Yukino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A slightly overweight friend of Aoi Minamo and Sayama Mikomoto.</description>
<picture>41959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19350" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="1">3.28</rating>
<name>Aoi Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19351" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="3">3.22</rating>
<name>Aoi Mizuho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19352" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="3">4.69</rating>
<name>Eliza</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19353" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="3">8.09</rating>
<name>Erika Patricia Takanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19354" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<name>Fujiwara Ayumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19355" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Yuujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19356" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Ichinose Kazune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3380" picture="187130.jpg">Nozawa Nachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19357" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="1">5.40</rating>
<name>Jenny Yen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19358" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="3">1.94</rating>
<name>Miaya Emi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19359" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="3">4.00</rating>
<name>Mikomoto Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19360" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="2">1.34</rating>
<name>Umuran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="491" picture="38232.jpg">Yokoyama Chisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19361" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Operator</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of many androids employed at Denriken who control and monitor the Divers` status, as well as sudden changes within the Metal. Like Holon, they all take the same appearance as Takanami.</description>
<picture>153834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="88813" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウラシマドライブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Underwater Island Drive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ura Shima Drive</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88843" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89054" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">欲望の環礁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Atoll of Desire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokubou no Kanshou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89055" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リダイブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re-Dive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re-Dive</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89096" update="2008-04-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89873" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90026" update="2008-04-11">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90414" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノー・フレンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">No Friend</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90415" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">手と手で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hand in Hand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Te to Te de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90416" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラブ・レター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Letter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love Letter</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90417" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーマラン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sous Marin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sous Marin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90814" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純正律</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Just Intonation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junseiritsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90815" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">至高の話手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Supremacy Negotiations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikou no Hanashi Te</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90816" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">職</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Employment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91349" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光のない朝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Morning Without Light</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari no Nai Asa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91350" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もうひとつの海</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Hitotsu no Umi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91351" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">1.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">波と風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wave and Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nami to Kaze</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91352" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の晩餐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Dinner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Bansan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91631" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">透明な力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clear Power</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toumei na Chikara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91632" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホームスイートホーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Home Sweet Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Home Sweet Home</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91905" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">緑の叛乱[はんらん]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Green Rebellion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midori no Hanran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92154" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">巡る雫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Returning Water Drops</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meguru Shizuku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92155" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その足で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With These Feet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Ashi de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92156" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eternity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92157" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">静かなる死</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Peaceful Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shizuka Naru Shi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92158" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間律</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Human Commandments</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningen Ritsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92159" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球律</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Earth Law</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Ritsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92160" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラストダイブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Dive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last Dive</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92803" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リアルドライブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Real Drive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Real Drive</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119021" update="2013-06-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119022" update="2013-06-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
