<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5549" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shigofumi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">シゴフミ ~Stories of Last Letter~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Stories of Last Letter</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Сигофуми: Письма с того света</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Сигофуми</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Шигофуми</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shigofumi: Stories of Last Letter</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Шіґофумі</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Листи від померлих</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Шіґофумі: Листи з того світу</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">亡者之信</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">死后文</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">シゴフミ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shigofumi: Letters from the Departed</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3291" approval="46" total="58">Jigoku Shoujo</anime>
<anime id="6772" approval="39" total="66">Tegami Bachi</anime>
<anime id="3572" approval="37" total="41">Shinigami no Ballad</anime>
<anime id="575" approval="6" total="13">Kino no Tabi: The Beautiful World</anime>
<anime id="12138" approval="3" total="4">Violet Evergarden</anime>
<anime id="11472" approval="1" total="1">Aru Hi: Inu no Kuni kara Tegami ga Kite</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="12">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="101560">Jigoku shoujo meets kino no tabi - herrlich!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="47306">Didn`t like it at first and only watched the first 4 episodes. 6 episodes later I gave the show another chance and from there on it got really interesting, and the introduction of other characters besides the expressionless Fumika just made it all better since I really like the facial extressions in this anime.&lt;br /&gt;Starts out a bit slow with a few introduction episodes, but once you get to the "main" story it`s a really good anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="75679">Average show with some interesting aspects. I found the side stories more interesting than the main.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="374287">Bittersweet, heartwarming, "shocking". Some really stunning moments. 
Some "forced" drama. 
Atmosphere is darkish, and storytelling rather nice. 
This is one of the series that left me in a state of "Must watch anotherr, what if next episode is as good as this one?" - ended up pulling all nighter.

Id say this is one of those "You either hate it or love it" - series.
Luckily I picked this one up.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="325967">I recommend this if you don`t tear up easily, the trajedy tag is indeed suited for this anime, i`m only on episode 9 and i`ve cried a few times, it`s a good anime and worth watching, i can`t comment on the end but i hope it`s a happy one=)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="132589">Not particularly great but it`s a good watch. You won`t waste your time because it`s pretty interesting but it could have been a lot better. I felt it was too short for the story to be fully conveyed. Still a decent way to spend a couple hours</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.shigofumi.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="8138" type="Character Design">Kawakami Tetsuya</name>
<name id="1857" type="Series Composition">Ookouchi Ichirou</name>
<name id="3613" type="Direction">Satou Tatsuo</name>
<name id="2302" type="Music">Nanase Hikaru</name>
<name id="7482" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nomura Fusako</name>
<name id="8138" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawakami Tetsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by Amamiya Ryo, illustrated by Poko.
http://anidb.net/ch7106 [Fumika] is a girl with a job as a Shigofumi. This requires her to deliver letters from the dead; the last resort of relaying a deceased person`s last message to his/her loved ones: family, friends or significant other. Together with her talking staff, http://anidb.net/ch11290 [Kanaka], she crosses the boundaries between the world of the living and the world of the dead in order to deliver the letters. But at some point, during a delivery, she gets seen by an old classmate who recognizes her. He then starts investigating what happened to her after she vanished from his class and why she is delivering letters from the dead.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2817">7.09</permanent>
<temporary count="2835">7.75</temporary>
<review count="2">8.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>229715.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8760</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4173</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3420</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4715</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3986</identifier>
<identifier>wmoxss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.shigofumi.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shigofumi:_Letters_from_the_Departed</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>シゴフミ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1290</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329461</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9572</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2488" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>multiple personality disorder</name>
<description>Multiple personality disorder is a psychiatric diagnosis that describes a condition in which a single person displays multiple distinct identities or personalities (known as alter egos or alters), each with its own pattern of perceiving and interacting with the environment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3086" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>parricide</name>
<description>Parricide, or the murder of family members, is the act of taking the life of of one or more of one`s own close family members, or even one`s entire family; that may include spouses, parents, grandparents, children, grandchildren, siblings, cousins, uncles, aunts, nephews, and nieces, among others.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3146" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-29">
<name>divorce</name>
<description>The parents depicted in this anime have divorced, usually upsetting the life of their children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3316" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>despair</name>
<description>Involves characters that may be lost in negatively emotional atmospheres created through feelings of hopelessness and suffering.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3703" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-01-26">
<name>fist fight</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3887" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-09-30">
<name>cheating</name>
<description>Cheating is an act of lying, deception, fraud, trickery, imposture, or imposition. Cheating characteristically is employed to create an unfair advantage, usually in one`s own interest, and often at the expense of others. Cheating implies the breaking of rules.
Note: In the game of Mahjong you HAVE to cheat to win.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3915" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>child abuse</name>
<description>Story depicts child abuse, which is a very complex and dangerous set of problems that include child neglect and the physical, emotional, and sexual abuse of children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4669" parentid="6249" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-27">
<name>parenting</name>
<description>This anime is about parenting and its many challenges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4811" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-30">
<name>internet</name>
<description>It`s not a big truck. It`s a series of tubes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5881" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-07">
<name>childhood memory</name>
<description>The childhood memory of one of the protagonists plays an important part as plot device in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5914" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-05">
<name>afterlife</name>
<description>The afterlife is the continued existence of an essential part of an individual`s identity or consciousness after the death of the body. When people continue existing beyond the death of their physical bodies, they may or may not keep interacting with the realm of the living and/or retain their memories. It is possible for them to start a new life without a physical body in a spirit realm, and they may or may not be able to understand that they`re already dead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6054" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-07-25">
<name>car crash</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7106" type="main character in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="27">7.61</rating>
<name>Fumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fumika is the main character in the anime series. She appears to be a young girl, though her real age is never mentioned. She works as a mail carrier from the afterlife realm of Shigo, delivering what are known as "shigofumi" to people in a Japanese city that she has been assigned to. These shigofumi are letters written by those who have recently died, and it is Fumika`s job to deliver the letters to whoever the dead wanted them to go to. Though typically the shigofumi mail carriers are people who have already died, and thus do not age, Fumika is different in that she ages at the same rate as a normal person, signifying that she has not died yet but is merely in a state of astral projection.</description>
<picture>25368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11290" type="main character in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="8">9.06</rating>
<name>Kanaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The artificial intelligence staff that Fumika carries is named Kanaka. The function of the staff is meant to aid the shigofumi mail carrier by keeping track of senders, receivers, the delivery area, and supplementing other usual tasks. The mail carrier can give the staff a numeral code pertaining to a program which can be activated and aid the mail carrier further, such as turning them invisible, or supplementing white wings on their back to enable them to fly, though there are time limits on these programs. The staffs carry their own personalities and have the ability to levitate. In the anime, Fumika`s staff Kanaka has a female voice and a loud, boisterous personality which directly contrasts Fumika`s otherwise placid disposition. Kanaka often gives Fumika her opinion on matters pertaining to who she is delivering letter to, though Fumika just goes along her business as usual either way. Despite technically not being alive, Kanaka still insists that "she" be referred to as a person, or in terms of what a person would do, such as while levitating or regenerating which she calls "standing" and "sleeping" respectively. Kanaka is prone to making mistakes while on the job, such as misplacing letters.</description>
<picture>42529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14791" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="3">8.33</rating>
<name>Nojima Kaname</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname is a male high school student who briefly knew Fumika Mikawa back in junior-high school when they were in the same class. After he initially met Fumika the mail carrier, he recognized her face and was reminded how Fumika had shot her father three years prior, which led him to continue to search for Fumika later on. Kaname had liked Fumika in junior-high, and even went so far as to confess his love to her, but she rejected him, though Fumika the mail carrier later tells him that she was merely surprised and does not dislike him. Even now, it would seem he still has feelings for Fumika.</description>
<picture>42530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14792" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="3">5.79</rating>
<name>Nojima Tatsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname`s father. He is a detective, and he is commonly referred to as Noji-san.</description>
<picture>42531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3093" picture="38195.jpg">Nojima Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14793" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="6">7.53</rating>
<name>Kasai Natsuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuka is an energetic high school girl who knew Fumika from junior-high school when they were in the same class, though they first talked in the school infirmary. She has a tendency to like guys who are intelligent and even goes as far as to read the same books of guys she likes; incidentally, she likes Kaname who is one such type. After Kaname comes to her regarding information pertaining to Fumika, she gets involved with him in his search to discover what really happened to Fumika three years prior to the beginning of the story.</description>
<picture>42532.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14794" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="12">7.67</rating>
<name>Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiaki is Fumika`s coworker and superior, though unlike Fumika, Chiaki has already died. Chiaki died due to a car accident and thus retains the appearance of how she looked before she died, which happens to be very similar to Fumika, though Chiaki does not age. She says she is "over twenty-one-years-old" (and admits in that she died over `fifty years ago`), however looks roughly as old as Fumika is. She is assigned a different city in Japan than Fumika, and the two rarely ever meet on Earth, but do see each other more often when in Shigo. Chiaki has a bright personality and likes to express her emotions outwardly, whether they be related to frustration, or happiness. As observed by Fumika, Chiaki usually is not as diligent about her job as Fumika is, and if a delivery is too much of a pain, she will generally drop it, marking the letter with an invalid addressee.</description>
<picture>42533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14795" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="4">7.82</rating>
<name>Matoma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matoma is the staff that Chiaki carries and like Fumika`s staff, helps her with her job. Matoma has a male voice and speaks in a monotonic tone. He is better at the job than Kanaka is and talks down to Kanaka for doing a poor job. Kanaka in turn needles Matoma by mocking him by twisting his name as in calling him `Tomato Juice`.</description>
<picture>42534.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14796" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="4">1.70</rating>
<name>Mikawa Kirameki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirameki is a famous writer and the father of Fumika. He is obsessed with beauty, and goes so far as to suggest that ugly people should kill themselves. Kirameki lives and works in a twisted glass building called "The forever leading silver road". His name, Kirameki, translates to glitter, or twinkle.</description>
<picture>42535.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14797" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="5">8.50</rating>
<name>Kasai Haruno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuka`s sister who works as a publisher. She has a gentle and carefree personality. She had been working in an editorial department for three years and was still only making copies. Because she was a fan of Mikawa Kirameki, even going so far as to send him fan mail several years earlier, she is assigned to his project.</description>
<picture>42536.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14798" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<name>Machiya Shouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school student with a bright and direct personality. He assembles a self-made rocket on top of an abandoned building believing that it will fly. Soon after the death of Asuna`s father, he receives a shigofumi from him explaining the truth behind his death. Nevertheless he decides that he believes in Asuna and tracks her down to tell her. However, in reality she really was the one who killed her father, and she stabs Shouta and kills him for knowing the truth. Following his death he sends her a shigofumi expressing his love for her.</description>
<picture>42537.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14799" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="4">3.65</rating>
<name>Ayase Asuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female high school student who lives in the same town as Shouta. She has an energetic personality and is an honor student at her school. She often visits Shouta at the abandoned building to talk. However, she has a huge secret. Her father makes money by forcing her to participate in sexual videos. When he mentions doing the same with her little sister Miku for a cash bonus, she finally snaps and kills him, wanting to protect Miku. When Shouta learns the truth, she stabs him to death as well and plans to escape into hiding. However, she recieves a shigofumi from him expressing his love for her, and she goes back to the abandoned building in order to launch the rocket he left behind. While she is in the progress of launching it, Detective Nojima finds her. A gust of wind blows a tarp onto the rocket, and she runs at it with a knife to cut it free. Another detective misunderstands the situation and shoots her to protect Nojima. She suffers a fatal wound, but she dies as she watches Shouta`s rocket successfully take off and fly into the sky.</description>
<picture>42538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14800" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<name>Ayase Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuna`s 6-year-old sister, whom she would do anything to protect. After the death of her father, she lives with her sister Asuna in a children`s home. After Asuna`s death, Miku receives a letter from her in hopes that she will understand.</description>
<picture>42539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1879" picture="20977.jpg">Oomae Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14801" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Kotake Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daiki`s closest friend. He tries to figure out why Daiki committed suicide. He receives a shigofumi from Daiki later explaining his reason.</description>
<picture>42540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14802" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<name>Senkawa Daiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tooru`s closest friend. He has a cheerful personality and gets along well with all of his classmates. One day, he commits suicide by jumping off the roof of his apartment building. He sends a shigofumi to Tooru explaining that he jumped because it was just what he felt like doing at the time.</description>
<picture>42541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14803" type="appears in" update="2010-02-06">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Yahiro Ran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female high school student who is the star of the girl`s tennis club. Because of her boyish looks and personality, she is very popular with the junior girls. Her mother left her when she was a child and she lives with her father. Because of this, she hates her mother and refuses to accept her mother`s shigofumi from Fumika. She is very close to Nanae.</description>
<picture>42542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14804" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Yotsugi Nanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school student at the same school as Ran. She is the captain of the girl`s tennis club. She is very effeminate and has a calming personality. Nanae has a very intimate friendship with Ran.</description>
<picture>42543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14805" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="1">9.22</rating>
<name>Schrodinger</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A black cat who was raised by an old couple. They each send the cat a shigofumi following their deaths, and inside is the key to their room that had been the cat`s home.</description>
<picture>42544.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14806" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="2">2.95</rating>
<name>Kikukawa Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school student who is constantly bullied by his classmates. He discusses his problems on an internet bulletin board. However, it becomes to much to deal with and he commits suicide.</description>
<picture>42545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2044" picture="21387.jpg">Iwanaga Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14807" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Morishita Shunsuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouichi`s classmate. He recognizes Kouichi`s messages about bullying on an internet bulletin board but doesn`t help him. After Kouichi`s death, the bullies switch to him. They corner him and he stabs one of them out of defense.</description>
<picture>42546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14808" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="2">4.89</rating>
<name>Shirakawa Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She travels to Suitenguu Island to visit her grandfather`s grave. She stays at the same inn as the others, and they learn that she is the adopted granddaughter of Chiaki`s former sweetheart, who never married after Chiaki`s death. Following the trip she decides that she now has the courage to confess to her unrequited love.</description>
<picture>42547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2227" picture="73301.jpg">Inamura Yuuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14809" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="2">9.18</rating>
<name>Hibiya Takehiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a 32-year-old otaku and video game designer. He always wanted to draw and bring happiness to people, and he joins a video game company with his friend to work as a graphic designer in order to do so. However, for some reason he quits his job, much to his friend`s dislike.
Takehiko is asked to watch a young relative of his named Fumika (a different Fumika from the main characters) for the day, and they get along very well. However, he gives his life to push her out of the way of an oncoming cat, but dies content after seeing the happiness on Fumika`s face while she plays one of the games he helped to create.</description>
<picture>42548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14810" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<name>Oda-keiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A detective who works with Tatsumi.</description>
<picture>42549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1630" picture="1887.gif">Tasaka Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14811" type="appears in" update="2015-02-08">
<rating votes="3">1.03</rating>
<name>Ayase Takezou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuna and Miku`s father.</description>
<picture>42550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14812" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<name>Tateishi Naoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ran`s mother. She left Ran behind with her father when she was a child and disappeared without a trace. Naoko sends a shigofumi to Ran after her death.</description>
<picture>42551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14813" type="appears in" update="2011-01-18">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Aoto Misuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3786" picture="223623.jpg">Kameoka Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14814" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Nojima Hisako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname`s mother.</description>
<seiyuu id="12450" picture="42010.jpg">Kouda Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14815" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="3">8.25</rating>
<name>Kiyosumi Saizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiaki`s former lover and Touko`s grandfather.</description>
<picture>42552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14816" type="appears in" update="2019-01-29">
<rating votes="4">8.59</rating>
<name>Fumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A little girl who teaches Takehiko that his drawings already make people happy. She is not the same person as either of the main Fumikas.</description>
<picture>229719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14817" type="appears in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Ueno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takehiko`s friend.</description>
<picture>42554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5626" picture="29921.jpg">Fujimoto Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14818" type="appears in" update="2019-01-29">
<rating votes="2">6.87</rating>
<name>Risala</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A woman very knowledgeable about the Gospel Department`s laws. Chiaki goes to her seeking help.</description>
<picture>229721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="653" picture="18181.jpg">Tsuda Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14819" type="appears in" update="2019-01-29">
<rating votes="5">1.31</rating>
<name>Kirei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikawa Fumika`s mother. She divorced Kirameki after giving birth to Fumika and now lives in Italy. Kirei has no interest in raising a daughter.</description>
<picture>229720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14823" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-28">
<rating votes="5">7.82</rating>
<name>Mikawa Fumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname and Natsuka`s friend who has been in the hospital for 3 years in a coma after shooting her father, Mikawa Kirameki. She has dissociative identity disorder stemming from her father`s abuse, and the postal worker Fumika is her alternate identity.
Mikawa Fumika is the more shy and reserved personality. She calls the other Fumika Mika-chan.</description>
<picture>229718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66699" type="appears in" update="2014-04-15">
<name>Senkawa no Chichioya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3225" picture="24205.jpg">Watabe Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93223" type="appears in" update="2019-01-29">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Shinozaki Suzune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="85835" update="2007-12-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コクハク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuhaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85836" update="2008-07-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロケット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rocket</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rocket</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86542" update="2013-09-10">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86556" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86916" update="2008-01-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トモダチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86970" update="2013-04-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サケビ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shout</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakebi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86971" update="2013-04-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タダイマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tadaima</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86972" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナミダ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87912" update="2013-04-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キラメキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kirameki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirameki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88165" update="2008-02-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハジマリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88427" update="2008-02-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイカイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88560" update="2008-03-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="14">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デアイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88618" update="2008-11-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シゴフミ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shigofumi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shigofumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88619" update="2008-11-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メザメ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89011" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 一通目 「でーと」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 1 - Dating</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama Ittsuume: Date</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90434" update="2011-05-31">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 二通目 「ひとみ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 2 - Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama Nitsuume: Hitomi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92569" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 三通目 「ひげ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 3 - Mustache</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama Santsuume: Hige</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92570" update="2011-05-31">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 四通目 「どいがき」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 4 - Scoreboard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama Yontsuume: Doigaki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92571" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 五通目 「よびだし」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 5 - Summon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama Gotsuume: Yobidashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92728" update="2013-04-12">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 六通目 「つえ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 6 - Staff</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama Rokutsuume: Tsue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92729" update="2011-05-31">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソレカラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After Then</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore kara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93157" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 七通目 「こもりうた」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 7 - Lullaby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama Shichitsuume: Komoriuta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95155" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117553" update="2010-04-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125413" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130641" update="2013-09-10">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153903" update="2013-09-10">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153904" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1m</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153905" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1l</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153906" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1k</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153907" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153908" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153909" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153910" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153911" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153912" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153913" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153914" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153915" update="2013-09-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153944" update="2013-09-10">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV-CM 3 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153945" update="2013-09-10">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV-CM 2 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153946" update="2013-09-10">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV-CM 1 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153947" update="2013-09-10">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153948" update="2013-09-10">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153949" update="2013-09-10">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (15s)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
