<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="557" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>296</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-07-07</startdate>
<enddate>2006-03-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tottoko Hamtarou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tottoko Hamutaro</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">とっとこハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hamtaro</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Hamtaro</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Hamtaro</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Hamtaro - wielkie przygody małych chomików</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">هامتارو</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Hamtaro - Pequenos Hamsters, Grandes Aventuras</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="official">Hamtaro</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Χαμτάρο: Μικρά Χάμστερ, Μεγάλες Περιπέτειες</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">המטארו</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">แฮมทาโร่ แก๊งจิ๋วผจญภัย</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Hamtaro</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9462" type="Sequel">Tottoko Hamtarou Hai!</anime>
<anime id="13387" type="Alternative Setting">Tottoko Hamtarou: Anime Dechu!</anime>
<anime id="1649" type="Side Story">Hamtarou no Otanjoubi: Mama o Tasunete Sanzen Techi Techi</anime>
<anime id="2395" type="Side Story">Gekijouban Tottoko Hamtarou: Ham-Ham Land Daibouken</anime>
<anime id="8297" type="Other">Tottoko Hamtarou Dechu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.hamutaro.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="1082" type="Unknown Relation">Shogakukan</name>
<name id="917" type="Animation Work">TMS Entertainment</name>
<name id="782" type="Animation Work">Tokyo Movie</name>
<name id="3743" type="Character Design">Sudou Masatomo</name>
<name id="5795" type="Character Design">Yamanaka Junko</name>
<name id="3474" type="Series Composition">Onodera Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="5771" type="Original Work">Kawai Ritsuko</name>
<name id="1966" type="Direction">Nabeshima Osamu</name>
<name id="5765" type="Music">Iwasaki Motoyoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>The cute and cuddly pet of fifth-grader Laura, Hamtaro is a golden hamster with an insatiable curiosity.
Together with the Ham-Ham Friends, a bunch of hamsters as clever and unique as Hamtaro himself, Hamtaro lives each day as a whole new adventure... complete with fun, excitement, and friendship.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="442">2.97</permanent>
<temporary count="449">5.44</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>126582.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>508</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1056</identifier>
<identifier>rzeuqt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.hamutaro.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hamtaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>とっとこハム太郎_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>185</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234369</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1283" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-24">
<name>tsukkomi</name>
<description>A tsukkomi is a comedy duo stock character in a traditional Japanese slapstick stand-up comedy style known as manzai. Tsukkomi characters are the smart, reasonable, and down-to-earth half of the unit; their simple-minded counterparts are the http://anidb.net/t1399 [boke] characters. As a result of their boke counterparts` simple mistakes and gross exaggerations, tsukkomi berate and abuse them both verbally and physically; a very common example of tsukkomi physical abuse is a paper fan slap, which is generally accompanied by a sound effect. Their approximate equivalent in Western culture is the comedy role of straight man.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6017" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>perpetual ongoing</name>
<description>No end in sight!
No matter what the genre may be or what the storyline consists of, this series just keeps on going... and on... and on.
The obvious downside to this is the lack of story-related focus, usually some vague goal is simply never reached. This lack of conclusion can tend to annoy, making the whole series pretty much pointless.
Examples: One Piece, Naruto, Bleach, Detective Conan, Dragon Ball (Z), or Pocket Monsters (Pokemon).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="27023" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-16">
<name>Koushi-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27025" type="appears in" update="2011-01-16">
<name>Don-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30723" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Kaburu-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4957" picture="91922.jpg">Uchikawa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30724" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Chibimaru-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8395" picture="32864.jpg">Matoi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30725" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Neteru-kun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="372" picture="141584.jpg">Sugimoto Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30726" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Noppo-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30727" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Megane-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30728" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Taishou-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30729" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Toraham-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30730" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Toraham-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68981.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30731" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Tongari-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30732" type="main character in" update="2011-04-03">
<rating votes="22">8.82</rating>
<name>Hamtarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Owned by Haruna, Hamtarou is a courageous Ham-Ham who`s always ready to help out his friends and his owner Haruna. However, he cannot stand being ignored by Haruna. He is clueless about many things being that he is of an innocent nature, especially love (much to Bijou`s dismay). Hamtarou makes the most of his life as a small hamster and lives each day in happiness hoping to make more friends and have fun. In the original anime, Hamtarou ends his sentences with `na no da`, a phrase often used by playful characters.</description>
<picture>68976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2766" picture="181834.jpg">Mamiya Kurumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30733" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Panda-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8393" picture="224321.jpg">Saitou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30734" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-25">
<name>Muffler-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30735" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Ribon-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30736" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Maido-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="372" picture="141584.jpg">Sugimoto Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30742" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-16">
<name>Iwata Takezou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30743" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Sensei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30744" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-16">
<name>Kana Mama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30745" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-16">
<name>Iwata Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4957" picture="91922.jpg">Uchikawa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30746" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Suzuki-kun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30747" type="main character in" update="2011-05-16">
<name>Haruna Hiroko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4150.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="394" picture="17239.jpg">Ikezawa Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32355" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-16">
<name>Kimura Taichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32356" type="appears in" update="2011-05-16">
<name>Haruna Hiromi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32357" type="appears in" update="2011-05-16">
<name>Haruna Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5243" picture="29266.jpg">Isobe Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32359" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-16">
<name>Maria-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32360" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-16">
<name>Ohamu Baa-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32363" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-16">
<name>Chourou Ham</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1416" picture="18579.jpg">Ishimori Takkou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34827" type="appears in" update="2011-07-19">
<name>Goham</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75799.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34828" type="appears in" update="2011-07-19">
<name>Kamehamu-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4425.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34829" type="appears in" update="2011-07-19">
<name>Otome-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9599" picture="222797.jpg">Aoyama Touko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34830" type="appears in" update="2011-07-19">
<name>Kururin-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4427.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="603" picture="223012.jpg">Jou Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34831" type="appears in" update="2011-07-19">
<name>Oasiss-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4428.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="20327" picture="224287.jpg">Ishikawa Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36841" type="appears in" update="2011-09-20">
<name>Jajahamu-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3794" picture="38865.jpg">Kumai Motoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="15651" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ登場! ハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hamtaro!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Neue Freunde, neues Glück</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La nouvelle maison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Toujou! Hamtarou</title>
<summary>An 11-year-old girl named Laura, along with her parents, her dog Brandy and hamster Hamtaro, moves into their new house. After their arrival in the new house, Hamtaro gets out of his cage and goes outside, where he meets a hamster named Oxnard.[4] Both Hamtaro and Oxnard fall underground, only to meet a hamster named Boss and his house. They go outside and sing a song for a female hamster named Bijou. But, after the dancing performance, Hamtaro notices something weird: Bijou winks at him and he notices, signaling her crush on him. Meanwhile, Laura and her father are walking around the city, where Laura meets Kana and buys a journal. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20804" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ作るよ! 地下ハウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ham-Ham Clubhouse</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Ham-Ham-Clubhaus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le club de Ham-Hams</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Tsukuru yo! Chika House</title>
<summary>Boss introduces Hamtaro and Oxnard to his friends, Pashmina, Penelope, Howdy and Dexter. When it`s raining, a cat appears and attacks Penelope, but Hamtaro defeats the cat. Boss shows everybody his house, only to find a sleeping hamster named Snoozer. The hamsters decide to convert Boss` house to the Ham-Ham Clubhouse. Meanwhile, Laura goes to a new school. Her new teacher is Mr. Yoshi and her new classmates are Kana, Travis, Kylie and June, owners of Penelope and Pashmina. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20805" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ集まれ! ハムちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calling All Ham-Hams!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ham-Hams halten zusammen!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De nouveaux venus au club</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Atsumare! Ham-chanz</title>
<summary>Pashmina and Penelope introduce their friends Maxwell, Panda, Sandy and Cappy to the others. While playing at the Ham-Ham Clubhouse, Howdy and Dexter start arguing and thanks to them, the Ham-Hams make a mess of the entire Clubhouse, only to be booted out of there by Boss. Boss feels he`s alone and wants the others to return. Hamtaro and the others finally return. Meanwhile, Laura gets an A and she tries to tell her parents, but they`re too busy and Laura tells them about that in the evening after their return. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20806" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ飛び出せ! リボンちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come Out, Bijou!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bijou traut sich</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bijou, descends !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Tobidase! Ribbon-chan</title>
<summary>Boss wants to see Bijou at the Ham-Ham Clubhouse. Bijou is reluctant to go, because she thinks that if her owner, Maria, returns before her, she`ll be sad if she sees her hamster has disappeared. Bijou learns she will return before her owner does, and finally arrives in the Clubhouse. Meanwhile, Laura accidentally gets splashed while carrying water. Travis gives her his towel and Laura dries off, then returns the towel. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20807" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこいっぱい! コンペイトウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Diamonds of Sugar</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Zucker-Diamanten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pépites de sucre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Ippai! Konpeitou</title>
<summary>Laura introduces Hamtaro to konpeito-shaped candies called Diamonds of Sugar. Boss says that the candies are the same things as stars in the sky. The Ham-Hams want to catch the supposed Diamonds of Sugar from the sky, but they`re unaware of the stars` actual distance from Earth until they spot a shooting star. Meanwhile, Laura and Kana`s families are having a garden party and watch the stars too. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20808" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ行くのだ! はじめての海</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Time at the Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zum ersten Mal am großen Meer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Excursion à la mer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Iku no Da! hajimete no Umi</title>
<summary>Laura`s family goes to the beach, but they can`t take Hamtaro, because hamsters are afraid of water. Hamtaro, along with the other Ham-Hams, go to the beach anyway, by hiding inside the family car. Later on, a storm breaks while Laura and Kana are away from the main beach. The Ham-Hams use Laura`s hat to get her father`s attention and successfully lead him to the girls. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20809" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ冒険! 夏祭り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Summer Festival Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abenteuer Sommerfest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête de l`été</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Bouken! Natsu Matsuri</title>
<summary>It`s a summer festival! The Ham-Hams learn from Maxwell that on the night of the festival, flowers (fireworks) will appear in the sky. Pashmina separates from the Ham-Hams to find the flowers and climbs to the roof of the Temple of the Sun, getting lost in the process. The Ham-Hams save her and watch the fireworks. Meanwhile, while Laura and Kana are walking around the festival, Kana gets separated from Laura. Laura sees Travis, and goes to find Kana. Laura finally finds Kana, and they also watch the fireworks. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20810" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ遊ぶよ! ひまわり畑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sunflower Field</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hamtaro im Sonnenblumenfeld</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les tournesols géants</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Asobu yo! Himawari Hatake</title>
<summary>Laura`s family goes to visit their grandmother, who lives near a sunflower field. Boss follows them. Hamtaro runs away from Laura while she paints with her grandmother and wanders around the field with Boss. Laura`s family discovers Hamtaro`s disappearance and looks for him everywhere. Hamtaro finally returns to Laura. Eventually Hamtaro and Boss share the story with the other Ham-Hams. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20811" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ学校! 大騒ぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Much Ado About School!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Ham-Ham-Schule</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Ham-Hams à l`école</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Gakkou! Oosawagi</title>
<summary>The summer vacation is over and school restarts. Laura and Kana return to school. Hamtaro, Oxnard and Boss (trapped inside Laura`s backpack) join them. Hamtaro decides to create a hamster school. Maxwell is appointed teacher, but the Ham-Hams quickly grow bored. Afterwards, he tries coaching them in soccer, with a fight resulting. They finally try a music class and like it. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20812" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこさすらう! トンガリくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jingle, the Wanderer</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Quadratisch, gelb und äußerst unlecker!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La disquette perdue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sasurau! Tongari-kun</title>
<summary>Laura takes a floppy disk to her father`s office. Hamtaro, Oxnard and Penelope are trapped inside her purse and Oxnard drops his sunflower seed. Hamtaro, Oxnard, Penelope and the disk fall from Laura`s purse, only to find the sunflower seed and meet a hamster named Jingle with a guitar. After arriving at her father`s office, Laura discovers the disk has disappeared and looks for it with her father. Hamtaro, Oxnard, Penelope and Jingle find the disk and put it in Laura`s pocket, where her father finds it. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20813" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこすごいぞ! 長老ハム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wise, Elder-Ham</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Rat der Weisen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La sagesse des anciens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sugoizo! Chourou Ham</title>
<summary>Laura`s grandmother visits and is sad she has lost her friend. Laura decides to find her grandmother`s friend. The Ham-Hams enlist the help of Elder-Ham in the search. With the help of the Ham-Hams, Laura`s grandmother`s friend is finally found and Laura`s grandmother is reunited with her friend. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20814" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ大変! リボンちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bijou`s in Danger!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rettet Bijou!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bijou en danger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Taihen! Ribbon-chan</title>
<summary>Bijou gets lost in the city, only to meet an alley cat and her kittens. The Ham-Hams try to save her, without success. Meanwhile, Laura buys a book named "The Adventures of Hamkins". Eventually, Laura and Kana find the cats and fawn over the kittens, allowing the Ham-Hams to escape. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20815" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ踊るよ! トラハムちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Dance, Sandy!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tikalis großer Auftritt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chanson de Tigrette</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Odoru yo! Toraham-chan</title>
<summary>As Elder-Ham`s Sunflower Seed Harvest Festival approaches, Sandy confesses to Hamtaro that she has a crush on Maxwell because he reminds her so much of her twin brother. Sandy asks Hamtaro to find out if Maxwell feels the same about her; Hamtaro is unable to do so. Elder-Ham, however, remarks how much Sandy looks like a boy hamster that he knew. The Ham-Hams vow to find Sandy`s brother, leading directly into the next episode. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20816" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこさがすぞ! トラハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Search for Sandy`s Brother</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Überraschungsparty für Tikali</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la recherche de Tigris</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sagasuzo! Toraham-kun</title>
<summary>Picking up where the last episode left off, Hamtaro and Oxnard locate Sandy`s twin brother, Stan, owned by another instructor at Hillary`s gym, and bring him back to the Clubhouse. To celebrate, the Ham-Ham gang decides to throw a surprise reunion party for Sandy. Sandy however, rebukes Stan for his flirtatious behavior. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20817" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ大切! リボンでちゅ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bijou`s Favorite Ribbon</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die blaue Schleife</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le gros chagrin de Bijou...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Taisetsu! Ribbon de Chu?</title>
<summary>Cappy takes Bijou`s ribbon for a game of "Blind Man`s Bluff". Bijou blames Hamtaro for that. Snoozer comforts Bijou and convinces her to make up with Hamtaro. The Ham-Hams decide to find acorns and cheer her up during this time. Hamtaro sprains his foot and Bijou uses her ribbon to wrap it. Meanwhile, it`s a school trip. Laura puts ribbons in her hair and Travis doesn`t seem to notice until he acknowledges her without the ribbon. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20818" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこロコちゃん! 元気になあれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Well Laura</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gute Besserung!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Guéris vite, Laura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Rocko-chan! Genki ni Naare</title>
<summary>After Hamtaro wakes Laura up in the night, she`s late for school. Boss develops a stomachache and the Ham-Hams raid Laura`s refrigerator for yogurt. While at PE class, Laura passes out and returns home early with a cold. Hamtaro blames himself for making Laura sick and with the help of the Ham-Hams, they heal her. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20819" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ名探偵! ハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hamtaro, the Super Sleuth!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Superspürnase Hamtaro</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hamtaro, le super détective</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Meitantei! Hamtarou</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams` things are relocating themselves under Boss`s bed. After Snoozer`s pillow is stolen, Hamtaro eventually finds that the thief is Penelope, trying to put everything away in an attempt at responsibility. Meanwhile, Laura`s things and those of her classmates have disappeared too, and the thief is a bird! 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20820" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ走るぞ! ガラスのくつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Slipper Chase</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aschenputtel ohne Schuh</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La pantoufle de verre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Hashiruzo! Glass no Kutsu</title>
<summary>Laura hurries to the spring concert play, Cinderella, but she forgets her second slipper and the Ham-Hams take it upon themselves to bring it to Laura before the play starts. Along the way, they encounter Jingle and some hostile chickens. After Jingle accidentally frightens the chickens away, the Ham-Hams deliver the slipper on time and enjoy the play. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20821" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ活躍[かつやく]! パンダくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Panda`s Ham-Ham Fun Park!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Ham-Ham-Fun-Park</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Ham-Hams Parc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Katsuyaku! Panda-kun</title>
<summary>Despite Boss, Howdy and Stan`s anger, the Ham-Hams decide to build a fun park under Panda`s leadership. Meanwhile, Laura`s family goes to the amusement park, but the car machinery breaks down. Kana`s family stops to help and Laura and Kana spend the day at the amusement park. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20822" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ謎だよ! ねてるくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Snoozer Mystery!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ratzis Geheimnis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère de Ronpschitt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Nazo Da yo! Neteru-kun</title>
<summary>Snoozer suddenly gets lost and finds himself with a hamster named Omar, who looks like Snoozer and sneaks into Kana`s house to scare Oxnard. When the Ham-Hams find Snoozer and Omar, he goes back to his family whom he left while exploring the world.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20823" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ勇気だ! かぶるくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Courage, Cappy!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Keppi, der Feldhamster</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Courage, Chapo !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Yuuki Da! Kaburu-kun</title>
<summary>Cappy runs away from home and decides to live with Boss forever, worrying the other Ham-Hams. When he discovers his owners are worried, he returns home. Meanwhile, Laura accidentally breaks Kana`s sketch and Kana returns home early. When Laura visits Kana, she learns Kana returned home early because of the cold and created lots of sketches while at home. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20824" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ贈るぞ! プレゼント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pashmina`s Present</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Geschenketag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cadeau de Pashmina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Okuruzo! Present</title>
<summary>Laura decides to buy a gift for Travis` birthday the next day. Seeing Laura trying to decide what to get, Hamtaro ignorantly proclaims to the Ham-Hams "It seems that tomorrow is the day to give a present to someone you care about". Dexter and Howdy each decide to give Pashmina a gift and both go to Hamtaro for help. Hamtaro suggest a hand-made gift after seeing Laura knitting a towel for Travis. They eventually work together and knit Pashmina a cap and matching pair of gloves. The glory they get from Pashmina for the presents is quickly taken away when Penelope gives Pashmina some sunflower seeds. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20825" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ特ダネ! のっぽくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maxwell`s Big Scoop!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schlaxos großer Knüller</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Librius rédacteur en chef</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Tokudane! Noppo-kun</title>
<summary>Maxwell decides to create a newspaper called The Ham-Ham Times after Hamtaro learns that Laura and Kana are making a newspaper for the school. They eventually reach a frozen over lake and start out towards an island on the lake. Maxwell faints after saving the Ham-Hams from a drainage hole, but, upon waking, he sees his rescue as the featured story in the Ham-Ham times. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20826" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ走れ! ハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hamtaro, Please Come Home!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Komm zurück, kleiner Hamtaro!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Reviens Hamtaro !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Hashire! Hamtaou</title>
<summary>While on a walk with Laura, Hamtaro falls into a box on a transport truck in an attempt to save one of Laura`s ribbons and is taken away. Laura becomes very depressed. The Ham-Hams are also sad and enlist Elder-Ham`s help in the search. After receiving help from a man and his dog, Hamtaro meets up with Jingle, a new hamster named Sabu, his bird Francoise, and Jingle`s pig, Herbert. With their help, Hamtaro returns home and makes the Ham-Hams happy and, most of all, Laura. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20827" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこメリー! クリスマス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Merry Christmas!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Weihnachtsgeschenk für Boss</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Joyeux Noël !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Merry! Christmas</title>
<summary>It`s Christmas time! Boss and Snoozer want to get a gift from Santa. The Ham-Hams decide to help and everyone gets gifts from the hamster-Santa: Elder-Ham. Meanwhile, Laura wants a dollhouse for her gift and gets it.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20828" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ勇者! ハム太郎伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend of the Courageos Hamtaro!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Mutige aus dem fernen Land</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La légende d`Hamtaro l`intrépide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Yuusha! Hamtarou Densetsu</title>
<summary>Hamtaro and Laura dream about being a princess and a knight in a fairy tale. The prophet hamster (Elder-Ham) foretells the arrival of an evil magician and a brave knight. The brave knight (Hamtaro) arrives, but is immediately arrested on suspiscions of him being the magician. Oxnard and Bijou help Hamtaro escape, but he is subsequently turned to stone by the evil magician (Boss). Hamtaro is revived after a time and rides a "steed" (Brandy) through the sky and successfully defeats the magician. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20829" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ元気に! 雪合戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Snowball Fight!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Winterkönige</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille de boules de neige</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Genki ni! Yukigassen</title>
<summary>A snowstorm has just dumped snow onto the town. The Ham-Hams are sleeping, because it`s cold outside. Hamtaro brings his friends out with him. Boss and Stan get into a quarrel which soon pulls everyone into a snowball fight. They are stopped when Penelope is caught in a snowball. Meanwhile, while skating with Kana, Laura has trouble with skating and Travis appears to help. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20830" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこすごすぎ! おハムばあさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Amazing Auntie Viv</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Mega-Marathonlauf</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tata Vivi est un phénomène</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sugo Sugi! Oham-baa-san</title>
<summary>Elder-Ham is reunited with Auntie Viv. After discovering which footrace Laura`s class is about to partake in, Hamtaro decides to run the same race. Auntie Viv and Boss bicker about who will win the race and Boss eventually takes the lead. Meanwhile, during the race, Laura sprains her ankle. Kana is unable to help, but Travis steps in. Boss sees this and goes back to check on Auntie Viv. Auntie Viv leaves after the race and Boss is sorry to see her go. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20831" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ追うのだ! パパのメガネ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Search for Dad`s Glasses!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Brillenabenteuer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la recherche des lunettes de papa !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Oou no Da! Papa no Megane</title>
<summary>Laura`s father loses his glasses at the bus stop and the Ham-Hams must find the glasses before Monday, or Laura`s father cannot go to his job and Hamtaro won`t be able to leave the house. The Ham-Hams find a pair of glasses and attempt to bring them to Laura`s father, but after the glasses are destroyed beyond repair, they turn out to be the wrong pair. Dexter takes the destroyed glasses and makes hamster-sized glasses for the Ham-Hams. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20832" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこどんちゃん! 大レース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brandy`s Big Race</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Brandos großes Rennen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La grande course de Brandy !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Don-chan! Dai Race</title>
<summary>Laura`s family take Brandy and (without knowing it) the Ham-Hams to the dog race. The Ham-Hams and Brandy accidentally get into the race after Brandy worries about embarrassing Laura and, after saving a rabbit, win after the rabbit gets Brandy to chase it to the finish line. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20833" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこママだよ! タイショーくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boss Is a Mom!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aus Feind wird Freund</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hamiral pouponne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Mama Da yo! Taishou-kun</title>
<summary>Boss meets a lost kitten and decides to be the cat`s mother. It is later revealed that cat belongs to one of Laura`s classmates, Mia. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20834" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこびっくり! バレンタイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Valentine`s Day!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Valentinstag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Saint Valentin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Bikkuri! Valentine</title>
<summary>The Ham-Ham girls and Auntie Viv decide to give Valentine gifts to their boyfriends. Meanwhile, Laura tries to give her Valentine gift to Travis. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20835" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ渡ろう! 虹の橋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Cross the Rainbow!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Suche nach dem Regenbogen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Traversons l`arc-en-ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Wataro! Niji no Hashi</title>
<summary>Bijou wants to see a rainbow and the Ham-Hams decide to find a rainbow for her. Meanwhile, Laura is upset because Kana was in the hospital during the time of rainbow`s disappearance. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20836" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこかわいい! ちび丸ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watching Over Cute Penelope</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wo ist Didu?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pénélope a disparu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Kawaii! Chibimaru-chan</title>
<summary>When Pashmina must leave for a day, Howdy and Dexter volunteer to take care of Penelope, who is upset with losing Pashmina. While Howdy and Dexter are arguing, Penelope gets lost and the other Ham-Hams must find her before Pashmina, Howdy and Dexter discover she`s gone. Meanwhile, while walking around the city, Laura and Kana meet a boy named Harold who lost his mother. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20837" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ楽しい! ひなまつり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Midnight Celebration</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Überraschung für Mimi!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un spectacle de rêve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Tanoshii! Hina Matsuri</title>
<summary>Panda`s owner Mimi is upset, because her mother is going to have a baby and no birthday party. The Ham-Hams decide to have a midnight party to cheer Mimi up. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20838" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこさよなら! リボンちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell Bijou!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Adieu, Bijou!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu Bijou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sayonara! Ribbon-chan</title>
<summary>Maria must leave with her parents and Bijou to go back to France. Boss is sad. After Bijou`s farewell day, she returns the next day because Maria`s family decided not to go to France after all. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20839" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ元気だ! じゃじゃハムちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oxnard`s Big Crush</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nicht so schüchtern!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hamidou est amoureux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Genki Da! Jaja Ham-chan</title>
<summary>Laura`s and Kana`s families visit Kana`s farmer cousin, Dylan. Oxnard needs help from Hamtaro to confess his love for his old friend, Pepper. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20841" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとことどけ! 大事な手紙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Precious Letter!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Postbotenhamster</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La précieuse lettre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Todoke! Daiji na Tegami</title>
<summary>Laura`s family decides to visit their old city. Laura is so excited to see her old friend, Melanie. After sending a letter to Melanie, there is no reply. Boss and Jingle decide to deliver the letter before Laura`s family leaves. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20842" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ空飛ぶ! ハムちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flying Ham-Hams!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Legende vom fliegenden Hamster</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Ham-Hams volent !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Soratobu! Ham-chanz</title>
<summary>Panda finds a picture of a flying hamster in his attic, inspiring Hamtaro to learn how to fly. Meanwhile, Laura is looking for a subject to make a painting from flowers. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20843" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ咲かそう! 友情の花</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blossom of Friendship!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Kirschblütenpicknick</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les cerisiers en fleurs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sakasou! Yuujou no Hana</title>
<summary>Laura and Kana`s families decide to have a picnic near the cherry blossom tree. The Ham-Hams decide to have a picnic as well, but Bijou can`t go because Maria is sick. The Ham-Hams bring some blossoms to Bijou.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20844" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこドキドキ! 博物館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scary Museum!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ausflugsziel Museum</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le musée hanté</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Dokidoki! Hakubutsukan</title>
<summary>Laura`s class is taking a trip to the museum to see a giant sunflower seed. The Ham-Hams think there are aliens and go too. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20845" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこようこそ! じゃじゃハムちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome Pepper!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Überraschung für Chili</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bienvenue, Paprika !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Youkoso! Jaja Ham-cha</title>
<summary>Dylan and Pepper visit Kana. After Laura and Kana leave to show Dylan the entire city, the Ham-Hams bring Pepper to see the Ham-Ham Clubhouse and the funpark.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20846" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこまごころ! 大作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Chicken Chase</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hilfe! Hühner!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La poursuite infernale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Magokoro! Dai Sakusen</title>
<summary>Oxnard accidentally lets the chickens out of the cage. After having trouble with the chickens, a female farmer named Charlotte Rooster saves the day. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20847" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ大好き! おじいちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Love My Grandpa!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alle Hamster fliegen hoch!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un amour de grand-père</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Daisuki! Ojii-chan</title>
<summary>Laura`s grandparents visit. Laura`s grandfather is so funny. After Laura`s grandfather`s invention puts Hamtaro in trouble, Laura runs away from home. The Ham-Hams and Laura`s grandfather go looking for her. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20848" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこおどろき! 水族館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ham-Ham Gang at the Aquarium!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Seedrachenpalast</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Ham-Hams à l`aquarium</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Odoroki! Suizokukan</title>
<summary>Laura, Kana and their fathers go to the aquarium and the Ham-Hams join them.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20849" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこファイトだ! 運動会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sports Festival!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Trödel-Sammel-Rennen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ensemble, c`est mieux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Fight Da! Undoukai</title>
<summary>Laura`s class is having a sports festival and must race with their parents. The Ham-Hams decide to do the sports festival too. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20850" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこお見合い! らぶらぶ大事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Romancing the Roosters</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Heiratskandidaten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les petits messages du cœur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Omiai! Lovelove Daijiken</title>
<summary>Mr. Yoshi has a crush on Charlotte and decides to get married to her. The Ham-Hams decide to bring Mr. Yoshi to Charlotte. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20851" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ脱出! 地下ハウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ham-Ham Clubhouse in Danger!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Überschwemmung im Clubhaus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le club en danger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Dasshutsu! Chika House</title>
<summary>After a mole creates a hole in the Ham-Ham Clubhouse on a very rainy day, the clubhouse is flooded with the Ham-Hams inside. The Ham-Hams must get back to the surface, and discover that Penelope and Brandy are their only hope to escape the flood. Meanwhile, Laura must do a project for school. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20852" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこさがせ! 幸せのペンダント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Search of the Pendant</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mamis Medaillon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le médaillon perdu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sagase! Shiawase no Pendant</title>
<summary>Laura`s parents start to argue. Laura and her father buy a pendant to cheer her mother up. Two boys run into Laura and her father and they end up dropping the pendant. The Ham-Hams and Jingle must go to the mall and find the pendant in the night. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20853" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこゆれるよ! 遊覧船</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Even the Ham-Ham`s Get Seasick!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auch ein Ham-Ham wird mal seekrank</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La croisière des Ham-Hams</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Yureru yo! Yuuransen</title>
<summary>Laura`s class, followed by the Ham-Hams and Auntie Viv, go on a cruise.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20854" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこなかよし! トラハム兄妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stan and Sandy Make Up</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gemüseknabberkuchen und Obstsalat</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La réconciliation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Nakayoshi! Toraham Kyoudai</title>
<summary>Sandy and Stan get into a big argument and storm off. The Ham-Hams learn it is their birthday and decide to throw them both a surprise birthday party. Meanwhile, Laura learns decorative food preparation in cooking class.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20855" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ参上! ハムハム小僧</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Robin-Ham!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Robin Ham und die Zaubermaske</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Robin des Stères</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sanjou! Hamham Kozou</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams and Laura have a dream about Howdy as an evil hamster named Howlin the Magician, who tries to take over the kingdom, but Hamtaro as Robin-Ham defeats him. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20856" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ七夕! じゃじゃハムちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pepper`s Visit!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Sternenfest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La visite de Paprika</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Tanabata! Jaja Ham-chan</title>
<summary>Country hamster Pepper comes for a visit in the city. Oxnard is all excitable over her visit, but things become complicated when Pepper ventures out into the city alone. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20857" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこアイドル! くるりんちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pop Star</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Stars und Sternchen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une nouvelle étoile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Idol! Kururin-chan</title>
<summary>A new student moves into Laura`s school, but she`s no ordinary person. She happens to be a celebrity singer named Glitter and she`s anything but nice when she tries to steal Laura`s crush Travis away from her. At the same time, Glitter`s hamster Sparkle meets Hamtaro and his fellow Hams. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20858" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこホント! 迷子のロコちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laura Is Really Gone!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Laura haut ab</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le départ de Laura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Honto! maigo no Rocko-chan</title>
<summary>When Laura`s parents find out that she failed to pass a test at school, they punish her by not buying a CD player she`s been wanting. Out of anger, she runs away from home. Really worried, the Ham-Hams try to find Laura in the city. Laura ends up meeting Maria and accompanying her to a piano concert. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20859" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ燃えろ! 海の若ダイショー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boss, the Cool Ham of the Sea!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der alte Seebär</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hamiral a le mal de mer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Moero! Umi no Waka Daishou</title>
<summary>Boss wants to head to the beach and go sailing with Bijou by allowing the fellow Ham-Hams to help him overcome his seasickness. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20860" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ怖いぞ! 峠のおばけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Mountain!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Hamsterjäger</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Fantômes de la Montagne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Kowaizo! Touge no Obake</title>
<summary>Laura and Kana (with Hamtaro and Oxnard) listen to a scary story from Mr. Yoshi`s mother at her house about a pair of travelers named Harry and Ernie who were lost in the very mountain pass they are currently within and were never found. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20861" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこさわやか! 夏の風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fresh Summer Breeze!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine frische Brise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Marina Craque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sawayaka! Natsu no Kaze</title>
<summary>When Bijou`s owner Maria begins struggling with her piano lessons and recital, Hamtaro and his fellow hams decide to bring Maria out into the open fields to relax. At the same time, Laura decides to visit Maria out of concern. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20862" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこピンチだ! ライバル登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In a Pinch, a Rival Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rivalen auf dem Fußballplatz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un Nouveau Venu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Pinch Da! Rival Toujou</title>
<summary>A new kid named Roberto arrives in the neighborhood and he`s not the type to make friends so easily. To make things more interesting, he is part of Travis` soccer team, but has difficulty working together with them. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20863" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこがんばれ! にわとり大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Chicken Contest</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Chicky-Chick-Wettkampf</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épreuve du coq</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Ganbare! Niwatori Taikai</title>
<summary>Charlotte`s father, Chairman Rooster holds a contest on who can win the heart of his daughter by capturing one of his chickens and returning it to him in the utmost care. Mr. Yoshi accepts the challenge, but at the same time another man (whom Chairman Rooster admires) is also going for the prize. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20864" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこさがそう! 宝物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Treasure Hunting</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Schatzkarte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chasse aux trésors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sagasou! Houmotsu</title>
<summary>While cleaning up Elder-Ham`s house, the Ham-Hams find a treasure map! They spend all day searching and searching for the mysterious treasure but the map leads them in circles right back to Elder-Ham`s house! Meanwhile, Laura`s Mom has lost a precious brooch but can`t find it anywhere. Are both the Ham-Ham`s and Laura`s Mom`s mysterious treasures never to be found? 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20865" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ初恋! ちび丸ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Penelope Makes a Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Didu ist verliebt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pénélope se fait un ami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Hatsukoi! Chibimaru-chan</title>
<summary>Kylie, Penelope`s owner has a cousin named Ethan who comes to visit! Young Ethan and Penelope take an immediate liking to each other, and play and play all day until they both fall asleep exhausted and happy. Penelope soon decides that she wants to give Ethan something to show him that he is her new best friend! But she is so shy and Ethan is carefree and oblivious. The Ham-Hams try to help Penelope out of her disappointment and bring her to Ethan`s school, where surprising news awaits the anxious and unsuspecting Penelope. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20866" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとここわ~い! 校長先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scary Principal!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die laufende Holzmaske</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Proviseur la terreur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Kowai! Kouchou-sensei</title>
<summary>Laura`s school principal is renowned for his love of plants and for his scary appearance. One day, Laura inadvertently breaks a flowerpot containing a plant that the principal values greatly! She is terrified of what her scary principal might do to her. The Ham-Hams come to the rescue and try to fix the flowerpot before the principal notices, but before they have time to finish, the principal returns! Everyone is in big trouble, and Laura has to face making a difficult apology. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20867" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこハラハラ! 仲直り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reconciliation!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wieder versöhnt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La réconciliation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Harahara! Nakanaori</title>
<summary>Both Howdy and Dexter`s owners have a huge quarrel, so the Hams do whatever they can to end it. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20868" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこモモちゃん! 夢の遊園地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mimi`s Dream Park!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mimis Traumpark</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête foraine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Momo-chan! Yume no Yuuenchi</title>
<summary>When Mimi (Panda`s owner) is unable to go to the amusement park, the Ham-Hams decide to create an amusement park of their own to cheer her up, but a powerful storm halts construction and it proves difficult for them to finish. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20869" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこまわるよ! ひまわり観覧車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spinning Sunflower Ferris Wheel</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Sonnenblumen-Riesenrad dreht sich</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le nouveau ham ham parc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Mawaru yo! Himawari Kanransha</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams resume construction on their amusement park after last night`s thunderstorm, but the storm had done some damage onto the entire unfinished park. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20870" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこデートだ! 動物園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Zoo Date</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Date im Zoo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rendez vous au Zoo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Date Da! Doubutsuen</title>
<summary>Charlotte and Mr. Yoshi are going on a date to the zoo. Mr. Yoshi has even prepared a special picnic lunch to share with Charlotte, Laura, and Kana. Of course, the Ham-Hams have found their way to the zoo, too! But things begin to go awry when Hector the ostrich not only escapes from his cage but also takes the picnic Mr. Yoshi so carefully prepared! 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20871" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこドッキリ! 怪事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Haunting</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Werwolfabenteuer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le manoir de la peur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Dokkiri! Kai Jiken</title>
<summary>Laura, Kana, Mr. Haruna, and the Ham-Hams all drive out to visit Gabriel, Mr. Haruna`s horror-story writer friend who lives in a big, fancy mansion. But as soon as they get to Gabriel`s house, Gabriel takes off on an impromptu errand and leaves everyone alone to keep watch over his big, creepy home. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20872" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ占い! 大当たり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fortune Comes True!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kana, die Kartenlegerin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bonne aventure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Uranai! Ooatari</title>
<summary>Kana likes to play with cards and tell people`s fortunes, and lately she is getting good at it! The Ham-Hams are immensely interested and want Oxnard to tell their fortunes, too. Boss thinks it`s all a bunch of hogwash but Oxnard predicts that Boss will meet up with something big, white, and round, and it isn`t long before as foreseen a big, white, round rabbit sits right on top of Boss! The rabbit turns out to be someone`s lost pet. The Ham-Hams, Laura and Kana all join in to help the rabbit find its owner. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20873" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ誕生! 赤ちゃんヤギ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Baby Goat</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Ziegenbaby</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pâquerette a un bébé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Tanjou! Akachan Yagi</title>
<summary>A goat is about to give birth at Pepper`s farm, so Oxnard tries to prove himself to Pepper that he is helpful and caring. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20874" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこはじめて! 動物病院</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Animal Hospital</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die neue Tierklinik</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bijou est malade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Hajimete! Doubutsu Byouin</title>
<summary>When Bijou catches a cold, Maria, Laura, and Kana visit the local animal hospital for help. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20875" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこあったか! マフラー大作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Knitting Craze</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Leuchten der Milchstraße</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une écharpe pour Brandy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Attaka! Muffler Dai Sakusen</title>
<summary>When Laura and Kana begin practice knitting scarves, the Ham-Hams decide to create some of their own as well. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20876" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ見つけた! 小さい秋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Breath of Autumn!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Herbstgrüße</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête des mères</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Mitsuketa! Chiisai Aki</title>
<summary>It`s Labor Day, and Laura and her Dad want to give Mrs. Haruna a special break from all her household chores. Hamtaro observes as Laura`s Mom, having a moment to relax at last, looks out the window and remembers fondly the last time she had free time to go out and enjoy the pretty autumn leaves. That gives the resourceful Hamtaro an idea for a Labor Day gift for Mrs. Haruna. On his way out, Hamtaro runs into Bijou and the other Ham-Hams and together, they set off for the mountains to gather nuts and colorful leaves to bring back "Autumn" for Mrs. Haruna. But Hamtaro, reaching for the perfect maple leaf, slips and finds himself dangling treacherously over a steep cliff. Meanwhile, a storm is brewing and rain threatens to wash away our furry friends! 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20877" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこおかえり! ちび丸ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome Home Penelope!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der rosarote Freund</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pénélope ne veut pas rentrer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Okaeri! Chibimaru-chan</title>
<summary>Penelope is wandering around by herself, when all of a sudden she falls into a deep ditch! Luckily, Jingle and his faithful wanderer companion, Herbert the pig, happen to be in town. Herbert, by chance, finds little Penelope and rescues her from the perilous hole. From that moment on, Penelope is absolutely taken with Herbert. But Herbert and Jingle are in the midst of their travels, and the time to say goodbye comes all too soon. Penelope, crushed to see her new friend go, runs away and has her mind set to follow Herbert wherever he goes. How can the other Ham-Hams persuade Penelope to come back home?
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20878" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ見たなぁ~! 雪女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Abominable Snow Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aufmarsch der Schneefrauen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`abominable femme des neiges</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Mitana! Yukionna</title>
<summary>It`s wintertime, and Laura and Kana bump into their teacher, Mr. Yoshi, while ice-skating in the mountains. Mr. Yoshi invites them back to his mother`s house. His mother, the gifted ghost-story teller who gave Laura and Kana shivers in the summertime with her story of hamster-hunting ghosts, has more tales to entertain our friends. This time, Laura, Kana, and the Ham-Hams tremble as Mr. Yoshi`s mother tells them about a mysterious snow woman who haunts the mountain. On the way home, Laura, Kana, the Ham-Hams, and Mr. Yoshi all get separated in the woods. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20879" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">76</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこスターだ! ハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laura and the Seven Hamsters</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Filmstar Hamtaro</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Laura et les sept hamsters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Star Da! Hamtarou</title>
<summary>In this take on Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs, Laura and Hamtaro dream that they are a part of the story filling in for the roles of the classic fairy tale.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20880" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">77</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこすてきな! サンタクロース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Wonderful Santa Claus!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Weihnachts-Ham-Ham</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le noël de Ham Ham</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Suteki na! Santa Claus</title>
<summary>Elder Ham has selected Hamtaro to be the next Santa Ham for Christmas, but when Bijou finds out, she tags along with Hamtaro to help him in delivering presents to other hamsters. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20881" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">78</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこラブリー! 怪盗ちーず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Little Bandits!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Edelkern des Herzogs von Kalau</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sherlock Hamtaro et les petits canards</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Lovely! Kaitouchi?</title>
<summary>Bijou, Sandy, Pashmina, and Penelope notice that there are not many female thieves in any stories they`ve heard before, so they and the other Hams come up with a story that involves a trio of female thieves known as "The Little Bandits." This episode reveals Boss, Maxwell, Dexter and Oxnard are ticklish. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20882" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">79</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ新春! たこあげ大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Year`s Kite Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Neujahrsdrachen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les cerfs volants du nouvel an</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Shinshun! Takoage Taikai</title>
<summary>The weather is beautiful on New Year`s and for the occasion, many people in Laura`s town have taken to flying kites. As we might expect, the Ham-Hams want a part in the fun, too! So Panda teaches each of the other Ham-Hams how to make their own kites! But when the Ham-Hams go out to fly them, Boss gets jealous that Hamtaro`s kite is flying next to Bijou`s. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20883" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">80</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ夕日だ! プロポーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunset Proposal</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Heiratsantrag bei Sonnenuntergang</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La demande en mariage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Yuuhi Da! Propose</title>
<summary>A reluctant Mr. Yoshi is hesitant to propose marriage to Charlotte, so the Ham-Hams do what they can to help him propose. However, Charlotte`s father does not approve, so he sends out one of his prized roosters to stop them (since Mr. Yoshi has a fear of chickens). But his plan fails and Mr.Yoshi proposed to Charlotte. Leaving the Ham-Hams cheering 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20884" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">81</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこトンネル! ぬけないくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stucky`s Tunnel</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Klemmi im Hamstertunnel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le champion du cache cache</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Tunnel! Nukenai-kun</title>
<summary>One day, the Ham-Hams are in the forest playing hide-and-seek and as always, Cappy is the last one left hiding. To the other Ham-Hams` great bewilderment, however, there seem to be two Cappies calling "I`m ready!". All of a sudden, out from under a bush, pops a young little hamster that the Ham-Hams have never seen before! 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20885" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">82</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこときめき! 恋占い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ham-Romance</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Amor greift ein</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hamtaro joue les cupidons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Tokimeki! Koi Uranai</title>
<summary>Laura has been feeling a little down lately, so Kana decides to tell her romance fortune. Her fortune says that a pet of hers will be her cupid! Who could her winged messenger be? None other than Hamtaro! At least that`s what Hamtaro leads himself to believe. All nervous about his new role, Hamtaro makes a few goofs...in his first set-up plan Laura ends up doing a face plant right in front of Travis! How embarrassing. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20886" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">83</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ豆まき! 鬼たいじ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scatter the Beans, Scare the Ogres!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Kindergartengeister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Mamemaki! Oni Taiji</title>
<summary>Mimi`s school participates in the traditional Setsubun festival, and Laura and Kana`s fathers are the ogres.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20887" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">84</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこドタバタ! バレンタイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laura`s Valentine</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Chaos am Valentinstag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête des garçons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Dotabata! Valengine</title>
<summary>Ah yes, Valentine`s Day. This year, Laura has made chocolates for Travis and candy to give to her dad. Each present has a special little note inside. But this morning, Laura is late for school, and on her way out the door, she accidentally snatches the candy for her dad rather than the chocolates for Travis! Hamtaro, realizing Laura`s mistake, decides to deliver the right present for Travis. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20888" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">85</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこどんちゃん! 大活躍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roberto`s Ally</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tierisch gute Hilfe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Roberto et Brandy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Don-chan! Dai Katsuyaku</title>
<summary>Roberto, who is on Travis` soccer team, is really good at soccer but he won`t cooperate with the rest of the team. Towards the end of practice one day, he gets into an argument with his teammates and quits, despite the fact that the regional championships are coming up soon! The Ham-Hams, who know that Roberto is a kind person who truly loves soccer, and that without Roberto Travis` soccer team won`t have a good chance in the championships, decide to try to patch things up. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20889" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">86</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこロボハム! メカじろう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Hamster Robo-Joe</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Roboham-Joe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Méca-ham un nouvel ami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Roboham! Mecha Jirou</title>
<summary>Laura`s grandpa comes over with a new invention: Robo-Joe. Hamtaro introduces Robo-Joe to his fellow Ham-Hams, but all things go awry when the mechanical hamster begins to malfunction and runs loose into the city, getting into a lot of trouble.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20890" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">87</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこパニック! ひなまつり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maria`s Birthday Party</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Panik beim Klavierkonzert</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`anniversaire de Marina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Panic! Hina Matsuri</title>
<summary>It`s Maria`s birthday and Laura has invited Kana, June, and Kylie along with her to celebrate. Meanwhile, the Ham-Hams secretly come along, but Boss seems very hesitant into entering the house (since he is wearing a fine suit to impress Bijou).
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20891" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">88</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ忍者だ! ニンハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nin-Ham the Ninja!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ninja Ninham</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ninjaro, le ninj-ham</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Ninja Da! Ninham-kun</title>
<summary>A hamster known as Nin-Ham appears out of nowhere. The Hams seem influenced and awe-inspired by this clever hamster that they decide to pass off as his students and follow his rigorous training methods. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20892" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">89</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこさがそう! 春とはる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Search for Spring!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Lenz ist weg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Printemps où es-tu ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sagasou! Haru to Haru</title>
<summary>Winter is at its end but the days still continue to be cold. Laura`s Dad has heard, however, that flowers are starting to bloom around Shimmer Lake! So the family...and the Ham-Hams of course...all hop in the car for a weekend trip to hunt for springtime! But on the way, Laura`s dad take a wrong turn and the whole gang ends up in a cold, gloomy place rather than at Shimmer Lake. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20893" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">90</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ宇宙だ! ハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hamtaro and the Space Ship!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Weltraumabenteuer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hamtaro, le hamelien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Uchuu Da! Hamtarou</title>
<summary>After watching a space film at the local Space Observatory, Hamtaro begins to wonder if he himself is really an alien and that he`s not destined to be with Laura. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20894" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">91</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこタイショー! ながれ旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boss Runs Away</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abschied von Boss</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hamiral a disparu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Taishou! Nagaretabi</title>
<summary>Boss once again tries to tell Bijou his feelings for her but freezes up again. Sabu comes and visits the clubhouse and meets the Ham-hams for the first time. Boss looks up to Sabu and runs away with him to learn how to be a man for Bijou. Meanwhile Laura`s mom is away. Even though Laura`s dad doesn`t know how to cook or clean. The Ham-hams worry about him especially Hamtaro. So he sets out to look for Boss with Sabu`s girlfriend Francios. Once he saw him Hamtaro convinced him to go back to the clubhouse and Laura`s mom came back home. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20895" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">92</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこお花見! おハムと長老</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Auntie Viv and Elder Ham</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tanti-Ham und Opi-Ham</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La magie des cerisiers en fleurs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Ohanami! Oham to Chourou</title>
<summary>After Auntie Viv and Elder Ham have a fight, the Ham-Hams gather around to try to cheer them both up. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20896" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">93</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこはなちゃん! 恋のはなはな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hannah Is in Love!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hana heiß verknallt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un amour de Rita</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Hana-chan! Koi no Hanahana</title>
<summary>Howdy`s childhood friend, Hannah, is over for a visit! During her stay, she develops a bit of a crush on Dexter. Confiding in Howdy, Hannah asks him to find out how Dexter feels about her. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20897" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">94</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこやさしい! ライオン先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Doctor Lion</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der nette Dr. Löwenhaupt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le docteur Lion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Yasashii! Lion-sensei</title>
<summary>Laura decides to take her dog Brandy for a check-up at Dr. Lion`s vehicle clinic, but Brandy is anything but excited to head there. Hamtaro becomes curious of what Dr. Lion is really like, so he and the Ham-Hams decide to investigate. Knowing Dr. Lion has a ton of work, the ham hams help him out.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20898" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">95</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ踊るよ! コックさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dance, Chef Ham!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Meisterkoch Koküni</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le festin de chef-ham</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Odoru yo! Kokku-san</title>
<summary>A hamster known as Chef Ham visits the Ham-Ham Clubhouse with several cooking methods up his sleeves. Oxnard becomes impressed by him that he would eat anything Chef Ham can prepare. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20899" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">96</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ飛ぶのだ! こいのぼり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flying Carp</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Flugkarpfen für Laura</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les poissons volants</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Tobu no Da! Koi Nobori</title>
<summary>Walking around her neighborhood, Laura sees that many houses have wind-socks in the form of flying carp that flow gracefully from their rafters. She runs home and asks her mom if she can put one up at their house, too! But her mom won`t let her. That day, however, Grandpa Woody comes over. He tells Laura that when he was younger, he dreamed of riding on the back of a flying fish, soaring through the sky. All excited, Laura embarks with Grandpa Woody on an invention escapade: to create a mechanical flying carp! Unfortunately, their attempts don`t go too smoothly. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20900" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">97</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ出発! ハムちゃんず号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ham-Ham Express</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lokführerin Didu</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`excursion à la montagne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Shupatsu! Ham-chanz</title>
<summary>While Laura, Kana and their classmates go on a class field trip to the mountains with Mr. Yoshi, the Ham-Hams decide to create their own expressway system underground that would lead to the mountains. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20901" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">98</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ捜すぞ! 消えたクツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who Stole My Shoe?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein klarer Fall für die Detekti-Hams</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le voleur de chaussures</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Sagasuzo! Kieta Kutsu</title>
<summary>At Laura`s school, something strange is happening. Everyone`s shoes are disappearing! So Hamtaro becomes a private investiham, and with his magnifying glass, goes on a hunt for the culprit. But Hamtaro and the Ham-Hams run into trouble when an escaped monkey begins to chase after them! 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20902" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">99</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ守るよ! 大事な約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Keeping Promises</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Versprochen ist versprochen!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une promesse est une promesse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Mamoru yo! Daiji na Yakusoku</title>
<summary>Laura and Kana have a huge fight, so Hamtaro and Oxnard try to end their quarrel. At the same time, Boss accuses Hamtaro of forgetting about helping Bijou and that she got hurt (when she really didn`t) in the process. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20903" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">100</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこモモちゃん! すてきな贈り物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Very Best Present</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Geschenk von ganzem Herzen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cadeau de Mimi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Momo-chan! Suteki na Okurimono</title>
<summary>Mimi`s father`s birthday is coming up very soon, but Mimi has no idea what to give him as a present. She really wants to do something special for him, so when she sees one day how emotional he gets when he hears Maria playing the piano, Mimi decides that she is going to learn to play something for him. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20904" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">101</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこハッピー! ウェディング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Rescue a Wedding!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rettet die Hochzeit!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un mariage à sauver</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totokko Happy! Wedding</title>
<summary>Mr. Yoshi and Charlotte`s wedding day has finally arrived, but Charlotte is nowhere to be seen. She sends Mr. Yoshi a letter at the church stating that she can`t be at the wedding without her father being there for her. The Ham-Hams subtly get involved and do what they can to help the wedding become realized. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20905" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">102</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ会社だ! 大はしゃぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Office Adventures</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vatertag in Gefahr!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête des pères</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Kaisha Da! Oohashagi</title>
<summary>Laura is preparing a very special celebration for Father`s Day! But her dad has been so busy at work these days, and he might not make it home in time to for the Father`s Day party. That`s no good! So Hamtaro and the Ham-Hams decide to make a visit to Forrest Haruna`s office and give him a hand. Maybe they can help him work faster! Pretty soon the Ham-Hams even know how to use a photocopying machine. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20906" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">103</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこよこどり! 地下ハウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clubhouse Intruders</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Évacuation d`urgence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko yo Kodori! Chika House</title>
<summary>After Laura tells Hamtaro about an earthquake and a fire drill, the Ham-Hams decide to practice for one. But meanwhile, Stan declines to go outside and while he stays in, the Chickies break into the clubhouse. And Stan is trapped in the clubhouse. So the Ham-Hams decide to help him out.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20907" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">104</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ御用だ! ひまわりのハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tale of Princess Bijou</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`histoire de la Princesse Bijou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Goyou Da! Himawari no Hamtarou</title>
<summary>One sleepy rainy evening, Laura and Hamtaro fall asleep while reading a book full of fairytales...and dream of a land full of castles and princesses. Bijou is a tough-girl princess who, tired of being cooped up in her castle all day, disappears disguised into the streets of her fiefdom. But she runs into troubles when an evil Sparkle orders her ninja team to get rid of Princess Bijou. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50717" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Undetermined Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51571" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52527" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">105</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこお願い! 天の川</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Milky Way</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Voie Lactée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totokko Negai! Amanogawa</title>
<summary>Laura and her class are studying the star constellations at school, and have a field trip planned to study the Milky Way under the real night sky! So Laura and Kana are all excited because they will have plenty of stars to wish on. Kana says jokingly to Laura that if you wish on a star at the same time as someone else, the two of you will fall in love! Laura, half believing, sets her mind on standing by Travis when her class goes to see the stars so that they can make a wish on a star together. However, Hamtaro thinks that she`ll be leaving on a star to make her wish. He and the Ham-Hams decide to stop Laura from making her wish. In the end, Laura forgets all about her wish, when she starts having fun focusing on the fireflies. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52528" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">106</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ恋する! ぬけないくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lovestruck Stucky!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Koi Suru! Nukenai-kun</title>
<summary>Stucky returns to play hide-and-seek with the Ham-Hams, and he falls in love with a bunny in a stump. Cappy wants to ask the bunny to play hide-and-seek with Stucky. Meanwhile, Laura and her mom help Laura`s cousin Erika prepare for her wedding. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52529" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">107</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ転がる! 大きなタマゴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rolling, Big Egg!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Korogaru! Ooki na Tamago</title>
<summary>An ostrich`s egg rolls away from Mr. Yoshi and Charlotte`s farm, and the Ham-Hams try to take care of it, but the Chicky-Chickies hassle them. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52530" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">108</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ夏だ! 海の家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The House at the Sea!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Natsu Da! Umi no Ie</title>
<summary>Laura, her parents and classmates, and Mr. Yoshi go to the beach, and the Ham-Hams go too. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52531" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">109</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこがんばる! メカじろう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do Your Best Robo-Joe!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Ganbaru! Mecha Jirou</title>
<summary>Laura and Kana visit Laura`s grandparents, and the Ham-Hams see Robo-Joe again.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52532" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">110</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ踊ろう! ハムちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Dance, Ham-Hams!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Odorou! Ham-chans</title>
<summary>Laura, Kana, their parents, and Kana`s cousin Dylan go to an Ondoda festival, and the Ham-Hams, Sabu, and Pepper have a Ham-Ham festival too, and Oxnard learns how to play the Ondoda drums. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52533" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">111</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこゾゾゾーッ! きもだめし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">S-S-Scary! Bravery Test!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Zozozo!! Kimodameshi</title>
<summary>Laura`s school has a bravery test, and the Ham-Hams go too. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52534" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">112</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ愛の! つなわたり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tightrope Walking Together!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Ai no! Tsunawatari</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams make their own circus. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52535" update="2017-03-18">
<epno type="1">113</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこバカンス! くるりんちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sparkle`s Vacances!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Vacance! Kururin-chan</title>
<summary>Glitter returns to Japan for her job, and so does Sparkle. The Ham-Hams want to play with Sparkle, but she wants to have a lovely "vacances", which is French for "vacation" or "holidays". 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52536" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">114</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこナイトだ! ハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Knight Hamtaro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Night Da! Hamtarou</title>
<summary>After Boss saves Bijou from a big ball that was headed toward her, everyone says that Boss is like a knight. Later, there is a typhoon and Laura`s parents can`t make it home, so Hamtaro decides to be like a knight and protect Laura from the storm. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52537" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">115</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとことんでる! メカじろう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Groovy Robo-Joe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Tonderu! Mecha Jirou</title>
<summary>Robo-Joe takes the Ham-Hams flying in a plane-like transformation. But something goes wrong... 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52538" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">116</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこふたたび! にわとりトリオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Chickens Strike Again!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Futabi! Niwatori Torio</title>
<summary>The chickens escape from Mr. Yoshi and Charlotte`s farm, and they have to get them back. The Ham-Hams decide to help too. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52539" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">117</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ夢みる! ちび丸ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Penelope`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Yume Miru! Chibimaru-chan</title>
<summary>Penelope dreams to see a castle. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52540" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">118</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこぼくらの! ハムハムキャッスル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Ham-Ham Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokura no! Hamham Castle</title>
<summary>After what happened yesterday, Pashmina got sick, and June messed up Kylie`s cake. Can the Ham-Hams help Penelope`s castle dream come true, or will the friendship between June and Kylie as well as Pashmina and Penelope fall apart? 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52541" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">119</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとことどけ! こうしの純情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oxnard Shows True Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Todoke! Koushi no Junjou</title>
<summary>Oxnard wants to see Pepper. Can he show the power of love? 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52542" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">120</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこどこなの! かぶるくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where Are You, Cappy?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Doko na no! Kaburu-kun</title>
<summary>When the Ham-Hams decide what to play, Cappy wants to play hide and seek, but he speaks so quietly, no one can hear him, and they go with Panda`s idea of playing dodgeball instead. While Boss is looking for the ball, Cappy asks about Boss`s tunnel. Boss says that it continues forever, and no matter how far you walk, you`ll have to walk even farther. Cappy is sad until Stucky shows up. They both decide to play hide and seek in the tunnel. They have a lot of fun, until an earthquake traps them! 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52543" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">121</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ勝負だ! タイショーくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s a Duel, Boss!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Shoubu Da! Taisho-kun</title>
<summary>A stray cat threatens Bijou, and Hamtaro and Boss try to protect her, but Boss is afraid and cowers. However, Hamtaro and Bijou think Boss was brave and that he "lowered his head to feint the cat". Boss is upset that he was such a coward, and he runs out of the clubhouse. Hamtaro goes to find him, but Boss yells at Hamtaro, saying he wants to be left alone. Hamtaro says he wouldn`t want to come near Boss. Sabu comes, and says that they shouldn`t fight, but instead they should have a duel. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52544" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">122</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこほんと! オオカミが出たぞ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s Really a Wolf!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Honto! Ookami ga Detazo</title>
<summary>Laura and Kana are in the school`s play of Little Red Riding Hood. Meanwhile, a scary wolf stalks the Ham-Hams, but is it really a wolf? 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52545" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">123</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこどうなる! 地下ハウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Will Become of the Clubhouse?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Dou Naru! Chika House</title>
<summary>Humans are going to dig up the tree above the Ham-Ham Clubhouse! Can the Ham-Hams save their precious club? 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52546" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">124</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ秋だよ! おふくろの味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Autumn, Mom`s Style</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Aki Da yo! Ofukuro no Aji</title>
<summary>Zack has an argument with his mom, so the Ham-Hams go on a trip to Trotting Mountain to find a gift for him. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52547" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">125</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとここまった! ニンハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Troublesome Nin-Ham</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Komatta! Ninhamu-kun</title>
<summary>Nin-Ham falls out of the sky and tells the Ham-Hams he has a special mission so they won`t think he`s clumsy. The Ham-Hams try to help him.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52548" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">126</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこやさしい! ナースちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kind Flora</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Yasashii! Nurse-chan</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams meet Flora the nurse hamster, an assistant to Dr. Lion, and Stan starts to fall for her.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52549" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">127</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこどんちゃん! レスキュー隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brandy and the Rescue Team</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Don-chan! Rescue Tai</title>
<summary>Laura and Kana get into problems while skiing, and Brandy and the Ham-Hams help. Also, Boss and Stan compete to see who is better at skiing. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52550" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">128</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ恋なの! くるりんちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sparkle`s Crush</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Koi na no! Kururin-chan</title>
<summary>Sparkle meets Omar, and she starts to like him mostly because Howdy says Omar lives like a prince. Sparkle misses the part about the "lives like" and thought he was actually a prince. She noticed that Omar was different from the Ham-Hams, because he is more charming. The Ham-Hams tell her that he travels around the world. But Sparkle actually wants to become a princess and travel. She daydreams about their marriage. However Sparkle doesn`t like Omar at the end of the episode, because when they actually traveled together (Sparkle stopped being a star just to be with Omar and become a princess), their adventure consisted of going to hot and cold places, and snake and shark infested places. Sparkle decides to stick to being a star. At the end of the episode it`s revealed Omar didn`t even have feelings for Sparkle. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52551" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">129</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこモモちゃん! クリスマス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mimi`s Christmas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Momo-chan! Christmas</title>
<summary>Mimi wishes to have the greatest Christmas ever, but her dad and Kana`s dad get into an argument and don`t want each other`s families to spend Christmas together. So the Ham-Hams try to help give Mimi a Christmas party. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52552" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">130</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこりんりん! エンジェルちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rin Rin! Harmony!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Rinrin! Angel-chan</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams dream and meet Harmony and Spat. Will Hamtaro, Bijou, and Harmony stop Spat?
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52553" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">131</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこめでたい! ハムちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happy New Year, Ham-Hams!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Medetai! Ham-chans</title>
<summary>It`s New Year`s, and Penelope and one of the chickens become friends. Will the Ham-Hams and chickens work together to save Penelope and the baby chicken? 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52554" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">132</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこリボンと! 思い出の絵本</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bijou`s Memorable Picture Book</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Ribon to! Omoide no Ehon</title>
<summary>Maria writes a letter to her grandmother, and Hamtaro and Bijou help Maria to get her letter to her grandmother. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52555" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">133</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこあみあみ! ポニーテールちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Knitting Barrette</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Amiami! Ponytail-chan</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams meet Barrette, a hamster who can knit. Barrette has a crush on Hamtaro and she sees Bijou as a rival. Meanwhile, Penelope is sad that Pashmina is not with the Ham-Hams. Will Barrette be friends with Penelope?
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52556" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">134</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ笑って! ヒカリさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laugh, Hillary!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Waratte! Hikari-san</title>
<summary>Sandy`s owner Hillary messes up gym training and Sandy gets worried. Can the Ham-Hams help Hillary master gym again? 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52557" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">135</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこかぜの! ハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hamtaro of the Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Kaze no! Hamtarou</title>
<summary>Hamtaro wants to go outside with Laura, but she leaves him behind because she thought he might be getting a cold. But Hamtaro hears her say that he was acting weird, which hurts his feelings, and he leaves on a journey with Jingle to find "the cloak of the wind". 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52558" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">136</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこイケイケ! トラハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come On, Stan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Ikeike! Toraham-kun</title>
<summary>It`s Valentine`s Day, and the Ham-Ham girls plan on what to give the Ham-Ham boys. Sandy wants to give her sweetheart Maxwell something, Boss thinks Bijou will give something to Hamtaro, and Stan wants to impress Flora. Will the Ham-Girls and Ham-Boys get what they desire? 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52559" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">137</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ消えた! ハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hamtaro Is Gone!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Kieta! Hamtarou</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams think Hamtaro has gotten stuck in a painting and try to get him out. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52560" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">138</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこじゃじゃハム! おひなさま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pepper, Empress of Spring!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Jajaham! Ohina-sama</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams visit Pepper, and Oxnard and Pepper are emperor and empress in the Doll Festival. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52561" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">139</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこユメちゃん! おはなしきかせて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yume, Tell Us a Story!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Yume-chan! Ohanashi Kikasete</title>
<summary>Maxwell`s owner Melissa is upset that Zack laughed at her. Maxwell and Howdy start to fight. Can they forgive each other so Maxwell and Howdy can become friends again? 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52562" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">140</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこウキウキ! ウキハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cheerful Ook-Ook!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Ukiuki ! Ukiham-kun</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams meet Ook-Ook, a hamster dressed like a monkey, and Buster, a security guard hamster who is pursuing Ook-Ook. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52563" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">141</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ好きなの! ハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Someone Likes Hamtaro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Suki na no! Hamtarou</title>
<summary>Sparkle becomes jealous of Bijou because she believes Bijou is prettier than her (She starts believing this when Bijou was able to get Hamtaro`s attention but she couldn`t). She begins to like Hamtaro and tries to capture his heart to make Bijou jealous.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52564" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">142</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこお願い! 花ふぶき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cherry Blossoms, Please Fall!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Onegai! Hanafubuki</title>
<summary>Panda`s owner Mimi wants to see cherry blossoms. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52565" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">143</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ三つ子の! ちびちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Three Hambini</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Mittsu Ko no! Chibi-chans</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams meet mischievous triplet hamsters called the Hambini Brothers. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52566" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">144</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ決闘! フラワー牧場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel at the Flower Ranch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Kettou! Flower Bokujou</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams and their owners visit Dylan`s farm, along with Travis and Roberto. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52567" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">145</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこタイショー! いこいの部屋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boss`s New Room</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Taishou! Ikoi no Heya</title>
<summary>The Ham-Hams make too much noise while playing, and they upset Boss, who is trying to sleep. So the Ham-Hams want to make a new room for Boss to play and relax in. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52568" update="2017-03-19">
<epno type="1">146</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこふたりの! 大事な思い出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Biggest Memories!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Futari no! Daiji na Omoide</title>
<summary>Laura and Hamtaro visit their old hometown, and see Laura`s old friend Claire. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="52569" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">147</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこおまかせ! ハムハムナース隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 147</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52570" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">148</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこあれれ! おハムかあさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 148</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52571" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">149</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこスキャンダルなの! くるりんちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 149</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52572" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">150</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこたたかえ! メカじろう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 150</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52573" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">151</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこねてると! カメゾウくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 151</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52574" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">152</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ雨ふり! アジサイの花</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 152</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52575" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">153</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ育て! ぼくらのミドリン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 153</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52576" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">154</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこてちてち! ハラペコの旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 154</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52577" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">155</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ正義の! 女ねずみ小僧</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 155</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52578" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">156</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ小さな! 恋の物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 156</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52579" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">157</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこデンジャー! にわとりトリオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 157</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52580" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">158</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこくるりん! スターなの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 158</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52581" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">159</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ恋の! あつあつポテト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 159</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52582" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">160</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこまいごだ! 遊園地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 160</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52583" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">161</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ泳ぐぞ! カメハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 161</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52584" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">162</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ夏だよ! きもだめし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 162</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52585" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">163</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ夏色! ひまわりちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 163</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52586" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">164</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこニンハム! イガイガの里</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 164</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52587" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">165</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこトマトくんと! ナッスーくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 165</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52588" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">166</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこピ~ヒョロ! ハムちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 166</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52589" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">167</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ赤ちゃん! 大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 167</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52590" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">168</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ会いたい! リボンちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 168</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52591" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">169</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ秋だ! ハム太郎まつり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 169</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52592" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">170</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこモモちゃん! 運動会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 170</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52593" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">171</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこイルカと! カメハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 171</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52594" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">172</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこちびくり! 秋まつり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 172</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52595" update="2011-06-21">
<epno type="1">173</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこハロウィン! 大へんしん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Halloween Transformation!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52596" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">174</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこロマンだ! ハムハム探検隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 174</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52597" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">175</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこどんちゃん! どこ行くの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 175</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52598" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">176</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこピーポー! ハムハムナース隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 176</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52599" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">177</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこぴかぴか! 流れ星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 177</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52600" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">178</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこどこへ! パパ大追跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 178</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52601" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">179</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ走れ! じゃじゃハムちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 179</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52602" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">180</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ不思議な! おくりもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 180</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52603" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">181</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこマンモス!? にじハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 181</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52604" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">182</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこハッピー! ウキハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 182</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52605" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">183</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこちびくり! 雪まつり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 183</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52606" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">184</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこパパだよ! ちびちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 184</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52607" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">185</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ赤ちゃん! オニは外</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 185</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52608" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">186</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこアミアミ娘と! カメハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 186</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52609" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">187</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ謎の! バレンタインチョコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 187</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52610" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">188</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ変身! マフラーちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 188</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52611" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">189</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ心配! いもうとよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 189</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52612" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">190</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこボンジュール! おしゃれちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 190</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52613" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">191</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこちびくり! 小さなヒミツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 191</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52614" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">192</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこくるりん! ハリウッドなの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 192</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52615" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">193</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこお別れ! 地下ハウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 193</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52616" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">194</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこラピスちゃんと! ラズリーちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 194</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52617" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">195</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこすい~ちゅ! ぱらだいす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 195</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52618" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">196</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこじっけん! ふしぎなタネ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 196</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52619" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">197</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ恋する! リボンちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 197</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52620" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">198</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこスカピー! 夢のなか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 198</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52621" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">199</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこだばっと! ヒーローハム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 199</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52622" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">200</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこクマった! クマ次郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 200</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52623" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">201</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこおしゃべり! 魔法の花</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 201</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52624" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">202</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこアートだ! おとめ・ずー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 202</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52625" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">203</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこいたずら! ユニコーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 203</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52626" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">204</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ出ました! ムハムハ星人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 204</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52627" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">205</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこびっくり! すい~ちゅゴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 205</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52628" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">206</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこただいま! 地下ハウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 206</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52629" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">207</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこすい~ちゅ! 天の川</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 207</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52630" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">208</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこくるりん! キューピットなの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 208</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52631" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">209</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこプンプン! ラピスとラズリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 209</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52632" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">210</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこふたりで! ひまわりの旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 210</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52633" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">211</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ来たジャン! ジャンガル王国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 211</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52634" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">212</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ夏ジャン! お宝さがし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 212</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52635" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">213</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこジャンジャン! 泳ぐのだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 213</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52636" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">214</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこなるジャン! 王様ジャン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 214</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52637" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">215</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこやるジャン! おとめちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 215</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52638" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">216</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ鏡で! とりかえっこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 216</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52639" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">217</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこワンちゃん! 会いたい気持ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 217</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52640" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">218</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこキラキラ! おしゃれでちゅ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 218</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52641" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">219</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこいなせな! ハムハム小僧</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 219</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52642" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">220</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこビッグな! ちび丸ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 220</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52643" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">221</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこちっちゃな! 応援団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 221</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52644" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">222</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ飛びます! ハムちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 222</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52645" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">223</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこヒーロー! 永遠(えいえん)に...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 223</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52646" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">224</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこジャンガル! ハロウィンじゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 224</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52647" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">225</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこコマッタネ! 魔法のタネ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 225</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52648" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">226</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ結婚! ナースちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 226</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52649" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">227</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこおはなし! わんわんクッキー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 227</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52650" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">228</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこパパだじぇ! つらいじぇ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 228</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52651" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">229</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこくるりん! アートなの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 229</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52652" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">230</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこラッキー! すい~ちゅ占い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 230</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52653" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">231</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ風船! 笑顔にとどけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 231</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52654" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">232</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこサンタだ! メリーくりすまちゅ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 232</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52655" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">233</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこめでたい! えんじぇるず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 233</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52656" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">234</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこまたね! 雪だるま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 234</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52657" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">235</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこノンノン! おしゃれちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 235</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52658" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">236</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこオニだよ! ハムちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 236</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52659" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">237</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ熱いの! レインボーガールズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 237</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52660" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">238</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこすきすき! バレンタインなの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 238</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52661" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">239</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ消えちゃう! すい~ちゅぱらだいす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 239</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52662" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">240</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこちこくだ! 王子さま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 240</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52663" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">241</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこハイパー! メカじろう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 241</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52664" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">242</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこヨロシク! じゃじゃハムちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 242</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52665" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">243</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ走るよ! ハムハムトレイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 243</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52666" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">244</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこデビっと! 大パニック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 244</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52667" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">245</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ消えた! ねてるくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 245</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52668" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">246</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこロコちゃん! ドキドキデート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 246</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52669" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">247</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ長老! お花見じゃ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 247</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52670" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">248</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ二人は! ベストフレンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 248</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52671" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">249</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこはじめて! ラブレター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 249</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52672" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">250</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこアカンで! おかんとサダ吉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 250</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52673" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">251</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこしまった! ハム太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 251</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52674" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">252</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこふわふわ! ジェラードちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 252</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52675" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">253</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ恋の! あつあつバトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 253</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52676" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">254</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ手と手で! とりかえっこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 254</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52677" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">255</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこプリプリ! ちびくりちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 255</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52678" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">256</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ笑顔の! おとしもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 256</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52679" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">257</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこスペース! ハムちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 257</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52680" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">258</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこゴーゴー! ハムちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 258</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52681" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">259</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこスパート! ハムちゃんず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 259</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52682" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">260</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ空から! そらハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 260</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52683" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">261</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこタネやで! オーキニーちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 261</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52684" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">262</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ占い! あたりんちゅ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 262</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52685" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">263</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこパタパタ! ハムハーの木</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 263</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52686" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">264</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこおどるぞ! ハムハム音頭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 264</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52687" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">265</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ笑って! ひまわり畑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 265</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52688" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">266</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ夏サー! サーファーくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 266</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52689" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">267</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ迷いを! けっとばせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 267</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52690" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">268</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこアイスと! キャンディーちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 268</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52691" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">269</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこホクホク! リボンちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 269</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52692" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">270</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこほるほる! もぐるくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 270</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52693" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">271</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ正義の! ハムハーマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 271</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52694" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">272</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ燃えよ! 運動会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 272</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52695" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">273</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこアートだ! トラハムちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 273</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52696" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">274</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこなんで! なんでくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 274</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52697" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">275</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこオーキニ! ショータイムなの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 275</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52698" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">276</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこモテモテ! 男はつらいじぇ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 276</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52699" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">277</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこレディよ! ラピスちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 277</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52700" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">278</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこまたまた! なんでやのん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 278</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52701" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">279</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこミラクル! マジカルくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 279</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52702" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">280</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこペローン! やきぐり星人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 280</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52703" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">281</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこペンハムくんと! あざらしちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 281</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52704" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">282</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこぶるぶる! 冬のおばけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 282</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52705" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">283</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこクリスマス! ライドオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 283</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52706" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">284</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ初夢! ハムハムトレイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 284</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52707" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">285</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとここうしくんと! じゃじゃハムちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 285</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52708" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">286</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ恋する! そらハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 286</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52709" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">287</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこカーカー! かんにんしてや</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 287</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52710" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">288</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこおかんだ! オーキニーちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 288</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52711" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">289</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこバトルだ! バレンタイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 289</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52712" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">290</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこヒーロー! そらハムくん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 290</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52713" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">291</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこほります! メカじろう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 291</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52714" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">292</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこニキニキ! 卒業でごじゃる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 292</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52715" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">293</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこ旅立ち! 春の風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 293</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52716" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">294</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこデートで! ピクニック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 294</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Date de! Picnic</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52717" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">295</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこどんちゃん! 大好きどんちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 295</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Don-chan! Daisuki Don-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52718" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">296</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっとこハッピー! ハムハムウエディング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 296</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottoko Happy! Hamham Wedding</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87880" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hamutaro Tottoko Uta Mata Tsuzuki dechu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120741" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
