<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5584" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2008-09-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Special A</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">S.A Special A-Class</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">S・A 特优生</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">S・A ~スペシャル・エー~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Special A</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Special A</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Special A</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7008" approval="303" total="329">Kaichou wa Maid-sama!</anime>
<anime id="4148" approval="48" total="58">Ouran Koukou Host Club</anime>
<anime id="2165" approval="8" total="16">School Rumble</anime>
<anime id="8719" approval="2" total="13">Haiyore! Nyaruko-san</anime>
<anime id="2835" approval="1" total="13">Hachimitsu to Clover</anime>
<anime id="10385" approval="1" total="10">Ao Haru Ride</anime>
<anime id="5053" approval="1" total="6">Lovely Complex</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="480721">I saw this on the basis that the main protagonist was called "2nd place".  I did enjoy Special A, even though it was filled with many cliche themes and characters.

Recommended for anyone who likes romance and comedy, but not get caught up in over 50 episodes where virtually nothing moves forward.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="424950">Just wanted to recommend an anime! ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="194504">A really nice comedy, made me laugh hard. Happy tear-drops guaranteed.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://special-a.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="1775" type="Series Composition">Hanada Jukki</name>
<name id="4360" type="Character Design">Nakahara Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="9166" type="Music">Kaida Shougo</name>
<name id="4360" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakahara Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="732" type="Animation Work">AIC</name>
<name id="3691" type="Direction">Miyao Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="7942" type="Original Work">Minami Maki</name>
<name id="44962" type="Music">Mitsunaga Rie</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shoujo manga by http://anidb.net/cr7942 [Minami Maki], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr30453 [Hana to Yume].
When http://anidb.net/ch3169 [Hikari] was little, she and her father liked to watch pro wrestling, and she became very good at it. She was the pride of her family until one day she was introduced to http://anidb.net/ch3170 [Kei], the son of her father`s friend. He instantly defeated her in wrestling, and started what would become Hikari`s major ambition to one day beat him. To do this she enrolled in Kei`s school, an ultra-elite school that costs her father a lot of money. This unusual school creates classes according to grades, and the top seven students become members of the Special A. They have their own building, and can optionally attend class. Hikari is usually the only one who does so, since she desperately wants to beat Kei in the test scores. The members of the Special A have been close friends since their first year.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2904">5.68</permanent>
<temporary count="2946">7.31</temporary>
<review count="4">6.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>52982.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8769</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3470</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4150</identifier>
<identifier>dkttzx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://special-a.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>S_·_A:_Special_A</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>S・A</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1366</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330186</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9678</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2138</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2008/special_a</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B0041HLXIG</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2670" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>school festival - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>THIS TAG NEEDS TO BE SPLIT:
into http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=6119&amp;reltb=eptb [school culture festival]
and http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=2665&amp;reltb=eptb [school sports festival]
The obligatory school festival (or cultural fair) with cosplay cafe, haunted house, theatre performance, and food booths cannot be missing in any school setting.
For good measure there may also be an athletics or sports festival in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2683" parentid="2812" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Hawaii</name>
<description>Hawaii is the 50th and most recent state to have joined the United States of America, having received statehood on August 21, 1959. Located in Oceania, Hawaii is the only U.S. state outside North America and the only one composed entirely of islands. It is the northernmost island group in Polynesia, occupying most of an archipelago in the central Pacific Ocean.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214273.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2777" parentid="2809" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>London</name>
<description>London is the capital and most populous city of both England and the United Kingdom. Standing on the River Thames in the south east of the island of Great Britain, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. It was founded by the Romans, who named it Londinium.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214379.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3508" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-09-26">
<name>school for the rich elite</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5840" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>birthday</name>
<description>All about the birthday celebration of at least one of the protagonists in this anime.
This includes a birthday party with a birthday cake and other food and presents — lots of them.</description>
<picurl>161031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3169" type="main character in" update="2011-01-15">
<rating votes="30">6.64</rating>
<name>Hanazono Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanazono Hikari is the protagonist of the story. She holds the 2nd position in school for having the best grades. Self-proclaimed as Kei Takishima`s greatest competitor, she is determined to beat him in any kind of competition. Stubborn, proud and hot-headed, Hikari never backs down from a challenge, especially one from Kei, because she is constantly looking for an opportunity to surpass him, though has never done so. A kind girl who always worries about others, Hikari sometimes lacks common sense. She is good at sports and academics, but she is very bad at teaching and cooking. Although she can handle her own in a fight (often against boys), Kei, nonetheless, gets irritated whenever she puts herself in danger. Although Hikari is rather sensitive to others, she is quite dense when it comes to love. She is oblivious to the romantic feelings Kei has for her, though everyone else knows that Kei is in love with her.</description>
<picture>18847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3170" type="main character in" update="2009-02-11">
<rating votes="28">7.48</rating>
<name>Takishima Kei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranked first in school, Kei is the son of the CEO of Takishima Corporation. As Hikari`s undefeated rival, he likes to refer to her as "Number Two", which never fails to provoke her. He has a photographic memory and the ability to do anything right on his first try. He usually prefers to do things on his own until Hikari shows him how much fun it can be to work together with others. Kei loves Hikari, a fact that he does not deny, and has loved her since they were children. However, he has not confessed his love to her because he knows that Hikari does not understand those feelings and would think that he is referring to a love between friends. Although he is stoic most of the time and always maintains a calm façade, things involving Hikari can bring intense anxiety out of him. It always bothers him whenever Hikari pushes herself too hard or causes trouble, but her strong will and determination are the reasons why he admires and respects her. He makes several attempts to express his feelings to Hikari, though is usually thwarted by some sort of misunderstanding on Hikari`s part.</description>
<picture>18848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3171" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-11">
<rating votes="8">3.38</rating>
<name>Yamamoto Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jun is ranked 3rd in school and is Megumi`s younger twin brother. The son of a music producer and a talented singer, Jun loves music more than anything else, but ironically has little talent for music. Usually quiet and kind-hearted, Jun has a split personality which he has concealed from everyone except Megumi and Ryuu. Triggered whenever he is kissed by a girl or receives a lot of affection, he becomes irresistible to nearly all women and is able to charm them effortlessly. His split personality resulted from an hypnotism program that Jun watched as a child and first emerged when he was still in grade six. During a date with a girl, he changed and all the other girls around him became mesmerised by him; this led the girl Jun was dating to hate him and call him disgusting. The only thing that can bring him back to his original self is by losing consciousness.</description>
<picture>18849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3172" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-11">
<rating votes="18">5.55</rating>
<name>Yamamoto Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Megumi is ranked 4th in school and is Jun`s older twin sister. She is the daughter of a famous vocalist and music producer and shares her brother`s love of music. A cute and nice girl who rarely joins in disputes, Megumi is always quiet and refuses to speak because she wants to save her voice for singing. She usually writes on a sketchpad to communicate with others, but will speak when deeply upset (usually in the form of a shout), which can generally have devastating after-effects. She rarely speaks to people normally on a consistent basis with the exception of Yahiro, who encourages her to sing.</description>
<picture>18850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3173" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-11">
<rating votes="14">7.66</rating>
<name>Karino Tadashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Innocent and carefree, Tadashi is ranked 5th in school. His mother, a fierce and intimidating woman, is the director of the school and the primary reason why he is in the SA; she told him he would be allowed to do whatever he wanted if he became a member of the SA. He suffers from wanderlust and frequently likes to vanish on some journey and return later for special school events. Tadashi is smarter than he looks and acts, though is usually the character who is most often comically attacked (frequently by Akira and Kei) because of his careless comments or reckless behaviour. He loves Akira, but often makes rude, weird, stupid or inappropriate comments that provoke her to beat him up.</description>
<picture>18851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3174" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-11">
<rating votes="17">6.77</rating>
<name>Toudou Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akira holds the 6th position in school and is the daughter of the owner of an airline company. She is very fond of Hikari and cute girls. Akira is very enthusiastic about her afternoon tea, and has even constructed her own kitchen on campus. Akira apparently loves Tadashi, but never seems to hold back when hitting him for teasing her.</description>
<picture>18852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3175" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-11">
<rating votes="8">5.69</rating>
<name>Tsuji Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuu holds the 7th position in school, although his test scores are a poor reflection of his intellectual prowess. He is in 7th place mainly because of the twins - Megumi tends to fall asleep and Jun becomes bored during the test, which results in Ryuu focusing the part of his attention on them instead of his own exam. He has been close to Megumi and Jun since they were very young; it is evident that he cares for the twins very much and that the three of them see each other as family. An even-tempered and kindhearted person, Ryuu loves animals and is good with children.</description>
<picture>18853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="403" picture="74821.jpg">Horie Kazuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19770" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-27">
<rating votes="9">5.34</rating>
<name>Saiga Yahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A carefree young man with a sinister side, Yahiro has known both Kei and Akira since they were children. He holds the distinction of having beaten Kei once during their childhood in a game of tag which Kei lost because Yahiro had locked the door to the roof to prevent Kei from winning. Yahiro attends Kokusen Academy, another high school, and is the heir to the Saiga Financial Group, a group that is even higher in status than the Takishima group. When he was young, Yahiro had no friends, for the most part because his attitude prevented him from making anyone smile or laugh and made them cry instead. He chose not to become friends with anyone until he met Sakura; at first, he had rejected her offer to become friends with her, but complied after they went through a lot of trouble to save the rabbit they were trying to bring back to its home in the mountains.
Yahiro has harboured a crush on Akira since childhood and is very protective of her, willing to use whatever means necessary to protect her, even if she hates him for it. It is this protective nature that made him drive away Akira`s only friend, Sayo, after he overheard her saying how she never liked Akira and was only her friend because Akira was rich and she enjoyed all the privileges and status that came with the friendship. Akira had believed that Yahiro had been jealous of her relationship with the "poor" kid she was playing with and never forgave Yahiro for ending her friendship with Sayo. He never told Akira the truth and has no intention of telling her. His hatred of "poor" people comes largely from this incident, which made him believe the poor exploit the rich. He eventually gives up his feelings for Akira, telling Tadashi that if he ever makes Akira cry, he will never forgive him. Because he still cares for Akira, Yahiro is initially unable to reciprocate Megumi`s feelings for him, but comes to see her as an important person to him and encourages her to sing.</description>
<picture>66611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29283" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-27">
<rating votes="3">5.42</rating>
<name>Takishima Sui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sui is Kei`s younger brother and resembles a younger version of Kei. Initially, he dislikes Kei because he finds living with him disgusting and thinks of him as a robot wearing human skin. Because Sui feels very inferior to his brother, who is good at everything, he believes that he cannot reach Kei`s level and he refuses to take his studies seriously. However, when he sees that even his "perfect" brother can become desperate and caring, Sui develops a huge brother complex. Sui likes to call Hikari "Stupid Girl", but approaches her frequently when he thinks that Kei needs help. He is in grade 6, class B at Hakusen Academy elementary school division.</description>
<picture>66604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29284" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-27">
<rating votes="4">3.16</rating>
<name>Takishima Satoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kei and Sui`s dad, age 36, who always looks young and baby-faced. He is very energetic and outgoing. Though he is the CEO of the Takishima company, he likes to escape from work and lets Kei handle his job, usually because people at business meetings tend not to take him seriously as a result of his young appearance. To Kei`s chagrin, his father also frequently tends to drag his son off to meetings, occasionally in foreign places. Satoru also possesses superb fighting skills and trained in his youth to be as strong as a pro-wrestler; he particularly enjoys Hikari`s company because it means they can fight, which Kei usually prevents from happening. He is a good friend of Hikari`s father, whom he met through their mutual love of pro-wrestling. Before marrying Midori and into the Takishima family, his surname was Utagawa.</description>
<picture>66607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29285" type="appears in" update="2011-02-27">
<name>Takishima Kaname</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kei`s grandfather, Kaname Takishima, is the head of the Takishima group and is a powerful man in a business world. However, he is rarely seen by others, including his own family members. He makes his first appearance in chapter 25, when he makes a phone call to Kei`s father. When Hikari speaks with him over the phone, he plants the idea in her head that Kei is burdened by her very presence. She meets him face to face in Chapter 59, when President Takishima tries to convince Hikari to transfer schools. He disapproves of Kei`s relationship with Hikari and makes many attempts to separate them, such as sending Aoi, arranging marriage meetings for Hikari in London, and arranging a marriage between Kei and a girl named Alisa. The President expresses a strong dislike of Hikari and the mere sight of her sickens him. It is eventually revealed that he feels that he and Hikari share similarities that will make the people they love suffer; as a result, he fears that if Kei remains with Hikari, he will endure the same fate as his grandfather did.</description>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29286" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<name>Hanazono Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hikari`s father is a carpenter and lives in the old shopping district of Tokyo. As a fan of pro-wrestling, he taught Hikari how to fight when she was a child. Through his interest in pro-wrestling, Jiro met Kei`s father and they introduced their children to one another when Hikari and Kei were six years old. After Hikari was defeated by Kei, she begged her father to allow her to enroll in the same schools as Kei in order to obtain the opportunity to defeat him. Headstrong and hot-headed like his daughter, Jiro agreed and has since supported her endeavours to defeat her rival. He and Kei`s father are friends.</description>
<picture>142322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29288" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<name>Hanazono Masako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hikari`s mother is a kind and good-natured person who seems to accept Hikari`s activities, whether it is taking care of Kei overnight or suddenly travelling to London, without too much fuss. She frequently welcomes Hikari`s friends to her house, usually without warning on Hikari`s part. However, she does lament that Hikari is unusually strong for a girl (such that she finds it difficult to even see Hikari as a girl at times) and absolutely refuses to allow her daughter to enter the kitchen, well aware of Hikari`s destructive inability to cook.</description>
<picture>142323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="334" picture="228623.jpg">Nabei Makiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29289" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-27">
<rating votes="7">5.44</rating>
<name>Ushikubo Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura is the daughter of the head of Ushikubo Medical Manufacturing Group and is Kei`s first marriage meeting (or omiai) partner to appear in the series. While she does not consider Kei her type, describing him as a "dark lord" rather than a "prince", she considers him a possible marriage partner because his abilities would be advantageous to her family`s business. Sakura hates dishonest people with a passion, and her family`s motto is centered around honesty and punishing/loathing dishonest people. Hikari`s straightforward and honest nature allows the girls to become friends. She attends the same school Yahiro does and sometimes plans stuff out with him (whether the plans be good or evil). Sakura falls in love with Jun at first sight, as he fit her ideal of someone who was a "prince", and accepts his split personality. She begins to date Jun soon after; however, because of her forceful personality, she is uncertain if Jun reciprocates her feelings until he admits to her that he does.</description>
<picture>66614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29290" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-27">
<rating votes="3">2.39</rating>
<name>Ogata Aoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoi Ogata is a junior secretary of President Takishima, Kei`s grandfather, and often serves as the President`s emissary. He is nineteen years old. Aoi has a cold and calm character, and has always been expressionless, not smiling even once, but is actually kindhearted and socially awkward in some respects. Like Kei, he has the ability to see something only once and memorize it, though his ability made him a victim of teasing as a child. He first met Kei when he was eight and Kei was five, and came to admire and deeply respect Kei, coming to see him as an almost kindred spirit. Aoi initially appears when he is sent to Japan from London, on orders to convince Kei to transfer to London, which had been planned by Kei`s grandfather. When Aoi discovers what is causing Kei to hesitate, Aoi tries to eliminate the problem: Hikari. He tries to threaten her, and Kei tries to beat Aoi up for threatening Hikari, but fails; even though he knows he is not going to convince Kei. Aoi then tries to bribe her but ends up having a cheque ripped to pieces by Hikari. At sometime, Hikari confronts Aoi and they both make up the "After School Takishima Fan Club," in which Aoi is the president and Hikari gets pictures of and writes up reports about Kei and sends them to Aoi. Afterwards, he realizes that he should not pressure Kei into the situation that he is not ready for and also realizes that he is most at peace when he sees Hikari and Kei smiling.</description>
<picture>66616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29291" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<name>Karino Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tadashi`s mother, age undisclosed, is the director of Private Hakusen Academy. Little is known about her and she never appears in front of the students. A woman whose actions speak for themselves, she is strict and intimidating. She is the primary reason why Tadashi entered the SA class and has threatened to punish him if he gets a lower rank than fifth place. In the past, she frequently punished Tadashi when he failed to please her and does not hesitate to do so in the present when he offends her, often extending the punishment to the rest of the SA if she deems fit. She and her husband were really popular in school when they were still students. As Tadashi stated, his parents always had a boyfriend and girlfriend.</description>
<picture>142320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29292" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<name>Saiga Chitose</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chitose is the younger brother of Yahiro and is about nine years old. He initially appears in (Chapter 13) Hawaii during the SA`s summer vacation when Ryuu (and by extension, the rest of the SA) is forced to entertain Chitose because he is the son of a client for his family. He is close to Ryuu, much to the chagrin of the twins, and it is implied that he has known Kei for a long time. Like his older brother, he dislikes poor people, which leads him to treat Hikari differently from others at first. However, when Hikari shows genuine concern for his well-being despite how badly he treated her, Chitose quickly becomes attached to her.</description>
<picture>142328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29293" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Oikawa Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When the S.A is punished by the director of the school as a result of Tadashi lying to her, they are forced to attend a regular high school where Akira meets Yui, a girl who resembles her childhood friend Sayo. Initially wary, Akira avoids contact with her, but eventually apologizes and befriends her. However, Akira`s fear that Yahiro would break up her newfound friendship results in Akira using extreme measures to protect Yui, who begins to feel awkward around her friends. When Yahiro investigates her for Akira`s sake, he discovers that Yui stole some of Akira`s jewellery and threatens her so that she will stay away from Akira. Though Yui had done so reluctantly because her family had financial issues that were forcing them to move, she agrees to Yahiro`s demand, but she feels that she needs to say goodbye to Akira and almost gets hit by a car in the process. Yahiro saves her and they end up in Yahiro`s home, where Akira finds them. When Akira believes that Yahiro has hurt Yui, Yui clarifies that Yahiro saved her and apologizes to Akira for stealing her jewellery. Happy that they are still friends, Akira ends up helping Yui`s family and they keep in touch.</description>
<picture>142321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29294" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-27">
<rating votes="2">1.62</rating>
<name>Kakei Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First appearing in chapter five, Hajime Kakei is the Student President at Hakusenkan and holds first place in the class 2-A. He is frequently hospitalized for feeling weak and relies on using money to get what he wants. He begins to send various challenges to the SA when nobody appears at his talk show; since none of the SA members wanted to attend his show, nobody else in the student body wanted to either. Because of Hikari`s open and kind nature, he seems to develop a crush on her, though is always scared off by Kei before he gets any chance to express his feelings. He is not very popular among his classmates, most of whom do not share his animosity towards the SA.</description>
<picture>66619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="408" picture="17255.jpg">Fujita Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29295" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<name>Takahashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5666" picture="157275.jpg">Satou Yuudai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29296" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<name>Nakamura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He hates SA, because he thinks they look down upon others and that they receive unjust treatment. On one occasion he claims they cheat on their academic tests.</description>
<picture>142324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11240" picture="223407.jpg">Fujii Keisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29297" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<name>Oogawara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="71" picture="171537.jpg">Ichiki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29298" type="appears in" update="2013-09-17">
<name>Matsumoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3797" picture="65487.jpg">Matsuo Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29300" type="appears in" update="2013-09-10">
<name>Maa-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3797" picture="65487.jpg">Matsuo Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29301" type="appears in" update="2013-09-10">
<name>Yukipon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142839.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29302" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<name>Yoshikawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3797" picture="65487.jpg">Matsuo Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29303" type="appears in" update="2013-09-13">
<name>Nagai Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3797" picture="65487.jpg">Matsuo Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59398" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<name>Sakura no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Only mentioned as Sakura`s father; no first name is given.
He is very supportive of his daughter love hunt.
He is also a fan of pro wrestling and old sempai to Takishima Satoru, who tends to do everything asked.</description>
<picture>142319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="278" picture="44088.jpg">Ootake Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59548" type="appears in" update="2013-09-08">
<name>Hanazono Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanazono Atsushi is Hikari`s older brother.</description>
<picture>142660.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59549" type="appears in" update="2013-09-08">
<name>Takishima Kei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Takishima Kei.</description>
<picture>142675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59550" type="appears in" update="2013-09-08">
<name>Hanazono Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Hanazono Hikari.</description>
<picture>142676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59646" type="appears in" update="2013-09-11">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Toudou Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59647" type="appears in" update="2013-09-11">
<name>Saiga Yahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59648" type="appears in" update="2013-09-11">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Sayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59649" type="appears in" update="2013-09-11">
<name>Yui no Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yui`s mother.</description>
<picture>142880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9202" picture="46799.jpg">Abe Sachie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75079" type="appears in" update="2015-05-10">
<name>Special A</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Special A, or A-class and is more commonly referred to as S.A. It is a class group consisting of the top 7 students of Hakusen Academy.</description>
<picture>173211.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="88809" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光・彗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hikari &amp; Kei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari Kei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89875" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89876" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Pre-Broadcast Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89924" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プライド・プロレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pride &amp; Pro-Wrestling</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`incontro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pride Pro Wres</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89925" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにぎり・まごころ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rice Ball &amp; Sincerity</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Polpette e premure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onigiri Magokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89926" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兄弟・先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brothers &amp; Teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Due fratelli e un`insegnante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoudai Sensei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89927" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祭り・勝負</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Festival &amp; Challenge</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il festival della discordia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matsuri Shoubu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89928" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">招待状・雑賀邸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invitation &amp; Saiga Estate</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Invito a casa Saiga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoutaijou Saiga Yashika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89929" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敏感・鈍感</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sensitive &amp; Thickheaded</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sensibilità e ottusità</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Binkan Donkan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90858" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅・犬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trip &amp; Dog</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il gioco delle parti</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabi Inu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90913" update="2013-09-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90968" update="2008-05-23">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">fandubbed op</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91115" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">別送・手紙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Villa &amp; Letter</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`esca</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bessou Tegami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91201" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">殿・竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anchor &amp; Ryu</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una sfida per Ryu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tono Ryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91483" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女・彼氏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girlfriend &amp; Boyfriend</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fidanzati</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo Kareshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91589" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">守りたい・ごめんね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protecting You &amp; Sorry</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ti proteggerò</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamoritai Gomenne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91590" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法・友達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magic &amp; Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Amici e magie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou Tomodachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91591" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高熱・情熱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">High Fever &amp; Passion</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Febbre e passione</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kounetsu Jounetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91982" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仁義・上等</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Justice &amp; Right On</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Primo appuntamento</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jingi Joutou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91983" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">好き・キス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Love You &amp; Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Corteggiamento</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suki Kiss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91984" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠慮・笑顔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Restraint &amp; Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Enryo Egao</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91985" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東堂・狩野</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toudou &amp; Karino</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Akira e Tadashi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toudou Karino</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91986" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌声・悪者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Voice &amp; Scoundrel</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un cuore gentile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utagoe Warumono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92047" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スイッチ・崖っぷち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Switch &amp; Edge</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Switch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Switch Gakeppuchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92368" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵う・叶う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evenly Matched &amp; Wish Granted</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Distanze</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanau Kanau</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92369" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋・変</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love &amp; Strange</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sentimenti</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92504" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SA・FA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SA &amp; FA</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un duro colpo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SA FA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92591" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">華園光・滝島彗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hanazono Hikari &amp; Takishima Kei</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Hikari Hanazono e Kei Takishima</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanazono Hikari Takishima Kei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92929" update="2008-09-08">
<epno type="5">P2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2008-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Fandubbed OP 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119317" update="2013-09-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119318" update="2013-09-17">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119319" update="2013-09-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
