<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5623" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2008-06-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Neo Angelique Abyss</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ネオアンジェリーク アビス</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">NAA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ネオアンジェリーク Abyss</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Neo Angelique Abyss</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5988" type="Sequel">Neo Angelique Abyss: Second Age</anime>
<anime id="3173" type="Other">Angelique</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.gamecity.ne.jp/neoromance/tv/neo/index.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="845" type="Animation Work">Yumeta Company</name>
<name id="2178" type="Series Composition">Yamada Yuka</name>
<name id="930" type="Original Work">Koei</name>
<name id="2302" type="Music">Nanase Hikaru</name>
<name id="22784" type="Direction">Katagai Shin</name>
<name id="4346" type="Character Design">Yura Kairi</name>
<name id="7768" type="Character Design">Fujioka Maki</name>
<name id="7768" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujioka Maki</name>
<name id="5802" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tsunaki Aki</name>
</creators>
<description>While the young Angelique lives out her days peacefully in her school, attacks from the monstrous Thanatos has been increasing everywhere else. Two Purifiers show up one day, men with the power to exterminate the Thanatos. One of them, Nyx, attempts to convince Angelique to join them in their work, as she has the power to be the only female Purifier. As Angelique hesitates, a Thanatos shows up in their school. Nyx and the other Purifier, Rayne, fight a losing battle. With her classmates falling prey to the Thanatos, and the Purifiers beaten to submission, Angelique`s desire to save everyone awakens. She became the only female Purifier in their land of Arcadia, the one known as the Queen`s Egg.
Source: MAL</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="467">3.63</permanent>
<temporary count="472">6.26</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>6979.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9068</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3615</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4198</identifier>
<identifier>wfkrry</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/contents/neoangelique/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gamecity.ne.jp/neoromance/tv/neo/index.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Neo_Angelique_Abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ネオアンジェリーク</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1365</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330185</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9795</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2159</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2170</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2008/neoangelique</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29016" type="appears in" update="2011-02-21">
<name>Erwin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="410" picture="228116.jpg">Aoki Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33548" type="appears in" update="2011-06-18">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Kai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kai was the first and best friend of J.D.. It was Kai who showed J.D. how to smile.</description>
<picture>73737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="565" picture="171984.jpg">Takagi Motoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40951" type="main character in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="5">6.85</rating>
<name>Angelique</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A charming, kindhearted girl. When she was a child, her village was attacked by Thanatos and she lost both her parents. This inspired and encouraged her more than anything to pursue her ambition to be a doctor when she grew up as she wants to help others and save lives. This is why she agreed to go with Nyx to fight Thanatos with the other Purifying Ability as she felt that this way, she would be able to save more lives than as a doctor.
She has a modest and reserved personality, but she also possesses inner strength and can be severe. It has always been her wish to help others as she, like her parents, always places others before herself.
In the second season, she learns how to use a sword. It has been revealed later on in the second season that in order to save Arcadia and Nyx she must sacrifice the life she has as a normal girl among her loving friends and become the Prophesied Queen, protecting Arcadia yet from far away.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>169334.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40952" type="main character in" update="2015-02-24">
<name>Erenfried</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a scientist that works at the Foundation who bears deep hatred for Rayne, since he always got all the attention. He gets angry or annoyed when Rayne simply calls him "Eren", telling him that he has a name and it is "Erenfried", and responds by calling Rayne "Professor".
Jet takes orders from Erenfried and Director Yorgo, whose attention Erenfried always intends to get. Erenfried admires and is grateful to Director Yorgo because he offered him a place as a researcher in the Foundation and assigned funding to his project.
In season 2 when Yorgo is imprisoned (due to mistakes of Erenfried with the Jinx project), he wants to rescue him. He somewhat befriends Angelique and company in season 2, when JD rescues him from the organization`s prison, and stays with the group for a while.
He also realizes that "Artifacts/Jasper Dolls" have hearts when JD rescues him from jail.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>169418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40953" type="main character in" update="2012-01-30">
<name>J.D.</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>JD is a Jasper Doll, a type of artifact. He Is referred to as a "defective product" by Jet. JD also said that he (Jet) is just like him (himself).
It seems that JD belonged to the Foundation, but somehow managed to escape and is now wanted. Hence, he avoided meeting the Foundation as much as he could, for fear of being taken away by them by force.
He always wants to see Angelique smile. He enjoys baking for others, often cookies or scones.
He fights with a pair of tonfa against Thanatos but possesses melee skills as well.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>2076.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40954" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-30">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Jet</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Like J.D., he is also an artifact made by the Foundation in a desperate attempt to make another Artifact like J.D., after they "lost" him during the mysterious fire. The fact that Jet and J.D. are both artifacts makes them "brothers".
In season 2, he takes order from Mathias. However, Mathias abandons him as he failed to complete his mission to capture Angelique, the Queen`s Egg. Mathias tells him to "go wherever he wants". Without a master and orders to follow, he was lost and attempted to carry out the last order he had been given (to capture Angelique), when he came across Angelique and her friends. He and J.D. began to fight, but he left after he saw that it was upsetting Angelique.
He then showed up where they were repairing the Ship of Stars and tells Erenfried to deactivate him because he was beginning to have feelings (primarily around Angelique) and he considered himself "defective". Erenfried refused because it meant that Jet was developing a heart and told him to act according to his own will from now on. Therefore he helps out in the repairs of the Ship Of Stars, but in the morning of the departure, he sacrificed his life to remove the bomb that Erebos planted in the ship.
However, he seems to have been saved by Erenfried in the last episode of season 2 (he is seen at the very end in a capsule being taken care of).
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>2092.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40955" type="main character in" update="2012-01-30">
<name>Nyx</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a mysterious nobleman and quite a gentleman. Rather than calling Angelique by her name, he often calls her "mademoiselle". He likes playing the piano and drinking tea.
In season 2 he is fully possessed by Erebos and seems to want to help Angelique and the others, but cannot always control his condition. Inside him, his real self and Erebos coexist.
He has lived for 200 years due to Erebos. When he was younger, the ship his family and him were in got caught in a fierce storm. As Nyx was drowning, he pleaded for his life, saying that he would do anything. Erebos heard him and saved him, possessing him, but Nyx`s parents drowned. This is why Nyx fears and hates the sound of the sea as it was when Erebos first possessed him. He is the core that Erebos uses to send Thanatos into the world.
The only hope he had to get rid of Erebos was the Queen`s Egg, so he traveled all over the world and found Angelique. When she becomes the Queen, Nyx wishes for her to give him a peaceful death.
Nyx blames himself for making Angelique suffer, taking away her home and parents but Angelique says it was Erebos who did that and that Nyx was the one who gave her many precious things, including a place to belong to.
He fights Thanathos with a whip.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>2066.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40956" type="main character in" update="2012-01-30">
<name>Hyuuga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A former Silver Knight and also an Aube Hunter. He will protect Angelique with all his being, even in exchange of his life. He refers to Angelique as "Angelique-sama" (Lady Angelique).
He is often seen practicing his spear skills during his free time outside the Mansion. At the end of the first season, Angelique gave him an "order" that in future, he was to simply call her Angelique as she felt that they were friends. Hyuuga has a hard time trying to say Angelique`s name without saying it in a formal form in the beginning.
In Season 2 he suffers from seasickness but eventually overcomes it.
He wields a spear in battle against Thanatos.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>2070.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40957" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-24">
<name>Bernard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A reporter who always writes the truth. Roche sells a lot of his pictures to Bernard, since he`s his tipster.
He recognizes Angelique`s necklace when she loses it after being kidnapped by Jet and seems to be hiding something.
Later on he is revealed to be a son of Angelique`s relative whom she stayed with after her parents were killed. He left to go work in the media and never saw Angelique again until now. Angelique calls him "nii-san" (big brother), after she finds out who he is.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>169367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40958" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-30">
<name>Mathias</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also known as Lord Mathias or Mathias-sama, he is the Leader of the Religious Organization which supports the Knights of the Silver Tree.
It is also revealed that he is a fake Leader that was only chosen for his exceptional memory, because a new true leader hadn`t been born at the time that the previous leader died.
The Organization is trying to kill him so that René can take the title, but in Season 2`s episode 5, he kills the High Elder. He places an Artifact chip created by Erenfried on his neck to receive powers. Due to the chip, half of Mathias is his own self, half is controlled by the chip (therefore by Thanatos).
In season 2, he was killed by Nyx/Erebos when trying to protect René.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>2091.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40959" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-30">
<name>Rene</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He lives in the Holy City of Celestizam and is allowed to move about freely within its walls but he is forbidden to go outside the city. He often comments how he is a "caged bird" to Mathias, who is his mentor.
His second appearance in the anime is in episode 6, where he rescues Angelique from the persistent journalist Roche, who keeps trying to take photos of "The Queen`s Egg" to get a scoop.
He is revealed to be the future and true leader of the Religious Order. He declares that he will unite his power with Angelique`s to help save the world of Arcadia.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>2079.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40960" type="main character in" update="2012-01-30">
<rating votes="4">9.42</rating>
<name>Rayne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A smart, stylish boy. He is impulsive, but extremely capable and reliable. He also has feelings for Angelique.
In the past he worked as a scientist and a professor, being an important member of the Foundation with his older brother Yorgo.
Rayne is referred to as "that guy" (ano hito) by Erenfried as Erenfried has a particular dislike for Rayne. Erenfried has always been jealous of all the attention that Rayne got from Yorgo and other researches in the Foundation when he worked there. He gets annoyed whenever referred to as "Professor" Rayne, which Erenfried does on purpose, and usually responds by calling him simply "Eren".
Rayne later reveals his Purifying Ability is not natural and is the result of self-experimentation.
He fights Thanatos with a gun.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>2078.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40961" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-30">
<name>Roche</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roche is a respectable journalist who loves money and women.
He has never taken photos without receiving a payment for them, but in episode 9, he sent the photos he took of Angelique - which he had originally intended to sell to Bernard for money - to Angelique herself. This was done out of kindness when he realized that Angelique, like himself, was an orphan and he didn`t feel that he should sell her information to others. He, however, did not regret making that decision and was a bit confused and surprised at himself as that was the first time he had taken photos of other people without charging for them.
The "secret date" he went on with Angelique was not a real date. He happened to see Angelique on the streets after Angelique ran from Sally and Hannah, since she was upset about her best friends refusing to accept the truth (the fact that the Jinx machines were destroying many people`s homes and even taking away some lives in the process of destroying Thanatos). He called it a "secret date" but in truth, he wanted to cheer up Angelique when he saw just how upset she was.
He eventually develops romantic feelings towards Angelique.
He is shown throwing knives in his fight with Erebos/Nyx.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>2083.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87004" type="appears in" update="2017-01-07">
<name>Rouki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="89113" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡の少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miracle Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki no Shoujo</title>
<summary>Nyx goes to Angelique`s school to ask her to aid him in protecting the world of Thanatos. While fighting the Thanatos Angelique discovers that she has a special power.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510364</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="89114" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テーブルの下で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Under the Table</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Table no Shita de</title>
<summary>Angelique and Rayne set off on their first mission to Rayne`s hometown to destroy a few Thanatos. During their mission, they meet another Purifying Ability Compatible, J.D. who helps them in their mission.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510366</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="89870" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89871" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89975" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀色の騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Silver Knight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giniro no Kishi</title>
<summary>Angelique and Rayne are sent to destroy Thanatos on the Ship of Stars. When few Thanatos escape from the ship, Hyuga, a man which Angelique met earlier helps to destroy them. It is revealed he is also a Purifying Ability Compatible and vows to protect Angelique.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510368</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="89976" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒の襲撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro no Shuugeki</title>
<summary>Bernard, a reporter for the Wodon Times, sets off to Hidamari Mansion to investigate the rumored “Queen`s Egg”. When Angelique is alone in the field Jet appears. Rayne, Nyx, J.D., and Hyuga show up fight back against the Thanatos and Jet while Angelique shows her power healing light.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510370</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90616" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決意の旅路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Journey of Determination</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketsui no Tabiji</title>
<summary>The group, now referred to as the Aube Hunters, set off to Celestizam to meet with the Religious Leader. On the way there they make a short stop off at the Melrose Girl`s Academy then continue on to a small town that welcomes them for the night. While there Angelique is put to the test to perform to people’s expectations and questions if she really can do it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510372</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90617" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖都参詣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Visiting the Holy Capital</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiyoshito Sankei</title>
<summary>The Aube Hunters enter Celestizam while Hyuga stays outside. Angelique has an audience with the Religious leader and sorts out her emotions. When leaving she runs into Roche, which persistently tries to get an exclusive interview. Angelique escapes with the help of Rene and is taken to his secret place the Silver Tree. Meanwhile J.D is starting to have a problem and is trying to desperately hide it from his friends
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510374</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90618" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幸せの種</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seed of Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase no Tane</title>
<summary>J.D. mysteriously collapses and is found out to be an artifact. Angelique and Hyuga set out to find his cure located in J.D’s past in a town called Kozu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510376</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90619" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジンクス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jinx</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinx</title>
<summary>The consortium has created a new weapon to battle the Thanatos. The orb hunters are invited to see a demonstration of Jinx`s awesome power.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510378</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90865" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウォードンの休日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Day Off in Wodon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wodon no Kyuujitsu</title>
<summary>Angelique takes a day off to visit friends, whom she runs away from when they have a fight. Roche finds Angelique and takes her out on a date.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510380</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90866" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時の輪舞曲(ロンド)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time`s Rondo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki no Rondo</title>
<summary>The Jinx are taking longer and longer to destroy the Thanatos. Nyx takes Angelique to a ball, where some questions are raised about Nyx`s past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510382</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90867" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗雲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dark Clouds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">An`un</title>
<summary>Thanatos attack Jinx and destroy them. More Thanatos appear at Angelique`s old school and Sally and Hannah are missing along with a photographer who turns out to be Bernard. The boys fight the Thanatos while Angelique looks for her friends, whom she finds cornered by a Thanatos, Angelique with the help of a broken Jinx kills the Thanatos, but as the episode ends, Angelique is kidnapped, by Jet.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510384</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91670" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">囚われのアンジェリーク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Captured Angelique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toraware no Angelique</title>
<summary>Agelique was kidnapped by Jet. She was brought in the Artifact Building. She was being experimented on by Erenfried. Later, the Aube Hunter came to save her. They have fought the jinx but they didn`t have enought power to defeat Jet. But hearing the voices of them, Angelique with her power help them to win. At last they won. They once united but suddenly Yorgo have a important talk to Rayne. Yorgo told him that Ange can save the world with her power. But Rayne was opposed of Yorgo. Angelique found Rayne and have a talk. Rayne was afraid that Angelique would not live but he let her decide if she wants to save the world with her power even it is exchange of her life. Agelique was able to decide she would do it even if she would die.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510386</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91765" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰還, そして...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return, and Then...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan, Soshite...</title>
<summary>The Aube Hunters agree to help Hyuga protect Angelique. They plan on releasing Angelique`s Purifying power. This will cause all the Thanatos to come and attack Angelique and then Hyuga and the Aube Hunters can destroy them all.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>510388</identifier>
<identifier>neo-angelique-abyss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116564" update="2010-03-07">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ある意味, 奇跡の少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In a Way, a Miracle Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aru Imi, Kiseki no Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119888" update="2010-07-12">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベルちゃんロシュくんの襲撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beru-chan and Roche-kun`s Attack.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beru-chan Roche-kun no Shuugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131013" update="2011-06-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131014" update="2011-06-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
