<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5656" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2008-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Macademi Wasshoi!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Magician`s Academy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Makademi Wasshoi!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">魔法学园MA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">まかでみWAっしょい!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4146" approval="5" total="14">Zero no Tsukaima</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="74379">suprisingly good</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="2975">Ecchi, light-hearted humor, some slapstick, no real villans, good show if you don`t expect to much.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="219832">Must see for people who like ecchi</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.mxtv.co.jp/makademi/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="788" type="Animation Work">Zexcs</name>
<name id="1785" type="Original Work">Sakaki Ichirou</name>
<name id="9160" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ookuma Takaharu</name>
<name id="12428" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugitou Sayuri</name>
<name id="7944" type="Chief Animation Direction">Isono Satoru</name>
<name id="4073" type="Music">Hasegawa Tomoki</name>
<name id="4152" type="Series Composition">Hasegawa Katsumi</name>
<name id="8492" type="Direction">Kanasaki Takaomi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr1785 [Sakaki Ichirou], with illustrations by http://anidb.net/cr34275 [Blade].
The Magician`s Academy, that normal people cannot attend, is located in a magical land. http://anidb.net/ch1645 [Hasegawa Takuto] is one of the students at the magic academy. During a summoning spell exam, he accidentally creates a girl named http://anidb.net/ch1648 [Tanarot], who happens to hold unheard of magical power. Fortunately Tanarot professes undying loyalty to her creator much to his embarrassment.
Notice: The DTV version is heavily censored, almost like http://anidb.net/a5029 [Kodomo no Jikan], but the at-x TV broadcast will be partially uncensored. The DVD version with the 1st volume, released on December 25th 2008, will have the fully uncensored version.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1534">4.89</permanent>
<temporary count="1551">6.92</temporary>
<review count="2">5.74</review>
</ratings>
<picture>13444.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9697</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3654</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4212</identifier>
<identifier>gjsytn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mxtv.co.jp/makademi/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Magician's_Academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>まじしゃんず・あかでみい#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1475</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331437</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2488" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>multiple personality disorder</name>
<description>Multiple personality disorder is a psychiatric diagnosis that describes a condition in which a single person displays multiple distinct identities or personalities (known as alter egos or alters), each with its own pattern of perceiving and interacting with the environment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4171" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-10-06">
<name>claymation</name>
<description>Short for clay animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4352" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-11">
<name>censored uncensored version</name>
<description>Even the DVD and Blu-ray releases do not let you see everything you were expecting to, and you will have to live with censorship in the show. That normally applies to fan service, but may also apply to gore and violence. A very common example is characters without nipples, as in http://anidb.net/a6083 [KissXSis]; in other cases, something such as steam or foam stays in the camera`s way, like in http://anidb.net/a6531 [Kanamemo]. In some shows, the censorship in the disk releases is even stronger than in the TV version, while others may use creative censorship as a replacement for the removed fan service or even as a joke.
This does not apply to censorship of what Japanese pornography laws still require to be censored.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1645" type="main character in" update="2008-12-27">
<rating votes="8">3.88</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Takuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2313.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1646" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-27">
<rating votes="6">6.12</rating>
<name>Kirishima Futaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1648" type="main character in" update="2009-11-03">
<rating votes="17">6.43</rating>
<name>Tanarot</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1652" type="main character in" update="2008-12-27">
<rating votes="15">5.06</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Suzuho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="184" picture="23381.jpg">Miyazaki Ui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1664" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="14">6.57</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Suzuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="184" picture="23381.jpg">Miyazaki Ui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1676" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="15">5.76</rating>
<name>Hapsiel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mid class level 3 angel who is a masochist and a former teacher of the magical academy. 20 years prior the story begins, he was a tyrant as he would give anyone a horrible kiss to his students whom he adores or to be challenged and finally being sealed away by the students to evade his horrible love. Later, his seal was broken due to metalys accidenttaly punched george to brake it.</description>
<picture>16218.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1690" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="4">3.15</rating>
<name>Sagami Kyouju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Described as being "Professor and also adviser of the discipline committee. He uses his droid army." A child-size professor with the unique ability to separate his head from his body, which he uses to instruct his class while his body writes on the board. However this has shown to be a problem as well as they tend to separate from any attack.</description>
<picture>16239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1694" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="15">8.63</rating>
<name>Falce</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also known as "Falcé the Variablewand". When Falcé is in her `humanoid` form, she has the appearance of a tall, well endowed woman with a pair of spiraled horns on either side of her head. She has a very ditsy and naive personality. Despite this, she is incredibly powerful (Magical power estimated to be around 58,000), able to use magic even when Suzuho is in her "Midnight Blue Vampire" form. She was the last and greatest masterpiece of a powerful dark magician and alchemist who died long ago leaving her alone without even naming her. When Takuto stumbled across her chamber during a training session, Falcé took him captive. After fighting with Tanarotte and Suzuho, she was defeated. Later she returned, having accepted Takuto as her new master. In episode 4 she uses her powers to transform into many class related objects (mechanical pencil, etc), though she transforms to her original form as a staff for Takuto, and also Tanarot describes her as being Takuto`s Dutch wife.</description>
<picture>16244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1695" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="1">4.06</rating>
<name>Kirishima Hazuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Described as being "His face is Yakuza. Attacked by his sister." He is the twin brother to his sister Futaba and knows about his sister`s crush on Takuto. He always figures out a way to add in his sentence hints of his sister`s attraction to Takuto, even though every time he does Futaba has no qualms of hitting him hard (to the point his body impression is left on a stone wall). Though, she seems to hit him after he speaks about anything</description>
<picture>16245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="185" picture="228625.jpg">Ishigami Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1696" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="6">4.64</rating>
<name>Metallis</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A robotic student that is powered by magic. Because of this he is heavily affected to Suzuho`s magic stealing ability. He is initially hinted to be homosexual and attracted to his friend George, although technically he doesn`t have a gender. However, it turns out that he is actually in love with the Midnight Blue Vampire, Suzuho`s other personality, and he is willing to risk his own life to save hers. Though he knows she has feelings for Takuto, he keeps trying to impress her though he needs to run off a separate battery system to be able to chat with her.</description>
<picture>16248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1698" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="19">8.53</rating>
<name>Eneus the Vergest</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Eitarou`s familiar described as being "She is a relatively ethical character in the show." She is actually a type of demonic beast, called Vergest, and she is known to be the strongest among them all. Eitarou has her dressed up as a dog-girl maid and is very devoted to him, but will not hesitate to harm him if he strays off because of his perverted ways. She is a very capable fighter, able to fight on-par with Tanarot with the ability to make copies of herself and fights with a spear which also has a broom on the other end. It is hinted that she might have feelings for Takuto as she was annoyed that he referred to her as a "mother figure" and has a picture of when they went out on their "date" stickered to her weapon.
Sakuma even made a bunch of miniature versions of her. All of them function properly except for one that is comically seen tripping and needing the help of the others and even a giant robot version. He is proud on how detailed he is at designing these robots from the same type of underwear she uses to the placement of her birthmarks, only to be harmed by Eneus before he describes where that birthmark is. Eneus is constantly lecturing him about his hobbies.</description>
<picture>68253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1702" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="2">3.00</rating>
<name>Mega Eneus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>16251.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1703" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-03">
<rating votes="11">7.39</rating>
<name>Sakuma Ataro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Described as being "Most stuff unknown Part-time teacher here and also very skilled magician." He is an easy-going teacher that helps out Takuto and Suzuho. He is clearly a powerful magician, evidence of this is when he easily broke the barrier that Miyabe and Synclavia erected and even overpowered them. He is also well-knowledge of the use of magic, since he was able to summon a black demon lord to do his bidding. However, his personality and behavior is a bit of a pervert, and also an otaku and often joining in on Professor Franken Stein`s perverted schemes. He appears to prefer the paws of animal girls to the point that he even made battle gloves for Tanarot in the shape of cat`s paws, and maid outfits which is why he dressed up Eneus, Miyabe, and Synclavia as maids. So much in fact that he works with his perverted hobbies more than he does actual work, as stated by Eneus.</description>
<picture>16252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1704" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="8">5.65</rating>
<name>Synclavia the Siren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1705" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="13">6.86</rating>
<name>Miyabi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1706" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-03">
<rating votes="4">5.39</rating>
<name>Trincia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Described as being "Virtural God in a PC. She works as a coach, guide and examiner for students." She appears to be a little girl in the computer system that helps students with their exams. Takuto usually calls her Trin or Torin.</description>
<picture>16255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="188" picture="1804.gif">Kimura Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1707" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="6">5.45</rating>
<name>Agaliarept</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1710" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Super Robot Metallis</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1711" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="8">4.37</rating>
<name>Gabriel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16259.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1712" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="6">5.01</rating>
<name>Fermi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1723" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-29">
<rating votes="3">3.59</rating>
<name>George</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9672" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-03-12">
<rating votes="29">7.97</rating>
<name>Midarezaki Kyouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The `mother` of Midarezaki family. She is twenty years old, however, she has an appearance of a little girl with cat`s ear and tail. Her real name is `Kyoukya Eaeriaea`, and she used to be worshiped by the people of an underground kingdom named `Shangri-la`, however, she ran away because she felt something was missing from her life.</description>
<picture>44559.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9674" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-03-12">
<name>Midarezaki Ouka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The `father` of Midarezaki family who is forced to participate in Cozy Family Operation. Sensible and collected, however, he is often teased and mocked by Kyouka. He lost his parents at the age of three, and has no memory before then. He is also the head of the operations department of `Supernatural Phenomenon Treatment Bureau`.</description>
<picture>44562.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19447" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-10">
<rating votes="3">4.65</rating>
<name>Finea</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30600" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-20">
<rating votes="2">2.71</rating>
<name>Frankram Stein Kyouju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A professor that is also perverted like Sakuma but is more vocal about it, even describing why girls dressed in animal cosplay are the best as one of his class lectures.</description>
<picture>183190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80451" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>O-mura</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80452" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Tomoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1444" picture="172066.jpg">Masu Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80453" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Homura 1-gata</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="633" picture="33549.jpg">Inoue Norihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80454" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Acrobat</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80455" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Anireon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80456" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Izumo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80457" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Ganto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2474" picture="228619.jpg">Endou Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80458" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Galactica Erefanga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80459" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Satou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80460" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Suzuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5632" picture="158531.jpg">Sugisaki Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80461" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Dwarf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80462" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Baltia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80463" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Fablom Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80464" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Mariela</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80465" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Michael</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80466" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Kawai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="33" picture="133462.jpg">Kimura Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80467" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Takamasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80468" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Mikaruya Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80469" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Toshiaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="17705" picture="188509.jpg">Asari Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80470" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Hasegawa Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80471" type="appears in" update="2016-02-20">
<name>Hasegawa Akiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="569" picture="242492.jpg">Takeda Hana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109426" type="appears in" update="2020-04-14">
<name>Tanarotte</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takuto`s childhood Cat that inspired him his familiar after her.</description>
<picture>246227.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="93322" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">1.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんか女の子出てきちゃったんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Somehow a Girl Came Out</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Onnanoko Dete Kichattandesu kedo.</title>
<summary>In a realm which exists right next to reality but no ordinary people can see, there is the "Magician’s Academy" – the school for today`s wizards and witches who live between the realms, hiding their true identities while they are among us. Takuto Hasegawa looks like a high school boy who embodies the word "ordinary" in every sense, but he is actually a wizard in the making who secretly attends the Academy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568632</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93533" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんか大変なことになっちゃってるんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Somehow, What You`re Doing Became a Serious Case.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Taihen na Koto ni Nacchatterundesu kedo.</title>
<summary>Despite being a wizard, Takuto still has a lot of things to deal with.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568634</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93534" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんか魔王まで出てきちゃったんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Somehow Got a Demon Lord Coming Out</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Maou made Dete Kichattandesu kedo.</title>
<summary>With Takuto injured, it`s up to Tanarotte to save the day!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568636</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93728" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんか犯罪みたいなんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This is Somewhat Like a Crime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Hanzai Mitai nandesu kedo.</title>
<summary>Tanarotte becomes a transfer student at Takuto`s school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568638</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93881" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんか復活とかしちゃったんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Love Of The Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Fukkatsu to ka Shichattandesu kedo.</title>
<summary>In the magic world, Metallis learns about love.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568640</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93882" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんか蒼いエンジョウなんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Blue Angel Happening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Aoi Enjou nandesu kedo.</title>
<summary>Metallis has trouble understanding love.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568642</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95276" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんかファッションショーなんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Somehow A Fashion Show</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Fashion Show nandesu kedo.</title>
<summary>A mysterious figure, Agarin, suddenly buys an entire manga section
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568644</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95535" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんかメイドに幽霊にメカなんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Somehow a Maid, a Ghost and a Mecha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Maid ni Yuurei ni Mecha nandesu kedo.</title>
<summary>A ghost suddenly appears and scares Agarin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568646</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95675" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんか可能性の問題なんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Somehow a Matter of Possibilities</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Kanousei no Mondai nandesu kedo.</title>
<summary>The sleeping child has awoken.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568652</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95676" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんか雪山はいろいろ招くんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Somehow, the Vacant, Snowy Peaks Invite Multitudes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Yukiyama wa Iroiro Manekundesu kedo.</title>
<summary>Three mysterious magicians appear and cause havok
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568650</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95677" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんか妹が来てデートなんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Somehow, a Sister Came &amp; It`s a Date</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Imouto ga Kite Date nandesu kedo.</title>
<summary>Snow finally falls and everyone is excited!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568648</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95873" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんか聖夜爆走なんですけど.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Somehow a Rampage on the Holy Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanka Seiya Bakusou nandesu kedo.</title>
<summary>Things in the real world are starting to change.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568654</identifier>
<identifier>magicians-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="102685" update="2010-09-04">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-11-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Special Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102686" update="2009-05-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102687" update="2009-05-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121755" update="2010-09-04">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening (Ending Version)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
