<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5673" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-11</startdate>
<enddate>2008-07-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaiba</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Кайба</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Кайба</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Каіба</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">カイバ</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">کایبا</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4392" approval="41" total="63">Kemonozume</anime>
<anime id="12681" approval="20" total="32">Made in Abyss</anime>
<anime id="484" approval="12" total="22">Ginga Tetsudou 999</anime>
<anime id="1834" approval="8" total="16">Mind Game</anime>
<anime id="2842" approval="7" total="14">Hotori: Tada Saiwai o Koinegau</anime>
<anime id="1440" approval="4" total="8">Tetsuwan Atom</anime>
<anime id="7529" approval="0" total="11">Panty &amp; Stocking with Garterbelt</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="51">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="404463">Despite it has a happy ending, i didn`t get any happier, it`s a classic dystopia with weird animation and confusing dialogues, somewhere in the middle of series you will get on track but it will continue to confuse you, it`s not that i didn`t like it but i would recommended only for fans of dystopias</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="371378">Mad, confusing and avant-garde, Kaiba immerses the viewer in a completely alien universe full of weirdness and dark beauty. You`ll know right away if you are part of Kaiba or not... and like watching Alice in Wonderland on LSD, Kaiba saturates your inner self and begs you to come along.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="684759">This anime is probably one of the artistically unique iv`e seen and it`s opening is simply beautiful. Honestly most if not all Yuasa Masaaki directed shows should be a mandatory watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="141220">unique.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="290127">Really great Art style!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="199844">*First, check to see if we share similar anime tastes.* I personally value story over cutting edge visuals, so I found this anime beautiful. But since anime is largely a visual medium, I could see how people might disagree with me.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="297941">Another masterpiece by Masaaki Yuasa. Kind of weird but definitely worth the watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="446567">A better love story than....Oh, just watch it already! You won`t be disappointed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="211945">Unique and cute! Yes it is a little different than what we, anime fans, usually see but it is too interesting to ignore.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="38418">strange. original. childish. with adult emotions!! a masterpiece!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="283829">The simplified style of animation contrasts this series mature dystopic setting heavily.

If you like shows that encourage you to think for yourself and are occasionally lightened up by over-the-top humour, this is definitely for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="66705">Ahdistava kuin mikä ainakin aluksi, mutta todella hyvä. Suosittelen!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="470717">I had a hard time getting into Kaiba and this definitely had to do with the weird art style and fantasy.  Eventually i stopped trying to make sense of anything that was animated and that allowed me to watch this through. I also had to get through the first episodes, i found those boring and it actually starts to get better at Episode 5.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="250792">It`s a bit cult, but it`s great! The songs are in mind my yet o.O</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="257906">This is the single saddest and most uplifting, lightest and most dramatic, ugliest and most beautiful anime I have ever seen, and I have seen a few.
Don`t try to understand it at the beginning - just take it in step by step, and everything will be crystal clear by ep. 12.
This is real art. Believe me - I am here for 20 years and this is the first time I am writing a recommendation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="507844">An ultimate amusement park for ripened people. So cruel, so fantastic. The little stories in this series is so amazing. I adore the writer and the execution of it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="554678">This is a one of a kind anime that will capture your attention and your heart. Explores the philosophical questions surrounding love and individuality in a world where your memories can`t and don`t define who or what you are.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="833543">one of the best anime works ever</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="691547">Don`t let the art fool you
this a SERIOUS anime
it`s very thought provoking
and mind blowing at the same time
Just watch it and you`ll see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="613777">An intense, poetic, WONDERFUL anime. Truly a masterpiece, a work of art.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="384413">One of the most creative and interesting anime ever. Solid plot, solid characters, solid soundtrack, solid art, solid themes, and mixed together it becomes one-of-a-kind.

Do yourself a favor and watch this right now if you consider yourself a fan of anime as a whole.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="91551">Quite unique and thought provoking.  The OP &amp; ED are really great too.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="31940">Refreshing, thought-provoking, unique artwork, interesting characters. Some aspects of the story are reminiscent of The Culture series by Ian M. Bainks for fans of his books.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="152176">very surreal and awesome.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="243072">This is one of the best animes out there. It will blow your mind.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="77646">unique</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="178310">Amazing !!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="364851">unusual at first - but Kaiba is simply the best Anime in years...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="396387">weird animation, awesome animation!watching the first episode is the thing wrapping you into this dystopian world, enchaining you to your chair, giving you the possibility of thinking hard about several matters</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="247340">Easily the deepest anime made to date. A dystopian view on what is popularly considered utopian - the conquering of death.

Not a sad show, contrary to popular opinion (but be ready to read between the lines a LOT to get this)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="372851">I watched this anime in one sitting!
I hope that it makes it clear that this is a must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="272102">Best Story ever! Don`t just quit cause of the Style. somewhere in the middle you will not notice anymore!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="559767">It was very good. I sign up this site just to just tell you all that this show is very good. It is the only one TV show that made me cry. Great plot, great storytelling,stylish.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20121010151816/http://www.wowow.co.jp/anime/kaiba/</url>
<creators>
<name id="49" type="Original Work">Yuasa Masaaki</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="731" type="Original Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="49" type="Direction">Yuasa Masaaki</name>
<name id="49" type="Series Composition">Yuasa Masaaki</name>
<name id="7785" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Nobutake</name>
<name id="6782" type="Music">Yoshida Kiyoshi</name>
<name id="7785" type="Character Design">Itou Nobutake</name>
</creators>
<description>* Original series directed by http://anidb.net/cr49 [Yuasa Masaaki], and animated by http://anidb.net/cr731 [Madhouse].
A sci-fi love story set in a world where digitization of memory made physical death obsolete. A world where memories can be stolen and altered, and replaced in a new human body.
http://anidb.net/ch5489 [Kaiba] wakes up in a room without knowing who he is. He has a pendant with the photograph of a woman he does not remember. After being attacked all of a sudden, he has to flee to space, meet various people, and rediscover the world.
"Even without my memories, I love you..."</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2874">8.32</permanent>
<temporary count="2926">8.09</temporary>
<review count="6">8.10</review>
</ratings>
<picture>222113.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9178</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3701</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4245</identifier>
<identifier>pnvslj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20121010151816/http://www.wowow.co.jp/anime/kaiba/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>カイバ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1391</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330124</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9948</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>海馬_(動畫)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10494</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3086" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>parricide</name>
<description>Parricide, or the murder of family members, is the act of taking the life of of one or more of one`s own close family members, or even one`s entire family; that may include spouses, parents, grandparents, children, grandchildren, siblings, cousins, uncles, aunts, nephews, and nieces, among others.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3837" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-09">
<name>memory transfer</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4113" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-20">
<name>body exchange</name>
<description>Two or more characters swap bodies (or, equally, swap minds).
When this plot is done, usually the voices also switch as narrative cheat to help viewers keep track of who`s who. More subtly, it`s just the eyes. More serious/action-oriented shows might not do this. The Flip often involves characters of different ages, genders, races, or social classes. Another variation is a protagonist and antagonist switching, which usually involves each trying to undermine the other`s organization while simultaneously trying to switch back. If one or both of the characters have superpowers or other special abilities, they`ll have a lot of trouble figuring their new powers out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4274" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>hidden agenda</name>
<description>Someone or some organization/government/etc. is misrepresenting themselves by doing/saying one thing while hoping/striving for something else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6901" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-23">
<name>underground</name>
<description>Some or all of the action occurs underground, in caves, mines, sewers, subways or underground cities.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="63" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-01">
<rating votes="23">8.68</rating>
<name>Chroniko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chroniko is a girl Kaiba meets during a stop Neuron makes. She sells her body (literally) so that the money can support her family and hopes that someday her family will become wealthy enough to buy her a new body in the future. However, she is killed by a corrupt doctor (by simply releasing her mind from storage) as her family doesn`t have any intentions of keeping her, and her body is sold anyway. Before her body is taken by the buyer, Hyo-Hyo places Kaiba`s mind inside her body, and Kaiba uses this disguise to avoid capture and get back aboard Neuron.</description>
<picture>14425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5488" type="main character in" update="2009-04-01">
<rating votes="13">6.43</rating>
<name>Warp</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaiba`s real name is Warp, and he is most commonly known as the king of memories, of whom he is the genuine original. He is one of six sons of his father, the former king; in a conflict to determine his father`s succession at the end of his life, all of Kaiba`s brothers were killed, and only Kaiba survives with his invulnerability. For some time he ruled in the place of his father, and invented the technology that enabled the preservation of memories, making it available to the people. Since then, it appears that he was closed off and tightly controlled in his palace, closely monitored by some other party through cameras and other devices while generally remaining in power.</description>
<picture>22243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5489" type="main character in" update="2009-04-01">
<rating votes="15">6.99</rating>
<name>Kaiba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character, who does not speak very much. Kaiba has a hole in the middle of his chest and a tattoo of three circles forming a triangle on his belly. At the beginning of the series, he has no memories he can access.
Kaiba has great power; it slowly becomes revealed that he is able to survive physical damage unscathed, and he also appears to have powerful abilities to halt or destroy large objects with his mind. However, as of yet he is unaware of and unable to control these abilities clearly. He also has a vastly detailed and complex memory, in effect total recall.
By the time the first episode begins, he has fallen down through the clouds, and his memories have been closed off to him by the electrical storms inside. Someone else in a clone of his body is currently reigning as king, though he does not have Warp`s powers nor memories.</description>
<picture>22244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5490" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-01">
<rating votes="11">3.93</rating>
<name>Popo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The first to encounter Kaiba upon awakening. After crossing paths with him again, he explains to Kaiba the nature of the current world, and that his life is in danger. Giving him the temporary name</description>
<picture>22245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5491" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-01">
<rating votes="11">7.65</rating>
<name>Vanilla</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The sadistic sheriff on board Neuron. Though Vanilla is extremely strict in enforcing his authority upon the passengers (and enjoys doing so thoroughly), he is not above corruption, and is willing to make deals, accept bribery, or steal memory chips for himself. He also has a weakness for extremely cute girls.
In spite of his shortcomings, however, he is surprisingly devoted to Kaiba, and has gone through great lengths to insure his safety (albeit not knowing his true identity, and in Chroniko`s body). This devotion comes to a head in episode 7, while the two are on the run from the law. He transfers Kaiba`s and Hyo-Hyo`s memories elsewhere as their ship is under bombardment, knowing full well that they would be unable to escape, and also telling Kaiba that he had back up bodies elsewhere to comfort him. However, after making sure that Kaiba is safe, Vanilla reveals that there was no such insurance for him, and he perishes alongside Chroniko`s memoryless body when the ship is destroyed.</description>
<picture>22246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5492" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-01">
<rating votes="8">4.85</rating>
<name>Chieki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5493" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-01">
<rating votes="8">7.28</rating>
<name>Kichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2044" picture="21387.jpg">Iwanaga Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5494" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-01">
<rating votes="9">8.58</rating>
<name>Hyo-Hyo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A small intelligent creature that accompanies Kaiba. It cannot speak (though it does have a voice) and it flies around using its two antennae to spin like propeller blades. It was dispatched by the memory merchant in episode 1 to follow Kaiba in his travels and helps Kaiba avoid capture.</description>
<picture>22249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2413" picture="22272.jpg">Mizuta Wasabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5495" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-01">
<rating votes="9">6.02</rating>
<name>Kaba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A stuffed animal-like body that resembles a hippo. Kaiba uses this body to smuggle himself in the ship. It is very difficult for him to move around in this state, and he is also incapable of speech or expressing facial emotion. He often makes use of the body when he doesn`t feel like being harassed by Vanilla any more.</description>
<picture>22250.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5496" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-01">
<rating votes="14">8.01</rating>
<name>Neiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who shares an unknown connection with Kaiba. Little is known about her, although she is currently under the care of Popo and a memory merchant.
Neiro grew up alongside Popo, and has been involved with Issoudan for a very long time. She is largely under Popo`s control, and he has her convinced that should she get into trouble, she has no other place to return to.</description>
<picture>22251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18230" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-30">
<rating votes="8">7.50</rating>
<name>Patch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4493.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101207" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Kochu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2982" picture="23710.jpg">Hibi Aiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101208" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Butter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3970" picture="25848.jpg">Nishiwaki Tamotsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101211" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Parm</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101212" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Lum</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3398" picture="224826.jpg">Kingetsu Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101213" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Negi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101214" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Moka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101215" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Naru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11049" picture="39830.jpg">Ueda Seiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101216" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Kona</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101224" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Gel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230870.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101227" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Sate</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="88814" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="30">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">名はワープ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Name Is Warp</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Na wa Warp</title>
<summary>A young man awakens without memories. There`s a hole in his chest, a symbol on his belly, and a blurry picture of a girl in a locket he has. Knowing nothing, he`s forced to rely on another man, named Popo, to help him escape a twisted city of stolen memories and exchangeable bodies.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784200</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="89852" update="2010-03-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89853" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90036" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="22">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶に残らない男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man Who Doesn`t Dwell in Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kioku ni Nokoranai Otoko</title>
<summary>Vanilla`s joy at showing Cronico around the underwater city on Nene gets interrupted when he learns the two of them are wanted criminals. Having sworn to protect Cronico, the forgettable man needs to make a choice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784211</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90037" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">筋肉質な女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Muscular Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinnikushitsu na Onna</title>
<summary>The ship`s next stop is Lolo, the "graveyard of memories," where all memory seeds end up. There, Cronico meets a woman, who is strangely familiar despite wearing the body of a man. And who might be a terrorist.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784209</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90038" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">憧れの星アビパ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Abipa, the Utopian Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akogare no Hoshi Abipa</title>
<summary>Abipa, a world of wonders and delight. The food is free, and you can obtain designer bodies there as you like! And toiling away to make it all possible is Patch, a mad inventor, and his faithful dog-companion Quilt.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784207</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90039" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ばあさんの記憶の部屋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Grandma`s Room of Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baa-san no Kioku no Heya</title>
<summary>While fleeing the attentions of Vanilla, Warp ends up in a light house, run by an old woman who doesn`t believe her husband is dead, and her twin grandchildren who greedily clamor to find the old "treasure" left behind by their grandfather.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784205</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90040" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="28">9.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クロニコのながぐつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chroniko`s Leather Boots</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chroniko no Nagagutsu</title>
<summary>Warp meets a young girl named Cronico, who is selling her body (literally) so her family can live happily. However, her family isn`t as kind as Cronico would like to believe, and amnesiac Warp is the only one who can hold onto those memories.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784203</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90041" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="23">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">密航</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stowaways</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikkou</title>
<summary>Given the name "Warp" and the body of a stuffed hippo, the man without memories illegally boards a ship bound for safety. Unfortunately, security officer Vanilla makes the lives of stowaways on his ship all too short.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784201</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90065" update="2008-04-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 15seconds</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90390" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワープを討て!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shoot Warp!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warp o Utte!</title>
<summary>Neiro thought she knew what the One Mind Society was. She committed atrocities in their name, to bring about that goal. But in the end, with Warp in her crosshairs... will she remember who she is?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784215</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90391" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">化けの皮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sheep`s Clothing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bake no Kawa</title>
<summary>Back on planet Lala, Popo continues to advance his own agenda within the One Mind Society, and things come to a head when he learns the truth behind the "King of Memories" who rules over them all.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784213</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91129" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんな雲の中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyone in the Clouds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna Kumo no Naka</title>
<summary>The misuse of his technology made Warp bitter and hollow. Kaiba wanted to live happily with Neiro. Cronico wanted everyone to be happy. Which of the three is this current Warp? Or might this be a case of me, myself, and I? Only Neiro can help Warp understand how to fill the hole in his chest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784220</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91130" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="14">9.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まわるファン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Turning Fan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mawaru Fan</title>
<summary>Popo has everything he`s ever wanted... but not one of the things he needs. As he loses more and more things precious to him, he wonders: why not make it that way for everyone?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784218</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91131" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="14">9.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カイバ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaiba</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaiba</title>
<summary>Who is Kaiba? Neiro remembers now. She remembers everything. She even remembers how the two of them ended up going down this path, with one of them a terrorist and the other lost, adrift the stars.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784217</identifier>
<identifier>kaiba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96471" update="2010-02-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Seira - Never (Music video)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96472" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96473" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191420" update="2017-10-04">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197577" update="2018-03-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Textless Inserts</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
