<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5674" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>51</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Zettai Karen Children</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Absolutely Lovely Children</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Восхитительные дети</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">绝对可怜Children</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">绝对可怜少女</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">zkc</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">絶対可憐チルドレン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Psychic Squad</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">绝对可怜小孩</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7664" type="Sequel">Zettai Karen Children OVA: Aitazousei! Ubawareta Mirai?</anime>
<anime id="9421" type="Side Story">Courtesy of Zettai Karen Children: The Unlimited - Hyoubu Kyousuke</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4917" approval="4" total="10">Hayate no Gotoku!</anime>
<anime id="1140" approval="3" total="3">Psychic Force</anime>
<anime id="6460" approval="1" total="5">Toaru Kagaku no Railgun</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="402833">I`m suprised at myself, honestly. For a show mainly aimed at a much younger audience I found myself enjoying this show alot. Alot of parody in the episodes, and the daily actions of the 3 main girl characters were always hilarious. I actualy think I shed a tear over an episode or two. Some of the situations were... well dumb, and some characters would be better off removed from the show, but it`s that moronic feeling that actualy makes you feel good inside while watching this. Thinking about picking up the manga, but hoping for a new season the most.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="66096">pure awesomeness :)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.z-child.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1163" type="Animation Work">SynergySP</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
<name id="6090" type="Direction">Kawaguchi Keiichirou</name>
<name id="3661" type="Series Composition">Nishizono Satoru</name>
<name id="7262" type="Original Work">Shiina Takashi</name>
<name id="2211" type="Main Character Design">Kagami Takahiro</name>
<name id="2211" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kagami Takahiro</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr7262 [Shiina Takashi], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23232 [Shounen Sunday] .
They`re cute, adorable and three of the most powerful Espers the world has ever seen: http://anidb.net/ch4730 [Kaoru], the brash psychokinetic who can move objects with her mind; http://anidb.net/ch4732 [Shiho], the sarcastic and dark natured psychometric able to pick thoughts from people`s minds and read the pasts of inanimate objects like a book; and http://anidb.net/ch4731 [Aoi], the most collected and rational of the three, who has the ability to teleport herself and the others at will.
So what to do with these potential psychic monsters in the making? Enter B.A.B.E.L., the Base of Backing ESP Laboratory, where hopefully The Children and others like them can become part of the answer to an increasing wave of psychic evolution. It`s a win-win solution... Unless you`re http://anidb.net/ch4733 [Minamoto Kouichi], the overworked young man stuck with the unenviable task of field commanding a team of three pre-teen girls! Will Kouichi survive the experience? Will the Planet survive the experience? Find out as the girls get meta-physical in Psychic Squad!
Source: Sentai Filmworks</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1031">6.10</permanent>
<temporary count="1040">7.19</temporary>
<review count="3">6.94</review>
</ratings>
<picture>13306.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9127</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4038</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5849</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4244</identifier>
<identifier>ldhpne</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.z-child.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Zettai_Karen_Children</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>絶対可憐チルドレン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1361</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330114</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9973</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1572</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-08">
<name>teleportation</name>
<description>Teleportation is the transfer of matter from one point to another, possibly a distant one, without application of force, and generally instantly. This contradicts scientific law as we know it, and is therefore nowadays impossible. Sometimes it appears as a paranormal or supernatural ability, and sometimes it is shown in science fiction through technological devices backed up by scientific laws yet to be discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="104" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-04-03">
<rating votes="132">6.08</rating>
<name>Perrine-H. Clostermann</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Perrine is a wealthy and proper fifteen year old Gallian girl who looks down on some of the less-refined habits of her peers. The emotional scars left by the Neuroi`s conquest of her homeland cause her numerous problems. She often refuses to work as part of a team, and develops a dislike for the upstart newcomer Yoshika due to her attachment to Mio, which eventually develops into full-blown jealousy. When wearing her Striker Unit, she gains the dark ears and tail of a Chartreux. Perrine holds the rank of Flying Officer and her original unit was the Armée de l`Air 802nd Flying Corps.</description>
<picture>65912.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="156" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="197">7.91</rating>
<name>Eila Ilmatar Juutilainen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eila Ilmatar Juutilainen is the fifteen year old top ace of the Suomus Air Force 24th Unit with the rank of Pilot Officer (although the three roses on her collar would indicate the rank of captain). Eila`s hobby is fortune-telling with tarot cards, although the accuracy of her predictions is questionable at best. In battle however, she literally has the magical power of seeing into the future, allowing her to evade incoming attacks with ease. Somewhat mischievous, like the black fox whose features she gains in flight. She is particularly affectionate towards Sanya and will become cold to anyone who comes too close to her, this usually being Yoshika. In combat her weapons of choice are the MG42 and Suomi M1931 submachine gun. Eila`s Striker Unit is based on the Messerschmitt Bf-109G-2 and she is based on the ace Eino Ilmari Juutilainen.</description>
<picture>193261.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="159" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="217">8.40</rating>
<name>Sanya V. Litvyak</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanya V. Litvyak is the single Witch out of the Orussia Empire at thirteen years old. Preferring to stay indoors during the day, Sanya has been described as "nocturnal." At times she is literally asleep on her feet, counting on Eila to move her around. Despite this somewhat limiting her contact with the other members of the 501st, her low profile makes her ideal for night missions and sneak attacks. Also helping her in this duty is her magical specialty, the ability to read signals such as radio waves that are invisible to the naked eye, giving her a highly advanced spatial awareness. Gains the ears and tail of a black cat with her Striker Unit equipped. Sanya`s rank is Flying Officer and her original unit affiliation is the Orussia Imperial Army 586th Fighter Regiment. Her Striker Unit design is based on the MiG60 (a fictional warbird combining features of the MiG-1, MiG-3, and Yakovlev Yak-1) and her pilot archetype is http://anidb.net/ch85347 [Lydia Litvyak].</description>
<picture>130691.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="528" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-05-18">
<rating votes="497">5.90</rating>
<name>Sanzen`in Nagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanzen`in Nagi is the only heir to the Sanzen`in fortune. She has an otaku-level hobby with manga, anime and video games, and draws her own manga, which is called Millennium Legend: Magical Destroy. She is good at finance and likes to learn. She has a crush on Hayate, and has misunderstood that Hayate loves her since they first met. But because this is only a misunderstanding, she often feels that Hayate isn`t interested in her. She sometimes tries to make him have interest in her in many ways. Nagi is afraid of dark places and has absolutely no sense of direction. Her only surviving family is her grandfather, whom she doesn`t like. She regards Maria as a mother or older sister figure, and warns Hayate not to touch Maria in any indecent way or she will never forgive him. She totally lacks experience with cooking and accordingly is prone to making mistakes (such as mistaking dish-washing detergent for cooking oil) when she attempts to cook. She has a pet tiger, Tama, whom she refers to as a cat.</description>
<picture>71769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="530" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="1086">9.09</rating>
<name>Katsura Hinagiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsura Hinagiku is the current http://anidb.net/ch16568 [student council] president, and kendo club president at http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuou Academy], the school that http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi], http://anidb.net/ch531 [Isumi], and eventually http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] attends. She is fifteen and is an expert with swords, specifically kendo. She first meets Hayate when he gets lost on the huge Hakuou campus and ends up rescuing her. She had been helping a baby bird who had fallen out of its nest, but due to her fear of heights, had become stuck without her realising it. Hayate ends up helping her down the tree, and then promises that he will come to help her should she ever call for him. In gratitude, she invites him to the top of the clocktower, where only student council elites are allowed. She allows Hayate to call her by her first name and also seems to be infatuated by Hayate and his attractive personality. Her family, while shown to be well off in volume 8 (chapter 76), does not show any signs of being rich in comparison to much of the cast.</description>
<picture>24934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="532" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-04-16">
<rating votes="292">6.45</rating>
<name>Ayasaki Hayate</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayasaki Hayate is the butler of the Sanzenin family, Hayate has had to work to support his parents` bad habits since the age of nine, always moving from job to job by the time he is found out to be underage. The experience gained does mean, however, that he of all characters possesses the most extensive practical knowledge as to how the world operates. Hayate`s dad has refused to get employed,while his mother is a compulsive gambler, and the whereabouts of Hayate`s older brother who is not named, are unknown. These events led to their bankruptcy - they abandon Hayate after selling his organs to the Yakuza to ease their financial burdens. With not many choices left to him, Hayate conspired to kidnap someone to get ransom money. He found a girl, http://anidb.net/ch528 [Sanzenin Nagi], and told her that he would kidnap her. However, Nagi mistook his words for his confession of love, so later he was employed as Nagi`s new butler but as the story progresses, Hayate began to like Nagi without realising it. In the beginning of the story he often mentioned Nello and Patrasche from the novel A Dog of Flanders and compared his miserable situation to the characters` life.</description>
<picture>14830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="641" type="cameo appearance in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="107">4.72</rating>
<name>Hanabishi Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanabishi Miki is a member of the Student Council. She specialises in investigation work, which may be the result of being the daughter of an important government official.</description>
<picture>14953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="218" picture="17036.jpg">Nakao Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="642" type="cameo appearance in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="102">4.57</rating>
<name>Asakaze Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asakaze Risa is the head of the disciplinary committee.</description>
<picture>14954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="679" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-04-09">
<rating votes="63">7.43</rating>
<name>Tama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tama is a white tiger from Africa, who was rescued by http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi] as a cub, and was raised on Matsuzaka beef and expensive tuna fish, making it incapable for him to go to the zoo or back to the wild. He can speak the human language, though he does not reveal this to http://anidb.net/ch529 [Maria] or Nagi because he doesn`t want to shatter the young girl`s dreams. He will lay his life down to protect Nagi, because his situation was a lot like http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate]`s. To him, Maria is the highest power there is, followed by an impassable wall, Nagi, then himself, and everyone else is below him.</description>
<picture>14973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1632" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-02-14">
<rating votes="20">6.79</rating>
<name>Nijihara Ink</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Even though Ink is 17, she is often mistaken as a grade-schooler, however she makes up for it with her high grades, especially in English. She meets Ark-kun who gives her the power to transform into the magical hero Pastel Ink; using a pink flip phone, changing into a duck-like outfit with blue hair. Using this new power she helps the people of her city while also using it to tutor Nao in English.</description>
<picture>135221.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1683" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-12-31">
<rating votes="19">7.24</rating>
<name>Kuroi Sumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sumi is 17 years old even though she looks like a grade-schooler. She is very rich and has a spoiled attitude because of that. She and Ink were friends when they were younger but for unknown reasons they broke apart, even though Ink still tries to be Sumi`s friend. The end of her ahoge (the long strand of hair coming from the front of her head) usually portrays whatever she is feeling.</description>
<picture>67008.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="3004" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="85">6.25</rating>
<name>Kobayakawa Yutaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konata`s cousin. She has been sickly since she was little. Having enrolled at Ryoo, she currently lives with Konata. She is adored by everyone for her honest nature and expressiveness. A bit absent-minded.</description>
<picture>18654.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3005" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="117">7.32</rating>
<name>Iwasaki Minami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quiet and caring model student. Because she is taciturn, she is sometimes mistaken as being scary. She excels both academically and athletically, but she has a complex about having no chest.</description>
<picture>18655.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4730" type="main character in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="45">7.05</rating>
<name>Akashi Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ten-year-old Level 7 psychokinetic (the maximum esper potency designation), Kaoru is the reckless and zealous member of "The Children" Special Esper Team alongside Shiho and Aoi that often goes overkill with her psychic powers.</description>
<picture>20851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4731" type="main character in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="26">6.46</rating>
<name>Nogami Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ten-year-old esper with Level 7 teleportation capability, Aoi is the rational member of "The Children" Special Esper Team alongside Kaoru and Shiho that likes playing video games in her spare time. Like her teammates, Aoi is introduced at series inception as behaving in a somewhat cavalier manner that annoys her adult superiors.</description>
<picture>20852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4732" type="main character in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="31">6.55</rating>
<name>Sannomiya Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ten-year-old esper with Level 7 psychometry, Shiho is the sarcastic, sharp-tongued and often childishly sadistic member of "The Children" Special Esper Team alongside Kaoru and Aoi. While initially not able to do much during missions aside from gathering information that is not immediately obvious from the environment, Shiho still supports her teammates by doing whatever she can.</description>
<picture>20853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4733" type="main character in" update="2012-08-11">
<rating votes="37">4.45</rating>
<name>Minamoto Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The first lieutenant workaholic field leader of "The Children" Special Esper Team, he is tasked with overseeing their day-to-day care and making sure they do not get too carried away when they are doing their jobs. Even as they mistreat him and generally give him super fits, the girls highly esteem Minamoto enough to ask the B.A.B.E.L. chief to be allowed to reside with him after he leads them in their introductory mission and protects Kaoru from her own out-of-control telekinesis. While he is quite courageous and sincere in his belief that Kaoru/Shiho/Aoi are little girls to be protected and cherished before they are Level 7 espers (which Shiho says are treated the same as mass-destruction weapons) and has grown to be very fond of them enough to spend time with them on diurnal outings, Minamoto has a hard time applying those life-equality ideals to Momotarou (who wrecks his apartment when Kaoru decides to nurse him back to health) and refraining from behaving toward his esper charges as if they are a bunch of brats (an accurate but counterproductive assessment). Minamoto generates quite a convoy of female admirers during the course of the Zettai Karen Children series as he works to pre-empt the precognition of a mortal showdown with Kaoru in a war-torn city during Kyousuke`s esper-led war against humans a decade in the future.</description>
<picture>20854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4734" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="27">6.37</rating>
<name>Kashiwagi Oboro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Even if her job title is simply being Taizou`s secretary or personal assistant, Kashiwagi is no exception to the sidekick/alter ego dynamic and is generally very handy to have around. Kashiwagi performs many roles as she accompanies Taizou which include assisting with visual aids during mission briefings and preventing Taizou from giving an order or making a decision whose aftermath would most likely be rather messy.</description>
<picture>20855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4735" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="11">3.50</rating>
<name>Kiritsubo Taizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of B.A.B.E.L. He dotes on "The Children" all the time and spoils them rotten not realising that this overindulgence is probably the reason for the bad behaviour of "The Children". Taizou can and does point to Minamoto as the scapegoat for The Children`s fallibilities and poor attitudes. Whether Taizou overindulges "The Children" because he really loves them or because he is frightened for his job/personal safety remains to be seen; still, Taizou is extremely attached to Kaoru, Shiho, and Aoi (who are starting to realize that Taizou`s intense affection for them is not entirely altruistic) and goes into a frenzy comparable to a Level 6 esper whenever he feels that "The Children" are in distress.</description>
<picture>20856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4736" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="6">3.29</rating>
<name>Tanizaki Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The heavy-smoking thirty-six-year-old supervisor of Umegae Naomi. He has become extremely attached to his esper charge over the four years since her supernatural powers were discovered when she was twelve-years-old. While he has done a good job of administrating the development of Naomi`s social character which has allowed the use of her telekinesis for constructive ends, Ichirou has also demonstrated signs of a lecherous personal agenda to refine Naomi into his "ideal woman". Despite having twice been on the receiving end of Naomi`s telekinesis misfiring and her telekinetic exhortations to keep a professional distance, Ichirou has not been convinced to abandon his lecherous personal agenda and has a developed a masochistic facet to his obsessions.</description>
<picture>20857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4737" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="14">6.50</rating>
<name>Tokiwa Natsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuko wields her Level 5 clairvoyance as one member of the Doubleface esper receptionist team alongside her partner Hotaru and is charged with identifying and intercepting possible incoming threats. Not only can she detect dangerous items such as packaged explosives or concealed personal weaponry, but Natsuko also can even tell if a visitor is in good hygienic repair. It would not be out of the question for Natsuko to use her clairvoyance to spy on a visitor during his time on the B.A.B.E.L. premises to ensure good behaviour.</description>
<picture>20858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="218" picture="17036.jpg">Nakao Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4738" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="14">6.58</rating>
<name>Nowaki Hotaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hotaru avails her Level 5 telepathy as the other member of The Doubleface esper receptionist team alongside her partner Natsuko. Hotaru is charged with reading the visitor`s thoughts to determine whether or not they pose a threat to either the espers or B.A.B.E.L`s other personnel. The infatuation that she and Natsuko share for Minamoto has ignited a low-level rivalry between the two even as they are often kept in the loop with all the drama involving Minamoto and his esper charges.</description>
<picture>20859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4739" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="11">7.45</rating>
<name>Umegae Naomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sixteen-year-old Level 6 psychokinetic high-schooler originally known as "Kitty Cat", at the beginning Naomi`s naive mistakes would make for a less-than-perfect working environment and would not be regarded as a laughing matter (either at the time or after the fact) under normal real-life circumstances. Naomi has built a solid four-year history with her supervisor Ichirou and seems to sincerely wants to do well for both herself and B.A.B.E.L.
However, during one of her missions when she is charged with stopping a psychic who uses his powers to molest women, she begins to have trouble using her powers and accidentally injures her supervisor. After training with the Children, she has a simulated duel with Kaoru acting exactly as the psychic she tried to stop. Naomi realizes that Ichirou`s intense affection for her is not entirely the altruistic and professional working relationship that it is supposed to be. When they next meet the peeping esper, Naomi takes out both the esper and her somewhat perverted supervisor. It is at this point Naomi gains the nickname "Wild Cat", the rationale of which is demonstrated whenever Ichirou tries to manipulate Naomi and fails to keep his professional (and physical) distance.</description>
<picture>20860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4740" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-11">
<rating votes="32">3.57</rating>
<name>Sakaki Shuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Sakaki Shuuji is the old-enough-to-know-better playboy psychometric physician of B.A.B.E.L. whose job it is to inspect espers at the conclusion of every mission as well as to take care of general medical needs. Before meeting Minamoto (who is originally a medical researcher before enrolling in an overseas supervisor course), Sakaki did not have anybody to understand him as a person and advocate for him. To compensate for this, he behaved like the typical sports jock - popular in school but dangerous if obstructed. Given how he had beaten up several people and how injured they were, it is not that unreasonable to speculate that Sakaki is very well-practised in the martial arts and that it was probably in that forum that he discovered his psychometry and taught himself how to use it to his advantage. Fortunately, Sakaki saw fit to clean up his act after his Level 6 psychometry imports an admonishment to grow up from Minamoto even as he behaves as quite a lady`s man.</description>
<picture>20861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4741" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-11">
<rating votes="72">7.75</rating>
<name>Hyoubu Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A misanthropic former major-rank military esper with eight decades of life under his belt, Kyousuke is one tough adversary with an abundant anthology of different esper capabilities. As is the case with Kaoru`s berserk runaway telekinesis, Kyousuke has the capability to defy fully powered-up ESP Counter Measure generators but does so as "the rule". Kyousuke has a lengthy history of teleporting out of his subterranean holding cell, walking around for a breath of fresh air, and teleporting back in without anybody detecting and challenging him. Given that there are few efficacious avenues for damaging him (never mind the subjugation and confinement), Kyousuke believes that he do whatever he wishes and it would not be that outrageous to suspect that Kyousuke is either one of the alpha adversaries or the alpha adversary. He delights in giving B.A.B.E.L. fits as he foils their attempts to apprehend him and using his hypnosis to especially manipulate Minamoto for his own amusement (such as creating the illusion that Kaoru, Shiho, and Aoi are physically older than in reality). Kyousuke`s misanthropy also extends to other espers if they defy him (although he will offer them a chance to serve him first). He views Kaoru as his queen and soul mate due to her ability to defy the fully powered-up ESP Counter Measure generator and wishes for her to grow up quickly not caring anything that Kaoru is much more like a child than she initially appears as Minamoto is forced to endure on a daily basis. He and Momotarou have a social dynamic where they always see the worst of normal people and behave as if the word of an esper always takes precedence over the word of a normal person—with which they both have had several dysphoric experiences.</description>
<picture>20862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4742" type="appears in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="7">4.18</rating>
<name>Muscle Ookama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Muscle is introduced as the criminal quarry The Children have been charged with apprehending that behaves as if he were a 1960/1970s disco party-goer and has an affinity for muscular male bodies, hence the aspiration for a gold statue fashioned as such. His esper capability is using his telekinesis to burrow through the ground and to petrify people using a gemstone on his belt. A running gag involves one or more of his female opponents striking his genitals in combat.</description>
<picture>20863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7357" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-05-26">
<rating votes="184">7.43</rating>
<name>Nabeshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25868.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9638" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="80">8.38</rating>
<name>Kasugano Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 16-year-old-girl who ends up as Seiji`s right hand. She has had a crush on him for three years. One day she wishes to be with him so much that she finds herself, in miniature form, in the place of his right hand. This causes problems for him, since it is the "Devil`s right-hand" he punches with. As soon as Midori finds out that she is on Seiji`s hand, she gathers the courage to admit her love, even though it isn`t requited. During the series she continually confesses her love, and gets jealous of other girls, often trying to compete with them; but over time she begins to like qualities of all of the characters, including her "rivals".</description>
<picture>29318.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10198" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-16">
<rating votes="113">6.37</rating>
<name>Harukaze Chiharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The secretary of the student council. Secretly, under the alias of "Haruko", she works as Sakuya`s maid. Although nobody in Hakuou is aware of that, with the exception of Aika Kasumi, who found everything about her out soon enough.</description>
<picture>33328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11501" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-09-02">
<rating votes="34">5.24</rating>
<name>Keroro Gunsou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34415.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12809" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-07">
<rating votes="25">4.30</rating>
<name>Momotarou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Being the sole surviving wartime experimentation specimen to manufacture an esper animal, Momotarou is Kyousuke`s squirrel companion that sometimes behaves quite cluelessly as to Kyousuke`s modus operandi as he adds his commentary to whatever Kyousuke does or is deciding. Momotarou`s strongly- and frequently-demonstrated affinity for sunflower seeds one night causes him to be sucked into the slipstream of a passing truck and electrocuted by live power lines for no other reason than his obdurate refusal to let go of the seeds. If pushed into combat, Momotarou has the capability to compress the air around him into acoustic concussion missiles that he launches at his adversaries as well as an intense but transient siren that scrambles and encrypts the brain waves of anybody in the vicinity. When Kaoru tries to nurse him back to health, Momotarou has psychotic episodes as he recalls all the experimentation he has undergone that cause him to lash out to tremendous effect but fortunately sees that Kaoru and her teammates are kindred spirits even if he has not yet resolved his hatred for humans as a whole.</description>
<picture>38453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15653" type="appears in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<name>Kugutsu Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced as a very quirky but handy fellow with a proficiency for constructing dolls, Takashi also has the esper ability to animate his creations with anthropoid authenticity. While it has never really been conclusively appraised, Takashi has demonstrated the ability to animate/maneuver several of his creations at one time and even conduct a nice conversation—an event that does not happen very often without a request as its ulterior motive.
Unfortunately, the euphoria of watching Takashi happily do his esper thing for B.A.B.E.L. is tempered by the fact that he is a spy whose purpose seems to be researching and appraising the B.A.B.E.L. Special Espers and ancillary personnel for Kyousuke. Although he is perfectly fine with being left in peace to do the whole doll thing, Takashi demonstrates signs of demonstrating the common anthropoid social affinities of infatuation and of wanting to be acknowledged/appreciated. Perhaps the most prominent manifestation of this is capitulating to Kaoru`s blackmail when she detects him appraising Kashiwagi`s corporeal dimensions at distance (a life-sized doll of Kashiwagi in exchange for her silence) and his quiescent morality being annihilated with that life-sized doll at Kashiwagi`s hands (who does not—or perhaps does not want to—understand that Kaoru is the intended benefactor rather than himself) during a confrontation in his workshop. Given how it has generally taken him for granted and marginalized him before accusing him of lecherous conduct that is more of the rule with Kaoru or Ichirou, B.A.B.E.L. has a dangerous enemy in Takashi. Takashi`s downfall is brought about when he tries to frame Dr. Sakaki as a traitor in order to have him killed without getting his hands dirty; thanks to Minamoto and company, his plot backfires even though he was willing to do his own dirty work.</description>
<picture>44316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5400" picture="29628.jpg">Souma Yukito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15654" type="appears in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="5">6.47</rating>
<name>Akashi Akie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Considering how well she maintains herself, it is difficult to believe that Akie is Kaoru`s actress mother who divorced Kaoru`s father five years ago when Kaoru was delivered into B.A.B.E.L. stewardship. Considering the time frame, it is not that much of a stretch to surmise that Kaoru`s father has either been driven off or killed by Kaoru`s Level 7 telekinesis going out of control which frightens Akie right out of administrating over her younger daughter`s childhood development in contrast to Minamoto actually setting limits for Kaoru -- and enduring the verbal and telekinetic objections thereof. Akie`s inability or unwillingness to see Kaoru as her daughter that happens to be an esper leads her to behave a heavy emphasis upon her work.</description>
<picture>44317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15655" type="appears in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Yamabe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Children`s homeroom teacher.</description>
<picture>44318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13990" picture="26937.jpg">Ootake Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15656" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Hanai Chisato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Level 2 telepath, Chisato is one of The Children`s classmates that has a warm childhood history with Masaru Touno. Curious about whether he will still accept her after learning that she is an esper, Chisato reads Touno`s thoughts to learn that he sees her for the person she is before her telepathy but makes the mistake of sharing the news. Chisato demonstrates the tendency to assume culpability for Touno`s aversion for all espers as well as his conflict with Kaoru.</description>
<picture>44319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="425" picture="17296.jpg">Fukuhara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15657" type="appears in" update="2011-04-19">
<name>Touno Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Offended by Chisato`s telepathic intrusion into his thoughts, Touno takes his anguish too far and it blossoms into an intense aversion for all espers. Fortunately, it seems that Touno has gotten over Chisato`s intrusion since he has met his athletic rival in his new classmate Kaoru who he suspects used her telekinesis to bean him in the head with an eraser when they first met.</description>
<picture>44320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15658" type="appears in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="2">2.92</rating>
<name>Mary Ford</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A lieutenant in the Japanese Comerican esper team Liberty Bell, Mary avails her telekinesis alongside her partner Ken to perform the same kind of police work that B.A.B.E.L. does in Japan but on an international scale. In spite of engaging a devious and dubious device for appraising Kaoru`s powers along with those of her teammates, Mary is also found to be a potent ally as she demonstrates when she and Kaoru combine their telekinesis to subdue the fleeing Mute and Lige.</description>
<picture>44321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15659" type="appears in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="2">2.92</rating>
<name>Ken McGwire</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A lieutenant in the Japanese Comerican esper team Liberty Bell, Ken wields his clairvoyance alongside his partner Mary to perform the same kind of police work that B.A.B.E.L. does in Japan but on an international scale. In spite of being suspected of voyeurism at a hot spring resort, Ken befriends Minamoto and Sakaki who guide him through the correct technique for eating soba noodles. He and Mary are after Mute and Lige for unknown reasons.</description>
<picture>44322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15660" type="appears in" update="2010-03-08">
<name>Shkii Piroshkiski</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The failure of the international conference of crucial importance to Japan being his prime volition and supreme objective, Shkii Piroshkiski is an international spy that acquired the rank of captain in the Roviet Air Force for that sole purpose. Even though he has his subordinates successfully capture Minamoto and Aoi before confiscating their payload, Piroshkiski`s downfall comes when he underestimates Aoi and dismisses her capabilities thinking that all the Esper Counter Measure generators in his base afford him the absolute advantage. After a fierce dogfight with a quartet of active homing missiles which Aoi returns to him destroying his fighter, the Roviet government (after Minamoto explains all about him) apprehends him for espionage.</description>
<picture>44323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15661" type="appears in" update="2010-03-08">
<name>Shushou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The prime minister of Japan in Zettai Karen Children.</description>
<picture>44324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15662" type="appears in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="5">5.94</rating>
<name>Akashi Yoshimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoshimi is Kaoru`s gravure idol elder sister that is about Minamoto`s age. Given the prominent cleavage that both she and Akie have, it can be argued that the origins of Kaoru`s lesbian lechery lie here. As pointed out by Akie, a gravure idol appears to be a sort of trainee-entertainer designation. Considering the 11-year difference in age, Yoshimi is probably not really affected that much by her parents` divorce and just has no clue how to help Kaoru. Like with Akie, she deals with this with her work and dating.</description>
<picture>44325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1662" picture="25819.jpg">Kouda Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15663" type="appears in" update="2010-03-08">
<name>Sannomiya Keisatsuchou Choukan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Director of the NPA and Shiho`s father.</description>
<picture>44326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15677" type="appears in" update="2010-03-09">
<rating votes="2">7.97</rating>
<name>J.D. Grisham</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His title of *Esper Killer* being justly earned due to his Level 7 telepathy enabling him to wield nearby adversarial esper powers to his advantage, Colonel J.D. Grisham is a sinister adversary that initially appears to possibly stand shoulder-to-shoulder with Kyousuke as a possible alpha adversary considering that he has really given Liberty Bell and B.A.B.E.L. quite a challenge by wielding their thoughts and esper powers to their detriment. Aside from being a horrible karaoke singer, J.D. teaches that an esper`s powers vary directly with its willpower—a lesson Kaoru has demonstrated upon her whenever her concentration falters while using her telekinesis. Fortunately, Kaoru figures this out and works alongside Mary and Naomi to help drain a reservoir after Minamoto excavates into his back story. J.D.`s prime volition is for B.A.B.E.L. and Liberty Bell collaboration to grant the terminally-ill Saya her final wish to see her birthplace under the reservoir after she nursed him back to health after an esper soldier (most likely Kyousuke Hyobu) destroyed his bomber and its crew, leaving him as the sole survivor.</description>
<picture>44375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15678" type="appears in" update="2010-03-09">
<rating votes="2">3.99</rating>
<name>Yadorigi Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15679" type="appears in" update="2010-03-09">
<rating votes="12">4.45</rating>
<name>Inugami Hatsune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fourteen-year-old Hatsune avails her Level 4 metamorphosis as a member of The Hound Special Esper Team alongside of her partner Akira. Much to Akira`s chagrined frustration, Hatsune demonstrates the proclivity to behave her default lupine alternate manifestation which is only at its greatest efficacy when she is hungry—hungry as in `have not eaten for days` ravenous rather than merely being peckish. Unfortunately, Hatsune`s voracious appetite does have the tendency to displace the mission at hand. Even as this flaw is somewhat diminished as Minamoto trains her, Hatsune still has to overcome the fact that she computes and conducts in lupine/canine maneuvering rather than anthropoid action. Even with her canine conduct and gluttony set aside for the moment, Hatsune demonstrates a proclivity to become enthralled with anyone that sees past her exterior to interact with her as a human being and twice tries to claim Minamoto for herself. As Kaoru emphatically and vigorously demonstrates at her natural potency designation during an exercise regarding Minamoto and his affiliation, whoever is decided upon to supervise Hatsune will have to establish and maintain dominance right from the start without being cruel or despotic.</description>
<picture>44378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15680" type="appears in" update="2010-03-09">
<name>Kuroki Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His affinity for astronomy matched only by his infatuation with Aoi, Kuroki is brainy and boasts abundant academic capability. Given his awkwardness in approaching Aoi with the weekend planetarium invitation, it is not that preposterous to speculate (after taking into account individual development) that Kuroki`s academic prowess is slightly overemphasized at the expense of his social development. Not suprisingly, Kuroki would love to be involved with the space program in some capacity when he grows up. Ultimately, Aoi decides to break up with Kuroki to spend time with Kaoru and chase after Minamoto.</description>
<picture>44379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="269" picture="25727.jpg">Miyake Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15681" type="appears in" update="2010-03-09">
<name>Hige Shougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His athletic genius matched only by his infatuation with Shiho, Hige demonstrates that he has a lot to be proudly admired for. Aside from revealing that Hige`s athletic prowess is more vividly demonstrated when he is cheered on from the sidelines and that Hige has been well-bred at home, Hige`s reaction to Shiho`s psychometry being properly explained is probably going to be the central benchmark of whether this relationship flourishes or expires, if Shiho had not already decided to break up with Hige to spend time with Kaoru and chase after Minamoto.</description>
<picture>44381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15743" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="19">5.89</rating>
<name>Magi Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A senior member of PANDRA.</description>
<picture>44504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="156" picture="227713.jpg">Ochiai Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15855" type="appears in" update="2010-03-16">
<name>Yamada Koremitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Accompanying Mio as her personal bodyguard, Yamada is a telepath that once did for a private job management security company what Hotaru does for B.A.B.E.L.—basically detecting and repelling trouble. It is not that out of the question that Yamada was probably prosecuting a security operation in which he was injured and is now Mio`s personal bodyguard to repay Mio having nursed him back to health. Yamada`s downfall comes about when Sakaki psychometrically detects his back story and thus cleverly takes advantage of Yamada`s disorganized thought processes along with his martial arts ability to use adversarial momentum and inertia to his advantage ultimately proving a match for Yamada`s reliance upon brute force.</description>
<picture>44726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15856" type="appears in" update="2010-03-26">
<rating votes="13">6.85</rating>
<name>Tsukushi Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In addition to the normal position displacement (disappearing in one position followed by reappearing in another) much like Aoi, the young teleporter Mio can also generate distance-displacement portals that can even ignore physical obstacles as Dr. Sakaki has been forced to endure while in the middle of a fight with her bodyguard Yamada. Mio is unwilling to accept Kaoru as any kind of ruler that could replace her crush Kyousuke and demonstrates this by kidnapping Minamoto to her very run-down hideout. Minamoto guiding her through proper nutrition/hygiene and even giving her a new outfit inspires Mio but does not stop her vendetta against Kaoru. Mio`s downfall is brought about when Minamoto reasons that Mio probably has the same weakness as Akira`s metempsychosis. Sure enough, Minamoto transporting Mio`s genuine lower half out of range causes Mio to recall her clones, one of which has gone maverick. Kaoru`s intercession along with Minamoto`s compassion for her inspires Mio to reflect on her conduct even if her jealousy is not yet resolved.</description>
<picture>44727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15857" type="appears in" update="2010-03-16">
<name>Suma Kiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Children`s former abusive handler/supervisor.</description>
<picture>44729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15858" type="appears in" update="2010-03-16">
<name>Uchida Hanto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A police detective.
Accosted and subjugated by a trio of thugs one night, he makes the life decision to wield his level 3 telekinesis against the criminals that he sees while on his nocturnal patrol as Masked Justice. The question of why he has not joined B.A.B.E.L. as a Special Esper set aside for the moment, Uchida behaves an intense hatred for society as he telekinetically precludes the trachea of his quarry and generally gets carried away with his powers (though not to the extent Kaoru does). Uchida`s downfall comes when he isolates and abducts Shiho when she psychometrically discovers his secret, prompting a fierce telekinetic sequence from Kaoru of forcibly decelerating his car and twice knocking him down to be later apprehended.</description>
<picture>44730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2258" picture="21881.jpg">Uchida Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15859" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="15">3.99</rating>
<name>Fujiura You</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of PANDRA.</description>
<picture>44731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15860" type="appears in" update="2010-03-16">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Kaneko Ranko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of BABEL`s technical division.</description>
<picture>44732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15861" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="20">5.27</rating>
<name>Kanou Momiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tall woman with long blue hair and (usually) sunglasses. She is a member of PANDRA. Her power is based on teleportation and allows her to manipulate air.</description>
<picture>44733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15862" type="appears in" update="2010-03-16">
<rating votes="4">4.15</rating>
<name>I Kyuu Gou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A dolphin with level 7 ESP precognition powers. His predictions always come true. He was the result of animal experiments during the war, much like Momotarou.</description>
<picture>44734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2143" picture="178043.jpg">Kayumi Iemasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15863" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="23">8.10</rating>
<name>Tsubomi Fujiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girlish and playful energy vampire with eight decades of life under her belt and the capability to practice the same powers as Kaoru and her teammates. She outranks Taizou who has established B.A.B.E.L. under her guidance.</description>
<picture>44735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15948" type="appears in" update="2010-03-18">
<rating votes="4">3.78</rating>
<name>Suetsumu Hanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of BABEL`s medical division with hypnotic abilities. She works at an old folk`s home pretending to be people the patients have lost in the past. Occasionally she is recruited to work with the Children.</description>
<picture>44841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15962" type="appears in" update="2010-03-19">
<name>Nogami Daisaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoi`s father.</description>
<picture>44902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15963" type="appears in" update="2010-03-19">
<name>Nogami Yuuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Younger brother of Aoi.</description>
<picture>44903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="690" picture="187038.jpg">Higa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15964" type="appears in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Nogami Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoi`s mother.</description>
<picture>44904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2491" picture="22429.jpg">Yamagata Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15965" type="appears in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="2">4.43</rating>
<name>Bonnie Parker</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clyde Barrow`s companion and creation. She is entirely controlled and ventriloquized by Clyde and is created from a sticky black liquid.</description>
<picture>44905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15966" type="appears in" update="2010-03-19">
<name>Clyde Barrow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Comerican esper criminal who wants to join PANDRA. He calls himself an artist and bases his abilities on teleportation. His companion Bonnie is one of his creations, created from a sticky black liquid controlled and ventriloquized by Clyde.</description>
<picture>44906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16010" type="appears in" update="2010-03-22">
<rating votes="5">3.85</rating>
<name>Kojika Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Hound`s new supervisor.</description>
<picture>45022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="215" picture="151687.jpg">Nakajima Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16011" type="appears in" update="2010-03-22">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Ruriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An art teacher in Naomi`s high school.</description>
<picture>45023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16012" type="appears in" update="2010-03-22">
<name>Kikuchi Naoya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2356" picture="22132.jpg">Yamaguchi Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16071" type="appears in" update="2010-03-25">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Black Phantom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The mysterious leader of the criminal esper organization Black Phantom.</description>
<picture>45174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16073" type="appears in" update="2010-03-25">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Bullet Silver</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An esper who specializes in controlling bullets using telekinesis. He can penetrate most espers` defenses in this way. He is a member of the esper criminal organization Black Phantom, perhaps against his will.</description>
<picture>45176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16074" type="appears in" update="2010-03-25">
<rating votes="3">4.73</rating>
<name>Kuromaki Setsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 19 year old former special agent esper trainee. Her power is based on telepathy and she uses it to manipulate dreams in order to create a dream world within the minds of others.</description>
<picture>45177.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16099" type="appears in" update="2010-03-26">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Badjura XVII</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The crown prince of the Imparahen Kingdom and a level 7 esper. Apparently he will be the 17th ruler of the Imparahen Kingdom with the name Badjura, making him Badjura XVII.</description>
<picture>45219.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16100" type="appears in" update="2010-03-26">
<name>Sera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A priestess in the Kingdom of Imparahen and a level 7 psychometer.
Her body was possessed by Masara, the grandmother of His Highness. Kaoru eventually forced her to leave Sera`s body and Sera and His Highness lived happily ever after, presumably.</description>
<picture>45220.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16101" type="appears in" update="2010-03-26">
<name>Tim Toy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Black Phantom whose esper abilities allow him to create, control and turn people into toys.</description>
<picture>45221.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16135" type="appears in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="6">6.16</rating>
<name>Caroline McGee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young woman Minamoto and Sakaki met while they were studying in Comerica. She originally had level 2 psychokinesis but she is currently a level 7 as a result of an experiment designed to improve esper powers. Another unexpected result of that experiment was the total loss of her memories that reverted her personality to that of a young child. Minamoto was put in charge of rehabilitating her to her former self and the two parted when her rehabilitation was completed. She is currently involved with the Comerica-Japan space program as a pilot.</description>
<picture>45266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16176" type="appears in" update="2010-03-28">
<name>Kawamura Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy in the third grade at the same school as the Children. He has latent esper abilities.</description>
<picture>45321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16177" type="appears in" update="2010-03-28">
<name>Kawamura Takenori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takeshi`s father. He is a researcher at Todou University and believes that espers are a danger to society.</description>
<picture>45322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16180" type="appears in" update="2010-03-28">
<name>Black Phantom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A criminal organisation.</description>
</character>
<character id="16194" type="appears in" update="2010-03-29">
<rating votes="13">2.79</rating>
<name>Patty Crew</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An unwilling member of Black Phantom. She can transform her entire body into black smoke and recreate herself at any location the black smoke occupies. Physical attacks have no effect on her.</description>
<picture>45347.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16201" type="appears in" update="2010-03-29">
<name>P.A.N.D.R.A.</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="19947" type="appears in" update="2010-07-23">
<rating votes="4">2.20</rating>
<name>Hino Kagari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy who is part of P.A.N.D.R.A. Kagari is a multipower esper, having abilities such as precog, psychokinesis, and pyrokinesis. He seems to be paired up on missions with Kazura often, considering her reactions towards her. In recent chapters, Kagari transferred into The Children`s class with other P.A.N.D.R.A. members as new students.</description>
<picture>45349.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19948" type="appears in" update="2010-07-23">
<rating votes="4">4.43</rating>
<name>Tamaki Kazura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl under P.A.N.D.R.A. who has a synthesized power, using tentacles and psychometry. She seems to be paired up on missions with Kagari often, considering her reactions towards him. In recent chapters, Kazura transferred into The Children`s class with other P.A.N.D.R.A. members as new students.</description>
<picture>45348.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19949" type="appears in" update="2010-07-23">
<rating votes="11">4.50</rating>
<name>Kumoi Yuuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Phantom Daughter, aka Kumoi Yuuri, is the daughter of the head of BLACK PHANTOM. She dresses in a gothic lolita fashion has long hair, and is of the same age as "The Children". She is an esper, her power being to put people in a different mindset, for example, Minamoto becoming a child in mind only, while Hyoubu from P.A.N.D.R.A. placed an illusion on him, making him seem like a child in every other way. She seems extremely loyal to her father, although when she meets Kaoru and reads her mind, she finds out that she is the Queen of Catastrophe, and seems extremely glad to have met her. She might think of her as a savior of some sort. At the end of the anime, Yuuri seems to have been liberated from BLACK PHANTOM, and is in fact joining the same middle school as Kaoru, Aoi and Shiho. Although it is known that she is the daughter of Black Phantom, not much is known about her, although later, Yuuri is revealed to have multiple personalities.</description>
<picture>45175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="88806" update="2008-04-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対可憐! その名はザ・チルドレン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Absolutely Lovely! Their Name Is "The Children"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Karen! Sono Na wa The Children</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89885" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">30 second commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89886" update="2008-04-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89949" update="2008-04-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高枕無憂! バベルの塔はそびえたつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Worry! The Soaring Tower of BABEL!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouchinbu Yuu! Babel no Tou wa Sobietatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90019" update="2017-02-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90085" update="2008-04-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪木盗泉! エスパーはつらいよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Virtuous Person! Being an Esper Is Tough</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aku Boku Tousen! Esper wa Tsurai yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90292" update="2008-04-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">柳暗花明! いけいけ♥プリティ女子高生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beautiful Spring Scenery! Go, Go Pretty Female High School Student</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuuankamei! Ike Ike Pretty Joshikousei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90379" update="2008-04-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">油断大敵! フツー入ってこないよね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unpreparedness Is Your Greatest Enemy! You Wouldn`t Normally Enter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yudantaiteki! Futsuu Haitte Konai yo ne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90503" update="2008-05-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">喧嘩上等! クラスメイトの目の前で...!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Superiority Quarrel! In Front of Your Classmate`s Eyes!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenka Joutou! Classmate no Me no Mae de...!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90651" update="2008-05-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">平々凡々! しばられたチルドレン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Very Ordinary! Restricted Children</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heihei Bonbon! Shibarareta Children</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90852" update="2008-05-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兵部京介! あ, 出ちゃったの?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hyobu Kyousuke! What, He Showed Up?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyoubu Kyousuke! A, Dechatta no?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91124" update="2008-05-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">容姿端麗! あたしたちがオトナに!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attractive Bodies! We`re Adults!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youshitanrei! Atashitachi ga Otona ni!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91179" update="2008-06-01">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">釜中之魚! いそげバベル2!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger Awaits! Hurry BABEL 2!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamanaka Kore Sakana! Isoge Babel2!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91438" update="2008-06-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">露天風呂! 湯けむりに光る目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot Springs! Shining Eyes in the Steam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rotenburo! Yukemuri ni Hikaru Me</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91575" update="2008-07-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">前途遼遠! 日本の未来をテレポート!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Long Road Ahead! Teleporting Japan`s Future!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zentouryouen! Nihon no Mirai o Teleport!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91594" update="2008-06-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">頭脳明晰!? チルドレンはメイ探偵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brilliant Minds!? The Children Are Great Detectives!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zunoumeiseki!? Children wa Meitantei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91595" update="2008-06-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家庭崩壊? ゴクラク大作戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Family Disruption? Operation Paradise!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katei Houkai? Gokuraku Daisakusen!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91973" update="2008-08-10">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金科玉条! 逃げちゃダメ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Golden Rule! Don`t Run Away!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinkagyokujou! Nigecha Dame!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92177" update="2008-08-10">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一諾千金! 遠い日の思い出...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Promise Is Worth Its Weight in Gold! Memories of a Distant Day...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichidakusenkin! Tooi Hi no Omoide...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92178" update="2008-08-10">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弱肉強食! 食べちゃうゾ♪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Survival of the Fittest! We`re Gonna Eat You!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jakunikukyoushoku! Tabechauzo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92439" update="2008-08-09">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走天使! ウチのナオミにかぎって...!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Runaway Angel! It Can`t Be My Naomi...!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou Tenshi! Uchi no Naomi ni Kagitte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92440" update="2008-08-09">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱愛発覚! チルドレン解散の危機!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Passionate Love Comes to Light! The Children`s Breakup Crisis!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Netsuai Hakkaku! Children Kaisan no Kiki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92677" update="2008-08-29">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超獣戯画! 時にはケダモノのように...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Beast Cartoon! Sometimes, You Act Like an Animal...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Kedamono Giga! Toki ni wa Kedamono no You ni...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92678" update="2008-08-29">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">器用貧乏! 彼は何で怒ったか!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jack of All Trades, Master of None! What`s He So Mad About!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiyoubinbou! Kare wa Nande Okottaka!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92737" update="2008-08-29">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孟母三遷! 皆本, 凶弾に散る!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Create a Learning Environment! Minamoto`s Been Gunned Down!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moubosansen! Minamoto, Kyoudan ni Chiru!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92804" update="2008-08-30">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">急転直下! 奪われちゃった...!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plot Twist! Stolen Away...!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuutenchokka! Ubawarechatta...!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92956" update="2008-09-09">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">専業主夫! 洗われちゃった...!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stay at Home Dad! Cleaned...!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sengyoushufu! Arawarechatta...!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93014" update="2008-09-16">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">安産祈願! こんにちは, 赤ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Prayer for an Easy Birth! Hello, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anzan Kigan! Konnichiwa, Aka-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93096" update="2008-09-22">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">予知改変? 未来は踊る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Change of Prediction? The Future Dances!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yochi Kaihen? Mirai wa Odoru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93097" update="2008-09-22">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宣戦布告! パンドラからの挑戦状</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Declaration of War! A Challenge from PANDORA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensenfukoku! Pandora kara no Chousenjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93313" update="2008-10-05">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">羞月閉花! 蕾見チュー意報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Lady`s Special Charms! Tsubomi Kiss Alert</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuugetsu Heika! Tsubomi Chuu Ihou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93515" update="2008-10-12">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">手練手管! 天国に一番近い海</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Art of Coaxing! The Sea Closest to Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Terentekuda! Tengoku ni Ichiban Chikai Umi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93699" update="2008-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">呉越同舟! 金庫破りは計画的に♥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enemies in the Same Boat! Safecracking Is Systematic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goetsu Doushuu! Kinkoyaburi wa Keikakuteki ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93871" update="2008-10-27">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界遺産! ほな, 京都に行こか!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">World Heritage! C`mon, Shall We Go to Kyoto?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai Isan! Hona, Kyoto ni Ikoka!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="94803" update="2008-11-04">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">珍味佳肴! タッチ・ミー・イフ・ユー・キャン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Rare Treat! Touch Me If You Can!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chinmikakou! Touch Me if You Can</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95091" update="2008-11-10">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秋之行楽! ランチボックスは藪の中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Autumn Outing! The Lunch Box Is in a Grove</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aki no Kouraku! Lunch Box wa Yabu no Naka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95171" update="2008-11-17">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">朝蠅暮蚊! 皆本が手をする足をする!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Overrun with Pests! Minamoto Uses His Hands &amp; Feet?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chouyou Bobun! Minamoto ga Te o Suru Ashi o Suru!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95330" update="2008-11-25">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">多情多恨! 初音の家出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Letting Your Feelings Hang Out! Hatsune Runs Away</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tajou Takon! Hatsune no Iede</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95613" update="2008-12-08">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">男子禁制! 天使たちの午後</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Boys Allowed! The Angels` Afternoon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Danshi Kinsei! Tenshi-tachi no Gogo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95614" update="2008-12-08">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強敵来襲! ブラック・ファントム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Mighty Enemy Attacks! Black Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouteki! Black Phantom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95693" update="2008-12-15">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">胡蝶之夢! ドリームメイカー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Butterfly`s Dream! Dream Maker</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kochou! Dream Maker</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95827" update="2008-12-22">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢幻泡影! サイコダイバーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Impermanent Existence! Psycho-Divers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mugen Houmatsu! Psycho Divers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95950" recap="true" update="2011-07-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大盤振舞! 奈津子とほたるのバベル通信</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Grand Banquet! Natsuko and Hotaru`s BABEL Report</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oobanburumai! Natsuko to Hotaruno B.A.B.E.L. Tsuushin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96197" update="2009-01-07">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蕾見山荘! 突入せよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsubomi Mountain Retreat! Break In!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubomi Sansou! Totsunyuu Seyo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96300" update="2009-01-12">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">比翼連理! 国王陛下のチルドレン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marital Vows! His Majesty`s Children!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiyokurenri! Kokuou Heika no Children</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96301" update="2009-01-12">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">合体問題! ファンタスティック・トイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Combination Complication! Fantastic Toy!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gattai Mondai! Fantastic Toy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96359" update="2017-02-16">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96504" update="2009-01-26">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">合縁奇縁! キャロライン, 運命の再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Oddly Perfect Couple! Caroline, a Destined Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aienkien! Caroline, Unmei no Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96831" update="2009-02-02">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛別離苦! キャリー, 永遠の別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Painful Parting! Goodbye Forever, Carry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aibetsuriku! Carrie, Eien no Wakare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96906" update="2009-02-09">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天賦自然! ギフト・オブ・チルドレン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Natural talents Are Natural! Gift of Children</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenpu Shizen! Gift of Children</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97018" update="2009-02-16">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疑心暗鬼! その通りになるのです帳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suspicion Raises Suspicion! The "Make It So" Book</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gishin Anki! Sono Toori ni Naru no Desu Chou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97058" update="2009-02-18">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">理力騒然! 見えざる脅威</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Disturbance in the Force! The Phantom Menace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Riryoku Souzen! Miezaru Kyoui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97059" update="2009-02-18">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一場春夢! 明日の想い出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life`s Troubles Are But a Dream! Memories of Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichijou Shunmu! Ashita no Omoide</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97324" update="2009-03-09">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">有為転変! えっ, 皆本が!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Impermanence of Life! Huh? Minamoto Has Been...?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uitenpen! Eh, Minamoto ga!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97363" update="2009-03-12">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜花爛漫! じゃあまたね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Riot of Cherry Blossoms! Bye-Bye, Till We Meet Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oukaranman! Jaa Mata ne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97364" update="2009-03-12">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一意奮闘! オーバー・ザ・フューチャー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Giving It All You Have! Over the Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichii Funtou! Over the Future</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119037" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Chou Sakidori Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125957" update="2017-02-16">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125958" update="2017-02-16">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125959" update="2017-02-16">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125960" update="2017-02-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138870" update="2012-04-14">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Sponsored Ads 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138871" update="2012-04-14">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Sponsored Ads 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184613" update="2017-02-16">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
