<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5679" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-07-14</startdate>
<enddate>2008-12-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mugen no Juunin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">L`habitant de l`infini</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">L`immortale</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Клинок Бессмертного</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="synonym">Ostří Nesmrtelného</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Nemirtingojo Kardas</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Ölümsüzün Kılıcı</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Острието на безсмъртния</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">無限之住人</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">BotI</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">無限の住人</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Blade of the Immortal</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Miecz Nieśmiertelnego</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Blade: A Lâmina do Imortal</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14912" type="Alternative Setting">Mugen no Juunin: Immortal</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2436" approval="49" total="56">Basilisk: Kouga Ninpou Chou</anime>
<anime id="5108" approval="39" total="49">Shigurui</anime>
<anime id="277" approval="29" total="34">Juubee Ninpuuchou</anime>
<anime id="73" approval="13" total="26">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan - Tsuioku Hen</anime>
<anime id="53" approval="5" total="18">Trigun</anime>
<anime id="98" approval="5" total="13">Kenpuu Denki Berserk</anime>
<anime id="13946" approval="5" total="11">Dororo (2019)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="130855">i didnt like it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="304586">It`s a verry good story</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="567284">It was a good story and nice design but it has also an open ending that was not good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="271087">It has some good action scenes in it and enjoyed blood and gore.
oOne of the downfalls i saw with this anime was the way it ended, it felt like only half of the story was told.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="269102">G0dL1k3</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://mugen.kc.kodansha.co.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="749" type="Animation Work">Bee Train</name>
<name id="2457" type="Character Design">Yamashita Yoshimitsu</name>
<name id="3718" type="Series Composition">Kawasaki Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="749" type="Work">Bee Train</name>
<name id="691" type="Direction">Mashimo Kouichi</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
<name id="5996" type="Original Work">Samura Hiroaki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr5996 [Samura Hiroaki], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr31447 [Afternoon].
"To end his eternal suffering, he must slay one thousand enemies!"
http://anidb.net/ch2643 [Manji], a ronin warrior of feudal Japan, has been cursed with immortality. To rid himself of this curse and end his life of misery, he must slay one thousand evil men. His quest begins when a young girl seeks his help in taking revenge on her parents` killers... and his quest will not end until the blood of a thousand has spilled!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1794">4.73</permanent>
<temporary count="1827">6.83</temporary>
<review count="2">4.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>52852.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9691</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4151</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4297</identifier>
<identifier>xfulaa</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mugen.kc.kodansha.co.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Blade_of_the_Immortal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>無限の住人</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1413</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330594</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2690" parentid="2641" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Tokugawa period</name>
<description>The anime takes place during a period of Japanese history running from 1603 to 1868.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3378" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>redemption</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2643" type="main character in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="11">7.35</rating>
<name>Manji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The immortal referred to in the title. While not lazy, he is very laid-back, often seen sleeping. The fallen samurai Manji served the Hatamoto Horii Shigenobu, a local daimyo, enforcing his brutal rule (unknowingly) on the local populace until he found out his lord was corrupt and killed him. For that he was considered an outlaw and hunted down by the same daimyo clan, achieving the nickname "Killer of 100" after the body count.</description>
<picture>68197.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2644" type="main character in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="12">4.42</rating>
<name>Asano Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The sole survivor of an Ittou-ryuu massacre at Anotsu`s hand and heir to her father`s sword school, the "Mutenichi-ryuu". She has mediocre swordsmanship skills but an intense desire to avenge the brutal death of her family. At the beginning of the series is she portrayed as somebody who is trying to act mature, but is still very childish - as the series progresses she steadily "grows up" and loses much of her naivety. She hires Manji as her bodyguard in this quest.</description>
<picture>68198.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2645" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="8">5.06</rating>
<name>Anotsu Kagehisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of the Ittou-ryuu and equal of Manji. This emotionally cold young man has prodigious skill with the sword, and leads the Ittou-ryuu in order to form a dojo dedicated not to form and rules, but to the simple test of superior lethality. Brought up by an abusive grandfather (a swordsman disgraced by the Asano dojo), Anotsu is as pragmatic and shrewd as he is deadly.</description>
<picture>68199.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2646" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="4">4.99</rating>
<name>Magatsu Taito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Among the Ittou-ryuu`s finest swordsmen. Of peasant origin, he became a swordsman to avenge his sister, who was killed as a child by a samurai. Taito is one of the few swordsmen who has fought Manji and survived. He has also fought by Manji`s side as well. He can be considered a kenshi, a swordsman who is not from the samurai class.</description>
<picture>68200.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2647" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="5">2.09</rating>
<name>Kuroi Sabato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Skilled pupil of Anotsu Saburou (Anotsu Kagehisa`s grandfather) and master Ittou-ryuu swordsman.</description>
<picture>68201.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2648" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Shizuma Eikuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Immortal swordsman. Gifted with the same blood-worms as Manji, he seeks to gain Manji as an ally to overthrow Anotsu.</description>
<picture>68202.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2649" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="4">2.09</rating>
<name>Kawakami Araya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An Ittou-ryuu swordsman living as a mask-maker.</description>
<picture>68204.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2650" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="6">7.82</rating>
<name>Otono-Tachibana Makie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Master swordswoman and in love with Anotsu. Said to be Anotsu`s match and saved his life with her deadly abilities when they were children.</description>
<picture>68203.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2651" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="6">7.04</rating>
<name>Hyakurin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female assassin and a lieutenant in the Mugai-ryuu.</description>
<picture>68206.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2652" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="5">6.14</rating>
<name>Giichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A highly skilled Mugai-ryuu killer.</description>
<picture>68207.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2653" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="3">4.60</rating>
<name>Shira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cold-blooded killer in the Mugai-ryuu. He`s responsible for the death of Magatsu Taito`s close friend, O-Ren. Shira`s a sadistic psychopath who derives sexual pleasure in the torture and murder of his victims, particularly young women.</description>
<picture>68208.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2654" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-23">
<rating votes="5">5.74</rating>
<name>Machi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2655" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="6">5.51</rating>
<name>Habaki Kagimura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the Shogun`s Banshu samurai, the Bangashira, and secret leader of the Mugai-ryuu. He simultaneously invites the Ittou-ryuu to become an official sword school while directing the Mugai-ryuu against it.</description>
<picture>68205.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2656" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Souri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high-ranking spy and ninja obsessed with art, driven into political intrigue in order to gain access to European art, which is contraband in that period.</description>
<picture>68210.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9599" type="appears in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Yaobikuni</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68211.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10177" type="appears in" update="2009-07-04">
<rating votes="1">1.03</rating>
<name>Shido Hishiyasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of the world`s baddest ronin gang, the Shinsengumi. After Manji killed his brother "Johnny", Hishiyasu sought revenge by kidnapping Manji`s sister, Machi, to use her as bait.
- from wikipedia</description>
<picture>30560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10178" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Shinriji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bumbling Mugai-ryuu swordsman.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>68209.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2258" picture="21881.jpg">Uchida Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10179" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-04">
<rating votes="3">6.22</rating>
<name>Tatsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daughter of Sori.</description>
<picture>30564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="90494" update="2008-05-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91678" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">罪人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Criminal</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الإجرام</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zainin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91679" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">征服</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conquest</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الفتح</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seifuku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92065" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92066" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92463" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋詠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Song</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">قصيدة الحب</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92464" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天才</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Genius</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">عبقري</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92465" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">執人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shogunate aka. Army Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuujin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93117" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蟲の唄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cries of the Bugs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mushi no Uta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93187" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三途</title>
<title xml:lang="en">3 ways</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanzu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93684" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">爪弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strumming</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumabiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="94822" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream Shot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yumebiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95280" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">變面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Changing Face</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawarimen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95352" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">羽根</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Feathers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hane</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95353" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">斜凜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nemesis of Rin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sharin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95354" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
