<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="572" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>47</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>1997-02-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mizuiro Jidai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Aqua Age</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Blue Green Years</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Temi d`amore tra i banchi di scuola</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">水色時代</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">L`âge bleu</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1213" approval="6" total="7">Miracle Girls</anime>
<anime id="11899" approval="3" total="6">12-Sai. Chicchana Mune no Tokimeki</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.asahi-net.or.jp/~hv8k-itu/aqua/aqua_age.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="839" type="Animation Work">Studio Comet</name>
<name id="3634" type="Series Composition">Takegami Junki</name>
<name id="114" type="Direction">Tokita Hiroko</name>
<name id="8919" type="Original Work">Yabuuchi Yuu</name>
<name id="5509" type="Character Design">Yamaoka Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="34483" type="Music">Saitou Neko</name>
<name id="5147" type="Music">Yamamoto Harukichi</name>
</creators>
<description>Mizuiro Jidai is the story of the life of http://anidb.net/ch27836 [Kawai Yuuko], a normal girl growing up. The series begins at the start of her 8th grade year of school, and follows her life through its many small and large ups and downs. The anime`s title refers to the time in a girl`s life when everything is new, a time of growing up.
Yuuko is a cute, somewhat insecure girl. She is a good writer but is somewhat shy of her talents and worries about others not liking her work. Yuuko has grown up all her life in the same house with her http://anidb.net/ch27837 [mother], http://anidb.net/ch27839 [father], and older http://anidb.net/ch27838 [sister]. Living right next door is one of Yuuko`s closest friends, http://anidb.net/ch27841 [Hiroshi]. Yuuko and Hiroshi have been friends since childhood, but recently their feelings for each other have been changing.
The series gives the audience a view at Yuuko`s life through the seasons as she goes through such events as school trips, jyuku (cram school), band, making new friends, finding love, dealing with her parents and learning more about them, holidays, and sports. Yuuko`s normal fears of the future and the unknown are explored, and the joys of her life are shared.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="112">6.09</permanent>
<temporary count="112">6.83</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>1818.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1162</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1040</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>271</identifier>
<identifier>htzesx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.asahi-net.or.jp/~hv8k-itu/aqua/aqua_age.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>水色時代</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88951</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1326</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="27824" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-27">
<name>Ayumi Senpai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3137" picture="24122.jpg">Nakao Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27825" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Nakagawara Nobuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3139">Yuasa Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27826" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-06">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kugayama Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27827" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-27">
<name>Igawa-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2799" picture="23198.jpg">Matsuno Taiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27828" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-28">
<name>Senkawa Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6928" picture="211675.jpg">Matsumoto Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27829" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Daitabashi-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21325" picture="55276.jpg">Akado Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27830" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-27">
<name>Hachiouji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4682" picture="27282.jpg">Kashiwakura Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27831" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-28">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kitano Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3853.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4428" picture="26693.jpg">Miyajima Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27832" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Miyauchi Fuyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7068" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27833" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Hirayama Rumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34596">Matsuura Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27834" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Shibazaki Haruhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27835" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-28">
<name>Hashimoto Norihito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64645.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27836" type="main character in" update="2011-01-28">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kawai Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27837" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-27">
<name>Kawai Atsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kawai Atsuko is Yuuko`s mother.</description>
<picture>64587.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27838" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Kawai Toshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kawai Toshiko is Yuuko`s older sister.</description>
<picture>64762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20279" picture="52921.jpg">Nakao Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27839" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Kawai Yasuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kawai Yasuo is Yuuko`s father.</description>
<picture>64648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23537" picture="64616.jpg">Tayama Ryousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27840" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Katakura Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="337" picture="223875.jpg">Namiki Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27841" type="main character in" update="2011-01-28">
<name>Naganumo Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23536">Akiyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27842" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Tobita Tomoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29992">Nakamura Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27843" type="main character in" update="2011-01-28">
<name>Takahata Takako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2140" picture="21615.jpg">Higuchi Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27987" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Hoken no Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27992" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Suugaku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3137" picture="24122.jpg">Nakao Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27995" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Kitano no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3137" picture="24122.jpg">Nakao Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27997" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Rika Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27999" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Yamashita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4682" picture="27282.jpg">Kashiwakura Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28010" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Rika Onna Kyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64738.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="28015" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Mit-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64744.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="28016" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Gan-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30015">Okada Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28018" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>1 Nen 5 Gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="28019" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>2 Nen 5 Gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="28020" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Inoue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="22083" picture="58333.jpg">Ishikawa Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28021" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Matsumoto</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="28022" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Ooyama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5046" picture="28852.jpg">Nakai Masataka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28023" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Kokugo Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2057" picture="21394.jpg">Kaneko Yukinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28024" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Murayama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="30015">Okada Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28025" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Biyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3137" picture="24122.jpg">Nakao Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28026" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Norinaga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="7068" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28027" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Shibazaki no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28028" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Sasatsuka-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28029" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<name>Takako no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="20279" picture="52921.jpg">Nakao Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28040" type="appears in" update="2011-01-30">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Karasuyama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20280" picture="81719.jpg">Matamura Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28095" type="appears in" update="2011-02-01">
<name>Uemizu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64868.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29152" type="appears in" update="2011-02-25">
<name>Ojisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29153" type="appears in" update="2011-02-25">
<name>Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20280" picture="81719.jpg">Matamura Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29154" type="appears in" update="2012-04-25">
<name>Kakegawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35136" type="appears in" update="2011-08-04">
<name>Inada Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76428.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35137" type="appears in" update="2011-08-04">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Tsutsumi Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11010" picture="39521.jpg">Fujieda Nariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35138" type="appears in" update="2011-08-04">
<name>Koushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41745" type="appears in" update="2012-02-25">
<name>Yamada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6446" update="2011-05-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新学期</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New School Term</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shingakki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6715" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7870" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">林間学校</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Outdoor School</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9193" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソフトボール大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Softball Tournament</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10061" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれちがい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chance Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12402" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お姉ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onee-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15231" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマス会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christmas Kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20793" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バレンタイン・デー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Valentine`s Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Valentine Day</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25675" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学年末テスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Exam</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25676" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩後輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pulling Rank</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25677" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タカ子の恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Takako`s Sweetheart</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25678" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クラス替え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Classes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Class Kae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64956" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジェラシー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jealousy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jealousy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64957" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイエット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Diet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Diet</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64958" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏休み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Vacation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsuyasumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64959" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の季節</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Stormy Season</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Kisetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64960" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふつう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ordinary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futsuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64961" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三角関係</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Triangle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sankakukankei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64962" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋と友情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love and Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi to Yuujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64963" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">初日の出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Sunrise of the New Year</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsu Hi no De</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64964" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">塾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cram School</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64965" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋人同士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boyfriend and Girlfriend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koibitodoushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64966" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">仲たがい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Friendship in Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakatagai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64967" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">修学旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Trip!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64968" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おいてけぼり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Left Behind</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64969" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カルい山田くん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Carefree Yamada-Kun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64970" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コンクール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Concours</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64971" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">笑わない代ばば</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Stoic Old Hag</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64972" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラブレター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Letter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love Letter</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64973" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢と現実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreams And Reality</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64974" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒロシの夏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hiroshi`s Summer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64975" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">文化祭前夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eve Of The Cultural Festival!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64976" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">いちばん星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Evening Star</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64977" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">進学問題</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New School Troubles</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64978" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレゼント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Present</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Present</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64979" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒業</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64980" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ちの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day Of Our Departure</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64981" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの頃のように</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Way We Were</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64982" recap="true" update="2015-12-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">水色の季節たち 総集編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aqua Seasons</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64983" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出アルバム1 恋愛未満</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unrequited Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64984" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出アルバム2 グローイングアップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Growing Up</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64985" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出アルバム3 みやうの恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miyau`s Crush</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64986" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出アルバム4 はじめての友達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Friends</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64987" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出アルバム5 お母さんの恋人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mom`s Sweetheart</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64988" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出アルバム6 ナイショの夏物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Secret Summer Story</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64989" update="2011-09-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出アルバム7 男たちの修学旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Boys-Only School Trip</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64990" update="2011-05-26">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出アルバム8 天使からフォー・ユー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Angel`s Gift</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127985" update="2011-02-07">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127986" update="2011-02-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1996-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127987" update="2011-02-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1996-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
