<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5746" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-12</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Golgo 13 (2008)</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">غولغو 13</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Giolginas 13</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Голго 13</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Голго 13 (2008)</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Ґолґо 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Golgo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Golgo TV</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゴルゴ13 (2008)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Golgo 13</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1076" type="Prequel">Golgo 13</anime>
<anime id="1077" type="Other">Golgo 13: Queen Bee</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4637" approval="4" total="6">009-1</anime>
<anime id="942" approval="3" total="10">City Hunter</anime>
<anime id="1018" approval="1" total="5">Crying Freeman</anime>
<anime id="3291" approval="1" total="4">Jigoku Shoujo</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="79753">Recommended for KILLING TIME; awesome seinen (lots of mundane sex) / underground / gunfight / Kenshirou (Fist of the North Star, but focused on his trusty m16) / walker (texas ranger - never dies... oops spoiler - like i said only to kill time.)
Despite all 50 episodes being the same, this anime was quite entertaining. Dont expect a superior plot with this anime...
It wasnt until episode 48; I thought to myself that GOLGO 13 is truly a machine with no human-emotions. 3/5 - 6.5/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="157201">It almost feels like a detective series. Except instead of solving crimes, he kills people. Otherwise it is relaxing, and an easy watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="358928">Mr. Togo dislike knife.
Easy to watch, relaxing and thrilling at the same time. Each (almost) unique plan to kill with occasionally twist part.Well, that`s what we are expecting from fantastic hitman series without some continuous plot.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="339886">M-16 action!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/golgo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1292" type="Animation Work">The Answer Studio</name>
<name id="7860" type="Character Design">Takeuchi Kazuyoshi</name>
<name id="5578" type="Chief Direction">Ooga Shunji</name>
<name id="8651" type="Original Work">Saitou Takao</name>
</creators>
<description>Duke Togo, aka http://anidb.net/ch9473 [Golgo 13], is a professional assassin. His age and birthplace are unknown and there is no consensus in the worldwide intelligence community as to his true identity. Most of his jobs are completed through the use of a customized, scoped M16 rifle.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="766">5.83</permanent>
<temporary count="783">7.11</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>7823.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9341</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4039</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4222</identifier>
<identifier>raklex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/golgo/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Golgo_13</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゴルゴ13</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1339</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330276</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4350" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>imperial stormtrooper marksmanship academy</name>
<description>When only the Bad Guys suffer from A-Team Firing. Also called The Principle of Evil Marksmanship. The good guys (the non-Red Shirt ones, at least - and sometimes even them, too) can stand in the middle of the firefight and never get hit, and can pick off any bad guy with even the most casually-aimed shot while the bad guys seem unable to hit the broad side of a barn.
This is a degree of Truth in Television, as by far most shots fired in firefights or combat are misses. Some sources report that in WWII, the average soldier needed to fire two hundred rounds for every hit scored on an enemy; numerous other examples are mentioned in the Real Life section of this page. So the fictional bad guys don`t actually suffer from unrealistic inaccuracy; rather, the heroes`s fictional performance would count as Improbable Aiming Skills in real life. Or they were instead ordered not to shoot the person. 
Source: TVTropes</description>
<picurl>162915.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9473" type="main character in" update="2009-06-16">
<rating votes="44">9.21</rating>
<name>Golgo 13</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5164" picture="29115.jpg">Tachi Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="88816" update="2008-04-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">AT PIN-HOLE!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At Pin-Hole!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">At Pin-Hole!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90075" update="2008-04-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ROOM・No.909</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Room No.909</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Room No.909</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90076" update="2008-04-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傑作・アサルトライフル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Masterpiece Assault Rifle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessaku Assault Rifle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90077" update="2008-06-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリティウーマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pretty Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pretty Woman</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90078" update="2008-05-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパースターの共演</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Superstars` Joint Appearance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Superstar no Kyouen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90675" update="2008-05-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神に贈られし物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Offering to God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami ni Okurareshi Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90676" update="2008-05-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">G線上の狙撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sharpshoot on the G String</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">G Senjou no Sogeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90677" update="2008-05-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">動作・24分の4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Action in 4/24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dousa 24 Bun no 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90678" update="2008-05-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">檻の中の眠り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sleep Inside the Cage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ori no Naka no Nemuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91385" update="2008-06-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰ってきた標的</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Target Returned</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaette Kita Hyouteki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91468" update="2010-11-12">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クロスアングル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cross Angle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cross Angle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91469" update="2009-04-13">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TOUCH DOWN</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Touchdown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touch Down</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91470" update="2008-06-19">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デッド・アングル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dead Angle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dead Angle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91898" update="2008-07-09">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">落日の死影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deadly Shadow of the Setting Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakujitsu no Shi Kage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91963" update="2008-07-14">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海へ向かうエバ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eva Heads Toward the Ocean</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi e Mukau Eva</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92046" update="2008-07-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死臭の聖者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saint That Reeks of Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shishuu no Shouja</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92251" update="2008-08-02">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">残光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Afterglow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zankou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92432" update="2009-04-02">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スタインベック三世</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steinbeck the Third</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Steinbeck Sansei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92559" update="2008-08-17">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">インディアン・サマー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Indian Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Indian Summer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92560" update="2008-08-17">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガリンペイロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Garimpeiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Garin Peiro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92561" update="2008-08-17">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メランコリー・夏[サマー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Melancholy Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Melancholy Summer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92562" update="2008-08-17">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">硝子[ガラス]の要塞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Glass Fortress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Glass no Yousai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92963" update="2008-09-09">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジェット・ストリーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jet Stream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jet Stream</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93118" update="2008-09-24">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サンタ・アナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Santa Ana</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Santa Ana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93128" update="2008-09-24">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冷血キャサリン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cold-Blooded Catherine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reiketsu Catherine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93129" update="2008-09-24">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フロリダ・チェイス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Florida Chase</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Florida Chase</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93513" update="2010-11-12">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フィアレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fearless</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fearless</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93658" update="2010-11-12">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白夜は愛のうめき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Midnight Sun Means Sighs of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Byakuya wa Ai no Umeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="94811" update="2010-11-12">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANGRY WAVES</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angry Waves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angry Waves</title>
</episode>
<episode id="94812" update="2010-11-12">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラブはナイフ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Is a Knife</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love wa Knife</title>
</episode>
<episode id="94813" update="2010-11-12">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">配役[キャスティング]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Casting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Casting</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95153" update="2010-11-12">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">殺意の交差</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Crossover of Murderous Intent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satsui no Kousa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95282" update="2010-11-12">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誇り高き葡萄酒(ワイン)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wine of Renown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokori Takaki Wine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95597" update="2010-11-12">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">殺人劇の夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Night of the Murder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satsujin Geki no Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95771" update="2008-12-19">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血統の掟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Lineage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kettou no Okite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95772" update="2008-12-19">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死に絶えた盛装</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Outmoded Livery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinitaeta Seiso</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95773" update="2008-12-19">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマス・24アワーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas, 24 Hours</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christmas 24 Hours</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95774" update="2008-12-19">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女サラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Young Girl Sarah</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Sarah</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95775" update="2009-01-22">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アッシュ最良の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ash`s Greatest Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ash Sairyou no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96446" update="2009-01-22">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼畜の宴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Banquet for Brutes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kichiku no Utage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96455" update="2009-01-22">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ペチコートレーンの夜霧</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Night Fog of Petticoat Lane</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Petticoat Lane no Yogiri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96521" update="2009-04-19">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大きな口(ラージ・マウス)の湖上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Above Largemouth Lake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Large Mouth no Kojou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96916" update="2009-04-19">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空白の依頼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blank Request</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuuhaku no Irai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97069" update="2009-04-19">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロックフォードの野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rockford`s Ambition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rockford no Yabou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97271" update="2009-04-19">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">36000秒分の1秒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Second Among 36,000</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">36000 Byou Bun no 1 Byou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97272" update="2009-04-19">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世紀末ハリウッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">End-of-the-Century Hollywood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seikimatsu Hollywood</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97385" update="2009-04-19">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜は消えず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lingering Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoru wa Kiezu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97386" update="2009-04-19">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い瞳 EBONY EYES</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Pupils, Ebony Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Hitomi, Ebony Eyes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97481" update="2009-04-19">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">装甲兵SDR2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Armored Soldier SDR2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soukouhei SDR2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97482" update="2009-04-19">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使と悪魔の "腕"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The "Skill" of Angels and Devils</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi to Akuma no "Ude"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98561" update="2009-04-02">
<epno type="5">P18</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Parody Ep 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125273" update="2010-11-16">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">ED2 - Yume no Hitotsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125274" update="2010-11-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">ED1 - Garasu no Haiwei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125275" update="2010-11-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">OP1 - Take The Wave</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
