<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5749" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-06-11</startdate>
<enddate>2008-08-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ikkitousen: Great Guardians</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ikkitousen 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">igg</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ikki3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">一騎当千 Great Guardians</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ikki Tousen: Great Guardians</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Ikki Tousen - Great Guardians</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ikki Tousen - Great Guardians</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">일기당천 그레이트 가디언스</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7219" type="Sequel">Ikkitousen: Xtreme Xecutor</anime>
<anime id="4870" type="Prequel">Ikkitousen: Dragon Destiny</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="22546">Only for extreme fans of the characters in the show. This can be likened to a side story or filler arc in a show like Naruto of Bleach, except with almost no actual fights that are exciting to watch. In the first 8 of 13 episodes there are no fights extending longer than 4 punches or kicks, and none of them end with a victory for any combatant. There`s no Dragon/Leader to fight, nothing. There are a lot more nipples but that`s about it. As a fan of the first two seasons I was quite disappointed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="104619">Seems better than the past seasons.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="310237">This Series Is Asome And have Atons OF Funny Staff</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="288870">If you like good fights and babes you must watch this (^_^)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ikkitousen.com/gg/</url>
<creators>
<name id="771" type="Animation Work">Arms</name>
<name id="3063" type="Character Design">Rin Sin</name>
<name id="1391" type="Direction">Oohata Kouichi</name>
<name id="3063" type="Chief Animation Direction">Rin Sin</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
<name id="6311" type="Series Composition">Akahoshi Masanao</name>
<name id="9123" type="Original Work">Shiozaki Yuuji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr9123 [Shiozaki Yuuji].
It is http://anidb.net/ch2075 [Hakufu]`s ambition to fight against new opponents from all over the world. To pay for the travelling expenses — to be able to visit these tournaments — she got a job, to earn enough money to make her dream come true.
Little did Hakufu expect that new allies and enemies would detract from her goal. Or that she might even be considered a weak leader in the eyes of her companions. To top it off a sister suddenly appears, making it painfully obvious to Hakufu that she does not really know much about her mother`s past.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1515">3.97</permanent>
<temporary count="1541">6.56</temporary>
<review count="2">5.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>9371.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9439</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5333</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4196</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4279</identifier>
<identifier>rpdodq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ikkitousen.com/gg/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ikki_Tousen</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>一騎当千_(漫画)#一騎当千_Great_Guardians</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1386</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330640</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10234</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3510" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-01">
<name>ancient rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3734" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-14">
<name>school rivalry</name>
<description>Simple description for a "School vs School in all-out physical-combat" series.
No matter how geographically close or far apart the schools are, students from different schools are enemies by default and are likely to engage in physical fights on sight (except on the occasion that certain schools form pacts of alliance or peace).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4192" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-22">
<name>broadcast cropped to 4-3</name>
<description>Although this anime was created in 16:9 (widescreen) aspect ratio, its Japanese TV broadcasts were all cropped to 4:3 (fullscreen). It was only made available in 16:9 upon its DVD/BD release.
Note: This tag does NOT apply to series that had initial broadcasts in 4:3 and 16:9 broadcasts several weeks later, such as Clannad, Asu no Yoichi, K-On!, etc. For those, use "Delayed 16-9 broadcast".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4399" parentid="2641" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>Three Kingdoms</name>
<description>Chinese names to the likes of Liu Bei, Guan Yu, Zhang Fei, Cao Cao, Sun Jian, as well as their allies, enemies and subordinates are used or referenced amongst primary and secondary characters.
The use of these names commonly portray the characters as they were historically as warlords and soldiers from the ancient Chinese novel or as foreshadowing to which characters are destined to be allies or enemies.
Certain characters are often glorified above others in relevance or conflict with the original novel (as to follow historically or just provide entertainment with the use of historical figures and events using fictional scenarios).
The supposed historical novel itself was written in the 14th century by Luo Guanzhong of China and is based upon events in the turbulent years near the end of the Han Dynasty and the Three Kingdoms era of China, starting in 169 and ending in 280.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2075" type="main character in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="217">5.97</rating>
<name>Sonsaku Hakufu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is busty, light red haired, green-eyed, not terribly bright.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>10492.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2076" type="main character in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="255">7.60</rating>
<name>Ryomou Shimei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An odd girl with short blue hair and green eyes, a distinctive mole on her left cheek and a very strange history, mainly tied to her mysterious left-eye patch. Powerful and a B-rank, she is one of the Four Devas of Nanyo. She has a habit of wearing a blue miniskirted French maid outfit and specialises in submission wrestling moves, throws, and joint attacks, which she uses in conjunction with a pair of handcuffs she carries; she is also very proficient in making chi blasts.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>10498.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2078" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="75">4.17</rating>
<name>Shuuyu Koukin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hakufu`s rich cousin and an attractive pretty boy; both Kan`u and Ukitsu have expressed exclusive interest in him. C-rank.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>43432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2079" type="main character in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="37">3.51</rating>
<name>Saji Genpou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious man with blond hair and a light tan, his real identity is Ouin Shishi. One of Ryomou`s oldest friends he has feelings for both her and Ryofu. However, he is a complete womanizer. His goals are uncertain as are his rank and power but he is easily an A-rank.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>16913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2080" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="51">4.90</rating>
<name>Gakushuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A large muscular man with a scary face but a very nice personality. A man of honor to the very core, he prides himself in this and in his rippling muscles but usually gets beaten by all but the weakest of opponents. He is a B-rank and one of the Four Devas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>16914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="318" picture="69041.jpg">Iijima Hajime</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2092" type="main character in" update="2018-09-19">
<rating votes="124">8.00</rating>
<name>Ryofu Housen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryofu Housen is a strong bisexual fighter with a very promiscuous personality and a habit for dressing skimpy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>224095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2095" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="41">7.16</rating>
<name>Kakouton Genjou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Affectionately referred to as Basics Ton-chan by Hakufu for his love of using only the most basic moves in combat abhorring (and perhaps being incapable of) any other kind of combat. A honorable but eccentric young man, he goes to great lengths to repair the damage done to any place he fights, patching walls and pavement and believing such a place to be a dojo he must maintain. He is a very good friend of both Sousou and Kakuka and has a crush on Hakufu, who is on very good terms with him.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>1415.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3156" picture="76983.jpg">Sakaguchi Shuuhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2096" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="47">3.62</rating>
<name>Sousou Moutoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The eccentric leader of Kyosho and best friend to Genjou and Houkou and a B-rank fighter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>1337.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="325" picture="223404.jpg">Akagi Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2098" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="365">8.71</rating>
<name>Kan`u Unchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Believed to be the most feared and powerful Toushi around, she even carries the nearly invincible Blue Dragon Crescent Blade from her predecessor as well as the legendary sword Kusanagi; she also has overwhelming chi. She believes her destiny is to die protecting Ryuubi.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>10493.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2101" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="54">7.13</rating>
<name>Goei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hakufu`s widowed, extremely promiscuous and flirtatious mother, a strong fighter, and a loving yet strict mother who is not above getting drunk at parties with her daughter or pummeling her into the floorboards. She unexpectedly moves in with Koukin and Hakufu.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>43434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7499" type="main character in" update="2018-09-19">
<rating votes="35">7.93</rating>
<name>Sonken Chuubou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224094.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14370" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="62">3.96</rating>
<name>Ryuubi Gentoku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A complete bookworm and a hopeless fighter (classified E-rank). Her dragon, on the other hand, is incredibly powerful. Initially reluctant to acknowledge her position as leader of Seito High School, this started changing when http://anidb.net/ch2098 [Kan`u] was captured, and she finally took charge of her responsibilities when she brought her dragon under control to defeat http://anidb.net/ch2096 [Sousou]. She is still a bookworm, though.</description>
<picture>10496.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14373" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="51">4.26</rating>
<name>Chouhi Ekitoku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10494.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14374" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="32">3.60</rating>
<name>Shokatsuryou Koumei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite her youth, she is Seito`s strategist and the nemesis of Shiba`i Chuutatsu.</description>
<picture>1315.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15655" picture="44791.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14375" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="117">8.52</rating>
<name>Chouun Shiryuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Super A-rank with a laidback attitude, she uses her katana to deadly effect, most of the time without even having to open her eyes. Devoted to Ryuubi and has deep respect for Kan`u.
Ranked #4 with 4758 votes in the March `13 official character poll.</description>
<picture>10495.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15895" type="appears in" update="2010-04-08">
<rating votes="8">5.13</rating>
<name>Nanyou Gakuin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>1333.jpeg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15897" type="appears in" update="2010-03-28">
<rating votes="6">7.35</rating>
<name>Seito Gakuen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>1335.jpeg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15898" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="43">6.12</rating>
<name>Kakouen Myousai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An A-rank Kyoshou fighter. She is completely devoted to Sousou (who appears to have saved her from a jungle war zone in the past). When she was under Saji Genpou`s spell, it took just a touch and a look from Sousou to bring her back to her self. She fights with a jade shot attached to a metal wire.</description>
<picture>10502.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16016" type="appears in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="30">4.35</rating>
<name>Bashoku Youjou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A B-rank fighter, she serves as assassin, bodyguard, messenger and spy for http://anidb.net/ch14374 [Koumei].</description>
<picture>10501.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3786" picture="223623.jpg">Kameoka Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16173" type="appears in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="9">2.78</rating>
<name>Kouchuu Kanshou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bald monk who was at Tougen Abbey with Koumei. Fights and knocks out Chouhi when she tries to follow Kan`u to the Abbey. When Koumei leaves for Seito, he goes along with her. An A-rank fighter, he has a perverted side that is revealed when he puts on the Sinroseki necklace. He appears to have a crush on Chouhi.</description>
<picture>1336.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16174" type="appears in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="6">4.45</rating>
<name>Shibaki Tokusou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kan`u and Chouhi`s master at Seito.</description>
<picture>1332.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2192" picture="196332.jpg">Kashii Shouto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16178" type="appears in" update="2010-03-28">
<rating votes="3">5.25</rating>
<name>Kada Genka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Doctor who treats Sonsaku and Ryoumou. He is the one who makes and renews the spell-infused eye-patch that Ryoumou uses to seal her dragon.</description>
<picture>1331.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16367" type="appears in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="21">3.24</rating>
<name>Rikuson Hakugen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1344.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16843" type="main character in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="10">5.73</rating>
<name>Saji Genpou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While her fighting abilities are limited, she is a powerful user of mind-control and illusion. She wishes to destroy every single toushi that exists, after first having broken all bonds of love or friendship that they have. This stems from her childhood, when she was harassed and assaulted for being different from the other children.
Finding friendship with Sonsaku and the others, she has given up her hatred and now stays with http://anidb.net/ch16844 [Choushou], along with http://anidb.net/ch7499 [Sonken].</description>
<picture>46556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16844" type="appears in" update="2020-01-27">
<rating votes="8">7.15</rating>
<name>Choushou Shifu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An old woman with the appearance of a young girl, she has helped train various toushi, including http://anidb.net/ch2076 [Ryomou] and http://anidb.net/ch2092 [Ryofu]. http://anidb.net/ch7499 [Sonken] stays with her.</description>
<picture>1350.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16848" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Rakuyou Koukou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="18742" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">3.43</rating>
<name>Shison Zui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154479.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1688" picture="19873.jpg">Ishizumi Akihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="90429" update="2008-06-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="4">2.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="x-unk">Promo</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91265" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兵は国の大事なり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">War Is of Vital Importance to the State</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Kriegskunst ist für den Staat von größter Bedeutung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`art de la guerre est d`une importance vitale pour l`état</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Siła militarna to ważna sprawa stanu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hei wa Kuni no Daiji Nari</title>
<summary>Hakufu and her crew get jobs in the hopes of earning enough money to attend tournaments stacked with the strongest opponents they can find! Things get crazy when her little sis shows up!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91461" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兵とは詭道なり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Warfare Is Based on Deception</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alle Kriegskunst gründet auf Täuschung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La guerre repose sur le mensonge</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Każda wojna to podstęp</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hei to wa Kidou Nari</title>
<summary>Hakufu goes on the rampage when her sweet little sister is kidnapped by a gang of thugs. The odds are stacked against her, but her friends are quick to back her up!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91462" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死者は復た生くべからず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dead Can Never Be Brought Back to Life</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tote können nicht zum Leben wiedererweckt werden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les morts ne reviennent pas à la vie</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Zmarli nie wracają do życia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shisha wa Mata Ikubekarazu</title>
<summary>Ryomou is shocked to stumble upon a girl everyone thought was dead, but all Hakufu can think of is taking the new girl to a karaoke bar!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91630" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒を視ること嬰児のごとし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Regard Soldiers as Your Children</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sieh deine Soldaten als deine Kinder an</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un chef chérit ses soldats comme un fils bien-aimé</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Miej wzgląd na wojowników niczym na dzieci</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sotsu o Miru Koto Eiji no Gotoshi</title>
<summary>When a pair of mysterious necklaces that unleash the wearer’s deepest desire make the rounds at martial arts shrine, no pretty face is safe from the lust that lurks within!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91835" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危うきに非ざれば戦わず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do Not Fight Unless It Is Critical</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kämpfe nur, wenn die Lage kritisch ist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On ne combat pas lorsqu`on n`est pas menacé</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Walcz jedynie, gdy zmusi cię do tego sytuacja</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayauki ni Arazareba Tatakawazu</title>
<summary>A day at the beach turns into a treasure hunt, but when giant man-eating sharks make an appearance, the bikini-clad warrior babes get a chance to show off their moves!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92041" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">上智を以て間者と為す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intelligence Makes Great Spies</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nutze deine weisesten Leute für die Spionage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Recruter ses espions chez des hommes à l`intelligence supérieur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jouchi o Motte Kanja to Nasu</title>
<summary>The quest to recover lost memories draws Hakufu and friends into an ambush at an abandoned school. Amidst a flurry of flying fists, the past is revisited.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92068" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">始めは処女の如く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At First, Like a Virgin</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zu Beginn so schüchtern wie eine Jungfrau...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Se présenter d`abord comme une vierge timide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajime wa Shojo no Gotoku</title>
<summary>Ryofu wreaks havoc on her new friends after she’s possessed by a mysterious girl in a cape, and her scandalous behavior with Gentoku threatens to send Kanu over the edge!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92069" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人を致して人に致されず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do Unto Others, Do Not Let Them Do Unto You</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kontrolliere deinen Gegner, lass dich nicht von ihm kontrollieren.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Diriger les mouvements de l`autre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito o Itashite Hito ni Itasarezu</title>
<summary>Suspicious of her master’s strange behavior, Kanu sends a messenger to ask Hakufu for help. Meanwhile, Ryomou’s dip in a peaceful hot spring is interrupted by Ryofu!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92070" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">算多きは勝ち算少なきは勝たず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bigger Odds Wins, the Smaller Odds Loses</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Viel Vorausplanung führt zum Sieg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Qui additionne de nombreux atouts sera victorieux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">San Ooki wa Kachi San Sukunaki wa Katazu</title>
<summary>Saji and the delicate magician who shares his name use Ryofu as the centerpiece of a heinous plan to awaken the dragon lurking within Ryomou!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92071" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">上兵は謀を伐つ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strike the Enemy`s Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der beste Krieger zerschlägt die Pläne des Feindes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Attaquer la stratégie de l`ennemi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jouhei wa Bou o Utsu</title>
<summary>When Hakufu is possessed by the magician, cousin Koukin and Chuubo must make a dangerous stand to prevent her from being lost forever
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92072" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先ずその愛する所を奪う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Start by Taking Away the Ones They Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Greife als Erstes das an, was dem Feind teuer ist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Commencer par attaquer ce à quoi l`ennemi tient</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mazu Sono Ai Suru Tokoro o Ubau</title>
<summary>Chuubo reveals her shocking true identity before joining Koukin and Hakufu on a mission to rescue Ryomou!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92187" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">専まりて一と為る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coming Together</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sich sammeln und Eins werden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ne former qu`un seul corps</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atsumarite Ichi to Naru</title>
<summary>Koukin and Hakufu risk their lives in the battle to save Chuubo. Meanwhile, Ryomou learns a lesson of vital importance in her brawl with Ryofu!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92996" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92997" update="2019-10-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93222" update="2008-11-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バトルツアークラブ♥セクシーコスプレ危険なアルバイト♥ 第一話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Tour Club - Sexy Cosplay - Dangerous Part-time Job, first part: Hakufu Sonsaku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Battle Tour Club Sexy Cosplay Kiken na Arbeit Daiichiwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93885" update="2008-11-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バトルツアークラブ♥セクシーコスプレ危険なアルバイト♥ 第ニ話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Tour Club - Sexy Cosplay - Dangerous Part-time Job, second part: Ryofu Housen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93947" update="2008-11-02">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バトルツアークラブ♥セクシーコスプレ危険なアルバイト♥ 第三話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Tour Club - Sexy Cosplay - Dangerous Part-time Job, third part: Kan`u Unchou and Kakouen Myousai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96119" update="2018-01-02">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バトルツアークラブ♥セクシーコスプレ危険なアルバイト♥ 第四話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Tour Club - Sexy Cosplay - Dangerous Part-time Job, fourth part: Kakouen Myousai, Kan`u Unchou &amp; Ryomou Shimei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96947" update="2018-01-02">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バトルツアークラブ♥セクシーコスプレ危険なアルバイト♥ 第五話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Tour Club - Sexy Cosplay - Dangerous Part-time Job, fifth part</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96952" update="2009-02-13">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バトルツアークラブ♥セクシーコスプレ危険なアルバイト♥ 第六話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Tour Club - Sexy Cosplay - Dangerous Part-time Job, sixth part</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116702" update="2010-03-01">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="x-unk">Trailer</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139243" update="2012-04-29">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Radio Show</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183476" update="2019-10-04">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183477" update="2017-01-06">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183478" update="2017-01-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
