<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5751" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-02-28</startdate>
<enddate>2008-02-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">The Idolmaster: Live for You!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">アイドルマスター ライブフォーユー!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">THE iDOLM@STER Live For You!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4773" type="Other">Idol Master Xenoglossia</anime>
<anime id="8218" type="Other">The Idolmaster</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.idolmaster.jp/l4u/top.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1038" type="Animation Work">Actas</name>
<name id="6241" type="Character Design">Nishio Kimitake</name>
<name id="926" type="Work">Frontier Works</name>
<name id="3512" type="Original Work">Bandai Namco Games</name>
<name id="6090" type="Direction">Kawaguchi Keiichirou</name>
<name id="3512" type="Music">Bandai Namco Games</name>
</creators>
<description>On the day before the http://anidb.net/ch8372 [765 Productions] Fan Appreciation Event, each of the idols prepare to head home. However, http://anidb.net/ch6303 [Kisaragi Chihaya], uneasy about tomorrow`s event, decides to have a last minute personal rehearsal. One thing leads to another as Chihaya, http://anidb.net/ch6302 [Miki] and http://anidb.net/ch6293 [Haruka] are dragged from one exciting situation to the next.
What is the truck driver`s true destination? What is the secret behind the old house? And will the girls make it in time for the event?
Source: www.e-n-m.net/projects/imas_l4u</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="371">2.93</permanent>
<temporary count="376">5.68</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>9390.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11323</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4033</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4267</identifier>
<identifier>zbpvxh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.idolmaster.jp/l4u/top.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6293" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="100">5.66</rating>
<name>Amami Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4712" picture="27521.jpg">Nakamura Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6294" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-08">
<rating votes="89">4.83</rating>
<name>Futami Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6295" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-08">
<rating votes="92">6.12</rating>
<name>Futami Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6296" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="101">6.39</rating>
<name>Kikuchi Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3006" picture="226210.jpg">Hirata Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6297" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-10">
<rating votes="86">7.15</rating>
<name>Miura Azusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6298" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="77">5.78</rating>
<name>Hagiwara Yukiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="134" picture="16880.jpg">Ochiai Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6299" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-10">
<rating votes="138">7.71</rating>
<name>Minase Iori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75114.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6300" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-10">
<rating votes="132">6.52</rating>
<name>Takatsuki Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4714" picture="171986.jpg">Nigo Mayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6301" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-10">
<rating votes="51">6.20</rating>
<name>Akizuki Ritsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2039" picture="41388.jpg">Wakabayashi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6302" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="187">8.37</rating>
<name>Hoshii Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4713" picture="186249.jpg">Hasegawa Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6303" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="162">7.76</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Chihaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8372" type="appears in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="1">7.75</rating>
<name>765 Production</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>765 Production is the fictional studio which created the iDOLM@STER project, featuring a group of 10 new idols.</description>
<picture>27525.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="88494" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2008-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
