<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="579" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-05-09</startdate>
<enddate>2003-06-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Saint Beast: Seijuu Kourin Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">セイント・ビースト 聖獣降臨編</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Saint Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Saint Beast 四聖獣 ~聖獣降臨編~</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="175" type="Character">Otogi Story Tenshi no Shippo</anime>
<anime id="4444" type="Side Story">Saint Beast: Ikusen no Hiru to Yoru Hen</anime>
<anime id="4902" type="Other">Saint Beast: Kouin Jojishi Tenshi Tan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.wonderfarm.co.jp/s-beast/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4388" type="Direction">Kosaka Harume</name>
<name id="4604" type="Series Composition">Arisugawa Kei</name>
<name id="4604" type="Original Work">Arisugawa Kei</name>
<name id="786" type="Work">Wonderfarm</name>
<name id="822" type="Animation Work">Tokyo Kids</name>
<name id="4992" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sasaki Toshiko</name>
</creators>
<description>The guardian angels that descended to the Human World went missing one after another. Behind this incident, the presence of an evil animal spirit is felt---
The 4 Saint Beasts (http://anidb.net/ch14497 [Seiryuu no Gou], http://anidb.net/ch14498 [Genbu no Shin], http://anidb.net/ch14499 [Shuzaku no Rei], http://anidb.net/ch14500 [Byakko no Gai]) descended upon knowledge of this incident. In an attempt to rescue the guardian angels, as well as to find out what this evil animal spirit is...
What in the world could be the reason behind these disappearances? How would the Saint Beasts fight the evil animal spirit? And, what kind of scheme underlying all these incidents?
A must see for female fans, for the appearance of beautiful characters appear one after another. Gorgeous battles, an easily understandable outlook of the world, charismatic characters fill each episodes, making it a must-watch series.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="282">2.25</permanent>
<temporary count="286">5.43</temporary>
<review count="2">5.08</review>
</ratings>
<picture>3924.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>81</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1037</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1181</identifier>
<identifier>ttzelz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.wonderfarm.co.jp/s-beast/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kids-station.com/minisite/tokushu/saintbeast/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mmv.co.jp/special/saintbeast/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>241178</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="14420" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="6">8.71</rating>
<name>Hebi no Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuki is a strong and calm woman. She usually remains quiet but will give useful advice when called upon. She acts and is seen as a mother to the younger angels. Mika uses "mother" as an insult towards her. Yuki is the bride of Gou the Azure Dragon (Seiryuu). She was a white snake in her past life. Yuki is in the Senior rank.
In season 2, Yuki became a goddess. She works and watches over the world, especially the animals and Goro. In this season she replaces the previous goddess who broke a part of their rules. As the goddess she became stronger and had a stronger will to take part in the sage`s dream.
Her white skin represents a snake`s skin. Her name means snow, alluding to the color of her skin and scales. Her color image is blue. In Yuki`s past life she died of being burnt to death; because of this she is afraid of fire.</description>
<picture>2918.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14422" type="appears in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="5">5.43</rating>
<name>Kame no Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayumi was a turtle in her past life. Because of this, she is always slow to make decisions because she is always thinking ahead. Ayumi always wears a green beret-like hat that symbolizes her turtle-shell in her past life. Ayumi is the bride of Shin the Black Turtle (Genbu). He has deep feelings for her and, on one occasion, risked his life to save hers in a collapsing warehouse. It is noted that of the four abducted angels, she returns his feelings the most. Ayumi often scolds Mika and argues with her most of the time. Ayumi is in the Senior rank. Her name means walk. Her color image is black. Ayumi was crushed to death in her past life, so now she is afraid of the dark and small places.</description>
<picture>2920.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14424" type="appears in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="5">5.43</rating>
<name>Inko no Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsubasa was a parakeet in her past life. She was rescued by Gorou when she broke her wing and he took care of her. She is afraid of heights; this is because after she believed her wing was healed she tried to show her appreciation by showing him her beauty in flight. She tried to fly but fell from the house`s window and died. Her hairstyle represents a parakeet`s wings.
Tsubasa too has deep feelings for Gorou. She`s angry at Rei, the Red Phoenix (Suzaku), who is in love with her but hurt her beloved master. Her name means wing, alluding to her animal self. Her color image is red.
In Season 2 Tsubasa is a girl like none other. She may be a bit boyish but she still has the characteristics of being a girl or even a woman. Despite this she still strived for her master and eventually became stronger. Tsubasa is in the Intermediate rank (Senior rank in Season 2).</description>
<picture>2922.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="313" picture="158104.jpg">Nogawa Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14428" type="appears in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="8">6.51</rating>
<name>Neko no Tamami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamami is very catlike and has many catgirl personality traits. She is very hyperactive and has kept her cat-like ability to scale walls with ease. Tamami is the bride of Gai, the White Tiger (Byakko) but says she`s too young. It is noted that Gai is protective of her and always tries to help her out of danger. A defining trait of hers is that she`s occasionally business-oriented in both seasons. Her color image is white.
Whenever you cannot find her she is most likely in a grassy place taking a nap. She is afraid of cars and traffic because in her past life she was a cat who died after she was hit by a car.
Her hairstyle represents a cat`s ears and she belongs to the Intermediate rank. In the second Season Tamami is in the Senior rank due to her achievements in the human world.</description>
<picture>2926.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="6786" picture="79639.jpg">Oosawa Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14497" type="main character in" update="2010-06-12">
<name>Seiryuu no Gou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The reincarnation of Seiryuu the Azure Dragon of the East (Spring). He is the leader of the Saint Beasts and the most powerful. He is heterochromatic (his right eye is blue while his left is red).
In Tenshi no Shippo: He is the last Saint Beast to appear, and his reappearance frightens even the goddess, who accidentally drops her staff in fear. He takes Yuki as his bride, since Oriental dragons, which Seiryu is commonly depicted as, are serpentine. He is clearly in love with Yuki, as she is with him. Sacred Power: Fang (Sword) of the Blue Dragon. Lightning Blast.
In Saint Beast: Gou is the oldest of the Saint Beasts (the four Saint Beast calls him Anija which means older brother) and tends to be very serious and in charge of the missions given to him by the Goddess. He has a deep friendship with Gai.
Attribute: Fire
Ability: Manipulating nature
Attack: Fire Beam
Image Color: Blue</description>
<picture>2929.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14498" type="main character in" update="2010-06-12">
<name>Genbu no Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The reincarnation of Genbu the Black Tortoise of the North (Winter). He is the sensible, calm and brooding member of the group and its second-in-command, leading it in Gou`s absence.
In Tenshi no Shippo: He bypassed Ayumi while she was doing groceries. He later saw her again when the three tricked Gorou into working at an abandoned site under the pretense of a part-time job but to use him as a sacrifice to revive Gou. It was here that he fell in love with her enough to save her from the collapsing building. He later made her his bride, both being closely related animals (shelled reptiles). However, when the four joined Gorou`s side, Ayumi unconsciously hints that the relationship may not be one sided even before her abduction, the same goes for Yuki and Gou and Tsubasa and Rei, and later perhaps, Tamami and Gai. His Saint Beast counterpart constantly wears glasses and has shoulder-length blue-green hair, unlike the original Shin, who only wore his glasses in disguise, as well as having shorter black hair. Sacred Power: Shield of the Black Turtle. Shell Shards.
In Saint Beast: Shin has an affinity for tortoises and plays the golden harp (or a harp-like instrument). He received the Shield of Genbu from Zeus (which is almost 3/4 his size and looks like the back of a turtle). He is very close to Kirin no Yudas and is very calm and quiet. He also has the ability to manipulate time but using such power has a backslash. First, he needs a lot of energy and also his life is at risk. He used it once and he was unconcsious for 1 whole week.
Attribute: Wind
Ability: Manipulating time
Attack: Wind Arrow
Image Color: Black</description>
<picture>2930.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14499" type="main character in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="4">2.34</rating>
<name>Suzaku no Rei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The reincarnation of Suzaku the Vermilion Bird of the South (Summer). He is the most feminine in appearance, behavior (though not as extreme enough to be considered homosexual, which he himself states).
In Tenshi no Shippo: He first appears to hypnotize Gorou while on a date with Tsubasa to a theme park to ride the ferris wheel, knowing full well of Tsubasa`s fear of heights. He later takes Tsubasa as his bride, since both are birds. When she later regains control of her will, she slaps Rei, without a care of who he was, to prove a point of how much grief and trouble they caused. Later on, even he notes that Tsubasa has feelings for him, but as he was leaving, he was contented with the result. Unlike his Saint Beast counterpart, his hair covers his left eye, hence the bishounen appearance. Sacred Power: Wings of the Red Phoenix. Talon Strike. Scorched Flame.
In Saint Beast: Zeus gave him the Spear of Suzaku. He has an affinity for birds of any sort, including chickens. Ray gained the ability to fly after he became an adult angel; his wings are gold in color. He is very close to Houou no Luka. He is also disgusted at humans because they eat fried chicken which happens to be Gai`s favorite food. Very good at cooking.
Attribute: Water
Ability: Manipulating minds
Attack: Ice Blade
Image Color: Red</description>
<picture>2931.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14500" type="main character in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="4">1.70</rating>
<name>Byakko no Gai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The reincarnation of Byakko the White Tiger of the West (Autumn). He is the most impulsive of the group and is prone to wild fits.
In Tenshi no Shippo: He is the first to appear, attempting to run over Goro with a truck but is saved by Tamami, whom he later takes as his bride, both being cats. Though he complained about Tamami`s age at first, he really is fond of her, and always tries to protect her. Sacred Power: Armour of the White Tiger. Tiger Claw.
In Saint Beast: Zeus gave him the Armor of Byakko. Tends to be a little childish, inventive (but most of the time his inventions were useless) and full of energy. He has an affinity for felines. He likes to play pranks on Rei and is good friends with Maya. Gai has the ability to control and channel the laws of nature. When they descended on Earth, he has this favorite tv show called `Venom Saint` that shows an animation of their recent encounters (or more like a chibi version of them that is drawn rather differently) and seems like Maya also has taken a liking to it. Also, he liked the concept of `convenience store` and wishes that Heaven also has one.
Attribute: Earth
Ability: Manipulating physics
Attack: Earthquake
Image Color: White</description>
<picture>2932.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14502" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-12">
<name>Kirin no Judas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is one of the two fallen angels that broke free from his imprisonment in hell and begins to cause the disappearance of the guardian angels on earth. He has a red hair. Zeus gave him the ability to heal with his lips, when he became a Saint Beast. He was the leader of the Six Saint Beast and was very close to Genbu no Shin.
Attribute: Light
Ability: Manipulating space
Attack: Cosmo Menace
Image Color: Bordeaux</description>
<picture>2933.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14503" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-12">
<name>Houou no Luka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is one of the two fallen angels that broke free from his imprisonment in hell and begins to cause the disappearance of the guardian angels on earth. Zeus gave him the ability to read minds with his fingertips, when he became a Saint Beast. He is very close to Suzaku no Rei and he has the ability to fly (his wings is pure white in color with a shade of blue) and he was also referred to as the Golden Phoenix.
Attribute: Darkness
Ability: Manipulating light and dark
Attack: Brilliant Shadow
Image Color: Sapphire</description>
<picture>2934.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14505" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-12">
<name>Ryuusei no Kira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kira is blonde-haired and likes to bully Rei. He is very bad tempered and cold hearted to everyone but Maya, his younger brother. He left Heaven with Maya and became a Wandering Angel in order to search for his mother. He is especially rude towards Gou. Kira is the son of Lucifer.
Attribute: Shadow
Ability: Entering and manipulating dreams
Image Color: Amber</description>
<picture>2935.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14507" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-12">
<name>Fuuga no Maya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maya is the younger brother of Kira. Red-haired, he is half human half angel, his mother being the human. He left Heaven with Kira and wanders around Earth in the hopes of finding their mother. He was very upset when Kira told him that they were leaving (especially since Maya wishes to be one of the Saint Beast so that everyone who bullied him - for being half human - will look at him with respect), and needed convincing by Judas who got hurt in the process. He is very close friends with Gai. He is the son of Lucifer.
Attribute: Sunlight
Ability: Manipulating spirits
Image Color: Orange</description>
<picture>2936.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14508" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-12">
<name>Kagerou no Shiva</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A spy for Judas and Luka. Shiva appears to be rather obsessed with Judas and hates the Saint Beasts, especially Shin. Prior to the ascent to the Holy Summit to choose the Six Saint Beast, Shiva entered the Forest of Darkness and got a demon to attack Shin who nearly succeeded (he managed to poisoned him by inflicting a wound on his left biceps), if weren`t for the timely arrival of Judas. Shiva was the 5th candidate to reach the Holy Summit, but due to his encounter with the demon, Zeus (who sees everything with his transparent crystal ball) rejected him the position.
Attribute: Darkness
Ability: Transforming into others (for a short time)
Image Color: Indigo</description>
<picture>2937.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27569" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Pinky</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pinky is a messenger of http://anidb.net/ch14420 [Megami Yuki].</description>
<picture>64121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="330" picture="171543.jpg">Morinaga Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27570" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<name>Hakuja no Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27571" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<name>Seija</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seija is a wise saint who gives the 4 Saint Beasts their weapons in http://anidb.net/a579 [Saint Beast: Seijuu Kourin Hen].</description>
<picture>64122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="416" picture="23206.jpg">Saka Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27580" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Yuria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuria is the older sister of http://anidb.net/ch27581 [Seira].</description>
<picture>64142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27581" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Seira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seira is the younger sister of http://anidb.net/ch27580 [Yuria].</description>
<picture>64141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3710" picture="25089.jpg">Satou Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27582" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the mother of http://anidb.net/ch27580 [Yuria] and http://anidb.net/ch27581 [Seira].</description>
<picture>64140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3240" picture="45305.jpg">Yokoo Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27585" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<name>Hayabusa no Hiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27586" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Bambi no Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bambi no Mio is the twin sister of http://anidb.net/ch27587 [Rio]. She wears pink clothing, and has her ponytail on the right side.</description>
<picture>64148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27587" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Bambi no Rio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bambi no Rio is the twin sister of http://anidb.net/ch27586 [Mio]. She wears blue clothing, and has her ponytail on the left side.</description>
<picture>64149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="7783" update="2011-01-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖獣降臨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Descend On The Surface</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seijuu Kourin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8123" update="2011-01-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いじわるなエンジェル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ill-Tempered Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ijiwaruna Angel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8371" update="2011-01-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">許されざる想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unforgivable Desire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yurusarezaru Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10668" update="2011-01-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">堕天使達の野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Treachery Of The Fallen Angels</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Datenshi-tachi no Yabou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13683" update="2011-01-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">守護天使の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guardian Angel`s Trap!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shugotenshi-tachi no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14549" update="2006-03-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誰がために...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Whose Sake...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dare ga Tame ni...</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
