<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="580" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-04-19</startdate>
<enddate>2003-04-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">RahXephon: Tagen Hensoukyoku</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">RahXephon - Harmonic Convergence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Rahxephon Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ラーゼフォン 多元変奏曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">RahXephon: Pluralitas Concentio</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">라제폰</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14" type="Alternative Setting">RahXephon</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/rahxephon-movie</url>
<creators>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
<name id="2181" type="Music">Hashimoto Ichiko</name>
<name id="2283" type="Character Design">Yamada Akihiro</name>
<name id="755" type="Original Work">Bones</name>
<name id="2282" type="Original Work">Izubuchi Yutaka</name>
<name id="2298" type="Direction">Kyouda Tomoki</name>
<name id="2282" type="Chief Direction">Izubuchi Yutaka</name>
<name id="2284" type="Animation Character Design">Kanno Hiroki</name>
<name id="2285" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sano Hirotoshi</name>
<name id="2298" type="Series Composition">Kyouda Tomoki</name>
<name id="2284" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kanno Hiroki</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch1513 [Shitou Haruka] -- a 29 year old lady who lost her life with her beloved in a flash. She tries to retrieve "something" that was important to her, and joins the special institution TERRA. Haruka`s target was http://anidb.net/ch1511 [Kamina Ayato]. He was a high school student 12 years younger than her. However, that Ayato was the person she had feelings for when she parted with him in Junior High.
Lovers parted by the time, a Sci-Fi setting and the test for the truth of people`s hearts. The movie heats up with Ayato`s RahXephon and the battle with the Dolems. If Ayato awakens completely, the world will turn into a horrific situation. To prevent that, Haruka needs to kill Ayato. Would Haruka be able to go pass this decision? And the "sleeping beauty" that is waiting for Ayato`s kiss. How would their love change?
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1638">5.63</permanent>
<temporary count="1646">7.23</temporary>
<review count="2">6.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>85915.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>212</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1164</identifier>
<identifier>vncrgl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mediafactory.co.jp/anime/rahxephon/movie/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/rahxephon-movie</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Pluralitas_Concentio</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ラーゼフォン_多元変奏曲</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240115</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5845</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4330" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-09">
<name>quantum mechanics</name>
<description>Quantum mechanics (or physics) is a set of principles that describe the physical world (everything that is material) in terms of atoms and subatomic particles (e.g. electrons, photons, neutrons, quarks) and the relations between them. (See wikipedia for detailed info).
The story or plot used in this anime is directly related with one or more of this principles; mainly the simultaneous wave-like and particle-like behavior of all matter and radiation, or the "Heisenberg uncertainty principle" (one can never know both the location and the speed of a particle with all certainty).
Sometimes just some terms of quantum mechanics are used in the anime, like "Schrödinger`s cat" or "synchrotron radiation", to make the story more "real".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4555" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-22">
<name>man the hell up!</name>
<description>There is a male character in this anime that is overall not very manly. Most of the time he starts off as your typical high school student. In time there are, through major changes in his life, several more characteristics added to his personality. Usually these add up to be extremely pathetic and the character becomes quite annoying. This goes along with the viewers wish for him to get over it and do something about it. Hence, he should "Man the hell up!".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5213" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-04">
<name>the effects of time and distance on human relationships</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1511" type="main character in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="36">4.41</rating>
<name>Kamina Ayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At the beginning of the series, Ayato Kamina is a student and artist living with his mother in Tokyo. Most of his artwork shown in the series consists of drawings or paintings of a girl on a cliff looking towards the sea. He has birthmark-like symbols on his belly resembling runes, which are revealed to be a sign of his being a potential instrumentalist for the RahXephon.
After being taken from Tokyo by Haruka and the RahXephon, Ayato moves in with Rikudo Shougo, Haruka`s uncle on Nirai Kanai. At first, this arrangement does not sit well with Ayato, as Haruka and her younger sister Megumi live in Rikudo`s annex, but they slowly adapt to each others` presences. As a stranger from Tokyo Jupiter, Ayato struggles to find his place and acceptance in the outside world. Although he pilots the RahXephon in defending Nirai Kanai, he questions his abilities and self-worth. He also struggles with trying to piece together and understand his relationship with Haruka, handling the feisty Megumi, and interacting with the other TERRA personnel, who regard him with a broad spectrum of reactions, from acceptance and friendship to cool scientific interest to distrust and even contempt.</description>
<picture>16044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1512" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="32">8.36</rating>
<name>Mishima Reika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reika Mishima first appears in the series as the subject of one of Ayato`s paintings. She then appears, in person, during the attack on Tokyo in episode 1. She leads Ayato to the RahXephon, and is shown to have some sort of connection to it via her singing.</description>
<picture>16045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1513" type="main character in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="49">5.95</rating>
<name>Shitou Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 29 year old officer within the TERRA organisation, Shitou Haruka is partially responsible for aiding Ayato in leaving Tokyo Jupiter. Originally a Captain in the Intelligence Division, she is promoted to Major in the Tactical Division.
Haruka is shown to have very strong feelings for Ayato and struggles at maintaining a relationship with him for many reasons. Her position within TERRA makes Ayato think that she is only using him because of his ability to pilot the RahXephon. Ayato`s own personal struggles also create barriers for their relationship.
It is later revealed that the girl that Ayato is constantly drawing and painting is actually a young Haruka. They had fallen in love when they were younger. The earliest date when the show places them together is at August 10, 2011, at age 13. When the Tokyo Jupiter barrier was established (just after the end of 2012), Haruka was on a vacation in a different part of Japan. Ixtli uses Ayato`s distorted memories of Haruka to create the form of Mishima Reika. Haruka aged much more than Ayato in the outside world due to Tokyo Jupiter`s time dilation effect. She had a relationship with Kisaragi Itsuki, possibly due to his similarity to Ayato.
There is no real difference between Haruka`s portrayal in the series and in the movie.
In the manga, Haruka is more ditzy but has a similar role in the story until the end, where she is revealed to be a reincarnation of Reika.</description>
<picture>51448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1514" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="67">6.59</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Quon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quon Kisaragi is a mysterious young girl who speaks the first words of the TV series and is shown meeting Ayato in episode 4. Her standard expression of surprise or agreement is "La-la" and most of her dialogue is cryptic and musically themed. She and Ayato do not connect romantically, but she displays a level of both physical and interpersonal comfort and intimacy with Ayato that is unmatched by any of the other characters, even Haruka. She is also one of the few people who never treats Ayato as a curiosity or an annoyance, and she seems to have an understanding of his situation and what his eventual role is, calling him "Orin".</description>
<picture>16047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1516" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="18">5.61</rating>
<name>Asahina Hiroko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiroko Asahina is a classmate and friend of Ayato and Mamoru Torugai. During the attack on Tokyo in episode 1, she is lightly injured, and bleeds red blood.</description>
<picture>16350.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1517" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="12">2.63</rating>
<name>Torigai Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mamoru Torigai is another friend and classmate of Kamina`s in Tokyo Jupiter. He was seeing Hiroko Asahina before she left Tokyo Jupiter with Ayato. Deep down, he dislikes Ayato because of Asahina`s feelings for him.</description>
<picture>16051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1518" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="9">4.86</rating>
<name>Kamina Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maya Kamina is Ayato`s mother and is often away from home, leaving Ayato feeling neglected and wishing to spend more time with her.</description>
<picture>16052.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2181" picture="90276.jpg">Hashimoto Ichiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1523" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="10">5.94</rating>
<name>Kunugi Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jin Kunugi is the stern and quiet commander of TERRA`s military operations. He prefers delegating tasks to his subordinates and "managing by exception." Kunugi was an officer of the Japan Self-Defense Forces, under the command of Kuki Masayoshi, who ordered him to perform a hydrogen bomb on the Mu. His daughter Michiru was killed in the following war, and Kunugi became estranged from his wife.</description>
<picture>16057.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1524" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="8">6.31</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Itsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Itsuki Kisaragi is an urbane doctor with TERRA who studies music and is part of the analysis team studying the RahXephon. He is also the adoptive brother of Quon.</description>
<picture>16058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1526" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-06">
<rating votes="25">7.05</rating>
<name>Shitou Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shitou Megumi is http://anidb.net/ch1513 [Haruka]`s younger sister.
She initially protests Ayato living with her, Haruka, and their uncle, but she does her best to help Ayato feel at home, and develops a crush on Ayato as the series progresses. She often serves pocky and other snacks, and introduces Ayato to ramune. Although seemingly energetic and upbeat, she has many internal issues. She did not fit in well in school, so she joined TERRA as a trainee. She would later be promoted to the rank of a full officer.
She initially has a crush on Yakumo Souichi, but gives up on him when she finds out that he is seeing her friend, Hotal Kim. She feels as if she is constantly living in her sister`s shadow, and this comes to a head when she learns that Ayato and Haruka had a relationship when they were younger, as by the end of the series she has developed a crush on Ayato. In the end, she openly renounces her feelings for Ayato for the sake of her sister.
In the movie, as in the series, Megumi helps make Ayato feel at home, but does not fall in love with Ayato or Yagumo — at least not in the scenes shown.
In the manga, Megumi and Kim have minor roles as classmates, "bodyguards" and observers of Reika.</description>
<picture>68236.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1528" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-16">
<rating votes="12">2.13</rating>
<name>Isshiki Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makoto Isshiki, called "The White Snake" because of his albinism and personality, is sent by the Earth Federation to observe at TERRA. He has an extremely haughty and arrogant attitude, and is contemptuous and dismissive of Ayato. His cover is rather shallow, as it is easily discovered that he was sent at the request of the Bähbem Foundation.</description>
<picture>16062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1530" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="8">6.60</rating>
<name>Rikudou Shougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shougo Rikudo is a retired archaeologist living in Nirai-Kanai. He is Haruka and Megumi Shitow`s uncle, and welcomes Ayato into his household. Soft-spoken and wise, he helps to ground the other characters. He is an expert at shogi, the Japanese equivalent of chess, and at Japanese calligraphy (shodo). It is revealed that it was Professor Rikudoh and his assistant Shirow Watari who found Maya and Quon at the shrine, and that Maya was raised as Rikudoh`s adoptive daughter.</description>
<picture>16064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="456" picture="17358.jpg">Ootsuka Chikao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1531" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="10">5.33</rating>
<name>Futagami Jouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Johji Futagami is a reporter from Amato News who is given exclusive press access to TERRA, making his way around the island of Nirai Kanai asking questions of both principal characters and other local residents. Throughout the series, he is able to supply new information to Haruka, while being involved in investigative journalism.</description>
<picture>16065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="710" picture="228657.jpg">Hori Katsunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1532" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="6">2.75</rating>
<name>Ernst von Bahbem</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ernst von Bähbem, also called The Designer, is the cloned host body of an ancient Mulian. His practice of cloning himself has some characters mistakenly calling him a modern Methuselah. Bähbem was responsible for the continent of Mu disappearing into another dimension, and he seeks to rectify the situation by having the world "re-tuned" before the dimensions destroy each other and turn into "mud." Bähbem seems not to care about whether the humans or the Mu are the ones that will succeed in the tuning, or indeed care about the people that he uses to attain his goals.</description>
<picture>16066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2143" picture="178043.jpg">Kayumi Iemasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1533" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-25">
<rating votes="8">3.79</rating>
<name>Helena Bahbem</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Helena von Bähbem is the niece of Ernst von Bähbem. A childhood acquaintance of Makoto Isshiki and Itsuki Kisaragi, she serves as the second in command in the Bähbem Foundation. In addition to being a childhood dabbler in witchcraft, she was a potential instrumentalist, but passed the ideal age without realising her potential. This makes her jealous of Quon and others that might succeed in tuning the world.</description>
<picture>16067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2184" picture="49347.jpg">Hyoudou Mako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="10606" update="2005-09-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>120</length>
<airdate>2003-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13373" update="2005-09-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2003-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13375" update="2005-09-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2003-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150957" update="2013-06-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150958" update="2013-06-02">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150959" update="2013-06-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
