<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5815" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>39</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2009-02-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kyou kara Maou! (2008)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">今日からマ王! 第3シリーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Отныне Мао, король демонов! (3 сезон)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kyou Kara Maou! 3rd Series</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kyo Kara Maoh! - 3rd Series</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kyou Kara Maoh! - 3rd Series</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">今日起是魔王!第三季</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kkm3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">今日からマ王! (2008)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1677" type="Prequel">Kyou kara Maou!</anime>
<anime id="5457" type="Alternative Setting">Kyou kara Maou! R</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="183638">got to see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="242315">season 1 and 2 was better and this needs another season since it seems incomplete.  Better watch the first 2 seasons before watching this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="104619">Very entertaining with good plot twists.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www3.nhk.or.jp/anime/mao/main.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="2241" type="Direction">Nishimura Junji</name>
<name id="6586" type="Character Design">Kudou Yuka</name>
<name id="4304" type="Series Composition">Omode Akemi</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="963" type="Work">Sougou Vision</name>
<name id="1050" type="Work">NHK</name>
<name id="6811" type="Music">Yoshikawa Youichirou</name>
<name id="8347" type="Original Work">Takabayashi Tomo</name>
</creators>
<description>Before Yuri returned to the Great Demon Kingdom at the end of Season 2, the Ten Noble families chose Wolfram to become the next Demon King. Conflict arises when Yuri returns, and Wolfram is forced to call off their engagement due to Wolfram`s proud mazoku uncle. In the end, Yuri becomes the Maou to defend himself and Wolfram, and proves to the noble family that he is a responsible Maou. This is later followed by a few individual side stories, such as the episode about bear bees being sold in Shin Makoku, in which later are proven to be fakes; and the episode of Leila`s wedding to Antoine, the king of the Francia kingdom. In this episode, Yuri and his companions encounter a group of bandits that have been stealing important swords from different kingdoms, it is later revealed that they have a deeper purpose. The story continues on as Conrad and Murata travel to Big Shimaron to fulfill some somewhat hidden agendas, who are later followed by Yuri and Wolfram. A new character is introduced, the new king of Small Shimaron- Saralegui, who seems to be interested in Yuri (or in his powers). In order to get information about the group White Crows, Yuri and Wolfram gets help from Lady Celi`s suitor-"Fanfan". Yuri and Wolfram attend a baquet in Big Shimaron disguised as girls as when Yuri trips over and is helped by Saralegui or Sara. The Original King appears to be well as he appears to Yuri to give him advice, as well as threatened those who oppose Yuri`s rule. There`s also a dark organization of sorcerers ; the White Crows, originally formed by the Great Sage Navon. They`re on a quest of getting all the holy and spiritual swords they could find.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="533">6.48</permanent>
<temporary count="546">7.56</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>52361.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10056</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4080</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4168</identifier>
<identifier>orjjfv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www3.nhk.or.jp/anime/mao/main.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1383</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330072</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6705</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3539" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-16">
<name>growing hair</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4182" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-01-22">
<name>hidden power</name>
<description>For some reason or another a character has powers (or potential) he or she can`t access and may not even know about. 
In some anime these hidden powers are used quite frequently to overcome an enemy or threat (e.g. Naruto, Bleach).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5162" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-14">
<name>inter-dimensional travel</name>
<description>Inter-dimensional travel is the ability to move between dimensions. It is often also explained as moving between dimensional planes. Holders of this ability are generally called sliders.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8834" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="19">6.05</rating>
<name>von Christ Guenter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teacher and swordsman who adores Yuuri. Günter is a skilled swordsman and magician, but has retired to teach Yuuri about Shin Makoku and his future duties as the Maou. Günter once stated that he was the one who taught Conrad to "become His Majesty`s sword and shield" indicating that perhaps Günter was once Conrad`s teacher. When Günter accidentally travels to Earth, he becomes a model in New York City for a brief period of time so that he can earn money to find Yuuri. He is a very whimsical person and poetic in his thoughts. Günter is another test subject of Anissina.
Günter, along with the three brothers, helps Yuuri run the country. He is Yuuri`s adviser and mentor, teaching Yuuri various aspects of Shin Makoku. He usually spends his time doing numerous duties for Yuuri and Shin Makoku.</description>
<picture>52385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18102" type="main character in" update="2010-05-24">
<rating votes="33">4.63</rating>
<name>Shibuya Yuuri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born in Boston and grew up in Saitama prefecture. A high school student who enjoys baseball more than textbooks.</description>
<picture>48547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20233" type="main character in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="24">6.88</rating>
<name>Weller Conrad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His given name is Conrart; Yuuri nicknames him "Conrad," which is "closer to English" and easier to pronounce with a Japanese tongue. Conrad is the second child of the previous Maoh, Cecilie von Spitzweig. His father was human (also considered the greatest swordsman in the Demon Kingdom; Dan Hiri Weller). His ancestor, Lawrence Weller, fought alongside the Original King during the war against Soushu. On his 16th birthday, he decided to live as a Mazoku instead of a human. He fought on the front lines for the Mazoku during a war against the humans. He and Yozak are the only two survivors of the Battle of Lütenburg. He was also put in charge of the soul at the request of Suzanna Julia von Wincott, that was to be the new Maou, and brought it safely to Earth so that it could be born.
Furthermore, he was the one who was the inspiration for Yuuri`s name. He stated that "Where I come from, the month of July is called Yuuri", which made Yuuri`s mother name him Yuuri because he was born in July. For this reason, Yuuri dubs him `Nazukeoya`, which is a person who names someone (Conrad is also known as Yuuri`s Godfather by his mother). Cecilie named the blue flowers she grew "Conrad Stands Upon Earth".</description>
<picture>52369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20236" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="12">8.11</rating>
<name>von Voltaire Gwendal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The eldest son of Cecilie. From the beginning, Gwendal has objections to Yuuri becoming the Maou. He is a skilled tactician and is capable of using earth magic and can cast barriers. When not otherwise busy, Gwendal indulges in his hobby of knitting and sewing but often his creatures look nothing like what they`re supposed to (for example a bear got mistaken for a black pig or a cat that looks like a raccoon). He is adamnant that knitting helps him sharpen his concentration but actually its a stress reliever for him since childhood. He is also quite fond of cute animals or cute objects such as the dolphin keychain (Bandou-kun) Yuuri received at the dolphin show and later gave to him. His childhood best friend is Anissina von Karbelnikoff, an inventor who often tests out her inventions on him, much to his displeasure. Anissina is also the one who taught Gwendal how to knit.
Gwendal is a tough guy except when it comes to his childhood friend, Anissina, and his brothers. He is afraid of Anissina and often hides from her so he can prevent being used in one of her crazy experiments. He is even seen sweating in panic at the thought of her. While he does not outwardly show much affection towards his brothers, he shows in times of great stress that he does care, an example being his decision to stand against the Original King to save his little brother, Wolfram. Jozak, who was sent to locate one of the Four Forbidden Boxes, tells Conrad that Gwendal really cares for Conrad`s wellbeing and doesn`t want Conrad to worry despite the Original King`s wishes for Conrad to find the Boxes. His ancestor, Siegbert Voltaire, fought along the Original King.</description>
<picture>52383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20238" type="main character in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="42">4.52</rating>
<name>von Bielefeld Wolfram</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young man who finds himself engaged to Yuuri after a mistake. He is a `bishounen`, which means a pretty or beautiful boy. He is very feminine looking, with a beautiful face, shoulder-length blond hair and long eyelashes. His appearance is so influential, that several dying people in the hospital have a miraculous recovery after laying eyes on him. Wolfram possesses fire magic, as well as being adept with a sword. He is the half-brother of Conrad and Gwendal. He has extremely high pride and is hot-headed. He is arrogant and short-tempered but can also be quite compassionate at times. He is called "little lord brat." He is the only one of the previous queen`s three sons who inherited her emerald green eyes and blonde hair, bearing a striking resemblance to her. It seems he inherited fire magic and selfishness from his fathers side. Wolfram is obsessed with Yuuri and insists on following him everywhere as he claims it is his duty to protect his fiancé, though he also seems to want to prevent him from cheating on him. His ancestor, Rufus Bielefeld, fought alongside the Original King.</description>
<picture>52386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20240" type="main character in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="12">3.98</rating>
<name>Murata Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born in Hong Kong and raised in Japan. Murata Ken met Yuuri in middle school, where they were in the same class for two years. He now goes to a famous private school. His name is similar to Yuuri`s favorite historical drama actor Matsudaira Ken, so he is the only one of Yuuri`s former classmates that he remembers the name and face of other than baseball club members. Ken is known to smile often and keep relatively quiet. He often tells jokes which don`t suit his age which makes Yuuri ask "how old are you really?".
Dr. Rodriguez was responsible for handling his soul, around the same time when Conrad transported Julia`s soul.
He is the reincarnation of the Great Sage. The double black tactician and strategist to the Original King of Shin Makoku. He remembers parts of the past lives he has had over the past 4000 years. Other people in the story don`t seem to remember any of their past lives, so his remembering some seems to be very special. Because of his past lives he is able to speak Shin Makoku`s language, English and French. His parents are always busy with work so he is home alone a lot. He also spends a lot of time with Yuuri`s family.</description>
<picture>52391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20242" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="21">6.57</rating>
<name>von Spitzweg Cecilie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The previous Maou and mother of Wolfram, Conrad and Gwendal, each with different fathers. Although initially, Cecilie seems to be rather airheaded, she is actually very astute and intelligent and a very caring person. Having been replaced as the Maou by Yuuri, Cecilie takes advantage of her open schedule to hunt for men on her "free and easy quest for love." She has displayed interest in Yuuri (though she remains one of the chief supporters in his engagement to her son, Wolfram), his older brother Shouri, and even her childhood friend Raven. At one time, she wanted to marry him, much to her brother`s chagrin. Cecilie is also quite powerful, and has admirable skill with the whip. When fighting, she has the uncanny ability to quickly dress in red leather and mask. This form and her skill tends to scare her enemies, and if they ever meet her the second time, they are usually unwilling to fight her again.</description>
<picture>52528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20243" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="10">5.70</rating>
<name>von Karbelnikoff Anissina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anissina is an inventor and is also Gwendal`s childhood friend. She often uses him to test out her inventions and it is for this reason that Gwendal seems to fear Anissina. When Gwendal is not around, Günter becomes her test subject. She is also the one who taught Gwendal, and later Greta, how to knit.
If the men are away from the castle, it is usually Anissina who takes control. When she does so, her inventions are usually seen everywhere. The names of her inventions often end in `kun`, and usually state what they are supposed to do. Her inventions often require the use of maryoku (a kind of magic) and they actually do more harm than good.
Aside from her inventions, she spends her time writing adventure story books involving herself as a super-heroine figure. These also usually keep Greta entertained, though Yuuri and Wolfram often doubt whether they are even appropriate for children.</description>
<picture>52394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20244" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="12">6.97</rating>
<name>Ulrike</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An 800-year old Genshi Miko or oracle with the form of a young girl. Ulrike comes from a long line of priestesses each chosen by the Original King to act as a channel between him and the people of Shin Makoku. She succeeds Ondine, whose final assignment after retirement was to get Yuuri to form a pact with the elements. Ulrike is the one who, at the order of and with additional powers from the Original King, transports Yuuri to and from his world to Shin Makoku. Just like all other priestesses, she is not permitted to leave the Original King`s castle. Yuri however, once tried to take her out to show her the beautiful world outside, but Wolfram barged in thinking he was flirting with her.
At one point in the anime, her "childhood spirit" escaped from her body and went outside to play. Her skills frightened the other children and caused chaos in the village. Ulrike chased after her younger form, and revealed her ability to take on the form of a young woman (as opposed to her current child-like one) to "comfort" her younger self.</description>
<picture>52395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20245" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="6">4.78</rating>
<name>Grie Yozak</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He originally doubted Yuuri, but Yuuri eventually gaines his trust by entrusting him with Morgif`s Jewel. This is Morgif`s source of power, and Yozak later returns it so Morgif can help Yuuri defend a human village from a stolen Holy Sword and its not-quite-human wielder.
He goes back a long way with Conrad: they`ve known each other since they were children. Yozak and Conrad are the only survivors of the Lütenburg army, a portion of the army of Shin Makoku that fought in the past war with the humans for the mazoku. The Lütenburg warriors were all half-human half-mazoku fighters that wished to prove their loyalty to Shin Makoku. Halfbloods were - and are - looked down upon by both mazoku and humans because of the hatred between the races.
It can only be assumed that as relations between the species change, so will the treatment of halfbreeds. Yuuri`s efforts to unite humans and mazoku are one of the main reasons Yosak supports Yuuri. He is the first one to find out that Murata Ken is the person with the soul of the Great Sage, the Original King`s trusted friend.</description>
<picture>52396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4196" picture="26343.jpg">Takeda Masanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20246" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="12">3.39</rating>
<name>Greta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Greta is the adopted human daughter of Shibuya Yuuri and Wolfram von Bielefeld. Unknown to herself, she is a princess of the fallen kingdom of Zoracca. Her mother, the Queen of Zoracca, sent her to be raised by her uncle, the King of Svelera, before the kingdom fell. At first Greta tried to kill Yuuri by posing as his illegitimate daughter because her uncaring foster parents hated the Maou and she believed she could earn their love by assassinating him. Not much later Yuuri forgives and adopts her. Wolfram follows suit, reasoning that as Yuuri`s fiancé he is also Greta`s parent.</description>
<picture>52397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3794" picture="38865.jpg">Kumai Motoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20247" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Dacascos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the men-at-arms of Covenant Castle, Dorcas (Dacauscas) sacrificed his hair for one of Günter`s schemes but ultimately remains a loyal subject - even as he`s often the source of comic relief. Dorcas often becomes emotional over good food.</description>
<picture>53320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20248" type="appears in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="15">7.82</rating>
<name>von Christ Gisela</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="638" picture="151683.jpg">Taguchi Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20249" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<rating votes="18">8.81</rating>
<name>Shibuya Miko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shibuya Miko, also known as Jennifer of Yokohama is Yuuri and Shouri`s human mother. She has known about Yuuri becoming Maou since before Yuuri was born but did not tell him. She is very energetic, loves fantasy and has a big imagination. Miko had always wanted to have a baby girl, so when Yuuri was young she let his hair grow long and dressed him in girls` clothes. Through the series little is learned about her, but she is known to be an excellent fencer, always ready and willing to defend her family.
Miko often gives strange advice to Yuuri, and in some situations it really helps Yuuri out. She likes to be called "Mama" instead of "Mom" or "Mother" by her sons, and "Jennifer" by other people. The only ones who actually call her "Mama" are not her sons, but Murata and Wolfram.
Her specialty is curry, which she says can unite the world in peace.</description>
<picture>52690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20250" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Shibuya Shouri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuri`s older brother who is apparently a genius, likes to play dating simulators and is very protective of Yuuri. He is to become Bob`s successor as the Maou of Earth. When he was younger, he met Bob who rescued Yuuri and him from some bullies. While initially despising his parents for having a divorcement argument, he also resented the fact that Yuuri will have to go to Shin Makoku eventually. Bob explained to him it will happen in the future, and Shouri was contented being with Yuuri for the time being. Shouri wanted Yuuri to call him "onii-chan" but Yuuri refused to and became more independent when he went to elementary school. It is seen that Shouri communicates regularly with Bob, who he complains emphasizes his age more than anything else.
Often carrying a cold attitude, he did not welcome having Wolfram and the others in his house. He seems especially distasteful to Conrad, and makes a point of demanding that Conrad returns his clothes to him properly cleaned (since the two of them are about the same build and size, Jennifer usually lends Shouri`s clothing to Conrad). Later, he and Conrad form an understanding based on their mutual desire to protect Yuuri.
Once Shouri ends up in Shin Makoku, he becomes suspicious about the Original King, MurataKen, and the four forbidden boxes.
Shouri eventually goes to Shin Makoku where he learns to use the powerful maryoku he possesses. Wolfram gave Shouri a pact to the elements, somewhat like how Odine (Andine by some translations) gave a pact to Yuuri to gain control of his maryoku. Shouri`s maryoku is like of Yuuri`s, the control of water, but initially Shouri`s maryoku takes the form of a giant hand. He is, however, seen to be able to shape his maryoku into water dragons after some training with Ulrike, who comments that Shouri is extraordinary because he learned to control his maryoku slightly in a short span of time.</description>
<picture>52692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9365" picture="34581.jpg">Kokuryuu Sachi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20251" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>Shibuya Shouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shibuya Shouma is the father of Yuuri and Shouri. He is a Mazoku from Shin Makoku. He originally knew about Yuuri becoming Maou when he met with Conrad shortly after Conrad came to Earth. Shouma was originally angered by Conrad`s cold attitude, and told him to never let his son or wife see that unsmiling face. Conrad takes those words to heart, and later grows to become the `smiling godfather` Yuuri often sees. Shouma is much more soft-spoken than his wife, and a fan of the Boston Red Sox.</description>
<picture>52691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20252" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-05">
<rating votes="7">5.23</rating>
<name>Doria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maid in the castle.</description>
<picture>52677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20253" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-05">
<rating votes="7">6.20</rating>
<name>Lasania</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A maid in the castle.</description>
<picture>52679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="312" picture="245047.jpg">Nakanishi Tamaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20254" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="7">6.20</rating>
<name>Sangria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20255" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="4">6.19</rating>
<name>Eefe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the servants at the castle.
Her specialty is making sweets.</description>
<picture>52412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2126" picture="145389.jpg">Niino Michi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20256" type="appears in" update="2010-08-03">
<name>von Grantz Adalbert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Adelbert is the first important character that Yuuri meets in Shin Makoku. He is Julia`s former fiancée and abandons Shin Makoku, as he feels that the way of the Mazoku is wrong. He believes that the Mazoku are simply pawns of the Original King. Though in the beginning he is considered an enemy, as the series progresses he begins to protect Yuuri, though he still wants Yuuri to show him what he is worth as the new king.</description>
<picture>52534.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20257" type="appears in" update="2010-08-09">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>von Wincott Susannah Julia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Julia was a kind woman who gave up her happiness for the sake of others. Her father remarked that she, like her ancestors, had inherited the trait of being mischievous, but she often sacrificed herself for other people. Many around her, such as Gisela and Celi, have commented that Julia pushed herself over the limit when trying to help people on the battlefield, which eventually resulted in her death. Gisela was one who remained by Julia`s side in during the latter`s final moments.</description>
<picture>53067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="613" picture="155849.jpg">Mizuno Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20258" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>von Spitzweg Stoffel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cecilie`s older brother; he was the former regent of the former Maou and was kicked out of the castle when Yuuri arrived for trying to forcefully assert his influence on the kingdom. His own nephews do not trust him, as he was responsible for the last war against the humans.</description>
<picture>52725.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20259" type="appears in" update="2010-08-02">
<name>von Karbelnikoff Densham</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20260" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>von Wincott Del Kiasun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20271" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-05">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Shin`ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Great One (known as the Shin`ou) is the first King of Shin Makoku. His soul watches over the lands of Shin Makoku, and priestess such as Ulrike and Ondine can communicate with him in a limited fashion, one they call "hearing His Majesty`s voice". Murata also appears to be able to communicate with him, and is often seen scolding him for meddling in Shin Makoku`s affairs.
4000 years ago, the Great One sealed the Soushu into four boxes, which became known as the "Four Forbidden Boxes". However, while part of the Soushu was sealed in the boxes, a small part of the Soushu infected the Great One to the extent where his right arm seemed slightly decayed. The Great One knew that the Soushu would eventually take over his mind and body completely, so the Great One came up with a plan along with his Great Sage to completely eradicate the Soushu in the future. This involved sealing the Soushu with a pure soul, and destroying it. This soul turned out to be the Great One, but Yuuri manages to eradicate the Soushu without harming the Great One, earning Yuuri the title of the greatest Maou. The Original King commented that he was glad he chose Yuuri as the Maou.</description>
<picture>52730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20272" type="appears in" update="2010-08-02">
<name>von Bielefeld Voltrana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20273" type="appears in" update="2010-08-02">
<name>Ryan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20274" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>von Rochefort</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52727.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20275" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>von Gyllenhaal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2248" picture="170362.jpg">Kawashima Tokuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20276" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>von Radford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52728.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20291" type="appears in" update="2010-08-02">
<rating votes="7">8.44</rating>
<name>Shibuya Yuuri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20321" type="appears in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Laila</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52507.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20322" type="appears in" update="2010-08-03">
<name>Antoine Jean Le Pierre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The King of Francia.</description>
<picture>52508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20323" type="appears in" update="2010-08-03">
<name>Laila no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20324" type="appears in" update="2010-08-03">
<name>Laila no Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20325" type="main character in" update="2010-08-05">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Janeus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At first he appears as a mysterious cloaked man, later on, we can see his face.</description>
<picture>52684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20335" type="appears in" update="2010-08-03">
<name>Grisela Geigenhuber</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Years ago, Hube`s bigotry and ambition led to many deaths forcing Gwendal, his cousin, to banish Hube from the Demon Kingdom to search for a lost artifact, the Great Demon Flute. Twenty years later, Yuuri discovers Hube in Conansia Svelera (Suberera) from the human woman, Nicola, who is bearing Hube`s child. Yuuri struggles to learn details about Hube`s past but no one wants to talk about the acts that were so terrible, even Conrad is content to watch him die. Hube becomes the bodyguard for a corrupt lord who swindles people into gambling and taking their shop deeds. When Yuuri eventually discovers the truth, he forgave Hube for unintentionally trying to kill him, and begs Gwendel not to kill Hube. Gwendal eventually agrees not to, and Hube leaves for his own castle, but not before he tells Gwendal about a box he saw in Suberera. The incident left Hube without his left eye, indicating this box was one of the Four Forbidden Boxes.
Hube swore loyalty to Yuuri because Yuuri chose spare his life despite Hube`s crime. As such, Hube would go to extreme lengths to protect Yuuri, such as leaving Nicola to fight against the possessed Original King.</description>
<picture>52526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20336" type="appears in" update="2010-08-03">
<name>Chevalier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20337" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="3">4.11</rating>
<name>Saralegui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The young king of Small Shimaron who asks Yuuri to call him Sara. He is extremely beautiful and usually said to be someone who`s beauty could rival that of Wolfram. At first glance seems soft-spoken and kind-hearted. He`s already at adult age but still uses `boku` which is usually used by young males when referring to themselves. He can`t remember much about his parents. He has the power of hypnosis, which he tried to use on Yuuri, but with no effect. The two become friends despite misgivings Yuuri`s friends have concerning the human king. Yuuri wants very badly to become very close friends with Sara.</description>
<picture>52531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20338" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Berias</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20339" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-05">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Lanzhil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20340" type="main character in" update="2010-08-09">
<rating votes="2">4.42</rating>
<name>Alazon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20422" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<rating votes="3">2.34</rating>
<name>Flynn Gilbit</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lady Flynn Gilbit assumed the role of her husband Lord Norman Gilbit to protect her small country, Caloria, and its lands after his death. She chose to wear a mask and pretend to be her husband because Small Shimaron had conquered Caloria and, under their laws, women cannot inherit lands or titles, and adoptions are only valid before the death of the husband. Upon discovering that Big Shimaron has one of the Forbidden boxes ("The End of the Wind"), she assists Yuuri and his group in retrieving it.
The original rulers of Caloria were the Wincott family, and because of Flynn`s ancestors, the Wincott family was forcefully removed from rule. Due to this incident, Flynn is troubled when Julia`s father, Lord Odell von Wincott, visits Blood Pledge castle on Yuuri`s request.</description>
<picture>52674.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3890" picture="186170.jpg">Takamori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20423" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>Baker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A close friend of Flynn.</description>
<picture>52675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20255" picture="52681.jpg">Shinohara Daisaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20424" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>T-Zou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sheep from Caloria. He hates Manjuu and turns into a rampaging sheep with red eyes when he sees one. That behaviour is sometimes used by Yuuri for his aid.
His "catchphrase" is "moushikashite" which can be translated as "Could it be that....".
T-Zou can fly/glide through the air.</description>
<picture>52676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20425" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<rating votes="3">3.49</rating>
<name>Alford Maquina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20426" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>Jose Rodriguez</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Associate of the Maou of Earth and also a friend of Conrad. He lives on earth and transported the Great Sage`s soul (who ended up being Murata Ken) to Japan at the same time Conrad transported Julia`s. He became Ken`s pediatrician when Ken was younger and began to remember his previous lives. Later on he is seen working for the Maou of Earth.
Dr. Rodriguez is a pediatrician who loves Japanese anime and often travels to Akihabara to buy anime toys.</description>
<picture>52694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20427" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>Bob</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Maou of Earth. A businessman who owns several prosperous companies and is even called "the Maou in the business world" and "The Mazoku who looks like a movie star" by Shibuya Miko. He met Yuuri and Shouri when they were children and saved them from some bullies. His ancestor was Christel Wincott, who brought "The Mirror at the Bottom of the Sea" from Shin Makoku to Earth. He was the last keeper of the box, before he entrusted it to Yuuri, who took it back with him to Shin Makoku.
Bob hates to have any semblance of home life in his office and so his workers have to wash the dishes in a bathtub and he also does not keep tissues in his office.</description>
<picture>52695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20430" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>Maurittsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Greta`s grandfather from Zuratia.</description>
<picture>52696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20431" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>Izura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Greta`s mother.</description>
<picture>52699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20435" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>von Wincott Rinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The son of Susannah Julia von Wincott`s younger brother (older brother in the manga).
He`s the "enemy" of Günter and likes to play tricks on people.</description>
<picture>52704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20436" type="appears in" update="2010-08-12">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Daikenja</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reincarnated as Murata Ken, the Great Sage is the trusted friend of the Shin`ou.</description>
<picture>53244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20437" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>Gerald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="324" picture="223539.jpg">Saitou Jirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20439" type="appears in" update="2010-08-05">
<name>Raven</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raven, a childhood friend of Celi and Stoffel, advises Lord Stoffel and executes orders on the ex-Regent`s behalf. Raven`s strategies and ruthlessness endanger Yuuri, however in his heart Raven is more loving than malicious.</description>
<picture>52726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20550" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Nicola</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nicola first met Yuuri and Gwendel at her "wedding" where she escaped after hearing Yuuri`s speech about gloves and mates. She was delighted to learn that her rescuers include her lover Hube`s cousin. She was the one to change Hube`s views about humans. The couple fell in love and she was already pregnant by Lord Grisela "Hube" Geigenhuber when she met Yuuri. Nicola kept half of the Great Demon Flute which she gave to Yuuri.</description>
<picture>52969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1888" picture="228611.jpg">Masuda Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20551" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Grisela Ernst</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The child of Nicola and Geigenhuber. Despite being called Ernst, he`s simply called El by everybody.</description>
<picture>52971.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20600" type="appears in" update="2010-08-09">
<name>Kiinan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="296" picture="17124.jpg">Nishimura Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20611" type="appears in" update="2010-08-09">
<name>Velma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20703" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-12">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Berias</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20704" type="appears in" update="2010-08-12">
<name>Gilbert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Once a king of Shoushimaron, found his love in Azalon, queen of Seisakoku. Together they had a child: Saralegui, of Shinzoku and human blood.</description>
<picture>53243.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="89967" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">㋮王, 再び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maou, Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maou, Futatabi</title>
<summary>Yuri returns to the Great Demon Kingdom after an absence, only to find that Wolfram is about to replace him as king.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789521</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="89968" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">㋮王の条件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Requirements of a Maou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maou no Jouken</title>
<summary>Yuri has to prove himself if he`s going to retain his regal position.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789522</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="89969" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">㋮王の決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decision of the Maou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maou no Ketsui</title>
<summary>Wolfram breaks off his engagement with Yuri and returns to his ancestral land.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789524</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90369" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">グレタとユーラム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Greta and Yuuram</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Greta to Yuuram</title>
<summary>Yuri and Wolfram buy Greta a miniature bearbee, but bad things happen when water touches it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789525</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90483" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒のジェネウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Janeus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro no Janeus</title>
<summary>Langille orders Conrad to prove his loyalty to Big Cimaron by executing Yuri.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789533</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90484" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">囚われのマ王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Captured Maou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toraware no Maou</title>
<summary>Yuri is held captive by King Langille of Big Cimaron, while Murata discovers a cache of stolen swords.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789532</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90485" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宴の夜に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Night of the Banquet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utage no Yoru ni</title>
<summary>Yuri meets the young King Saralegi at a banquet while disguised as a woman, but is soon exposed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789531</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90486" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">潜入! 大シマロン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Infiltration! Big Shimaron</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sennyuu! Dai Shimaron</title>
<summary>Murata sneaks into Big Cimaron to retrieve something he left behind in a past life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789529</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90487" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライラの結婚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laila`s Marriage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Laila no Kekkon</title>
<summary>Yuri is tasked with finding a stolen sacred sword so Lyla can get married.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789527</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91315" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コンラッドとギュンター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conrad and Guenter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Conrad to Guenter</title>
<summary>The past relationship between Gunter and his former student, Conrad, is revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789534</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91316" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">花嫁はアニシナ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anissina the Bride!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanayome wa Anissina!?</title>
<summary>Anissina`s brother plans an arranged marriage for her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789536</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91317" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者と三本の剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero and the Three Swords</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha to Sanbon no Ken</title>
<summary>Geneus and the White Crows target Alford for his ancient sword.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789537</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91318" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小シマロン王サラレギー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shou Shimaron`s King, Saralegui</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shou Shimaron Ou Saralegui</title>
<summary>While on a mission to retrieve the stolen swords, Yuri properly meets King Saralegi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789542</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="91319" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">水に映る月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moon Reflected in Water</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizu ni Utsuru Tsuki</title>
<summary>Yuri`s back on Earth, but one of Anissina`s inventions switches his mind with Shori`s.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789546</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92578" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友のために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For the Sake of a Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo no Tame ni</title>
<summary>Just as Yuri is about to surrender himself to King Langille, an assassin shoots an arrow at him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789558</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92579" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">王の守護者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The King`s Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ou no Shugosha</title>
<summary>When Sara is captured by his traitorous army, Yuri infiltrates the castle to rescue him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789556</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92580" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Kings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Ou</title>
<summary>Yuri uncovers a conspiracy inside Saralegi`s castle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789554</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92581" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小シマロンへの招待</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invitation to Small Shimaron</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shou Shimaro e no Shoutai</title>
<summary>Yuri and company set off for Small Cimaron to make an alliance with Saralegi, but Wolfram is suspicious.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789552</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92582" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウィンコットの遺産</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wincott Inheritance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wincott no Isan</title>
<summary>Lindsay discovers a dangerous invention created by an ancestor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789549</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="92583" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">風の子守歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wind`s Lullaby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze no Komoriuta</title>
<summary>The trusted retainer of Greta`s late mother comes to the Great Demon Kingdom to take Greta home to be a queen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789548</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93178" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">苦い別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Bitter Farewell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nigai Wakare</title>
<summary>Yuri tries to uncover the mysterious assassin`s identity, while Saralegi hovers near death.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789560</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93600" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">円卓の人々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">People of the Round Table</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Entaku no Hitobito</title>
<summary>The Ten Aristocrats converge on Covenant Castle for the usual meeting, but Yuri gets them to become closer by playing games.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789562</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94814" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思いの果て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Edge of Imagination</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoi no Hate</title>
<summary>When Yuri and the others return to the Great Demon Kingdom, Shori is put under house arrest by the Ten Aristocrats.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789576</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94815" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">発動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invocation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsudou</title>
<summary>While Big Cimaron launches an all-out attack, Shori insists that he`s leaving with Queen Alazon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789574</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94816" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">神剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Holy Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinken</title>
<summary>With Adalbert`s help, Yuri and company sneak into the White Crows` lair to rescue Shori, while Big Cimaron`s army is already on the march.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789572</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94817" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">白い鴉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The White Crow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Karasu</title>
<summary>Shori meets the leader of the White Crows, while the shocking connection between Murata and Geneus is revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789570</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94818" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">荒野の追跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pursuit Across The Plains</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arano no Tsuiseki</title>
<summary>Yuri attempts to save his big brother from Geneus`s clutches.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789568</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94819" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">選ばれし者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Chosen One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Erabareshi Mono</title>
<summary>Shori manages to use his own magic to rescue Ernst, but is then captured by them instead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789566</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94820" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エル誘拐事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">El`s Kidnapping</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">El Yuukaijiken</title>
<summary>The White Crows abduct Hube`s son, Ernst, because of the unusual power he possesses.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789564</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95689" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">㋮王辞めます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Quitting as Maou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maou Yamemasu</title>
<summary>Yuri returns to Earth, but finds himself in the future, where he`s an adult, Shori is the governor of Tokyo, and no one except for Yuri remembers the Great Demon Kingdom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789580</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95720" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">開戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starting a War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaisen</title>
<summary>Yuri attempts to stave off an invasion of the kingdom by negotiating personally with King Langille, but his effort at teleporting to the king`s ship takes him somewhere else.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789578</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95846" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">吹き抜ける青い風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Blue Wind Blowing Through</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukinukeru Aoi Kaze</title>
<summary>On the way back home from Big Cimaron, Conrad is ambushed by Saralegi`s bodyguard, Berius.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789583</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96052" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しき咆哮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sad Howl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashiki Houkou</title>
<summary>Now that he is the master of the Divine Sword, Sara imbues the weakened Geneus with its power to get revenge.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789594</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96053" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真の力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Power of Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin no Chikara</title>
<summary>Yuri welcomes Alazon to Covenant Castle as a guest... but someone else doesn`t want her there.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789592</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96054" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">叶わぬ約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unfulfilled Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanawanu Yakusoku</title>
<summary>Geneus returns to the Great Demon Kingdom to wreak havoc.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789590</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96055" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖なる王国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Holy Kingdom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seinaru Oukoku</title>
<summary>The connections between Saralegi, Berius and Alazon are revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789588</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96056" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">予期せぬ再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Unexpected Union</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokisenu Saikai</title>
<summary>Saralegi journeys to the Great Demon Kingdom to retrieve his servant, Berius, but an unexpected guest shows up too.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789586</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="97175" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰る場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Place to Return to</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaeru Basho</title>
<summary>The Great One has a final confrontation with Geneus, unless Yuri has something to say about it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789596</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="97176" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">㋮た会える日を (終)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Until the Day We Can Meet Again (Finale)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mata Aeru Hi o (Owari)</title>
<summary>When Yuri wakes up after sleeping for days, he finds that his demon magic is gone, so he`s unable to go back to Earth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789598</identifier>
<identifier>kyo-kara-maoh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120609" update="2010-08-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120610" update="2010-08-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
