<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5818" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>2008-09-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Slayers Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Рубаки Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="synonym">Slayers: A kis boszorkány IV/I</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">秀逗魔导士REVOLUTION</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Slay Rev</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スレイヤーズ REVOLUTION</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Slayers Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Slayers Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Slayers -A kis boszorkány</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Непобедимите (сезон 4)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6179" type="Sequel">Slayers Evolution-R</anime>
<anime id="364" type="Prequel">Slayers Try</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="165330">Its Slayers watch it now or Lina will cast Dragon Slave</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="104619">It seems very good according to the first episode :D</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/slayers_revolution/r/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="2745" type="Character Design">Miyata Naomi</name>
<name id="2120" type="Direction">Watanabe Takashi</name>
<name id="3848" type="Original Work">Araizumi Rui</name>
<name id="4395" type="Music">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="2745" type="Chief Animation Direction">Miyata Naomi</name>
<name id="9744" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sano Takao</name>
<name id="9561" type="Chief Animation Direction">Washikita Kyouta</name>
<name id="6752" type="Music">Vink</name>
<name id="1338" type="Original Work">Kanzaka Hajime</name>
<name id="7271" type="Series Composition">Takayama Jirou</name>
</creators>
<description>Having lost the Sword of Light in the previous battle, http://anidb.net/ch1000 [Lina] and http://anidb.net/ch7616 [Gourry] continue their journey in search of a replacement weapon. On the way, the two of them meet up with http://anidb.net/ch7619 [Amelia] and http://anidb.net/ch7619 [Zelgadis] in the kingdom of Luvinagard while taunting some pirates. Lina is happy to reunite with her old friends, but appearing before her is Luvinagard`s Inspector of the Special Investigative Unit; a man called http://anidb.net/ch14843 [Wizer]. However, Lina is amazed at his unusual behaviour...
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1621">5.96</permanent>
<temporary count="1635">7.26</temporary>
<review count="3">6.77</review>
</ratings>
<picture>52972.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9500</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4028</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4287</identifier>
<identifier>uxpusv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/slayers_revolution/r/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1411</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330747</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1000" type="main character in" update="2014-09-22">
<rating votes="1994">9.10</rating>
<name>Lina Inverse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lina Inverse is the primary protagonist and the only character appearing in the whole Slayers-franchise. She is an adolescent but very powerful sorceress, with a great love for money, treasure and food. In the anime and manga (but not in the light novel) Lina uses overly destructive magic recklessly, often with little provocation. She is reputed to be an evil, powerful, destructive, diminutive sorceress (the evil part is arguably not true, though one may consider her greed and general lack of concern for others unless they are in danger of being killed can be considered "evil").
Lina has gained many different nicknames, including "Bandit Killer" and "Dragon Spooker", neither of which she`s very fond of, though to her, her most embarrassing nickname is "Lina the Pink" which is her official title amongst the sorcerer`s guild.</description>
<picture>161200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7489" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-23">
<rating votes="247">8.76</rating>
<name>Xellos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Xellos is a mazoku and the priest of Greater Beast Zelas Metallium.
Xellos was created by Zelas during the Kouma War. The mazoku put a barrier over the peninsula and managed keep the enemy`s reinforcements out of the battle. Because of this, however, four of the five lords were unable to participate in the war anymore, so priests and generals were created in order to represent them. Because he is her only immediate servant, and he was created from a great deal of her power, Xellos is more powerful than all the other priests and generals of Ruby Eye Shabranigdu`s subordinates.
In the Kouma War, Xellos single-handedly killed thousands of golden dragons; he is feared and hated by them ever since. They refer to him as the Dragon Slayer, although he does not like this name, probably because it does not fit the "image" he wants others to view him as. After the war, before serving Hellmaster, Xelloss`s duty for a thousand years was to find stray copies of the Claire Bible and destroy them so that humans could not find an easy way to defeat mazoku (with Zanaffar), or utilise the power of the Lord of Nightmares.
Xelloss` true astral form is that of a simple black cone. He is able to divide his power into dozens of tiny cones that can inflict damage over a long period of time.</description>
<picture>26124.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7616" type="main character in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="257">7.19</rating>
<name>Gourry Gabriev</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Lina Inverse destroyed the Dragon no Kiba (Dragon`s Fang) gang, and was later encountered by a small array of vengeful bandits, Gourry Gabriev jumped in to save her. Though Lina appreciated the offer, she initially opted against accepting Gourry as a bodyguard, but Gourry`s big-brotherly nature prevented him from acting otherwise. Gourry, dense as a brick, saw Lina as a younger girl in need of protection, and thus, he offered it.
Gourry is the owner of the most powerful sword known to man, the mysterious Sword of Light. The Sword of Light channels its users intentions into energy, usually taking the form of a gleaming blade of light. Gourry has learned how to utilize the sword`s energy in different forms, though, most notably the power of swinging it quickly downwards to form energy beam projectiles.
Gourry is the swordsman of the group, and acts the role very well. He`s single-minded in his protection of Lina, and even after helping Lina defeat Ruby-Eye Shabranigdu, he has resolved to follow Lina around wherever she goes. Supposedly, he has nothing better to do, and perhaps still sees himself as her guardian.</description>
<picture>26399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7617" type="appears in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="149">8.82</rating>
<name>The Slayers</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Major characters of the series, which form (mostly) stable group.</description>
<picture>26408.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7618" type="main character in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="293">7.70</rating>
<name>Zelgadis Greywords</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Lina Inverse overthrew the Dragon`s Fang bandit gang, one of Zelgadiss` men, Zolf, happened to be stuck inside. And, well, he got incinerated. Needless to say, Zelgadiss was mad. More importantly, though, Lina had gotten a very valuable Orihalcon statue, which was the reason Zolf was there to begin with. Zelgadiss wanted the statue in hopes that it could cure his chimaeric curse.
Only, it didn`t quite work out that way. Zelgadiss didn`t quite cure himself, even after the whole incident with Rezo, the Red Priest and Ruby-Eye Shabranigdu. So, he`s still searching for a cure, hoping to find one of the fabled Clair-Bibles in hopes to cure himself. The curse makes him 1/3 golem, 1/3 demon, and 1/3 human, which makes him impervious to most physical weapon such as swords and buckshot, but not to the physical impact of, say, a cannonball.
Zelgadiss is quite self-conscious about his appearance, almost ashamed of it. In fact, he`s a very quiet character all around, only speaking when necessary, and only interested in the shortest path to his cure. He also tends to get embarassed easily wherever the topic of romance is brought up.
Zelgadiss is a superb swordsman, having trained many long years. He often enhances his blade with the Astral Vine spell, one of many Shamanist spells at his disposal. He has more or less mastered the Spirit category of Shamanism, having learned its most powerful spell, the Ra-Tilt, among numerous other spells in other categories.</description>
<picture>26411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7619" type="main character in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="293">6.53</rating>
<name>Amelia Wil Tesla Seyruun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amelia is the daughter of Philionel el de Seyruun, Crown Prince of the kingdom of Seyruun. Like her father, Amelia is a self-proclaimed Champion of Justice(tm) and is singleminded in her quest for truth, honor, and dignity. Also like her father, she`s a complete klutz and has no clue of what IS and ISN`T a true cause for justice.
Amelia has trained since birth for her cause; once convinced, she isn`t easily dissuaded from inflicting her particular flavor of justice on whoever she perceives to be an "enemy of the people". She thinks of Lina as a hero - a destructive hero, but nevertheless a hero - and wants to be just like her and every other good hero that comes along.
Amelia gets bored being royalty sometimes - she often follows her father Phil on journeys around the countryside. She often looks for trouble, simply so that she can right it. Whenever scouting out an area, she always includes a quick look for the highest place to stand.
...
Why does she always look for the highest place to stand, you ask? In case the enemy strikes, she wants to be able to strike back with a dynamic, triumphant pose of her own, terrifying the enemy with fear of justice. A lot of times, she ends up falling, too, she`s only a young girl after all. In fact, Amelia has the reputation of being one of the clumsiest characters in all of Slayers, topped only by Martina.
Amelia is also a budding sorcerer in her own right. Her specialty is white magic, however she also has reached the highest level of training in Shamanist Spirit magic, a testament to her quick learning time and eagerness to learn. She has even developed a spell or two of her own, most notably the Visfarank spell, which seems to be the glowing manifestation of justice as a pair of boxing gloves.</description>
<picture>169335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7711" type="appears in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="49">6.24</rating>
<name>Philionel El Di Seyruun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Phil is the Crown Prince of Seyruun, and presumably the only one trusted to take the throne after numerous assassination attempts. Phil, like his daughter, is dominated by his thirst for justice, so much that he has dedicated his life to being a pacifist. Or at least that`s what he says, he acts more like a pro wrestler sometimes.
Unlike most of the Seyruun royal family, Phil has no magical powers, but he does have a lot of brute strength. He uses this mostly in the form of oxymoronic, justice-themed physical attacks, such as "Pacifist Crush", "Kindness to All Creatures Kick", "Benevolent Giant Swing", and "Goodwill Towards Man Smash". His sheer brute strength is even enough to destroy lesser demons.</description>
<picture>26578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7715" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-04">
<rating votes="105">5.91</rating>
<name>Sylphiel Nels Lahda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sylphiel Nels Lahda is the daughter of Eruk, one of the nobles of Sairaag. Not too much is known about her, strangely; she just seems to show up in the oddest of places.
Sylphiel plays her role in society well - she has a very dignified manner of speaking. She is also a very kind soul, altruistic in a way. She has no wish to see any undeserving person harmed, and has dedicated her life to that cause. She has reached what many would perceive to be the highest point of White Magic, having learned the potent spells of "Resurrection" and an insanely powerful variant of "Recovery".
However, Sylphiel can`t cast any other magic worth squat, it seems. Shamanist Fire magic is almost completely beyond her grasp; it seems that she might lack the drive to even be capable of causing destruction. Then again, she can if she wants to - she knows a very powerful Black Magic spell, the "Dragu-Slave". In fact, she learned it simply by watching Lina cast it.</description>
<picture>133182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7716" type="appears in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="50">5.60</rating>
<name>Aka Houshi Rezo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Red Priest Rezo was one of the Five Wise Men of the Age; born blind at birth, he wandered the countryside performing small miracles of the faith. Later, it seems that his faith wavered a bit more towards the dark side.</description>
<picture>26586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8329" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="17">2.01</rating>
<name>Zuuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zuuma is a highly skilled assassin, was first hired to kill Lina by Kanzel, a mazoku serving Chaos Dragon Garv.</description>
<picture>27457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8332" type="main character in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="24">2.31</rating>
<name>Pokota</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pokota was born a human, but when he was an adolescent, the Durum sickness plagued Taforashia. The king, Pokota`s father, became very ill. Rezo, the Red Priest, appeared and sealed the residents of Taforashia in sleeping chambers to isolate them until a cure was found. Rezo sealed Pokota`s human body in a chamber, but he used a magical vase to transfer Pokota`s spirit into his current form, an animal-like creature about 2 feet tall.
Pokota`s primary physical characteristics are his large ears that function as his primary set of arms and hands, even though he has a smaller set of arms on his torso. He uses these ears to cast spells, make gestures, and glide through the air. His left ear has a gold ring near its four-fingered "hand," resembling a bracelet. In addition to flying, Pokota can also walk or run on his two short legs.
Pokota has short, beige-colored fur, a mohawk of lavender-colored hair and green fur on the ends of his ears. Beginning at his neck and ending part-way down his torso is a zipper that he opens to remove a replica Sword of Light from inside his body. He wears a red cape.</description>
<picture>27462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8333" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="11">3.27</rating>
<name>Posel Korba Taforashia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Posel Korba Taforashia, is a sorcerer and prince of the kingdom of Taforashia.
He was born a human, but when he was an adolescent, the Durum sickness plagued Taforashia. The king, Pokota`s father, became very ill. Rezo, the Red Priest, appeared and sealed the residents of Taforashia in sleeping chambers to isolate them until a cure was found. Rezo sealed Pokota`s human body in a chamber, but he used a magical vase to transfer Pokota`s spirit into his current form, an animal-like creature about 2 feet tall.
Posel has long, lavender hair with a mohawk in the front. He wears a gold hoop in his left ear, and his clothes are for the most part green.</description>
<picture>27463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8480" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="26">5.46</rating>
<name>Ozel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ozel is a servant of Rezo. She first appeared as maid to Gioconda, who was assumed to be the owner of Hellmaster`s Jar then, since she specifically said that her orders were to "guard the jar and its owner". Despite being human in appearance, she is actually an artificial human doll.</description>
<picture>27626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33" picture="133462.jpg">Kimura Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14829" type="appears in" update="2010-02-06">
<rating votes="7">3.09</rating>
<name>Kuppii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12603" picture="42573.jpg">Katou Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14843" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">4.58</rating>
<name>Wizer Freion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wizer Freion is an inspector of the Ruvinagald kingdom. He appears in both Slayers REVOLUTION and the Slayers novels. However, he plays significantly different roles in each.
Wizer appears in volume 10 of the novels. When Lina and Gourry are in Solaria, Wizer appears in a mask to rescue them multiple times. His identity is not revealed until the end.
In Slayers REVOLUTION, Wizer at first glance seems to serve as the comic relief of the series. However, he is actually quite intelligent and schemes well (except when he took Xelloss`s advice in episode eight). He also displayed some physical and personality similarities to Xelloss; most notably, his eyes are rarely open, and when they are, are shown to also have little to no light in them, portraying a rather sinister face to match his underlying cunning disposition.
Wizer first appeared in episode 1 of REVOLUTION, where he tried to arrest Lina Inverse "for being Lina Inverse." He was investigating the destruction of the mage-tanks of Ruvinagald, and suspected Lina was the culprit. However, the tanks actually being destroyed by Pokota, the designer of said tanks and a magic user on the same level as Lina herself.
His stated reason for his single-minded fervency was to impress the ladies of Ruvinagald`s court. Wizer may or may not have been assigned the case of the disappeared aid relief meant for the Taforashia kingdom, but he was intelligent enough to suspect and confirm Gioconda`s guilt, to even Xelloss` surprise. While he wasn`t a participant in the final battle of Slayers REVOLUTION, he was a key witness, as he knew that even if he tried to help the Slayers he would only end up getting in their way. He was last seen speaking to Xelloss as they watched the battle unfold.
Source: kanzaka.wikia.com</description>
<picture>42597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14844" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="6">2.06</rating>
<name>Duclis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Duclis was a friend of the royal family of Taforashia. When the Durum sickness struck the kingdom, Duclis and Taforashia`s prince, Pokota, tried to heal the residents, but the illness was too fast. Rezo, the Red Priest, appeared and put the kingdom`s residents to sleep until a cure could be found. Rezo transferred the spirits of Duclis and Pokota into their current animal-like forms so they could try to find a cure without being affected by the disease.
Source: kanzaka.wikia.com</description>
<picture>42598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16701" picture="33550.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14845" type="appears in" update="2010-02-06">
<rating votes="3">1.19</rating>
<name>Gioconda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14846" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<rating votes="4">3.62</rating>
<name>Zanaffar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zanaffar is a chimera, created by the inappropriate usage of a magical process written in the Claire Bible, which originally described the creation of the so-called Zenaffa armor. The Zanaffar created by Copy Rezo was voiced by Koyasu Takehito (who also voiced Copy Rezo) and the Zanaffar that appears in Slayers REVOLUTION is voiced by Ishii Kouji.
The four legged silver beast has roughly the size of a medium dragon, and the head of a wolf. Whip-like tentacles sprout from its torso. It is not surely known which creatures serve as components to the chimera; it does seem to have, however, a connection to the golden dragons, as Zanaffar is able to use the same laser breath that they possess. It can be shot either from its mouth or from its tentacles.
Source: http://kanzaka.wikia.com/wiki/Zanaffar</description>
<picture>42600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14847" type="appears in" update="2010-02-06">
<rating votes="2">1.77</rating>
<name>Zoran</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12610" picture="42593.jpg">Taniko Mirei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14848" type="appears in" update="2010-02-06">
<rating votes="2">1.77</rating>
<name>Fran</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2233" picture="21784.jpg">Takewaka Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="91404" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Amazing 驚愕のドラグスレイブ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amazing: The Astonishing Dragon Slave!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amazing: Kyougaku no Drag Slave!?</title>
<summary>Lina’s captured by a government inspector, arrested for the crime of being Lina! He’s brought an entire battalion of soldiers - and a tank - but a furry, mysterious interloper might be the biggest threat.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91598" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Because それはリナ=インバースだから!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Because: You`re Lina Inverse, That`s Why!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Because: Sore wa Lina Inverse Dakara!</title>
<summary>To prove her innocence to Wizer, Lina battles Pokota, the tiny creature actually responsible for the recent wave of exploding tanks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91599" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Chase 終わりなき追走!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chase: The Endless Pursuit!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chase: Owarinaki Tsuisou!</title>
<summary>Wizer accuses Lina of abducting the pets of wealthy people. She’ll have to sail to a mysterious island - and survive an onslaught of strange beasts - to clear her name.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91600" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Drifter どっちが追うか追われるか!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drifter: Who`s Chasing Whom?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Drifter: Docchi ga Ou ka Owareru ka!</title>
<summary>After hearing why Pokota’s been destroying tanks, Amelia joins the tiny creature’s crusade of devastation. Their first battle as a team is against a powerful opponent - Lina!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91601" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Eternal 悠久に眠れし森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eternal: The Forever-Sleeping Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eternal: Yuukyuu ni Nemureshi Mori</title>
<summary>After Pokota explains how his people came to be trapped in a state of magical slumber, Lina’s crew discovers a familiar face among those involved with the stolen tanks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91703" update="2008-07-03">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92212" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Fall on 奇祭! 珍祭? あの玉を押しあげろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fall On: Strange Festival! Bizarre Festival? Push That Ball Up!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fall On: Kisai! Chinsai? Ano Tama o Oshiagero!</title>
<summary>In a village divided by a feud, Lina’s gang takes on Pokota and Duclis’s goons in a strange contest: each team must do whatever it takes to be the first to roll their giant ball to the top of a mountain!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92213" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Gorgeous 狙われた豪華客船!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gorgeous: The Targeted Luxury Liner!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gorgeous: Nerawareta Gouka Kyakusen!?</title>
<summary>A pleasure cruise turns into a nightmare! Someone is after the Sword of Light, and Lina, Pokota, and the rest might not survive to see dry land unless they can identify the hidden assassin - or is it assassins?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92214" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Hurry up つっこめっ! いや, つっこむな?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurry Up: Run Through! No, Don`t?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurry Up: Tsukkome! Iya, Tsukkomuna?</title>
<summary>Lina’s crew navigates a fortress full of traps set by Wizer. When a far more powerful adversary is revealed to be pulling the Inspector’s strings, Lina employs an odd strategy that surprises everyone!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92215" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Insider 真実を知るもの!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Insider: The One Who Knows the Truth!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Insider: Shinjitsu o Shiru Mono!</title>
<summary>Gioconda’s plan to start an arms race will soon come to fruition - unless Lina and her gang can bust out of their cell! Meanwhile, Pokota learns of Duclis’s plan to avenge the people of Taforashia.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92380" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Judgment 蘇る白銀!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Judgment: The Silver One Rises Again!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Judgment: Yomigaeru Shirogane!</title>
<summary>Lina and her friends battle Gioconda, Zuuma, and Ozzel! And thanks to some information shared by Wizer, Pokota and Duclis find they share a common enemy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92441" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Keep out しのびよる魔獣!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Keep Out: The Demon Beast Looms!</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Влизането Забранено!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keep Out: Shinobiyoru Majuu!</title>
<summary>Duclis unleashes the Zanaffar on those who failed the people of Taforashia during their darkest time! But even as the gang vows to fight alongside Pokota, time is running out for the beast’s next target!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92823" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Legacy 決戦セイルーン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legacy: Decisive Battle in Seyruun!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Legacy: Kessen Saillune!</title>
<summary>Duclis and Zanaffar begin their assault on Seyruun! Lina and the crew struggle against the demon’s awesome power - but with Gourry wielding Pokota’s Sword of Light, they just might have a chance!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="92824" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Misty 振り下ろされる刃!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Misty: The Blades Are Brought Down!</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Битката на Остриетата</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misty: Furiorosareru Yaiba!</title>
<summary>The warriors of Seyruun join Lina’s crew in battle against Zanaffar, but it’s Duclis who may hold the key to stopping the demon’s rampage. The fate of Taforashia - and the world - is on the line!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="112356" update="2016-11-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112357" update="2016-11-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
