<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5841" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>22</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Clannad: After Story</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">クラナド- AFTER STORY</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">クラナド アフターストーリー</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">كلاناد ما بعد القصة</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Кланнад: След историята</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Кланад: Продовження Історії</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">کلاناد ادامه داستان</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Clannad2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Clannad 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Clannad AS</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">CLANNAD ~AFTER STORY~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Clannad: After Story</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Clannad After Story</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">클라나드 애프터 스토리</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">แคลนนาด อาฟเตอร์ สตอรี่</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">CLANNAD ~AFTER STORY~</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">خانواده: ادامه داستان</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5101" type="Prequel">Clannad</anime>
<anime id="4402" type="Alternative Setting">Gekijouban Clannad</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4404" approval="218" total="234">Kanon (2006)</anime>
<anime id="2002" approval="165" total="176">Air</anime>
<anime id="8211" approval="7" total="25">Usagi Drop</anime>
<anime id="9822" approval="6" total="12">Little Busters! Refrain</anime>
<anime id="5678" approval="5" total="13">Itazura na Kiss</anime>
<anime id="9132" approval="2" total="8">Little Busters!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="136">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="86487">Like some have said, it`s a good watch. A bit overrated, very slow to start, definitely could have been better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="101987">This is the first anime that touches me to tears it was so amazing so touching so heart warming and taking that i couldn`t hold it inn this anime is one of the best anime i ever saw if its a anime like this it is the best if its overall one of the best i really recommend it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="363530">A great story filled with feeling and closure with the original movie.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="373218">This is the best romance/comedy I have ever seen! After watching the two seasons. I can say this anime made me laugh and cry, it has it`s ups and downs but this is the thing about romance, it will really touch your heart and you`ll realize how important you deal things. I really recommend this series to all people out there and I know you will never forget this anime. 10/10  ^_^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="348582">highly reccommended slice of life with some real sad points in it but worth watching</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="313812">As well as the first season (although personally enjoyed the After Story better)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="273549">Great sequel, very emotional and heartfelt.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="803616">I can`t remember laughing/smiling so much (Clannad) &amp; crying so much (Clannad: After Story) within one anime, would recommend to anyone with any emotions.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="466955">The first one was kinda ok, but didin`t have a serious feel. HOWEVER, this one.......is better than the first one. The first half was just a warmup with some comedy and silly moments, but the second half is more serious, tragic and darker. Kyoto Animation made this anime to make the viewers weep like babies, death + sadness + lonliness + depression + romance = THIS ANIME. I have nothing more to say soooooo-JUSTGOANDWATCHTHISANIMEITSGONNAMAKEYOUCRYSOMUCH!
BTW watch the Kyou chapter as well. It`s really good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="221259">I REALLY RECOMMEND THIS SERIES !!!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="420895">i really really recommend this anime.. the guys before me are very right.. this anime will made you laugh and cry.. but its worth it!

there is no anime like this.. good job on making this..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="202994">Way. Fucking. Awesome.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="81496">Very touching story</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="481404">i cant stop crying when i watch this anime ... nagisa and her child .. it;s too hurt . this is a anime must see ( romance and tragedy )</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="431242">Great plotline, continues the first season beautifully without replicating it.
One of three anime that has made me cry.
Has a deus ex machina ending</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="458655">This is an anime with amazing story with a basic concept. Those that have seen the season prior to this must watch. Anyone that hasn`t must see the original first. I`m more than halfway finished but I am amazed to tears!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="233028">just perfect</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="324464">i some what experience how a life is and i want all to experience what i experienced..&lt;br /&gt;its a beautiful anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="250429">Great coming of age drama with a mysterious magical twist.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="444806">A nice sequel to the first season, as beautiful than it.

If some events upset you after the middle of this season don`t stop watching it!

Enjoy the revelations about the dreams and the 2 seasons.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="194400">super</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="371579">After you finish this anime you begin to see life differently. Don`t take everything for granted. Cherish your friends and family, work hard and be positive in life. Because those things can be easily lost if you stray from your path.

What I can say... Just watch and experience it yourself. Amazing journey awaits you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="302786">Not quite as good as the first season, maybe I set my expectations too high. It`s still one of the better animes though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="292795">If you like Key + KyoAni`s style, this anime is so so so GREAT!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="475674">probably its the best shoujo type anime ull ever find ... atleast that`s my opinion VERY TRAGIC and VERY HEART WARMING...MUST SEE! u wont regret it !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="374759">Perfectly anime ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="526042">I laughed...
I cried...
I experienced something that changed my life...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="240815">at first, i thought it was a great sequel but not as brilliant as the first season. by the end of episode 13, i changed my mind. kyoto animation has produced one of the greatest anime ever. the animation, the music, the dialogue, the plot, etc all work together to produce a really emotional series about life. although there are some filler-like episodes near the beginning, the series is finally getting to the real story. a MUST SEE if you`re looking for a story about life and family.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="266839">Heartwarming Love Stories. Great characters, awesome animation. Truly one of the best. A real tear jerker.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="520037">This anime changed the way I see life.

A must see for everyone!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="495174">Clannad is... life</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="211996">This recommendation is a difficult one to write, mainly because I`m unable put into words why this show is a must see to the highest degree (I refuse to spoil any part of this series, in any small way). But if you value the experience of immersing yourself in an amazing series for the first time, then do not miss this one for the world!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="368156">It`s not about romance. It`s about family.
This show teaches me how important a family is, and packed with great storyline + heartwarming events.

I`ve really learned something from this anime, and that`s what makes Clannad series is one of the best anime I`ve ever seen. (alongside with ARIA series)
2 seasons full of tears. It`s just...beautiful.

Watch it, and get your heart changed to a better one. :D

NB: In my opinion, this show has the best anime scene I`ve ever seen. Eps 18.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="54309">You will never be the same after watching this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="504234">This is the most heart-breaking and tear-yanking, animes I have ever seen.  Its got everything comedy drama romance cuteness, but no ecchi(sorry pervs).  I cried for 5 episodes straight.  I seriously say that you need to watch this anime, after watching the first season of course.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="90098">Best drama//school life// family ever.  If you are into this kind of anime , this is definetly a must see. for me... it`s the king of the kings, and most definetly the best anime i`ve ever seen</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="479327">The best anime I`ve ever watched
A MUST SEE!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="270436">While the first Clannad was maa maa, this season starts like a slow moving 18-wheeler, slowly reaching 100 mph.  Then, packs the punch of said vehicle slamming into a brick wall of emotions.  This is a must see for anyone who liked the first series.  If you didn`t like the first series, give this one a chance.  You`ll be awarded with intricate emotional attachments that will make you watch over and over again.  This is the series that finally makes Clannad shine over-all.  If you like anime like Please Teacher, Itazura na Kiss, and ef - A Tale of Memories, then you`ll definitely love this anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="336403">This god damn series sucker punched me so many times into tears that i`m not even sure how many times i had a tear in my eye. i dont even remember when was the last time i cryed because of a movie or an animation. Probably when i was like 5 or something. Some times i tought that whats so good about this anime and it was because that the anime was so slow paced that you wouldn`t always think so highly of it. But after i have watched all the eppisodes i understand that i was all a build up for one of those freaking great moments that i got tears running down my face. This is truly an unique anime. i highly recommend this to anyone that has a slightest hint of human emotions running through their bodies.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="492184">best anime ever 

Clannad serie i Wan season III 

MUST SEE</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="335602">A real tearjerker. For this second season the comedy has been put aside almost in it`s entirety, so this series could be turned into a drama. It still has all the good points from the first season, but it`s still missing something to get the top score. It leaves those of us who haven`t played the visual novel with too many questions unanswered and it should have ended a couple of episodes earlier. Nevertheless, this series still got some tears out of me at it`s highlights.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="372950">This is probably the most sad and taking story i have every watched as an anime. At first, say Ep1-Ep7, i was convinced it was just a money making sequel... but i have to take back on that thought. The story is no fun at all, it sad to a sick level and i honestly had shed one or another tear. I even shouted at my computer after i came to the point where Tomoya had to endure the most horrible to thing in life, again. But in all this sadness and hardship there still is all this stuff that makes you comfortable again. I am only now starting to watch the 3 special episodes, lets hope they don`t ruin this work.

In case you didn`t watch Clanned and much less didn`t watch this: Shame on you! You are missing the most beatuful work of art i know there is. At least for Drama/Romance anime.

This actually could be the first sequel i am actually going to give 100% as rating.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="550129">One of my all-time favorites. It may have flaws, but overall it`s brilliant.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="543918">Awesome animation, character development, and STORY! A must see, honestly. :) Outstanding. But, there is too much cuteness for such a serious story. If you can handle that, then give it a chance. ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="507844">From what i read, everybody found a special side for theirselves in this tremendeous and stupendous and inspirational story and immense world of its soundtrack. After the first episode, it`ll pull you in and you`ll never be able to give up from then. A milestone in anime world.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="480721">This series could define the term "Legendary".  Never before has an animated series played such a vital impact on the lives of its viewership, and I firmly am hard pressed to think of other series which can do what Clannad ~After Story~ has done. 

Only the most cynical people will view this series with malcontent.  I have been truly blessed to have been able to view something this good.  Clannad ~After Story~ has the potential to join the ranks of the truly elite anime series (Neon Genesis Evangelion, DBZ, Sailor Moon, etc.) as something truly special.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="554983">If you like moving animes, Clannad and Clannad ~ After Story are definitely worth watching.

The first season, Clannad, is really enjoyable because you get to know interesting characters and you start caring for them; the show is light-hearted at first and drama elements are included little by little, at a good pace. The storyline is sometimes a bit obvious, still, it doesn`t prevent it from being moving and interesting, and I was happy to see that the harem feature is not the purpose of the show.

The second season is quite different, because you now care a lot for the main two protagonists. The story which is developed thereafter is way more serious and tragic... there are still many times when you laugh and rejoice, especially thanks to some great characters, but the hardships that the Okazaki couple has to go through are quite moving. This season has also its share of flaws, but it is definitely worth watching. It brings the light-hearted Clannad to a whole new level.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="538195">Epic...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="585958">when you watching this story you can feel yourself in an emotional storm; must see!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="540649">This anime is really a piece of art. It influenced me so much. Totally a must see!  MASTERPIECE.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="401111">This series, along with its prior series (Clannad) is hands down the best anime I have ever seen.  as a matter of fact, I cannot think of a better movie or series, period, live, CG, or anime.  It is SO powerful that I came away from the series fundamentally changed in the way I look at my life and family.  It is amazingly well animated, with absolutely stunning art, direction, sound, characters and character development, story, and voice acting. It is an emotional roller-coaster, and I had a hard time continuing to watch the series after a few episodes, but I made it to the end and will NEVER regret watching this series. I plan to buy the DVDs if I can find them...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="332605">A bit slow and uneventful at the beginning but stick with it till pass mid season, you won`t regret it. Soooo emotionally charged.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="487479">Funny, Heart-warming, Beautiful. First anime to make me shed a tear, seriously this anime is amazing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="463248">When an anime moves me so much that tears start to appear, I`d say it`s a must see. The anime is not a season 2 of Clannad, it`s a follow-up of Clannad, just as Code Geass R2 does.
Conclusion: Watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="324935">Just finished watching this and I have to say this is truly one of the best. I will never look at life as I did before! I have never cried so much at an anime before. I remember I just postponed watching this saying that it`s probably overrated and  2 days ago I decided to give it a go ( yes I finished it all in 2 days ) and I have to say it has been an epic journey. Do yourself a favour and watch this, I guarantee it will get to your heart!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="609308">This anime is a masterpiece. A score of
Infinity would be appropriate here. The music and the story are breathtaking.

I never thought was possible that an anime touched me so. I am glad to have seen him. A wonderful love story. It shows a the Things that are important to you in life. The things for which one lives: Family, friends, his great love and / or his own children. I envy Tomoya
to have found all that so many are looking for (myself included). I am now motivated my dreams come true and to find the great good fortune.
"The world is beautiful," this I have now understood.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="204142">A heart-wrenching story about loss, grief, forgiveness, love, and accepting the world in which one lives. While most of the prequel characters return, the tone and feeling of the entire setting is drastically different, no dating-sim scenario here.

This one will break your heart.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="367634">I will not say 1 off the best becouse this is THE BEST ROMANCE THERE IS loved it when it first came STILL LOVE IT NOW and still crying and im 21 damit A MUST SEE ITS TO LOW of a rating for this ANIME</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="471794">It`s really hard to choose an word to describe this sequel other than "masterpiece"! Saying that i think it`s just perfect in most aspects may sound a little exaggerated (though i may be overlooking some  plot details for example), but i must say that, at least for me, it was really striking, specially beacause of a certain chain of events that occur later in the story which, i must admit, made me brake down into tears for the first time in years (maybe i`m getting old after all XD). Also it has one of the best opening musics ever! Definitely a must see!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="340905">contiuation from 1st season.&lt;br /&gt;again... you will cry laughing from your heart</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="158977">If you laughed, cried, and despaired in the first season, you will do it all over again with this one. Clannad still keeps its spectacular, emotion filled story while not dulling down to its first season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="626235">I think this might be the best animated series I have seen so far. Nothing more to add really.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="545305">It is a beautiful story that makes you feel like you are part of it. It conveys joy, happiness, sadness, grief and all other kinds of emotions so perfectly. 

The animation, music and story are wonderful. It is full of touching moments, moments that might have happened to you, both happy and sad. I for one am happy to have watched such a wonderful anime. There were moments my eyes became full of tears before me realizing it. Words aren`t enough to describe it well, a must see for everyone.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="422234">If all anime formed a planet, clannad would be its SUN.
Clannad is category itself :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="567315">This is the must-see anime for any man like me. A perfect sequel to a perfect visual novel adaptation, aside from a few completely forgivable tricks up the sleeve in the final few scenes, this show dwells completely within the realistic, without denying the magic of everyday life. This show touched on all my hopes and dreams as a hopeful future husband and father, but also all of my fears with the careful precision of a surgeon, tugging at the heartstrings and managing to ring truth in every moment regardless of whether the viewer has experienced the events portrayed in the story or not. This is one show that nobody should miss.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="469382">Obviously a must watch if you have seen the first season. And if you haven`t and are just here to look at reviews or something, I highly recommend getting through the first season to experience this series. It`s one of the few shows that can actually alter your outlook on certain aspects of life. The theme of family is strong in this one and something that is easily relatable to.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="38355">The series of fairly short side stories that makes up the first half of After Story is good in its own right, but starting with about episode 12 or 13, the show becomes one of the most touching and emotional works of art I`ve ever seen. It actually has me worried about how it`s going to turn out. That`s how good it is.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="219832">This is unique . No other anime has touched me so much like Clannad did . It is romantic , sad and funny . But the story is the best in this genre of anime , and i can guarantee you that you will not regret watching this . And have tissues because you are going to cry a lot . But for me this is the best anime in the Genre , or all . I recomend it to anyone who wants to see something unique and beautiful that will surely touch your heart</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="432650">You`ll remember it forever. It`s one of those things that you`ll remember like a friend`s death.

This is fun, though, and poignant. The way it creates, breaks, structures... Nothing better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="21286">This is like an epic work. Very good storyline, but it is a little difficult to understand the ending without the specials.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="47940">See it this way: If you don’t watch this anime, you will never be able to say, you have seen this master-piece of anime-art!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="81562">As many people said, it`s really tear-jerking and emotional in the second half of this season. If the ending is also awesome, this series would become a must-see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="297993">You have to watch it to appreciate this anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="161487">ahh nakimashita, it was really touching with a great storry. this show is a must for all pepole even if the dont watch anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="302110">this season is an excellent continues first`s.&lt;br /&gt;must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="281330">MUST SEE.I liked it more than the first season.This anime grabes you and shows you a very great and beautiful story. Love it :X</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="224530">awesome... simply like that XD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="327739">Very, very touching and heartwarming. Never cried so far in my whole anime experience, but this one managed to make me. (besides KGNE, but that`s overdoing it). Definitely a must watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="352227">I want to be Tomoya, with all his pain and luck. So fantastic, it touches your heart and let you think about yourself. I still get tears in my eyes when i think about Clannad.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="296499">perfect</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="261604">INCREDIBLE~!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="125253">Bahkan istri saya banjir air mata saat menonton ini!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="35101">Already watch CLANNAD in one sitting? Done the 8 hours++ marathon for CLANNAD? Want more? Then continue on with After Story! You will not regret it! It is the best anime of the year!! I said that again, IT IS THE BEST Anime of the year! It beats Bleach and Naruto or whatever anime you like before!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="256742">EPIC!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="114814">This is one of the best anime out there, and I have seen quite a few.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="421948">Best Anime Ever. Outstanding story line. Awesome BGM. Great character building. good at playing people emotion. you`ll laugh at one scene, angry at the second, and cried a lot at the other. Definately a-must-see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="245563">Give it a try, i love it but even if it is not your type of anime, it as more than enough quality for you to watch any way.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="383828">Not watching this will make you regret your entire life. Definetely the best Anime ever created.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="382047">Watch this, a definite must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="422884">The kind of anime that you`ll never forget. I never cried watching movie or anime, cause i`ve considered it stupid and unreasonable. But this one is different. It didn`t really make me cry, but it was only because i was keeping back so hard...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="58620">an absolute masterpiece anime.
a true example of why a combination of Kyoani and Key can lead to something truly magical.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="419926">This anime is by all means a masterpiece. Superb plot and character development. Extraordinary music. Animation is also perfect (although i don`t care about that). So emotional that is hard not to spill any tears but funny at times too. I`ve never cried so much at a series. But still with all this crying , it leaves you with a lighthearted emotion after you finish watching it. By any means you must not leave this series out of your list. MUST WATCH!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="232143">A definite MUST SEE for everyone who likes romance and slice-of-life categories. Avoids most clichés of it`s category and has it`s own twists in plot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It`s prequel highly recommended to enjoy this one to the fullest.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="417365">do not miss it, you will cry, and you`ll feel good for doing it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="465426">If you want cry, you must see CLANNAD After Story. I think this is the most best drama i ever seen. It has drama, comedy, drama, fantasy and drama, and do you know? It`s works!

CLANNAD After Story will show you how is live a "normal" life, but with a touch of fantasy.

You must see. Have fun :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="162375">Watch this anime, you won`t regret it.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/clannad/</url>
<creators>
<name id="736" type="Animation Work">Kyoto Animation</name>
<name id="525" type="Character Design">Ikeda Kazumi</name>
<name id="535" type="Series Composition">Shimo Fumihiko</name>
<name id="1046" type="Original Work">Visual Art`s/Key</name>
<name id="519" type="Direction">Ishihara Tatsuya</name>
<name id="525" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ikeda Kazumi</name>
<name id="1859" type="Music">Orito Shinji</name>
<name id="1860" type="Music">Togoshi Magome</name>
<name id="1855" type="Music">Maeda Jun</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a visual novel by http://anidb.net/cr1046 [Visual Art`s/Key]. After Story is a path that opens in the original visual novel after all the other paths have been cleared.
Life continues on for http://anidb.net/ch1113 [Okazaki Tomoya]. A few months have passed since he confessed his love to http://anidb.net/ch1116 [Furukawa Nagisa]. Now entering the second semester, he continues to meet a variety of different people, expanding his own world in the process. As well, Tomoya and Nagisa`s relationship begins to enter a level of intimacy unlike before. Through his relationship with Nagisa, and his various encounters, Tomoya begins to understand the meaning and importance of family. Unfortunately, as Tomoya and Nagisa begin their own family together, they are faced with many hardships and challenges along the way.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7838">9.28</permanent>
<temporary count="8030">8.82</temporary>
<review count="9">8.47</review>
</ratings>
<picture>83807.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9701</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6351</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4181</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4303</identifier>
<identifier>qyscyl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/clannad/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Clannad_(visual_novel)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>CLANNAD_(ゲーム)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1462</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331618</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10473</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2243</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10678</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>11445</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="215" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-03">
<name>lonely</name>
<description>Loneliness is an unpleasant feeling in which a person feels a strong sense of emptiness and solitude resulting from inadequate levels of social relationships. However, it is a subjective experience. Loneliness has also been described as social pain — a psychological mechanism meant to alert an individual of isolation and motivate her/him to seek social connections.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3129" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-13">
<name>fake relationship</name>
<description>A relationship where characters just play the boyfriend and girlfriend roles.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3132" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-11">
<name>helpful couple</name>
<description>This is a very low key type of romance in which the main two characters spend a great deal of time hanging out together just helping other people solve problems. The couple`s personal interaction tends to be subtle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3975" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-22">
<name>delayed 16-9 broadcast</name>
<description>This anime was created with an aspect ratio of 16:9 (widescreen), but its initial Japanese TV broadcasts were cropped to 4:3 (fullscreen). At some point (usually 2-4 weeks) down the line, it was rebroadcast in 16:9.
Note: This tag does NOT apply to series created in 16:9, but only broadcast in 4:3 and not made available in 16:9 until their DVD/BD release. For those, use "Broadcast cropped to 4-3".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4296" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-09">
<name>illness</name>
<description>It could be life threatening, debilitating or just an annoyance, but one character in this anime has a disease that affects not only them but those around them.
Friends and family may need to help the character perform day to day activities, or nurse them round the clock.
Sometimes the character recovers, sometimes not.
The attitude of the character to their illness can be inspiring or galling to the viewer... some characters rise above their illness, but others use it as an excuse to do whatever they want and take advantage of others.
And then there are the hypochondriacs...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4558" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-12">
<name>long time span</name>
<description>The anime spans a much longer than usual (for that genre) period of time, typically several years (possibly decades or even centuries).
Example: In a school setting this could mean the character development is followed from school through college right into working life and the founding of a family with children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5335" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>dreams and reality</name>
<description>This genre of anime is typically set in both the world as we know it (reality) and a world of dreams, mythology or imagination.
Sometimes this dreamworld is actually real, sometimes it is not. Other times what we think is the real world is the dreamworld, and vice versa. They are not always easy to distinguish from each other, neither by the characters nor the viewer.
Whatever is real, and whatever is reality, both worlds are integral in shaping both the plot of this anime and the development of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5807" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2007-08-08">
<name>cosmic reset</name>
<description>All events that occurred up to a certain point are mysteriously undone, as if the Universe pressed a rewind button. This usually means some characters are being given another chance to unknowingly play out events differently, perhaps to prevent certain consequences from the previous time line`s actions. Occasionally they become doomed to repeat portions of their life over and over again until an individual event or series of events are performed correctly in just the right way, as seemingly to gain the Universe`s approval.</description>
<picurl>36685.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1113" type="main character in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="607">8.61</rating>
<name>Okazaki Tomoya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoya is the male protagonist of Clannad. Due to his habit of always arriving late to school, skipping classes during the day, and staying out all night, he has been labeled as a delinquent, or a young person who defies authority. Ever since his mother, Atsuko, died in a car accident when he was young, Tomoya has been living with his father, Naoyuki, with whom he argues constantly. Tomoya was injured during a fight with his father three years ago; since then, their relationship has been very distant. While walking to school, Tomoya met Nagisa Furukawa, since then, his life changed. Nagisa describes him as someone who is mean and bad-mouthed, but actually kind-hearted.</description>
<picture>139558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1116" type="main character in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="701">7.52</rating>
<name>Furukawa Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nagisa is the main heroine of Clannad. Although she is in her third year in high school, as is Tomoya, Nagisa is actually one year older since she had to repeat her third year after an illness that lasted nine months. On the first day of school, She meets Tomoya on a long hill path in front of the school. She has a strange habit of muttering the names of food that she plans to eat as a way to motivate herself, such as anpan. She wants to re-establish the once-disbanded drama club. She does not have much self-confidence so she often needs help in order to motivate herself through the day.</description>
<picture>144026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1117" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="556">8.46</rating>
<name>Fujibayashi Kyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyou is a bad-mouthed and aggressive girl who is also well known as a good cook. She is the older of the Fujibayashi twins. She was in Tomoya`s class in their second year, and has maintained a steady friendship with Tomoya even though they are put in different classes on their third year. She is currently the class representative of her class. She has a pet baby boar named Botan. She even has her own motorbike (in this case a scooter), which is known only to Tomoya and her sister, as Kyou does not want the news of her possession of it to be known, as she fears suspension from school because she is not allowed to ride a motorbike to school. Her favourite weapon is various types of dictionaries, which are thrown at anyone she gets furious with, typically Youhei. In the anime, Kyou uses various books as weapons more often, and while Tomoya almost always avoids them, Youhei gets hit almost every single time.</description>
<picture>60742.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1118" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-15">
<rating votes="378">7.98</rating>
<name>Ichinose Kotomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kotomi is another schoolmate of Tomoya`s in the same year, but, like Kyou, is in a separate class from Tomoya. The "Koto" in Kotomi is derived from the Japanese musical stringed instrument of the same name. She is in the top ten for every subject throughout the whole country in standardized exam results — she always goes to library to read extra materials, especially books in foreign languages. Kotomi is a very quiet girl and it is quite difficult to communicate with her. In her spare time, she plays the violin, although she is very poor at it to the point of causing pain to those who hear her play.</description>
<picture>15476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1119" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="583">8.46</rating>
<name>Sakagami Tomoyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoyo transferred to Tomoya`s school as a second year student during spring. Although Tomoya is older than her, Tomoyo does not show him his due respect as a senior student.</description>
<picture>139567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1120" type="appears in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="277">6.02</rating>
<name>Ibuki Fuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A first year student at Tomoya`s school. She is always alone, making wood carvings of starfish with a small knife to give to others as presents. This hobby completely drains her concentration and awareness of her surroundings.</description>
<picture>139559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1121" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="181">5.12</rating>
<name>Fujibayashi Ryou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryou is Tomoya`s classmate and class representative. She is the younger of the Fujibayashi twins. Unlike her older sister, she is timid and doesn`t cook well. Ryou is very keen about fortune telling, but her predictions, while incredibly specific, always manage to be either somewhat skewed or extremely wrong.</description>
<picture>15474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1122" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-15">
<rating votes="144">7.33</rating>
<name>Sagara Misae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misae Sagara is the resident manager at Youhei`s dorm. She was a student council president when she was in high school. Misae is friendly with the dorm students but strict when it comes to the dorm rules. She is also well-liked by the rugby members. Depending on decisions, Tomoya can change her to a violent dorm lady through his lecture, which is her original personality, who uses brute force to convince the dorm students to do their cleaning duty.</description>
<picture>15481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1123" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="149">6.22</rating>
<name>Sunohara Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Youhei`s younger sister who loves Youhei as a brother and lives in the countryside. Mei is a smart girl and likes to see new things. She is a fan of Yoshino Yuusuke, an older male graduate from Tomoya`s school, who is a member of a band. Worried about her brother`s situation, she calls Youhei, but instead of her brother, Tomoya disguised as Youhei tells her to come.</description>
<picture>139563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1124" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="257">8.15</rating>
<name>Furukawa Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanae is Nagisa`s mother. Normally she`s very childish and a cry-baby, but when needed she can be very strong-willed and dependable. She runs the Furukawa Bakery with her husband Akio. She often tries out strange concepts to make breads that are anything but edible and never get sold. Outside of the bakery, she tutors children. She`s quite proud of the way people often mistaken her as Nagisa`s older sister because of her youthful appearance. When Akio accidentally makes Sanae cry because of his accidental bad remarks on her bread, he will have to chase after her with her bread stuffed into his mouth, to calm her down, or else she will run around the town crying.</description>
<picture>139568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1125" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="109">4.24</rating>
<name>Ibuki Kouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuuko`s older sister. She used to be an art teacher at Tomoya`s school, and she treats everyone kindly. Kouko is one of the familiar faces in the Furukawa Bakery, and Nagisa admires her very much. Currently she is engaged with Yoshino Yuusuke, and is the major reason why Fuuko still exists in the school, despite still sleeping in the hospital.</description>
<picture>15478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1127" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="296">7.18</rating>
<name>Sunohara Youhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoya`s friend and also a delinquent. He entered the school on an athletic recommendation in football, but was kicked out of the football club after being involved in a fight. After this incident, he became lazy, becoming the only student with a higher absence rate than Tomoya. He and Tomoya are known as the "Dirty Pair" in school. He has a sister named Mei. Youhei is basically a comic relief character, and his most notable punishment he receives includes him getting bullied and attacked by Tomoya and Kyou, beaten to a pulp by Tomoyo for trying to assault her, and getting attacked by the Rugby Team Members for various unfortunate events involving them.</description>
<picture>139566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1128" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="88">6.38</rating>
<name>Miyazawa Yukine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukine is a second year student who hangs around in the library`s reference room during lunchtime. Tomoya first met her in the library`s reference room while trying to find a place to sleep. He is immediately greeted by her hospitality, and returns the next day with Youhei due to Youhei`s insistent. Ever since, Tomoya and Youhei start to enter the library reference room routinely. She later avails Tomoya and Youhei an instruction book for magical spells for them to try. Most of them are in the favor of Tomoya, involving the girls they met.
She has friends outside of her school, which turns out to be delinquents from other schools. She made friends with the delinquents through her brother, Kazuto, who is also a delinquent, after his death trying to save a friend from an accident. She sees Tomoya as her older brother, who has a similar personality as her dead brother. Tomoya learns briefly about the light orbs through Yukine, which are called the symbol of happiness. The light orbs are actually the people`s feelings inside the city Tomoya is staying.
According to the script writers, Yukine was originally intended to be one of the heroines of Clannad, but as her story did not reach their expectations, she was made into a secondary character. However, she was still depicted on the regular edition cover of the PC release, and on the PlayStation 2 release which used the same art as the regular PC release.</description>
<picture>139564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1129" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="436">9.00</rating>
<name>Furukawa Akio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nagisa`s father. Although he often talks and plays rough, he is kind and sympathetic. His childish side makes it easy for people to befriend him. He runs the Furukawa Bakery with his wife Sanae. In his spare time, Akio plays baseball with children in the small park next to the bakery, and indulges in the Gundam fandom. He is often the victim of Sanae`s bread, especially when Sanae runs around the town crying due to his accidental bad remark about her bread, and always have to eat her bread in front of her to calm Sanae down.</description>
<picture>139565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1134" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="111">7.83</rating>
<name>Yoshino Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An electrician who once attended Tomoya`s high school and lived as a rock musician. He is admired by Mei for his infrequent rock play. Tomoya first met Yuusuke during a street light accident involving a person`s car, but was actually a cat that cause the dent on the car. Tomoya assists Yuusuke in his work, and after working Tomoya is tired, realizes the pain of working in society. He is engaged to Kouko, and is also one of the reason why Fuuko exists in the school.</description>
<picture>15492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5513" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-07">
<rating votes="201">8.38</rating>
<name>Okazaki Ushio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13572" type="appears in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="45">5.27</rating>
<name>Botan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Botan is Kyou`s pet baby boar, and is a comic relief character. Botan will sometimes go to Kyou`s school just to see her. Due to its small size and the fact that it is a baby boar, it is sometimes captured by several characters who talk of eating it. Botan hates Ryou because it mistook Ryou for trying to eat it when she took it for a warm bath. In the After Story, Botan has become an adult boar, but still acts the same. Botan has seven different skills, told him by Kyou, one of them being able to take the appearance of a stuffed animal by being extremely still. Another skill is called "Rugby Ball" in which Botan shrinks his legs until he resembles a ball, allowing Kyou to use him as a projectile. These skills are considered to be animal cruelty by Tomoya. Two other skills are mentioned in the visual novel, but never shown, called "massager" and "pillow".</description>
<picture>39770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7041" picture="78916.jpg">Kawana Machiko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13780" type="appears in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="3">2.93</rating>
<name>Sasaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13781" type="appears in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="3">3.11</rating>
<name>Tajima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3999" picture="51970.jpg">Yamamoto Keiichiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13782" type="appears in" update="2010-02-08">
<rating votes="29">3.42</rating>
<name>Sugisaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sugisaka is a member of the chorus club. She tries to force Nagisa to give up on establishing theatre club by threatening her, but later confronts Nagisa directly, telling Rie`s past, hoping she will not bother Rie`s dream. Youhei does not trust Sugisaka due to her usage of threat letter, and her attempt on messing up Nagisa`s shoe cabinet. In the After Story anime, Sugisaka works as a waitress in the same family restaurant as Nagisa.</description>
<picture>40851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1877" picture="23186.jpg">Bandou Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13783" type="appears in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="2">3.91</rating>
<name>Sudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5650" picture="30095.jpg">Murozono Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13784" type="appears in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="4">5.00</rating>
<name>Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11241" picture="40575.jpg">Sakamoto Azuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13785" type="appears in" update="2016-02-13">
<rating votes="6">6.18</rating>
<name>Yuu no Ane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13786" type="appears in" update="2009-12-25">
<rating votes="5">4.37</rating>
<name>Miyazawa Kazuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazuto is Yukine`s dead brother. He was a delinquent, but was kind to his sister. He died in an accident escorting his friends home. Yukine and her delinquent friends refer that Tomoya`s personality is the same as her brother. His death is the reason how Yukine gets close with the delinquents, who were Kazuto`s friends.</description>
<picture>40580.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13787" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="27">6.26</rating>
<name>Boku no Koe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He has no name, but narrates the situation in the illusionary world seen through Tomoya`s dream while referring to himself only as "Me" (boku). He had his body created by the girl out of garbage so that he can be with her. The body is about half the girl`s height. He can`t talk as he is created without a mouth, so relies on body language to communicate with the girl. This is Tomoya himself after his death. Ushio in the edge of death in the illusion told him to collect light orbs to create a miracle to save Nagisa, Ushio and himself from tragedy.</description>
<picture>40583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13788" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="47">8.12</rating>
<name>Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only human in the illusionary world, a world Tomoya dreams of. She creates a body out of garbage for an unnamed entity only referred to as "Me," so that she will not be alone in the illusionary world. This is Ushio after her death, who had lost her memories. In her edge of death after failing to get away from the illusionary world, Ushio, who had regained her memories, called the garbage doll (Tomoya) to collect the light orbs in order to save themselves for their doomed tragedy. In Clannad`s epilogue, she is shown sleeping under a tree where Akio begged for Nagisa`s life.</description>
<picture>40849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13789" type="appears in" update="2009-12-25">
<rating votes="13">5.59</rating>
<name>A-Kumi Tannin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11243" picture="40585.jpg">Sagawa Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14889" type="appears in" update="2010-02-08">
<rating votes="45">4.84</rating>
<name>Okazaki Naoyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naoyuki is Tomoya`s father. Tomoya`s mother, Atsuko, died when Tomoya was young, thus leaving only himself to raise Tomoya. After the accident, Naoyuki turned to alcohol and smoking, and held frequent fights with his son. One day while arguing with his son on trivial things, he slammed Tomoya against the wall, dislocating Tomoya`s right shoulder. Immediately after that, Tomoya refused to come out of his room, and by the time he finally went to the hospital, it was declared to be untreatable. Ever since then, his father has treated Tomoya more kindly, but like a stranger rather than family. This only hurt Tomoya even more, so he becomes a delinquent, as he is unable to participate in basketball activities any longer, and he avoided returning to his home early enough to be confronted with his father. Tomoya has the intention of running away from his home, as revealed from Kotomi`s path.
As revealed from Shino`s story about Naoyuki, even though his wife died and he had become depressed, Naoyuki sacrificed everything in his life just for Tomoya`s sake, hoping Tomoya to grow up to be a proper man unlike him. After Tomoya comes to terms with his father, Naoyuki decides to return to his hometown to stay with his mother, claiming his role as a father has finally come to an end.
In the movie, Naoyuki works a graveyard shift instead of staying home and becoming a drunk. He also cares about his relationship with Tomoya and even tries to ease his son`s depression in order prevent his son from becoming like him.</description>
<picture>42717.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14890" type="appears in" update="2010-02-08">
<rating votes="36">5.60</rating>
<name>Nishina Rie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rie is a member of the chorus club. She used to be a talented violin player, entered a lot of concerts, but had to quit her violin career after an accident. She almost gave up her life when Koumura confronts her and teaches her chorus. Thus, Rie regained her meaning of her life, and wants to create the chorus club. In Kotomi`s path, she lends Kotomi a violin. In After Story, Rie works as a waitress in the same family restaurant as Nagisa.</description>
<picture>42718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14892" type="appears in" update="2010-02-08">
<rating votes="36">4.81</rating>
<name>Koumura Toshio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Koumura Toshio is a language teacher at Tomoya`s school and Tomoya`s home room teacher during his first year. His age conceals his once vigorous past marked by his enthusiasm in teaching. He taught Ibuki Kouko many years ago.
Five years ago, he was a strict teacher in an engineering school being well known for delinquents. He changed a lot of delinquents in the engineering school for the better, but at Tomoya`s school, his skill is not needed due to the prestigious image of the school. He finds Tomoya and Youhei to be odd ones and decides to change them for the better; he is the one who arranged Tomoya and Youhei to meet.
He retires one year later, prior to the end of the school segment of the story. In After Story, he returns and organizes the fake graduating ceremony intended for Nagisa, arranged by Tomoya.</description>
<picture>42720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14893" type="appears in" update="2010-02-08">
<rating votes="11">4.54</rating>
<name>Harada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harada is a member of the chorus club.</description>
<picture>42722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="412" picture="25833.jpg">Yasui Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14911" type="appears in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="10">7.11</rating>
<name>Shima Katsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsuki is a boy Misae met several years ago. She encourages Shima to recover when he is still in his wheelchair. His true identity is a cat kept by the real Shima, who asked the cat to grant Misae a wish before dying.</description>
<picture>42773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14912" type="appears in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="6">5.95</rating>
<name>Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misae`s high school friend.</description>
<picture>42774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="624" picture="25821.jpg">Kawashou Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14913" type="appears in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="6">5.95</rating>
<name>Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misae`s high school friend.</description>
<picture>42775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2291" picture="23193.jpg">Kano Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14914" type="appears in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="5">4.17</rating>
<name>Igarashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Igarashi is Misae`s past love interest, who already had a girlfriend. After finding out about Misae`s crush, he asks Shima to tell Misae about his relationship with another girl without hurting her. It is Igarashi`s rejection of Misae`s love that Shima and Misae`s feeling for each other develop.</description>
<picture>42776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3846" picture="25814.jpg">Kaneko Hidehiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14915" type="appears in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="4">3.26</rating>
<name>Isogai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isogai is an old lady who lives next door to the Furukawa bakery. She often sees Akio and Sanae running out of the store, and remarks on how the neighborhood finds it entertaining because of the two.</description>
<picture>42778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4832" picture="28136.jpg">Oda Fumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14916" type="appears in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="4">3.00</rating>
<name>Kinoshita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man who used to work in the same office as Tomoyo`s father.</description>
<picture>42779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5021" picture="188516.jpg">Taki Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14917" type="appears in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="5">5.97</rating>
<name>Yagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend of Sanae who is a midwife. She asks Yagi to deliver Nagisa`s child.</description>
<picture>42780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14918" type="appears in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="8">6.76</rating>
<name>Okazaki Shino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoyo`s grandmother on his father`s side.</description>
<picture>42781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1801" picture="146194.jpg">Asou Miyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14919" type="appears in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="4">4.70</rating>
<name>Kimura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend of Nagisa`s from before she was held back a year.</description>
<picture>42782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32055" type="appears in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Igarashi no Kanojo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="412" picture="25833.jpg">Yasui Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40473" type="appears in" update="2012-01-12">
<rating votes="4">5.33</rating>
<name>Shinshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Colleague of Ichinose`s.</description>
<picture>79858.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40543" type="appears in" update="2012-01-13">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Seitokai Yakuin (Ni-Nen)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Student council officer, second year.</description>
<picture>79906.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40581" type="appears in" update="2012-01-14">
<rating votes="7">8.14</rating>
<name>Nanashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misae`s cat with no name.</description>
<picture>79984.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40697" type="appears in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="6">2.88</rating>
<name>Botan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grown-up Botan.</description>
<picture>80166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7041" picture="78916.jpg">Kawana Machiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55246" type="appears in" update="2013-04-21">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Shima no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The real Shima`s mother.</description>
<picture>135638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4632" picture="135636.jpg">Mizogami Makiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79757" type="appears in" update="2016-02-04">
<rating votes="4">5.33</rating>
<name>Baske-bu Captain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Basketball club captain.</description>
<picture>182199.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="80135" type="appears in" update="2016-02-13">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Younger sister.</description>
<picture>182809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12656" picture="126428.jpg">Shitara Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80136" type="appears in" update="2016-02-13">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Older brother.</description>
<picture>182810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11153" picture="188722.jpg">Nishigaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80137" type="appears in" update="2016-02-13">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Soccer-bu Buchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Soccer club captain.</description>
<picture>182816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3100" picture="186161.jpg">Tsuchiya Toshihide</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80138" type="appears in" update="2016-02-13">
<rating votes="5">9.07</rating>
<name>Sagara Misae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80145" type="appears in" update="2016-02-13">
<rating votes="2">5.77</rating>
<name>Shima Katsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182824.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80203" type="appears in" update="2016-02-14">
<rating votes="1">9.65</rating>
<name>Hikarizaka Denki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Hikarizaka Denki is the electric company where http://anidb.net/ch1134 [Yoshino Yusuke] and later http://anidb.net/ch1113 [Okazaki Tomoya] work.</description>
<picture>182888.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="80204" type="appears in" update="2016-02-14">
<rating votes="2">6.49</rating>
<name>Shachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Company manager.</description>
<picture>182889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4425" picture="26689.jpg">Sugino Hiroomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80233" type="appears in" update="2016-02-14">
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<name>Tenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80234" type="appears in" update="2016-02-14">
<name>Ernesto Host</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Ernesto Host is a family restaurant where http://anidb.net/ch14890 [Nishina Rie], http://anidb.net/ch13782 [Sugisaka], and http://anidb.net/ch1116 [Nagisa] work.</description>
<picture>182912.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="80363" type="appears in" update="2016-02-16">
<rating votes="3">6.61</rating>
<name>Okazaki Ushio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80379" type="appears in" update="2016-02-17">
<rating votes="2">5.33</rating>
<name>Enchou-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kindergarten principal.</description>
<picture>183091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5026" picture="151676.jpg">Sawada Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="89043" update="2008-03-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2008-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93194" update="2011-05-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="38">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の終わりのサヨナラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Farewell to the End of Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Прощание с летом</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Owari no Sayonara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93195" update="2008-10-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="30">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつわりの愛をさがして</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Search of False Love</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">В поисках вымышленной любви</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuwari no Ai o Sagashite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93260" update="2008-10-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="32">8.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれちがう心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hearts Out of Synch</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Сердца в смятении</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigau Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93261" update="2008-11-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="31">8.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの日と同じ笑顔で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With the Same Smile as That Day</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">С той же улыбкой</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Hi to Onaji Egao de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93508" update="2008-11-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="33">8.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ずっとあなたのそばに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Forever by Your Side</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Навеки вместе</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zutto Anata no Soba ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93509" update="2008-11-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="29">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君のいた季節</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Season You Were There</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Дни вместе с тобой</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Ita Kisetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="94193" update="2012-12-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="24">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女の居場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where She Belongs</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Там, где она</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo no Ibasho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="94194" update="2012-12-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇気ある戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Courageous Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Благородная битва</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuki Aru Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="94195" update="2012-12-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="26">8.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">坂道の途中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Along the Path</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Поднимаясь на холм</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakamichi no Tochuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95082" update="2012-12-19">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">始まりの季節</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Season of Beginnings</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Сезон начинаний</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari no Kisetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95553" update="2012-12-19">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束の創立者祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Founder`s Day Festival Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Обещанный фестиваль</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku no Souritsushasai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95637" update="2012-12-19">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="26">9.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突然の出来事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Sudden Happening</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Внезапное происшествие</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsuzen no Dekigoto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95638" update="2008-12-28">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="26">8.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒業</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduation</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Прощай, школа</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sotsugyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95901" update="2008-12-28">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="26">8.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい家族</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Family</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Новая семья</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Kazoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95902" update="2008-12-28">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の名残に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Remains of Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">На память о лете</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Nagori ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95903" update="2008-12-28">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="40">9.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白い闇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Белая тьма</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Yami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96257" update="2009-01-27">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Time</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Летнее время</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsujikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96882" update="2009-02-07">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="64">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大地の果て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ends of the Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Край мира</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daichi no Hate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96898" update="2009-02-08">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="30">9.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Road Home</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Дорога домой</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ieji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96899" update="2009-02-08">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汐風の戯れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mischievous Sea Breeze</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Шалости морского бриза</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiokaze no Tawamure</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96900" update="2009-03-29">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="28">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界の終わり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Конец света</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai no Owari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97076" update="2009-02-27">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="43">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな手のひら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Small Hand</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ладошка</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Tenohira</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97204" update="2015-11-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="26">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一年前の出来事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Events from a Year Ago</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Что случилось годом ранее</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichinen Mae no Dekigoto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97217" recap="true" update="2015-11-01">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">総集編 緑の樹の下で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Under the Green Tree</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Под сенью зеленого леса</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushuuhen: Midori no Ki no Shita de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99620" update="2015-11-01">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="44">9.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もうひとつの世界, 杏編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another World: Kyou Arc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Hitotsu no Sekai, Kyou Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105232" update="2011-05-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105233" update="2017-01-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105234" update="2017-01-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105235" update="2017-02-14">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105236" update="2017-01-26">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129640" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">CM1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177900" update="2017-10-22">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S3 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195361" update="2018-01-22">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode S3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195362" update="2018-01-22">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode S2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
