<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5848" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-26</startdate>
<enddate>2010-02-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Uchuu Kaizoku Sara</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Space Pirates Sala</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Space Pirate Sara</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">우주해적 사라</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">宇宙海賊サラ</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.pixy-soft.com/product/product09_01.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="955" type="Work">Anime Antenna Group</name>
<name id="1318" type="Original Work">Lilith</name>
<name id="16390" type="Character Design">Sadayama Yanaha</name>
<name id="16390" type="Direction">Sadayama Yanaha</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the game by http://anidb.net/cr1318 [Lilith].
In a distant galaxy, it`s said that the one who holds the Sword of Bernstein is the destined for the Imperial Throne. And for that reason, the mysterious Gielen Twins lay waste to the Galactic Empire holding the Sword, finally obtaining it. The oldest princess of said Empire,http://anidb.net/ch25458 [Sara Bernstein], however, witnesses everything and swears not only to avenge her nation but also to recover the Sword. She is rescued from the destruction of her homeworld by an imperial knight, http://anidb.net/ch25455 [Hans Buro].
A decade later, Sara and Hans have formed a space privateer crew, http://anidb.net/ch104960 [Scorpion Heidan]. As it`s captain, Sara has taken the alias of "Sara Scorpion" and has established herself as a renown swordswoman. In exchange for information about the Sword of Bernstein, Sara delivers knight http://anidb.net/ch25457 [Sylia] in chains to the http://anidb.net/ch25454 [Duke of Blankenheim]. She is told about the location of the Sword, but the Duke attempts to persuade Sara to abandon her raison d`être and live in luxury as his mistress. The strong-willed captain rejects the offer and proceeds to antagonize the Duke in her way out.
Weeks later, while following the Duke`s information, Sara`s band walks into a trap laid by the Gielen Twins. Finding herself in captivity next to Sylia, the Twins reveal their plans for Sara, for they have discovered that the Sword of Bernstein can only be wielded by someone of the blood of Bernstein. The Twins also disclose that the vindictive Duke of Blankenheim is working with them and is eager to torment both her and Sylia.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="395">5.33</permanent>
<temporary count="403">6.51</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>236991.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9957</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4360</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10280</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4321</identifier>
<identifier>auhxrl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pixy-soft.com/product/product09_01.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>宇宙海賊サラ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4408</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="301" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-10">
<name>lactation</name>
<description>Capable of secreting breast milk, sometimes referred to as Mother`s milk.</description>
<picurl>176139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1700" parentid="2872" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>pirate</name>
<description>Pirates are people who attack ships on the high seas to rob others of their treasure. Well, at least usually. Other people calling themselves pirates are not unheard of, usually focusing on the freedom and romance involved in the piracy-related tropes and cliches. They may or may not be after the One Piece or a spaceship full of diamonds, too, if that`s what they see as treasure. Real-life pirates were extremely common a few centuries ago, and countries even sponsored their own pirates, called "privateers", to attack ships with flags of other countries. Nowadays, however, very few actual pirates still exist, and they rely more on terrorism and guerrilla warfare than anything else, demanding ransom in exchange for hostages instead of openly attacking the enemies with their swords. Another, more modern meaning for the word refers to people who illegally download copyrighted works they are not entitled to have a copy of. Be whichever it may, there are pirates around here. Arr, avast! Thar be pirates in these dark waters, matey!</description>
<picurl>126791.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2429" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>futanari</name>
<description>Futanari (a compound word meaning "two form" in Japanese) depicts hermaphrodites, intersex or other individuals with female body-types and sexual organs resembling penises, whether or not those organs are in fact enlarged clitorises, or they possess both male and female reproductive organs.</description>
<picurl>165411.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2702" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-16">
<name>mammary intercourse</name>
<description>Mammary intercourse is a sex act, performed as foreplay or as non-penetrative sex, that involves the stimulation of the male penis by the female breasts. Commonly, this sex act involves the man placing his penis in the woman`s cleavage and thrusting between her breasts, while the breasts are squeezed around the penis for additional stimulation, and fellatio may also be performed in combination. Mammary intercourse is also commonly known as titty-fucking or titfuck in the United States, as well as tit wank or French fuck in the United Kingdom. The Japanese term, paizuri (from oppai, breasts, and the verb suru, used in this context to describe the sexual act), is commonly used in the anime fandom. A variant term is "naizuri" (a pun on nai, the negative of the verb aru, indicating existence/presence), which describes an attempt to do a paizuri, but with insufficient cleavage.</description>
<picurl>174692.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2705" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>creampie</name>
<description>The act of a man ejaculating inside a girl`s vagina, leaving the semen oozing out of her.</description>
<picurl>160720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2707" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-20">
<name>internal shots</name>
<description>Internal shots are pictures that display the interior of the body of a living being, either through the skin, kind of as an "x-ray" of sorts, or from the inside, as if the camera was also inside. This is generally used during sex scenes to display the inside of any area being penetrated. Those shots may happen either by making an area of the body transparent or by displaying the same area again, but from the inside; the latter method is shown in the picture.</description>
<picurl>213307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2719" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-19">
<name>gang bang</name>
<description>A situation in which one person has sexual intercourse and performs other sex acts with a number of people, either in turn or at the same time.</description>
<picurl>181529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2720" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-04">
<name>bestiality</name>
<description>Is the practice of sex between humans and animals, or a preference or fixation on such practice.</description>
<picurl>161795.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2724" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>double penetration</name>
<description>Double penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by two penises or strap-ons.</description>
<picurl>172771.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2727" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>stomach stretch</name>
<description>Visible abdominal distortion from objects or anatomy pressing out from within the vaginal or anal cavity. Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2935 [stomach bulge] or http://anidb.net/t775 [pregnancy].</description>
<picurl>178246.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2742" parentid="2429" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>futa x futa</name>
<description>Futanari girls having fun with each other.</description>
<picurl>165414.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2743" parentid="2429" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>futa x male</name>
<description>A futa girl having sex with a guy.</description>
<picurl>165412.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2744" parentid="2429" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>futa x female</name>
<description>A futa girl having sex with a girl</description>
<picurl>165413.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2890" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>foot fetish</name>
<description>Anime contains scenes which revolve around foot-fetishism.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2905" parentid="2729" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-14">
<name>erotic torture</name>
<description>Erotic torture involves deliberately using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure. Examples include, among others, hot wax on skin, nipple clamps, electricity, extreme verbal and derogatory abuse, forced public exhibition, etc.
This is distinct from the common, non-erotic http://anidb.net/t6730 [torture], which is generally for the purpose of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or to apply coercion to compel action from the victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2911" parentid="2890" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>footjob</name>
<description>A foot is used to invoke sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2935" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-19">
<name>stomach bulge</name>
<description>Visible stomach distortion caused by large quantities of fluid or air having been inserted into the vaginal or anal cavity. Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2727 [stomach stretch] or http://anidb.net/t775 [pregnancy].</description>
<picurl>236454.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3309" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-12">
<name>space pirates</name>
<description>Depending how you view the future, lawlessness will always be present in society. There`s always going to be a shadier, nastier way of doing business, and that will almost certainly follow humanity to the stars. Thus, sci-fi authors will include Expies of modern and historic (un)organized crime—be they space mafia, gangs, or—in our case—pirates.
It`s not as anachronistic as it might seem. After all, pirates themselves have made a Real Life comeback in Somalia, and it`s a lucrative enough "business" that it`s taken a multinational military response to fight back. Surely an established society in outer space with significant trade and commerce would suffer similar problems!
... Well, maybe. The major problem with space pirates preying on space commerce is that space is vast. The challenge of catching commercial shipping in open space is orders of magnitudes more difficult than catching them on the open seas. Sometimes, this is cleverly worked around and justified. Most of the time, however, it isn`t.
There are two kinds of Space Pirates in science fiction. The normal version are violent criminals with a spaceship, who attack other spaceships, just like present-day pirates. Once you have shipping between different solar systems/planets, pirates preying on said shipping are bound to show. Simple as that. Done this way, piracy actually makes sense, provided there`s an enabling factor. That could be anything from the technology of the setting creating trade lanes (via a Portal Network, predictable Faster Than Light Travel routes thanks to Negative Space Wedgies, or timed space flights between planets to reduce time spent between planets, as in Real Life), to using a variant of the method employed by modern pirates (say, smaller ships striking at commercial shipping in the orbit of a planet).
The other version does a Recycled In SPACE on every eighteenth century pirate cliche ever. Reasons for including this version will typically be along the lines of "Because Space Is An Ocean, it has to have Pirates" rather than making any meaningful attempt at justifying their existence. They have Cornish accents, beards, say "Arr!" a lot, have parrots (probably robot) and false limbs (probably cybernetic) and wear tricorn hats and eyepatches (or have cybernetic eyes). They may even have ships shaped like boats.
One of the best known space pirates is http://anidb.net/ch2087 [Captain Harlock] from the same named popular http://anidb.net/a725 [TV anime series].
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>41919.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4049" parentid="2721" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>outdoor sex</name>
<description>Popular place for sex in visual novels and manga.</description>
<picurl>175405.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4492" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>gang rape</name>
<description>Gang rape occurs when a group of people (at least 2) participate in the rape of a single victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7247" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-22">
<name>intercrural sex</name>
<description>Intercrural sex (from inter- and Latin crura, "legs"), also known as femoral/interfemoral sex/intercourse, is a type of non-penetrative sex, in which a male places the penis between the receiving partner`s thighs and thrusts to create friction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7251" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-10">
<name>cockring</name>
<description>A cock ring is a ring worn around the penis, usually at the base. The primary purpose of wearing a cock ring is to restrict the flow of blood from the erect penis in order to produce a stronger erection or to maintain an erection for a longer period of time. Genital adornment is another purpose, as is repositioning the genitals to provide an enhanced appearance. 
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7399" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-11">
<name>orgasm denial</name>
<description>Orgasm denial, is a sexual practice or sex play in which a person is kept in a heightened state of sexual arousal for an extended length of time without orgasm, and is commonly practiced in association with BDSM and sexual bondage.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7402" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>corrupt nobility</name>
<description>The nobility is characterized by decadence, sadism, and contempt towards the baseborn.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="19074" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-21">
<rating votes="11">5.72</rating>
<name>Karin von Gielen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19119" picture="130579.jpg">Gogyou Nazuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25454" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-30">
<rating votes="3">1.97</rating>
<name>Joachim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39225" picture="39517.jpg">Miyawaki Masamichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25455" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-30">
<rating votes="3">3.47</rating>
<name>Hans Buro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30198">Chasuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25456" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-30">
<rating votes="10">5.56</rating>
<name>Cecil von Gielen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11261" picture="126428.jpg">Anzu Hana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25457" type="main character in" update="2010-11-30">
<rating votes="10">8.28</rating>
<name>Sylia von Bernstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60094.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25458" type="main character in" update="2010-11-30">
<rating votes="14">8.72</rating>
<name>Sara Bernstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20431" picture="25797.jpg">Hirokawa Kotone</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63994" type="appears in" update="2019-08-12">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Tokage Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5144">Shimoda Sukebee</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104960" type="appears in" update="2019-08-10">
<name>Skorpion Heidan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Skorpion Heidan is a mercenary company that also practices piracy.</description>
<picture>237142.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104973" type="appears in" update="2019-08-11">
<name>Elfenbein</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>237179.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="90359" update="2019-08-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギーレンの双子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Twins of Gielen</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Bliźnięta Gielen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giiren no Futago</title>
<summary>An exiled princess turned space pirate, Sara "Scorpion" Bernstein hunts for the lost heirloom in order to establish herself as the galactic empress and root out the corrupt nobility.
Sara`s voyage, however, lands her in the chains of the people who stole the heirloom and murdered her family, the mysterious Twins of Gielen.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93795" update="2009-07-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虜囚の被虐騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Abusing the Captive Knight</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Maltretowani rycerze</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryoshuu no Higyaku Kishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104668" update="2009-07-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2009-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂宴のふたなり騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Futanari Knight Feast</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Orgia obojnaków</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouen no Futanari Kishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113318" update="2010-09-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆転の海賊騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revenge of the Pirate Knight</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Zemsta piratki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakuten no Kaizoku Kishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126547" update="2011-01-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus Video</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Dodatek</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
