<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5873" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2008-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Rosario to Vampire Capu2</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Крестик + Вампир Чмок 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Rosario + Vampire capu 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Rosario + Vampire Capu2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">rtv capu2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">r+v2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">rtv2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ロザリオとバンパイア Capu2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Rosario + Vampire: Capu 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5273" type="Prequel">Rosario to Vampire</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="9">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="770700">If you liked the first season, then the second season here is a treat for you. Its still got the fun comedy aspect it had before. But the whole focus on fanservice gets old fast. Besides how lame they made the main male Tskune(He was kinda better in the 1st season) he`s okay at best here.
though if it followed the manga it could have been so much more than this.
Personally, I find the harem/fanservice gets old relatively quick. The comedy is good with some pretty good funny moments. But if it stayed true to the manga I think this could have been a bigger hit.
If you aren`t a fan of the 1st season then this probably isn`t for you. 

Overall
Fanservice af with but enjoyable just for some of the characters and the comedy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="248668">if you have the patience to see all the episodes this makes a great anime, especially the last 4 episodes :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="507564">Consists of unrelated fillers except the last few episodes where there`s a continuous and decent plot comparable to S1. Mostly fanservice (skiing, field trips, spas...).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="623957">Like the first season, everything goes with panty. A few character development, with no changes to the main story. Also a new character emerge to the series, even that doesn`t give any minor changes to this second season. All in all, if you`re a HUGE harem fan, this anime is for you, along with panty side dish.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="9391">Great, fun, cheerful anime :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="170749">Almost entirely filler when compared to the manga.
But on its own terms I liked Capu2 far more than the first season.
Considering how much the first season deviated anyway, approaching from that kind of mindset is pointless.
So pop open a cold one, roll one up, and kick back because this anime is a good solid ecchi with plenty of slapstick moments.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.rosa-vam.com/top.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="1519" type="Series Composition">Yamaguchi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
<name id="2019" type="Music">Hamaguchi Shirou</name>
<name id="8114" type="Direction">Inagaki Takayuki</name>
<name id="6028" type="Character Design">Fujita Mariko</name>
<name id="10053" type="Original Work">Ikeda Akihisa</name>
<name id="9769" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kiyomaru Satoru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr10053 [Ikeda Akihisa], serialised in Monthly Shounen Jump.
A new semester begins for http://anidb.net/ch7250 [Aono Tsukune] at Youkai Academy — the academy that only monsters attend — and his troubles are far from over:
A female gang of girl-obsessed first-year students makes itself known on campus, giving the second-year girls http://anidb.net/ch7923 [Moka] (vampire), http://anidb.net/ch7924 [Kurumu] (succubus), http://anidb.net/ch9642 [Yukari] (witch), and http://anidb.net/ch4422 [Mizore] (yuki-onna) a hard time. One of these newly arrived first-year girls is a vampire, holding a deep grudge against her older sister, who happens to be http://anidb.net/ch7922 [Ura Moka] — accusing her of not being true to herself when sealed in her http://anidb.net/ch7923 [Akashiya Moka] form.
Will Tsukune succeed in healing more ruffled hearts?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3820">4.42</permanent>
<temporary count="3885">6.81</temporary>
<review count="1">6.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>84063.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9727</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4214</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4310</identifier>
<identifier>gttxse</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.rosa-vam.com/top.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rosario_to_Vampire</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ロザリオとバンパイア</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1481</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331391</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10307</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2245</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2008/rosario_vampire2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1179" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-21">
<name>indecisive</name>
<description>This character has trouble taking their own decisions, and may rely on others to do that instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2143" parentid="2646" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-28">
<name>succubus</name>
<description>A demon who takes the form of a woman to seduce men in dreams to have sexual intercourse. In modern times, a succubus is often depicted as highly attractive, while in the past succubi were depicted as frightening and demonic. Succubi draw energy from men to sustain themselves, often until the victim becomes exhausted or dies. The male counterpart is the incubus.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2259" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-30">
<name>naked apron</name>
<description>A character wearing nothing but an apron appears in the show.</description>
<picurl>162045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2662" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>school excursion</name>
<description>True for almost all anime with school setting, there will be a school excursion or field trip. Tokyo and Kyoto seem to be particularly popular as sightseeing destinations. So are hiking excursions into the local mountains. This also is a good excuse to present the prefecture`s / city`s food specialities.
Potential for ecchi moments: Obviously the "boys" will get all sorts of ideas with the "girls" sleeping so close by.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2983" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body sharing</name>
<description>A character shares the same body with another entity. Usually this is due to a secret/hidden identity either due to DNA/blood, a ritual, an item or some freak accident.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3663 [body snatcher].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3202" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-04">
<name>adoring fan club</name>
<description>A character, group or characters, or an organisation is considered so awesome that a adoring fan club is formed to idolise them. Not only do they have notable admirers, but their fans become organised in such a fashion to have a following that could only be guaranteed in real life by precise and long increments of paparazzi-like stalking.
If the character is sufficiently cool, an instant fan club may happen practically overnight (i.e., within a few episodes of them being introduced), although the subject of admiration typically has mixed feelings about the entire affair.</description>
<picurl>48684.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3233" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-13">
<name>cooking curry</name>
<description>Japanese curry, usually eaten as curry rice, and often pickled vegetables, served on the same plate and eaten with a spoon, is one of the most popular dishes in Japan, where people eat it 125 times a year according to a survey made in 2005.
As such Japanese series will often devote a whole episode to the characters cooking and eating curry dishes.</description>
<picurl>160828.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5992" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-28">
<name>animal transforms into weapon</name>
<description>A being that appears to be a normal animal, is actually something much more, for it can transform into a weapon.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6074" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>physical examination</name>
<description>A comedy element with ecchi potential in your typical school setting: The (especially female) cast is measured for weight, height and other measurements by the school’s nurse.
The female cast may then be upset about the lack of “development” in certain areas, or shocked about a perceived weight gain. The male cast on the other hand will try to “sneak a peek”.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4422" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="282">8.54</rating>
<name>Shirayuki Mizore</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirayuki Mizore is a http://anidb.net/t2516 [yukionna]. Keeping in line with Japanese mythological creatures, she has the ability to control ice at will and can form clones composed of it. She`s frequently seen with a lollipop in her mouth, as yukionna are vulnerable to warm climates and doing so keeps their bodies cool and let them melt. Mizore returns to school after a delayed absence and shows an immediate interest in http://anidb.net/ch7250 [Tsukune].</description>
<picture>27568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7250" type="main character in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="95">2.38</rating>
<name>Aono Tsukune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A human who gets accepted into a school for monsters. Though scared at first, he soon comes to like his new school life thanks to his new friend Moka.</description>
<picture>25625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7922" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-17">
<rating votes="178">8.24</rating>
<name>Ura Moka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When the rosary on Akashiya Moka`s chest is removed, the seal breaks off and her inner self is awakened. Rated as an S-class monster, the inner Moka is a powerful and ruthless vampire, possessing a completely different personality to the original kind and sweet-looking Moka. Although she is merciless towards her enemies, she does care for Tsukune, Moka`s first friend in Youkai Academy and the only person who can take off the rosary on Moka`s chest.</description>
<picture>26997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7923" type="main character in" update="2019-03-17">
<rating votes="175">6.87</rating>
<name>Akashiya Moka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Moka is a student of the Yokai Private Academy. She`s the first person Tsukune met when he first set foot on the monster realm. Moka`s true form is a vampire but she is very sweet and kind. She takes a liking to Tsukune after sucking his blood and seems to get addicted on doing so.</description>
<picture>26998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7924" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-17">
<rating votes="158">7.75</rating>
<name>Kurono Kurumu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurono Kurumu is a succubus, and is initially jealous of Moka`s popularity overshadowing her own, though she eventually considers Moka a friend.</description>
<picture>26999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9642" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-08">
<rating votes="69">4.26</rating>
<name>Sendou Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sendou Yukari is the smartest student at Yokai Academy, and the youngest at age 11. She is a witch who dons a typical witch costume (consisting of a hat and cape), which is considered by some students to be a violation of the school rules, and frequently ends her sentences with desuu (ですぅ), which roughly translates to "it is". As a witch, she has problems with her classmates discriminating against her (according to Kurumu, witches are viewed as "Beings of the Borderline", those that are something between humans and the supernatural, as it is impossible to tell their difference by appearance alone). Despite ranking #1 on the examinations, she was a lonely prankster before meeting Tsukune and Moka. She initially hated Tsukune, claiming that she has fallen in love with Moka, and uses her magical powers to try to drive them apart. However, after both Tsukune and Moka save her from bullying classmates, she falls for him too, and her obsession with both has driven her to try to create a three-way relationship between them. Despite her genius IQ, Yukari is very childish in nature, and is often indecisive on whether or not she either loves Tsukune or Moka more than the other. This action was displayed in an omake when Kurumu asks Yukari a similar question to which Yukari answers both, only for her to choose Moka. She often clashes with Kurumu, often teasing her about her large breasts, but they often team up on some occasions, such as the case in the Witch`s Knoll arc, and are in reality friendly rivals. In the anime, she is the only girl of the group to actually kiss Tsukune.
As a witch, Yukari can cast various spells through her heart-shaped magic wand, with her motif revolving around tarot cards and washtubs. She can also use her wand to manipulate various objects and use them as weapons, as with the case where she uses brooms to drive away Tsukune in her introductory chapter. A running gag throughout the series is where she often drops a washtub on someone who is annoying, usually Kurumu or Mizore (and Gin on rare occasions). Yukari is quite powerful as a witch and has great potential given the right motivation, one instance is when she defeats an army of monster plants by herself during the Witch`s Knoll arc. Yukari has, on occasion, developed some bizarre items, such as the Gro-Gro Drops for Kokoa, often leading to hilarious results or farfetched situations. Her parents, both highly skilled and adept in magic, appear during the start of the school festival seen in the anime adaptation, when they repair the torn-up academy.</description>
<picture>215987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16671" type="appears in" update="2010-05-04">
<rating votes="22">2.79</rating>
<name>Morioka Gin`ei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A werewolf, originally an antagonist for taking pictures of the girls at the school.</description>
<picture>46228.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16672" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-08">
<rating votes="53">6.59</rating>
<name>Toujou Rubi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced as an antagonist, defending the field of her mistress, a powerful witch. Had an intense hatred for humans.</description>
<picture>216010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16673" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="38">5.18</rating>
<name>Nekonome Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukune`s cat-girl homeroom teacher. She is a little flighty and loves fish.</description>
<picture>46231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16674" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="28">7.87</rating>
<name>Ririko Kagome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The mathematics teacher, offers lessons after class at a price. Sucks intelligence from students. Very chesty!; lots of cleavage fanservice.</description>
<picture>46232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16675" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="6">1.31</rating>
<name>Kotsubo Okuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The phys-ed teacher at Youkai Academy. Shirayuki once confessed that she liked him, and he tried to take advantage of her, so she froze him. He was later punished, after trying to kill Shirayuki.</description>
<picture>46234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19071" type="appears in" update="2010-10-04">
<rating votes="19">5.18</rating>
<name>Aono Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55821.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19072" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-19">
<rating votes="23">5.94</rating>
<name>Shuzen Kokoa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26444" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="14">5.16</rating>
<name>Kou-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as "Batty" in the English manga, Kou is Kokoa`s shapeshifting bat possesses the ability to transform itself into a variety of blunt weapons for Kokoa to use (in one instance, he transformed into a rapier). Weighing in at 100 kilograms, he was originally a birthday gift from Moka, but since Moka did not have superhuman strength when she was 10 years old, Kou-chan ended up with Kokoa. In the anime, he acts as the narrator and occasionally covers up various shots of fanservice (done in the television broadcast, while the DVD version is uncensored), and also appears to state the exact duration of a fight. In the manga, various bats of similar design are used to give information on the various youkai encountered at the academy. He does not have any lines of speech in the manga, but in the anime, he frequently ends his sentences with dechuu (でちゅー, translated as "Squee" in Funimation`s subs).
In Rosario + Vampire Capu2, Kou takes a more active part in the story as Kokoa`s pet (much to the characters` surprise, since all believed he was simply a narrator), and in one episode, assumed the guise of a student named Ijuuin Koutarou. His powers as Koutarou allow him to use hypnosis through the uttering of a specific word (Je t`aime, the French phrase for "I love you"), specifically to that of an incubus. He intended to use his abilities to enslave the entire female student body (including Gin and Nekonome), even to the extent of enslaving Kokoa and Moka, who atttempted to resist his powers. He was swiftly defeated by the two vampires and reverted to his bat form, returning the female student body to normal after one of his teeth fell out.</description>
<picture>62118.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26445" type="appears in" update="2011-01-05">
<rating votes="10">5.84</rating>
<name>Aono Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26447" type="appears in" update="2011-01-05">
<rating votes="7">7.18</rating>
<name>Untenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious, unnamed bus driver who seems to know more than he reveals and constantly shows up to offer advice to Tsukune, he is usually portrayed smoking a cigar. He is the one who requests the board chairman help keep Tsukune`s ghoulish nature at bay. It is unknown if the bus driver is human or a youkai, but he does have an extensive knowledge in the supernatural, having identified Ishigami`s Lilith Mirror as the cause of the uproar during the school festival.
He is also one of the three Dark Lords.</description>
<picture>62123.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="633" picture="33549.jpg">Inoue Norihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26450" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="10">8.84</rating>
<name>Kurono Ageha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ageha is Kurumu`s mother who appears during the start of the school festival under the belief that Tsukune is her daughter`s fiancé, going so far as to allow him to "jump" her daughter anytime he wants. She also sports large breasts like her daughter and according to Tsukune, her breasts are softer than Kurumu`s. Exclusively in the anime`s second season, Ageha and Tsurara hold a long grudge against one another, being rivals for the affection of a student during their days as students at Youkai Academy. Due to having a long-time grudge against Tsurara, she is similar to the Meryl Streep character Madeline from the Robert Zemeckis film Death Becomes Her.</description>
<picture>62126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26451" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="11">8.25</rating>
<name>Shirayuki Tsurara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsurara is Mizore`s mother. Like her daughter, she is very shy and serene, including the tendency to hide behind corners and having a lollipop in her mouth. She comes to the Academy`s festival under the belief from her daughter`s stories that Tsukune is Mizore`s boyfriend. She has a bad habit of making sharp ice spears when she gets emotional. Tsurara is also an avid gun collector, with a wide variety of handguns and rifles stored in her home, once dreaming of becoming a spy.
Exclusively in Rosario + Vampire Capu2, Tsurara and Ageha hold a long grudge against one another, being rivals for the affection of a student during their days as students at Youkai Academy. She also runs a ski resort in the human world. Due to having a long-time grudge against Ageha, she is similar to the Goldie Hawn character Helen from the Robert Zemeckis film Death Becomes Her.</description>
<picture>62127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26456" type="appears in" update="2011-01-05">
<rating votes="3">2.68</rating>
<name>Komiya Gonzo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26457" type="appears in" update="2011-01-05">
<rating votes="7">1.57</rating>
<name>Komiya Saizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Komiya Saizou is a typical class bully with a playboy persona who is in the same class as Tsukune and Moka. It was stated in the manga that he was sent to Youkai Academy after causing a lot trouble in the human world, and that he was always chasing girls. He is infatuated with Moka and attempted to rape her, but is quickly knocked out by her super-vampire form and disappears from Youkai Academy for a while. The anime classifies him as an orc, while in the manga he was left unclassified. In the manga only, he reappears when Tsukune is elected class president and joins ANTI-THESIS in the hopes of exacting revenge, but ends up defeated when Tsukune temporarily transforms into a vampire. For hastily rushing ahead and bringing other members of ANTI-THESIS without consent, Saizou is killed for insubordination.</description>
<picture>62133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26458" type="appears in" update="2011-01-05">
<rating votes="3">2.68</rating>
<name>Komiya Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26459" type="appears in" update="2011-01-05">
<rating votes="2">3.76</rating>
<name>Katou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2840" picture="22915.jpg">Suzuki Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26460" type="appears in" update="2011-01-05">
<rating votes="5">6.59</rating>
<name>Sendou Fujiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukari`s mother who appears in chapter 24 of the second serialization alongside Tsurara and Ageha to aid their daughters in an athletic carnival. She had a short appearance in the first series at the school festival. Because Fujiko does not have any lines of speech in the manga, the anime renders her as indefinitely mute, only using a wide array of expressions to communicate. Her husband (and Yukari`s father) is Taminori Sendou.</description>
<picture>62135.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26461" type="appears in" update="2011-01-05">
<rating votes="3">3.88</rating>
<name>Sendou Taminori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62136.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26462" type="appears in" update="2011-01-05">
<rating votes="4">5.66</rating>
<name>Yakumaru Mako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Disguised as a nurse in the school`s hospital, Mako Yakumaru is a member of ANTI-THESIS first sent to assassinate Kusabi Midou after he fails to kill Tsukune. In order to sow dissesion among Tsukune and his friends, Mako controls and manipulates Yukari`s body after injecting her with a hypnotic fluid, forcing her to try to kill him. When this tactic fails, Mako injects her fluid into a multitude of bystanders, all forced to attack Tsukune. She appears in the second season of the anime and designated as the actual school nurse, rather than in disguise as one.</description>
<picture>62137.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1662" picture="25819.jpg">Kouda Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26463" type="appears in" update="2011-01-05">
<rating votes="5">2.32</rating>
<name>Nagai Kubisaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26464" type="appears in" update="2011-01-18">
<rating votes="11">5.04</rating>
<name>Oniyama Tonko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26465" type="appears in" update="2013-08-24">
<rating votes="8">4.97</rating>
<name>Chouno Shijimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Former president of Tea Ceremony Club, before PSC (Public Safety Commission) closed it down.</description>
<picture>141854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26466" type="appears in" update="2011-01-18">
<rating votes="7">4.46</rating>
<name>Mizuno Sumae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26475" type="appears in" update="2011-01-06">
<rating votes="6">5.07</rating>
<name>Apsara-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Apsara is the Indian cooking teacher of Youkai Academy and, as her name implies, an apsara appearing exclusively in Rosario + Vampire Capu2. Her favorite dish is curry and is very passionate about the dish. Unfortunately, her curry takes a side-effect of turning anyone who eats it into a "curry zombie". She is later defeated by Inner Moka.</description>
<picture>62168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26477" type="appears in" update="2011-01-06">
<rating votes="2">2.17</rating>
<name>Tosa no Tengu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26478" type="appears in" update="2011-01-06">
<rating votes="3">3.15</rating>
<name>Iyo no Zashiki Warashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26479" type="appears in" update="2011-01-06">
<rating votes="3">3.88</rating>
<name>Sanuki no Shiranui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="403" picture="74821.jpg">Horie Kazuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26480" type="appears in" update="2011-01-06">
<rating votes="3">3.15</rating>
<name>Awa no Umibouzu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26481" type="appears in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="9">5.16</rating>
<name>Mikogami Tenmei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikogami is a mysterious exorcist who is an old friend of the bus driver (and having the same strange eyes as the latter) and the dean of Youkai Academy. He is always seen hooded beneath his garments and possesses extremely strong, anti-demonic powers, having the ability to seal Tsukune`s ghoul nature using a "Holy Lock".</description>
<picture>62175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26482" type="appears in" update="2011-01-06">
<rating votes="2">6.25</rating>
<name>Yukiotoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26484" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="3">4.01</rating>
<name>Ijuuin Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26485" type="appears in" update="2011-04-11">
<rating votes="11">5.66</rating>
<name>Deshi Deshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Deshiko is a red-haired member of the PSC who ends her sentences with deshi and is always seen with a bou across her shoulders. She appears as a generic member in the manga, but her role is expanded in the anime and in the second season, she becomes the first girl on campus to fall under Kou (as Koutarou)`s hypnosis. Her true monster form pays homage to Lei-Lei of Darkstalkers, as Capcom is one of the anime`s sponsors.</description>
<picture>62179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26486" type="appears in" update="2011-01-06">
<rating votes="5">8.26</rating>
<name>Lilith no Kagami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lilith is a small fairy who carries the Lilith Mirror, an object allowing whoever holds it to see a monster`s true form as well as their hidden desires, but at the cost of the user`s soul. The mirror was given to Kyoko by Ishigami with the intention to create a schoolwide uproar by revealing the students` true forms as well as with the intention of stealing Tsukune`s soul, but it eventually failed. In the anime, Kyoko accidentally obtains Lilith and the Lilith Mirror after a run-in with Kokoa, who was intending to use it to split Inner Moka from Outer Moka. Lilith was eventually defeated by the teamwork of Mizore, Ruby, Yukari and Kurumu.</description>
<picture>62180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26487" type="appears in" update="2011-01-18">
<rating votes="5">2.32</rating>
<name>Kasahara Kouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26488" type="appears in" update="2011-01-18">
<rating votes="5">2.55</rating>
<name>Taira Bouzaburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="414" picture="211148.jpg">Onozuka Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26489" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="4">5.98</rating>
<name>Shuzen Issa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Issa Shuzen is Moka`s stepfather and the head of the Shuzen Family, which is well-known and respected as far as China for its reputation of dealing with "problems" in the underground. It is also the only location in Japan that houses vampires. Upon Akua`s arrival to the mansion from China, he orders her and Kalua to kill each other so that he may test his eldest daughter`s strength. He stops the fight before either one becomes badly injured, however, having measured her ability to his satisfaction.
Issa makes a full appearance in Rosario + Vampire Capu2 and is the third Dark Lord. In this adaptation, he created Moka`s rosario and the one used for the school barrier. His contempt for humans knows no bounds and according to Komori, and his powers exceed that of a standard S-class youkai, able to throw anyone with just a wave of his hand.</description>
<picture>62181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1816" picture="20691.jpg">Mori Katsuji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="92258" update="2008-08-03">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93219" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会とバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wiedersehen + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Riunione + Vampiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai to Vampire</title>
<summary>Tsukune’s back at the academy for another year! Moka’s popularity has only grown, but that could be a problem - one of the letters in her locker is a death threat!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93224" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹とバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Sister and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kleine Schwester + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sorellina + Vampiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto to Vampire</title>
<summary>The new girl at school shares quite a history with Moka - they’re sisters! Back in the day, Moka was able to defeat her younger sibling every time they sparred. Now it looks like Kokoa is out for vengeance!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93288" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">1.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カレーとバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Curry and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Curry + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Salsa al curry + Vampiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Curry to Vampire</title>
<summary>Mizore’s not having fun in cooking class; the group is making curry, and she’s not into spicy foods. She’s missing out on the culinary adventure, but she’ll see action soon enough when she has to save the school!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93289" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">身体測定とバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Body Measurements and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Körpermaße + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Esame del corpo + Vampiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shintai Sokutei to Vampire</title>
<summary>Yukari’s feeling down about her under-developed body, so Mako helps out with a little magic. Yukari’s new look makes quite a splash at school - but she still can’t seem to catch Tsukune’s eye!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93290" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">母と子とバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother and Child and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mutter + Kind + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Mamma e figlio + Vampiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haha to Ko to Vampire</title>
<summary>It`s Parents Day at the school and there’s drama in the air! Kurumi and Mizore`s mothers don’t get along, and they get a little crazy when they learn that both of their daughters are into Tsukune.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93512" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">修学旅行とバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Trip and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schulausflug + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Gita + Vampiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuugakuryokou to Vampire</title>
<summary>Tsukune’s gang heads to the hot springs on a field trip. Meanwhile, a rough and tumble rival school has set its sights on the Academy - and they’ve got an agent on the inside!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93655" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93656" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95040" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バスルームとバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bathroom and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Badezimmer + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Bagno + Vampiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bathroom to Vampire</title>
<summary>Tsukune goes to see his mom, who sees exactly what her son is up against when the girls start showing up in skimpy outfits! Later, Tsukune`s cousin sets up a contest for the girls - and the winner gets Tsukune!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95041" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青春とバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Youth and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Jugend + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seishun to Vampire</title>
<summary>It’s an episode of super-short mini-episodes! The subjects include shopping, recollections into the past, superheroism, bike riding, clashing taste buds, puppies, mini-skirts, and more!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95042" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スキーとバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Skiing and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ski + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ski to Vampire</title>
<summary>A ski trip turns into disaster when Kokoa goes after Moka in the snow! After a massive avalanche roars down the mountain, Tsukune becomes trapped in a cave - and he’s not alone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95043" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美少年とバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pretty Boy and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hübscher Junge + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bishounen to Vampire</title>
<summary>The popular new boy in school is making waves with Tsukune’s girls. It’s easy to see there’s something fishy going on, but the ladies seem to be powerless against his smooth-talking charm.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95141" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リリスの鏡とバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lilith`s Mirror and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Spiegel der Lilith + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lilith no Kagami to Vampire</title>
<summary>Tsukune`s sister stops by the Academy for a visit, but chaos ensues when she gets her hands on a special mirror that has the power to reveal the true nature of the student body.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95421" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">封印とバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Holy Seal and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Siegel + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuuin to Vampire</title>
<summary>Moka sacrifices her own rosary to seal the deteriorating barrier between the human world and the monster world. Will she ever be able to contain her true identity again?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95422" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">十字架と家族とバンパイア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cross and Family and a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kreuz + Familie + Vampir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juujika to Kazoku to Vampire</title>
<summary>If they ever hope to see the sweet side of Moka again, Tsukune and the girls must survive the perilous journey through the demon world to confront a monster whose powers are even greater than Moka’s!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
