<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="588" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>1997-12-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Virus: Virus Buster Serge</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">VIRUS - VIRUS BUSTER SERGE -</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Virus Buster Serge</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Virus Buster Serge</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Virus - O Caçador</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="895" type="Animation Work">Plum</name>
<name id="153" type="Character Design">Oobari Masami</name>
<name id="853" type="Series Composition">Studio G-1Neo</name>
<name id="153" type="Direction">Oobari Masami</name>
<name id="116" type="Music">Oomori Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="5532" type="Series Composition">Souma Kazuhiko</name>
<name id="25699" type="Series Composition">Kaneko Jirou</name>
</creators>
<description>Virus Buster Serge takes place in 2097, in a little place called Neo Hong Kong, which I thought was rather cool -- finally a bit of a departure from constant Neo Tokyo references. The denizens of earth are currently being threatened by an entity that calls himself the Incubator, who has created an evil virus which can infect both man and machine. Infect machines? Sound rather weird? At first I thought so as well. The virus does infect mecha, called Armored Gears in this series, taking them over. Enter STAND, a group of elite individuals encased in really cool powered armor suits called Variable Gear. The Knight Sabers ... err, wait ... STAND ... uses these suits to great effect fighting rampant virus infected Armored Gears. Serge himself enters the scenario against his will, as all reluctant heroes must. He has been plagued by really bad dreams, which have convinced him that STAND`s leader, Raven, should be dead. He decides to make this happen by assassinating Raven himself, but only succeeds in earning Raven`s attention. Raven decides Serge is quite a potential fighter and manages to snare him through cunning and trickery into joining STAND to help fight against the Incubator`s viral attacks.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="152">2.61</permanent>
<temporary count="155">5.33</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238129.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1024</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2364</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>524</identifier>
<identifier>dzjxqq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88930</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="6586" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Cutthroat Puppets</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cutthroat Puppets</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cutthroat Puppets</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6587" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Path Via Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Path Via Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Path Via Hell</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7644" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Incubating the Succubus</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Incubating the Succubus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Incubating the Succubus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8361" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Behold Change or Die</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Behold Change or Die</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Behold Change or Die</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13121" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">We Stand Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Stand Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">We Stand Alone</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13122" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Deep Down Exposure</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deep Down Exposure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deep Down Exposure</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13123" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Another Boy Missing</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Boy Missing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Another Boy Missing</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13124" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Behold Change or Die II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Behold Change or Die II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Behold Change or Die II</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13125" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Reactivate the Body</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reactivate the Body</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reactivate the Body</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13126" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Struggle Within</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Struggle Within</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Struggle Within</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13127" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blend the Strength</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blend the Strength</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blend the Strength</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13128" update="2005-02-16">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">To Have and to Hold</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Have and to Hold</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">To Have and to Hold</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
