<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5880" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-04-25</startdate>
<enddate>2009-04-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Koukyoushihen: Eureka Seven - Pocket ga Niji de Ippai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Psalms of Planets: Eureka Seven - Pocket Full of Rainbows</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Eureka Seven - Pocketful of Rainbows</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Псалмы Планет: Эврика 7 - Радуга в Кaрмане</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Псалмы Планет: Эврика 7 - Полный Карман Радуги</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="synonym">Žalmy planet: Eureka sedM - Kapsa plná duhy</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Еурека Седем - Джоб, пълен с цветове</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">e7 movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">交響詩篇エウレカセブン ポケットが虹でいっぱい</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Eureka Seven: Good Night, Sleep Tight, Young Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Eureka Seven - Der Film: Good Night, Sleep Tight, Young Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Eureka Seven - Le Film: Good Night, Sleep Tight, Young Lovers</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2826" type="Alternative Setting">Koukyoushihen: Eureka Seven</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="276230">The recommendation I selected was "For Fans"? but actually I would suggest the opposite.  Too many things have been turned on their heads.  For example the Image are invading Earth - What?  Did they not watch the series at all?  The only similarity to the series is most of the Characters, though often greatly changed and a bit of social background.  This movie would have been much better as an independent effort with no pretense of being related to Eureka Seven.&lt;br /&gt;Still, it might be enjoyable if you did not watch the series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="326521">A totally different story.  Only some main plots transferred from the series.  Most all of the same characters make at least cameo appearances. Very enjoyable overall.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="302924">Gorgeous! 11/10</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.eureka-prj.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="755" type="Work">Bones</name>
<name id="2298" type="Chief Direction">Kyouda Tomoki</name>
<name id="755" type="Original Work">Bones</name>
<name id="17225" type="Direction">Haraguchi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="503" type="Character Design">Yoshida Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="16151" type="Chief Animation Direction">Saitou Tsunenori</name>
<name id="2950" type="Animation Work">Kinema Citrus</name>
<name id="24300" type="Work">Amano Naoki</name>
<name id="18338" type="Work">Watanabe Makoto</name>
<name id="4131" type="Music">Satou Naoki</name>
<name id="27375" type="Work">Tsukada Takurou</name>
</creators>
<description>The war between humanity and the Image, a mysterious life form from space, has already spanned half a century.
In the year 2054, there is a boy on board the http://anidb.net/ch2950 [Gekko], the mother ship of the 303rd Independent Horde under the command of http://anidb.net/ch2900 [Holland Novak]. His name is http://anidb.net/ch2874 [Renton] and his dream is to ride into battle on his http://anidb.net/ch2959 [Nirvash]. He has resolved to one day rescue http://anidb.net/ch2875 [Eureka], his childhood friend who was kidnapped eight years ago, and to return home.
But fate decides to test the love between Eureka and Renton and puts them through many trials. Duty and emotions, truths and lies, past and future, life and death, reality and dreams, and Holland. Fate seems to conspire against them. As the final battle with the Image approaches, the pair`s actions may well decide the fate of humanity.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1502">5.21</permanent>
<temporary count="1516">6.89</temporary>
<review count="1">6.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>54714.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9750</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4246</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.eureka-prj.net/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/eureka-movie</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>交響詩篇エウレカセブン_ポケットが虹でいっぱい</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1805</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>333021</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2973" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>cute monster</name>
<description>Cute monster refers to animal soldiers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3277" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-28">
<name>bendy lasers</name>
<description>Lasers — of all things — bend at strange angles, are profusely in effect in this anime. Usually seen in a space setting, as part of a weapon system on spaceships.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4004" parentid="2638" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>organic mecha</name>
<description>An organic mecha is a mecha that has organic tissue in its composition. The most prominent historical example is http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion].</description>
<picurl>224892.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5767" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Itano circus</name>
<description>The Itano circus is named after Itano Ichirou, a Japanese animator, and refers to a highly stylized and acrobatic method of depicting aerial combat and dogfights in many anime, particularly the Macross series, where it was utilised by Itano for the first time and was ground-breaking.
The Itano circus is characterized by detailed, fluid shading of the mecha, the close-range acrobatic moves the duelling fighters make in combat, as well as twisting contrails left by fighters and missiles. It is also commonly used in specific reference to an attack where a mecha or spaceship launches a large swarm of missiles with meticulously animated spiralling smoke trails and erratic trajectories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2873" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="61">8.22</rating>
<name>Anemone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2874" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="90">4.91</rating>
<name>Renton Thurston</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Renton Thurston is the main protagonist of the Eureka Seven series. He is referred to in episode previews simply as "the boy". Renton thinks his life is mundane and dreams of doing the extraordinary. At the beginning of the series, he becomes a member of http://anidb.net/ch2961 [Gekkostate] in order to be near his idol, http://anidb.net/ch2900 [Holland], and his love at first sight, http://anidb.net/ch2875 [Eureka]. In seasons one and two, the other crew members generally see Renton as Gekkostate`s "busboy", doing chores such as cooking and cleaning. He occasionally rides with Eureka in the http://anidb.net/ch2958 [Nirvash typeZERO] and is able to lift. In the third season, Renton is shown to mature a bit. Eureka and Renton continue to pilot the typeZERO, and his relationship with Eureka deepens, though the kids (http://anidb.net/ch2895 [Maurice], http://anidb.net/ch2896 [Maeter], and http://anidb.net/ch2897 [Linck]) still refuse to regard Renton as their "papa". In season four Renton matures even further, coming into his own as a father to the kids and a prominent member of Gekkostate.</description>
<picture>18566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2875" type="main character in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="104">8.13</rating>
<name>Eureka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2876" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="30">7.46</rating>
<name>Dominic Sorel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1409" picture="18508.jpg">Yamazaki Shigenori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2877" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="37">7.64</rating>
<name>Talho Yuuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2900" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="34">5.74</rating>
<name>Holland Novak</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="97453" update="2009-03-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="100203" update="2017-09-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2009-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Fall in love all over again in this film set in an alternate timeline within the Eureka Seven universe! As mankind prepares to fire a weapon that will end a half-century war, the world’s fate rests in the hearts of two recently reunited childhood friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102433" update="2010-10-10">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
