<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5917" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>65</episodecount>
<startdate>2006</startdate>
<enddate>2013</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Usavich</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ウサビッチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Usavich</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Усавич</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11750" type="Prequel">Usavich Zero</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8471" approval="1" total="2">Popee the Performer</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="287993">Nice comedy show with great drawings, animation style and funny jokes.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.usavich.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9874" type="Animation Work">Kanaban Graphics</name>
<name id="9876" type="Original Work">Miyazaki Aguri</name>
<name id="9031" type="Original Work">Tomioka Satoshi</name>
<name id="9031" type="Direction">Tomioka Satoshi</name>
<name id="25691" type="Music">Ueno Hironori</name>
</creators>
<description>Usavich (ウサビッチ) (from Japanese うさぎ "usagi", rabbit, with "vich" giving it faux Russian flavour) is a series of animated short films being produced for MTV Japan by Kanaban Graphics. It`s about an odd couple of rabbits imprisoned in a Russian prison. While the first season (1-13) shows the absurd everyday occurrences of the two rabbits` prison life, the second season (14-26) tells the adventures of their escape and life on the run.
The Third Season (27-39) Shows their Struggle with a rich rabbit as they aim for a pair of running shoes. The Forth Season (40-52) Shows the Comedy of their everyday life again with the new creature made by Putin, and the Fifth Season shows their life in a forest after they ran away from city.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="419">6.03</permanent>
<temporary count="420">6.74</temporary>
<review count="2">6.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>32028.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11360</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6878</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3737</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3738</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5397</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10513</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>16347</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.usavich.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mtvjapan.com/tv/program/sp_usavich_s4</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Usavich</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ウサビッチ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331359</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12487</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2633" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>prison</name>
<description>A building used to house convicted criminals and accused persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2675" parentid="2831" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Russia</name>
<description>Russia, officially known as the Russian Federation, is a sovereign country in Eurasia. Russia is the largest country in the world by area, covering more than one-eighth of the Earth`s inhabited land area, and the ninth most populous. The European western part of the country is much more populated and urbanised than the eastern; about 77% of the population live in European Russia. Russia`s capital Moscow is one of the largest cities in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4542" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-25">
<name>no dialogue</name>
<description>The anime either has no spoken dialogue or no dialogue at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6623" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-04-02">
<name>tank warfare</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="719" type="main character in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="14">8.36</rating>
<name>Kirenenko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirenenko wears a prison uniform with red stripes, number 04. He has a safety pin stuck through his left ear. Originally a mafia boss, he was sentenced to death. He once had a twin brother. Generally quiet, but very dangerous when he becomes angry and goes berserk. He likes order and does not forgive anyone who crosses his path or otherwise "meddles" in his life. He collects sneakers (shoes) and is generally oblivious (apathetic) to the world around him while he reads his magazine advertising sneakers. He cares for nothing but his sneakers.</description>
<picture>15014.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="720" type="main character in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="4">8.43</rating>
<name>Putin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Putin wears a prison uniform with green stripes, number 541. Has his ears tied together and is good-natured. He likes to dance kazachok on his bed. Although generally dim-witted, when the door gave him a test he was passing with flying colors until he failed to correctly identify the gender of all the chicks when he placed the transvestite chick into the female slot instead of the male slot. Likes fun but often gets in trouble. An honest laborer who once missed a day of work due to hangover and was sentenced to 3 years in jail as a capitalist agent. However, he enjoys life in prison with its free food. He was only one day from being released when he followed Kirenenko out of the cell.</description>
<picture>15015.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7350" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-25">
<name>Leningrad</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leningrad is a frog living in the toilet in Putin and Kirenenko`s cell. He does little more than croak, eat Komanech, and defecate her out again.</description>
<picture>25846.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7351" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-27">
<name>Comaneci</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Comaneci is a transvestite ("okama") chick found by Putin while sorting chicks by gender in Episode 2. Her mother visited during episode 6 and was eaten by Kirenenko.</description>
<picture>25847.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7377" type="appears in" update="2009-05-26">
<name>Kanshukov</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25905.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7378" type="appears in" update="2009-05-26">
<name>Shokeiski</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25913.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7404" type="appears in" update="2009-05-26">
<name>Rodov</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25920.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7405" type="appears in" update="2009-05-26">
<name>Zenirov</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25921.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7409" type="appears in" update="2009-05-26">
<name>Boris</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25924.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7410" type="appears in" update="2009-05-26">
<name>Koputchev</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25926.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="90696" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="5">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">食事の時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for Food</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shokuji no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90697" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="5">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">労働の時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for Work</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roudou no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90698" update="2009-08-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="5">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャワーの時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for a Shower</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shower no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90699" update="2009-08-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="5">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">娯楽の時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for Games</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goraku no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90700" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="5">6.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダンスの時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for Dancing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dance no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90701" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="5">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">面会の時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for Visitors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Menkai no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90702" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="4">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">体操の時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for Exercise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taisou no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90703" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギャンブルの時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for Cards</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gamble no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90704" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おやつの時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for a Snack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oyatsu no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90705" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トイレの時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for Toilet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toilet no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90706" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">処刑の時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for an Execution</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shokei no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90707" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リンチの時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for Torture</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lynch no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90708" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出所の時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for an Exit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shussho no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90709" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">3.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乱暴運転注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for Aggressive Drivers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ranbou Unten Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90710" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">脇見運転注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch the Road</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakimi Unten Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90711" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">5.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">坂道発進注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for Uphill Traffic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakamichi Hasshin Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90712" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">5.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狙撃注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for Snipers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sogeki Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90713" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダンス注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for Dancers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dance Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90714" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">2.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミサイル注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for Missiles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Millise Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90715" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パンク注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for Punctures</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Panku Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90716" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スピード注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch your Speed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Speed Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90717" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦車注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for Tanks</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensha Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90718" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">改造注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for Mods</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaizou Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90719" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">5.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">偽者注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for Fakes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nisemono Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90720" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">検問注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for Inspection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenmon Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90721" update="2008-05-13">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">総攻撃注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watch for General Offensive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soukougeki Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93622" update="2008-10-18">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">1階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">1st Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95199" update="2008-11-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">労働の時間 (裏)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2.5 Time for Work (Another Point of View)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Randou no Jikan (Ura)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97275" update="2009-03-06">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">4階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">4th Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">4-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97276" update="2009-03-06">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">3.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">3階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">3-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97277" update="2009-03-06">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">2階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">2-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97441" update="2009-03-17">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">5階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">5th Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">5-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97449" update="2009-03-18">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">6階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">6th Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">6-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99611" update="2009-04-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">VMAJの時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for VMAJ - MTV Video Music Japan 2007 Promo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">VMAJ no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102641" update="2009-05-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">7階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">7th Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">7-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102642" update="2009-05-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">8階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">8th Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">8-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102643" update="2009-05-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">9階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">9th Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">9-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102644" update="2009-05-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">10階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">10th Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">10-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102645" update="2009-05-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">3.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">11階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">11th Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">11-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102646" update="2009-05-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">3.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">12階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">12th Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">12-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105148" update="2009-07-17">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">13階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">13th Storey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">13-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105165" update="2019-02-04">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Making Of</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130396" update="2011-05-24">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">洗面マシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wash Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seimei Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130397" update="2011-05-24">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冷蔵庫マシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fridge Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reizouko Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130398" update="2011-05-24">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダンスマシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dance Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dance Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130399" update="2011-05-24">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">洗濯マシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Washing Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentaku Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130400" update="2011-05-24">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">合体マシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Combine Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gattai Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130401" update="2011-05-24">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お掃除マシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cleaning Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osouji Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130402" update="2011-05-24">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クッキングマシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cooking Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cooking Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132179" update="2015-11-05">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲームマシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Game Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Game Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132180" update="2015-11-05">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TV電話マシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phone TV Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Denwa Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132181" update="2011-08-03">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">手品マシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magic Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tejina Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132182" update="2011-08-03">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走マシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Insane Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132183" update="2011-08-03">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">窓拭きマシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Window Cleaning Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mado Fuki Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132184" update="2011-08-03">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">車マシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Car Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuruma Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147547" update="2014-07-30">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">毛皮の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fur Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kegawa no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147548" update="2013-02-17">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かくれんぼの森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hide and Seek Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakurenbo no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147673" update="2013-03-15">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コマネチの森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Komanetsyn Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komanechi no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147674" update="2014-08-08">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダッシュの森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dash Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dash no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147675" update="2014-05-08">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Horror Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu nno Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147676" update="2014-05-08">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">釣りの森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fishing Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuri no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147677" update="2014-05-08">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">罠の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trap Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wana no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147678" update="2014-05-08">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">居眠りの森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drowsiness Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inemuri no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147679" update="2014-05-08">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">穴掘の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Digging Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anahori no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147680" update="2014-05-08">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兄弟の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brothers Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoudai no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147681" update="2014-05-08">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蛙の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frog Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">kaeru no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147682" update="2014-05-08">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダンスの森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dance Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dance no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147683" update="2013-02-24">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キノコの森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mushroom Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinoko no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212425" update="2019-02-04">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ちの時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13.5 Time for Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212426" update="2019-02-04">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドM注意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26.5 Beware of Extreme Masochist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">DO M Chuui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212427" update="2019-02-04">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 39.5 The Sound Floor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onkai</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
