<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="594" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2003-12-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bakuten Shoot Beyblade G Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Beyblade revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">爆転シュート ベイブレードGレボリューション</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Beyblade G Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Beyblade G Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Beyblade G Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Beyblade G Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">เบย์เบลดภาค 3 ศึกอวสานลูกข่างสายฟ้า</title>
<title xml:lang="hr" type="official">Beyblade G</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1964" type="Prequel">Bakuten Shoot Beyblade 2002</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Unknown Relation">Madhouse</name>
<name id="4152" type="Series Composition">Hasegawa Katsumi</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
<name id="4938" type="Character Design">Nagamori Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="5476" type="Direction">Hashimoto Mitsuo</name>
</creators>
<description>Finally succesively completing the two world tournaments, the talented young man Takao meets with Daichi Sumeragi and the mysterious character, Jing "Shippo". With the appearance of these new rivals, Takao burns with greater excitement.
Apart from Takao, Max also receives notice of a new tournament that`s was going to be held. And this time, there`s a rule. Players must be in teams of two to participate in a tag match. So that they can battle with Takao, Max and Rei battles with various other teams. And of course, Takao just can`t wait to do battle!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="497">2.96</permanent>
<temporary count="513">5.71</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>2215.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2085</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1668</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1136</identifier>
<identifier>frtkye</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>爆転シュート_ベイブレードGレボリューション</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>190</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240585</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00C3BU5VS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3622" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>merchandising show</name>
<description>The bane of the parent`s wallet; this show usually has only a single reason for existence: to advertise the toy line it is based upon to the intended target audience. The variety of toys can range from accessories for girls and boys, to cards and figures or models. Most often the ability of the toys will be exaggerated or invokes magic to work in the anime. The toys`s names will also be continuously repeated in the anime, often accompanied by flashy effects and loud shouting. Combined with an intricate story that typically involves an adventure or a tournament of sorts, it makes for an effective commercial.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="25712" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆転劇の幕開けだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When in Rome... Let It Rip!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Let it Rip in Rom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakuten Geki no Makuake Da</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25713" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タカオ, 勝負だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Kid in Town</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Überflieger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takao, Shoubu Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25714" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレには勝てん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invitation to Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Herausforderung</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ni wa Katen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25715" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">合宿じゃねえ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roughing It</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Not macht erfinderisch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gasshuku ja Nee!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25716" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレが悪いんじゃねえ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blame Game</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine Riesenblamage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ga Waruinja Nee!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25717" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キョウジュはキョウジュだ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kenny`s Big Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kennys großer Kampf</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouju wa Kyouju Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25718" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">100年早いぜ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A League of His Own</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein und dieselbe Liga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">100 Nen Hayaize!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25719" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">まとめてきやがれ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s a Battle Royale...!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aus Freund wird Feind...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matomete Kiyagare!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25720" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カイしかいねえ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`re the Man, Kai!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kai Shikai Nee!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25721" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">1+1は無限大だぜ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Swiped On the Streets</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abenteuer in New York City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1+1 wa Mugen Dai Daze!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25722" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友達じゃねえ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Team Divided</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Team teilt sich</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi Ja Nee!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25723" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレの道はオレが決める</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Were Once Bladebreakers</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rick, der Rüpel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Michi wa Ore ga Kimeru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25724" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オマエしだいだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take Your Best Shot!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zeig, was du drauf hast!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omae Shidai Da</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25725" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレにやらせろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picking Up the Pieces</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tyson im Abseits</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ni Yarasero!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25726" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パートナーだろ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sleepless in Madrid</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schlaflos in Madrid</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Partner Daro!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25727" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26277" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンタなら勝てる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sibling Rivalry</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rivalität unter Geschwistern</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anta Naru Kateru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26278" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">負けるなよ...タカオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burdens of a Champion</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Champion hat`s nicht einfach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maerku na yo... Takao</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26279" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">まだだ...?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ray and Kai: The Ultimate Face-Off...</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ray und Kai, der Kampf der Giganten</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mada Da...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26280" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダサダサだぜ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Under Pressure</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Champion unter Druck</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dasadasa Daze!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26281" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パワー全開だ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Down Under Thunder!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Überraschungssieger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Power Zenkai Da!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26282" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">NOーーーッ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One For All... Free For All!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Jeder gegen jeden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">No!!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26283" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">GOーーーッ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Max Attacks!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Max greift an</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Go!!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26284" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">気を付けろ, 大地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Same Old Dirty Tricks...</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kampf im Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiotsukero, Daichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26285" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">いい顔してるね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beyblade Like An Egyptian</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Team wehrt sich</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ii Kao Shiteru ne!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26286" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">邪魔するな!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fire and Water</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Feuer und Wasser</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jama Suru na!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26787" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お前に会えてよかったぜ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pros and Ex-Cons</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wird Beyblade zum Profisport?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omae ni Aete Yokattaze</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26788" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最高に面白いぞ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What a Blast!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wer kommt ins Endspiel?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikou ni Omoshiroizo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26789" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふざけるな!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boris, The Blade Stops Here!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hey Boris, bis hierher und nicht weiter!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuzakeruna!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26790" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">BBAの最終兵器</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebel Alliance</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Allianz der Rebellen!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BBA no Saishuu Heiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26791" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミスターX(エックス)だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When You Wish Upon a Star...</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die G-Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mister Z Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26792" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わけわかんねえ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beyblade Idol</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wer steckt hinter BEGA?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waka Wakannee!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26793" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄を見るぞ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bega on the Rise</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die BEGA hat alles im Griff!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku o Miruzo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26794" update="2019-02-28">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりじゃねえ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let the Games Begin... Again!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Kampf der Kämpfe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owari Ja Nee!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26795" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アーユーレディ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sing Ming Ming, sing!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sing MingMing, sing!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Are You Ready?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26796" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんのつもりだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And Justice-Five For All</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Justice Five-Turnier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nan no Tsumori Da</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26797" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よっしゃー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Familiar Faces</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Drei Teams im Finale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yossha!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26798" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">じゃあな!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Runaway Daichi!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Daichi auf Achse!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jaa na!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26799" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレならここだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And Then There Were Two</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Dann waren es nur noch zwei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore Nara Koko Da</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26800" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">まだかよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Changing Gears</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Spiel auf Zeit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mada ka yo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26801" update="2019-02-28">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あやまれ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Out of Their League</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Boris ist zurück!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayamare!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26802" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギブアップか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Back to Basics</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zurück zu den Anfängen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Give Up ka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26803" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">OK!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Max to the Max</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Maximaler Einsatz!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">OK!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26804" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">1000%だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bega Challenge</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die BEGA-Herausforderung!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1000% Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26805" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キミの名は...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Mystel...</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der geheimnisvolle Mystel!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Na wa...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26806" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対に勝つ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Refuse to Lose</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kampf der Titanen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai ni Katsu!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26807" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トレビア~ン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Return of Kai</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kai in der Krise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Torebian!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26808" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">えっ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Now You`re Making Me Mad</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zurück im Team</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ee!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26809" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛だ...!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beyblading Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kein echter Beyblader...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai Da...!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26810" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アチョーーー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Principles of Victory</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Prinzipien des Siegs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Acho!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26811" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">この負け犬が!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to My Nightmare!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Willkommen im Albtraum!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Makeinu ga!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26812" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウザいんだよっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brooklyn`s Back!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">In einer anderen Dimension</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uzain Da yo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26813" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">GO! シュート!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beybattle For the Ages</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Kampf für die Ewigkeit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Go! Shoot!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120220" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">German Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
