<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5956" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-03-01</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Chou Gekijouban Keroro Gunsou 3: Keroro Tai Keroro - Tenkuu Daikessen de Arimasu!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Sergeant Keroro: The Super Duper Movie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Keroro Gunsou: Creation! Ultimate Keroro, Wonder Space-Time Island!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Keroro Gunsou Movie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Keroro Gunsou: Tenkuu Daikessen de Arimasu!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">超劇場版 ケロロ軍曹3 ケロロ対ケロロ 天空大決戦であります!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1552" type="Parent Story">Keroro Gunsou</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20070901201249/http://www.keroro-movie.net/?</url>
<creators>
<name id="3611" type="Chief Direction">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="4158" type="Character Design">Oizaki Fumitoshi</name>
<name id="7617" type="Music">Suzuki Saeko</name>
<name id="9231" type="Direction">Yamaguchi Susumu</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="4241" type="Original Work">Yoshizaki Mine</name>
<name id="4158" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oizaki Fumitoshi</name>
<name id="24618" type="Animation Work">Bridge</name>
</creators>
<description>The movie begins with Fuyuki Hinata and the Keroro Platoon exploring an abandoned temple in the mountaintop city of Machu Picchu in Peru. While on the exploration, Keroro accidentally sets off a trap, and by chance they find a hidden chamber with a large blue crystal in the center, on a stand that has a key in it. Keroro leans on the key, causing the room to activate a mysterious machine, this caused the entire temple to shake. As soon as the group realized what was happening, they run out of the room. While running, Keroro accidentally loses his Kero Ball while Fuyuki catches a fleeting glimpse of a glowing young woman as he is running out, and tells Keroro that there was a girl in the room, but he is forced to leave the room before he can say anything else. The group successfully escapes, while the girl (now sprouting a pair of glowing wings) watches them leave - while back in the chamber, something is growing within the crystal...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="67">6.94</permanent>
<temporary count="67">6.82</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>65872.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8867</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5290</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4295</identifier>
<identifier>qcevll</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20070901201249/http://www.keroro-movie.net/?</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>357</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329223</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11501" type="main character in" update="2009-09-02">
<rating votes="34">5.24</rating>
<name>Keroro Gunsou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12064" type="main character in" update="2009-10-01">
<rating votes="14">4.79</rating>
<name>Giroro Gochou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Giroro is the single unit mobile infantry of the Keroro Platoon. He is a red Keronian who has a scar over his left eye. His symbol is a skull which, unlike the other Keronians, is only on his hat. In lieu of a belly symbol, he diagonally straps across his body a belt with a rectangular buckle. It is revealed that it contains a picture of Natsumi Hinata. The belt is priceless since it serves both as his good luck charm and as a reminder of his friends who died in a Keron War. Without it, he loses most of his abilities and is utterly inept as a soldier. However, as a young Keronian, he carried his skull symbol on his hat and belly and was not afflicted with the scar across his face.
His often irritably short tempered self is caused by the unfocused members of the Platoon, especially Keroro, in their invasion of Pekopon. This often leads Giroro to physically assault Keroro by all means, including shoving a grenade in his mouth. Occasionally, his anger (usually triggered when defending Natsumi) drives him into "combat mode"— where most of his intelligence is converted into battle power and he only speaks in short sentences. He is in love with Natsumi and he almost always turns into a lovesick puppy around her. He lives just outside the Hinata house, slightly under Natsumi`s window.
In the past, he was a typical Keronian who trained with Keroro and Zeroro so one day he could be just like his idolized brother.
Giroro seldom wears a tailed white tuxedo, ruffled shirt, and either a black or pink bow tie, accompanied by a long, blond wig which he curls up in an old-fashioned way, to impress Natsumi.</description>
<picture>3560.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12065" type="main character in" update="2011-10-09">
<rating votes="67">7.52</rating>
<name>Hinata Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The older sister of Fuyuki Hinata, Natsumi is a vivacious and fiery teenager whose most notable points are her great athletic prowess and her bitter rivalry with the series` antihero, Sergeant Keroro. As her mother, Aki, is mostly at work, Natsumi often takes care of the house chores, although she leaves most of them to Keroro, whom she always calls "bokegaeru" (ボケガエル, stupid frog). She deeply cares about her family, and, although she rarely admits it, her surrogate alien "family," and desperately wishes for her mother to spend some quality time with her and Fuyuki. Within her family, Natsumi is probably the only one capable of noticing the presence of the house spirit. Whenever the spirit causes mischief or makes an appearance, Natsumi immediately feels under the weather due to the ghost`s spiritual presence.
During her grade-school days in the manga, Natsumi was nicknamed "Devil Summer" (her name literally means "summer beauty") due to her violent temper, though she became more mature when she reached middle school. Although generally tomboyish for her athletism, Natsumi has a number of typical "teenage-girl" insecurities, especially around her crush, Saburo. She is an avid listener to 623`s radio show, though her failure on ever listening to any of her postcards over the show has become a running gag in the series.
Natsumi is fairly popular among the alumni at her school, especially among girls due to her masculine interests like sports. One of her most notable admirers is Koyuki Azumaya, her best friend, although Koyuki`s feelings for her may as well extend to a crush (in the manga it is a crush).
At times, Natsumi and Keroro seem to absolutely hate each other, as Keroro is an idiotic annoyance to her once-peaceful life and as she herself is Keroro`s main obstacle from world invasion. However, their relationship is one of the most complex within the series, as it varies from rivalry and hate to concern and understanding.
Natsumi has feminine interests like sweet things and snacks in general, as well as flowers and cute things, and her least favorite things are said to be anything creepy-crawly, especially slugs. She has the word `summer` in English on her bedroom door, and is part of the kaito team `MorePeachSummerSnow`.</description>
<picture>67356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12660" type="main character in" update="2011-10-09">
<rating votes="11">3.77</rating>
<name>Hinata Fuyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15186" type="main character in" update="2011-10-09">
<rating votes="44">7.65</rating>
<name>Kururu Souchou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15187" type="main character in" update="2011-10-09">
<rating votes="21">2.41</rating>
<name>Tamama Nitouhei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamama is private second class of the Keroro Platoon. He is the newest member in the planetary invasion troop, and also the youngest. His name stems from the Japanese word otamajakushi "tadpole". While his age is unknown, Etsuko Kozakura has stated that she voiced Tamama as someone who was 19 years old. He is a very faithful subordinate to Keroro.
Tamama is possessed of a tendency to have mood swings that border on a split personality, just like his partner Momoka Nishizawa. While usually gentle and cheerful, Tamama can become a vengeful, raving maniac at the drop of a hat. This change is usually accompanied by the sound of a balloon popping.
Tamama is also prone to fits of jealousy, usually towards anyone who gets near Keroro (especially Angol Mois, who he frequently refers to as "that woman").
Tamama likes junk food (especially candy, cake, cola, and potato chips) and physical training (he has his own private training room in the Nishizawa Mansion). In the anime, Tamama is diagnosed with high blood sugar because of his love of sweets, as revealed with a physical checkup.
Tamama`s least favourite sound is nails on a chalkboard. He also dislikes Angol Mois and often calls her "that woman", as he considers her a rival for Keroro`s attention. Despite this, Mois seems blissfully unaware of Tamama`s hatred towards her.</description>
<picture>67200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15188" type="main character in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="23">8.40</rating>
<name>Dororo Heichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lance Corporal Dororo (Formerly known as Zeroro) is the Keroro Platoon`s assassin who crash landed on Pekopon and was forgotten about by his platoonmates (as usual). Soon after, he found his leg caught in a bear trap and awaited his lonely death, until he was rescued by female ninja Koyuki Azumaya (with the help of Zeroyasha, the dog, in the anime). He decided to follow the way of the ninja, he changed his name to Dororo, the name of the forest where Koyuki rescued him. Dororo is often forgotten about by the rest of the platoon and most everyone else but Koyuki, which will cause his Trauma Switch to turn on. When this happens, a purple, gloomy era radiates from Dororo and he will sit in a corner or dark space and cry. His Trauma switch is usually activated when he is reminded of something done to him by Keroro during thier childhood, Such as using him as a sheild in a snowball fight caused him to remember when he was used in the same way during a dodgeball game.
Dororo has a love for all creatures and nature of Pekopon. He has stated that he has "fallen deeply in love" with the planet (Episode 13). As a result, he will not participate in plans that will potentially harm people`s feeling or nature, or endanger any wildlife species on the planet. Dororo has vowed to protect Pekopon at all costs along with Koyuki.
As a child, Zeroro loved to garden, which he still does. Dororo even has his own lovely garden in the underground base of the platoon, where he grows both plant species that are native to Pekopon and other alien planets. He uses gardening as a way of meditating (along with reading and actual meditating, usually on top of high places like lamp posts or trees) to train his physical and mental swiftness.
Young Zeroro was part of a large, wealthy family. Unfortunately, Dororo has never had a strong aura of presence, much to the point where people won`t notice he`s there even if he`s standing right next to them. Thus, little Zeroro never had many friends until Keroro and Giroro came along. Zeroro would do most anything to stay friends with the two, even when they (mostly Keroro) would often to things that led to his feelings being hurt or his possessions broken, and occasionally physically hurt. Over the years, Keroro has broken Zeroro`s precious music box, used his stamp collection, stolen the strawberries of Zeroro`s cake, wrote all over his books and taken advantage of his kind nature.
Despite his mistreatment, Zeroro retained his sweet, humble and kind personality and doesn`t hold a grudge or want revenge against Keroro (unlike his counterpart in the Garuru platoon, Zoruru), though he will break down and cry when reminded of one of his experiences as a child. Dororo used his natural quietness and ability to be unnoticed in the form of stealth after inspired (ironically) by Keroro to become an assassin in the Keronian Military. He joined an elite group of assassins along with Zoruru, led by Jirara, before departing for Pekopon as a Lance Corporal (In the manga, formerly a Private Second Class).
Dororo often ends his speech with "De Gozaru", an archaic form of "Desu". Also, Dororo addressed himself as "Sessha", an archaic male form of "I" primarily used by Samurai.
Early in the series, one of Dororo`s more common actions was to speak to Keroro and the others in the form of a shuriken made of paper which acted as a note, when needed. The shuriken would always seem to stick itself in Keroro`s head, usually causing him to freak out until it`s removed by another platoonmate. Dororo does not need to be close by to perform this.</description>
<picture>67201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="97679" update="2010-04-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2008-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116573" update="2010-04-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116574" update="2010-04-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2008-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116575" update="2010-04-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2008-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116576" update="2010-04-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 4 of 4</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
