<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6031" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-17</startdate>
<enddate>2009-02-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Goku Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Сбогом, отчаян учителю: Тишина</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">狱·再见! 绝望老师</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gszs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">szs ova</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">szs3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">獄・さよなら絶望先生</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Прощай, безрадостный учитель OVA-1</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6509" type="Sequel">Zan Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei</anime>
<anime id="5576" type="Prequel">Zoku Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://zetsubou.kc.kodansha.co.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="59" type="Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="3013" type="Character Design">Morioka Hideyuki</name>
<name id="3019" type="Original Work">Kumeta Kouji</name>
<name id="3013" type="Chief Animation Direction">Morioka Hideyuki</name>
<name id="4073" type="Music">Hasegawa Tomoki</name>
<name id="59" type="Series Composition">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="1512" type="Chief Direction">Miyamoto Yukihiro</name>
<name id="9789" type="Series Composition">Tou Fuyashi</name>
<name id="3528" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamamura Hiroki</name>
<name id="9789" type="Series Composition">Tou Fuyashi</name>
</creators>
<description>A continuation of Zoku Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei, with more stories revolving around Nozomu Itoshiki, the extremely pessimistic or despairing teacher, and the students of class 2-H, who are each hilariously abnormal in their own unique way except for the one relatively normal girl who hates being called normal.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1920">7.56</permanent>
<temporary count="1931">7.75</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>15971.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10224</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4872</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4367</identifier>
<identifier>liluac</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://zetsubou.kc.kodansha.co.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331827</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10331</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1283" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-24">
<name>tsukkomi</name>
<description>A tsukkomi is a comedy duo stock character in a traditional Japanese slapstick stand-up comedy style known as manzai. Tsukkomi characters are the smart, reasonable, and down-to-earth half of the unit; their simple-minded counterparts are the http://anidb.net/t1399 [boke] characters. As a result of their boke counterparts` simple mistakes and gross exaggerations, tsukkomi berate and abuse them both verbally and physically; a very common example of tsukkomi physical abuse is a paper fan slap, which is generally accompanied by a sound effect. Their approximate equivalent in Western culture is the comedy role of straight man.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2019" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-16">
<name>suicidal</name>
<description>The character has suicidal tendencies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3316" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>despair</name>
<description>Involves characters that may be lost in negatively emotional atmospheres created through feelings of hopelessness and suffering.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4462" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>barefoot</name>
<description>This character never seems to wear any shoes — possibly a martial artist that prefers to stay in close contact with the ground, or a girl from the country now living in the city.
Alas, under more dire circumstances this can also be a sign of real poverty.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-26">
<name>alternating animation style</name>
<description>The animation style in this show may change between scenes, usually making the anime experimental in a way. This may be a form of artistic visualisation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5769" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>panels that require pausing</name>
<description>Panels that require pausing are image or text panels that interrupt regular animation and flash by so quickly that the viewer cannot recognize the image or read the text fast enough while playing at regular speed; they require pausing the video, or at least viewing it at a lower speed. Given the short screen time these panels are given, they are usually not relevant to the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="32" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-12-28">
<rating votes="653">8.96</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Kagami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukasa`s elder twin sister. Konata`s close friend. Her thought process is normal, so she often pokes fun at Konata. She may be the most right-minded character. An aloof-chummy type, who is warm-hearted only when she has gotten to know you.</description>
<picture>18662.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="103" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-07-17">
<rating votes="1943">8.60</rating>
<name>Lelouch Lamperouge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16249.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="306" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-06-30">
<rating votes="830">6.27</rating>
<name>Louise Francoise Le Blanc de La Valliere</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Louise Françoise le Blanc de La Vallière, the heroine of the series, is a student at the Tristain Magical Academy. She earned the sobriquet Zero Louise because of her ineptness at magic, and was frequently the butt of jokes among her classmates. On the day that all students at her level were to summon their magical familiars, she performs the rite, but instead of the usual magical creatures, unexpectedly summons a Japanese teenager, http://anidb.net/ch4052 [Hiraga Saito], who, being inscribed with the runes of a familiar, reluctantly assumes that role.
[SPOILER]It turns out that her ineptitude at normal magic is because she is actually a very rare Void Mage, and normal magical training does not cover that.[/SPOILER]
She is named after Louise Françoise de la Baume le Blanc de La Vallière (1644-1710), one of the most famous Maîtresses-en-titre of Louis XIV.</description>
<picture>14583.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="337" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="938">7.91</rating>
<name>Kouzuki Kallen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kallen Stadtfeld is a Britannian-Japanese girl, who believes herself to be a Japanese person at heart and prefers to be known by her birth name, Kouzuki. Her father is Britannian and her mother is an Eleven; her father comes from a prestigious Britannian family, which Kallen benefits from. Her brother, Naoto Kouzuki, with whom she had a deep connection, was a former leader of her resistance cell before his death.
Kallen is a highly-skilled Knightmare Frame pilot, rivaling the abilities of even the Knights of the Round. She is acknowledged as the best pilot of the Black Knights by enemies and allies alike. Her codename, "Q-1," is the Queen`s starting spot in descriptive chess notation. In Lelouch`s assessment of the core members of the Black Knights, her "Combat Ability" score is 100 out of 100, matching that of Kyoshiro Tohdoh; she also has the highest possible "Loyalty" score of 100.
Even when piloting outdated Knightmare Frames such as the Glasgow, Kallen proves to be a dangerous opponent easily defeating numerous Sutherlands, despite the Sutherland being a more advanced Knightmare. With the radiation arm of her Guren Mk-II, Kallen can take down almost any Knightmare Frame in a single attack should they allow her to make physical contact, and later models also have numerous secondary attack modes for mid- and long-range combat. Her Knightmare Frame is also incredibly fast, allowing her to fight on the same level as some of the most advanced Knightmare Frames in the series.
Outside of a Knightmare, Kallen displays superior fighting abilities. She is nimble enough to swat a bee with a single swipe (and cut it in half), and on two occasions she defeats numerous armed men with little trouble. She is also apparently intelligent, since her grades in school are top of the class despite frequent absences.</description>
<picture>14626.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="470" type="cameo appearance in" update="2020-01-16">
<rating votes="1477">8.55</rating>
<name>Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl from Jeeha`s neighbouring village of Littner, who had been chasing the Gunmen which entered Jeeha village. She wields an extensive arsenal of firearms and has previous experience fighting Gunmen. She uses her marksmanship from afar to assist Kamina and Simon, while they pilot their respective Gunmen.</description>
<picture>14767.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1493" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-10-08">
<rating votes="42">8.50</rating>
<name>Lagann</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Lagann is Simon`s personal Gunmen which he finds in the first episode while digging tunnels in his village. It received its name, Lagann (羅顔), meaning "enveloping face", from Kamina and draws power from the Core Drill, a small golden drill Simon uses similar to an ignition key. Unlike any other Gunmen in the series, the Lagann sports a unique cockpit and stands just short of an average human adult as opposed to the others which are all mostly the sizes of small buildings or larger. This physical handicap, in tandem with the usually average level of fighting spirit supplied to it by Simon, puts the Lagann at a considerable disadvantage in single combat against enemy Gunmen. However, when Simon is driven to give his best during combat the Lagann`s power increases exponentially, giving it the unique ability to generate drills from nearly any part of its frame. Lagann`s other and most notable power is the "Lagann Impact", its trademark ability to combine with other machines by piercing them with its drills. It`s through this ability that the titular Gurren Lagann is created, along with the other more large-scale mechas in the series.</description>
<picture>16032.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2051" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="44">7.84</rating>
<name>Casshern</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist of the series. In this latest incarnation, he was originally a subordinate of Braiking Boss and the strongest warrior in his robot army -- with his advanced cybernetic body and quick reflexes, he had the ability to destroy any opponent he comes across, and was able to regenerate from any injuries. Casshern was ordered by Braiking Boss to assassinate Luna, however, this act triggered a cataclysmic event and he fell into a deep slumber. Upon waking hundreds of years later, he finds that the world has become a poisonous wasteland, and has no memory of who he was before his coma. When he learns that it was in fact he who caused the ruination which lead to the present Dark Ages, he is stricken with agony. He attempts to elude the many people who want him dead, as repayment for his role in the destruction of the world. He is also unable to distinguish himself as a savior or a destroyer, as his violent impulses often get in the way of his quest for good.</description>
<picture>18064.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2069" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-05-11">
<rating votes="1320">6.46</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Ichigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurosaki Ichigo was raised by his father together with his two sisters after the traumatic experience of losing his mother. One day, minding his own business, he meets Rukia, the Shinigami, who needs his help. While protecting his family they find out about his supernatural abilities and thus a still-living - substitute - Shinigami is born....</description>
<picture>136529.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2103" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="2804">8.56</rating>
<name>Son Gokuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son Gokuu is a Saiyajin warrior who was sent to Earth when he was a child.</description>
<picture>135352.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2105" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-02-25">
<rating votes="1212">8.57</rating>
<name>Vegeta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vegeta is the prince of the Saiyajin race and http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu]`s most fearsome rival. He is a very prideful person and, as a full-blooded saiyajin, loves the prospect of a good battle.</description>
<picture>230630.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2142" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="164">7.72</rating>
<name>Kirihara Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirihara Misaki is the Section-Chief of the Foreign Affairs Section 4 who is investigating matters that concern Contractors. Misaki has long brown hair and glasses and rarely smiles or laughs. She has a strong sense of justice and a sharp intuition. Kirihara became a policewoman in order to protect the weak, has a distaste for smokers due to their smell, and is sensitive about the exposure of her body. She likes eating greasy food but claims to stay fit due to constantly moving around everyday as part of her job. Her father is Superintendent Supervisor Naoyasu Kirihara of the National Police Agency.It appears that she has feelings for Hei.</description>
<picture>17000.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2402" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-24">
<rating votes="77">6.33</rating>
<name>Miyamura Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyako has an energetic personality and enjoys doing unorthodox things. Initially appears chasing after a purse thief, borrowing Hiro`s bicycle. She eventually starts to become attracted to Hiro after they start spending more time together, but during this time Hiro`s childhood friend Kei Shindo begins to feel left out and a love triangle develops between the three students.</description>
<picture>23880.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3487" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-02-18">
<rating votes="159">6.60</rating>
<name>Maka Albarn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maka is Soul`s meister. They live together in an appartment in Death City, though Maka seems to be the one doing most of the household chores such as cooking. Where Soul seems to be the brawn, Maka is the brain. She always tries to think of a way to beat their opponent by exploiting the opponent`s weaknesses. Maka and Soul make an efficient team, as shown at the start of the series when they had already claimed ninety-nine evil souls. Maka is a dedicated student at Shibusen, and scored highest of her class during doctor Stein`s test. Maka`s father is Shinigami`s current death scythe and her mother was a very powerful scythe meister. They are currently divorced. While she adores her mother, Maka`s relationship with her father is strained. She seems to hate him for constantly flirting with other women (which caused the divorce). Deep down she still loves him though.</description>
<picture>19247.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4055" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="227">6.10</rating>
<name>Siesta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A maid at the academy. Her hometown is Tarbes, Tristain and is the eldest of eight children. She loves Saito, and treats him very kindly, and is willing to do a lot of things to defeat her "rival" Louise for the love of Saito. She seems to know how Saito is treated, which could be what makes her so aggressive to take him away from Louise. She truthfully thinks to herself that she would make Saito much happier.</description>
<picture>20005.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4680" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="199">6.91</rating>
<name>Kagurazaka Asuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuna Kagurazaka`s mouth may be big, but her attitude is bigger. A quick tempered redhead with a tough exterior, Asuna`s brash personality serves her well in her constant struggles with her class rival, Ayaka. Asuna usually reserves her softer side for the unrequited longings she expresses toward Professor Takahata, her former teacher. It doesn`t sit well when the manly object of her affection is replaced with a new instructor! Little Negi Springfield. Her misfortunes seem to stack up when the kid is around, and her hostility and suspicion toward the brainy boy lead her to a startling discovery! She soon finds Negi`s destiny in her hands. Will she take the steps to make the magician to disappear?</description>
<picture>72769.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5047" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="51">9.01</rating>
<name>Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryu is a pretty simple guy. He wears the same outfit wherever he goes - white gi, black belt, red headband, period - and he has the same aim wherever he goes as well. He wants to fight whoever he thinks can make him a stronger fighter.</description>
<picture>21382.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6407" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="33">8.69</rating>
<name>Ritsuko Kubel Kettenkrad</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A half-German girl, Ritsuko is the current President of the Student Council, and a childhood friend of Chihiro. Despite their childhood promise (revealed in the anime as a promise that he will marry her if she stops "being a crybaby") and her obvious feelings for him, she works hard to hide these from him throughout the series. She wears a helmet which seems to be a mark of the office she holds. It seems she used to cry a lot, and has been working hard to stop her tears in an attempt to perhaps live up to a promise she made to Chihiro.</description>
<picture>23775.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6421" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-23">
<rating votes="42">8.07</rating>
<name>Di Gi Charat</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character of the story. She is also known as Chocola but despite this alternate name implying she likes chocolate, she prefers broccoli. Dejiko has a Type A personality and can be aggressive at times.
Dejiko dresses up as a catgirl and is the princess of Planet Di Gi Charat. She is ten years old when she comes to Earth with hopes of becoming an idol singer. She has green eyes and green hair and her maid-like uniform consists of a white and navy blue dress with big cat bells tied to her hair with navy blue ribbons. On the very top of her head are her cat ears, which are white with pink inside and have a set of large, non-functional yellow cat eyes. She always wears white gloves and boots (with the exception of her sleeping outfit) and she has a white tail.
She has the ability to use her eye-beam weapon called the Me kara BEAM!. She ends each sentence with nyo.</description>
<picture>23835.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6443" type="main character in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="792">8.94</rating>
<name>Itoshiki Nozomu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6444" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="223">7.72</rating>
<name>Fuura Kafuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6445" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="262">8.14</rating>
<name>Kitsu Chiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6446" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-06">
<rating votes="286">8.79</rating>
<name>Komori Kiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3131" picture="234931.jpg">Tanii Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6447" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="214">8.54</rating>
<name>Tsunetsuki Matoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6448" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="142">6.43</rating>
<name>Kimura Kaere</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6449" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="121">5.95</rating>
<name>Sekiutsu Maria Tarou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6450" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="113">5.73</rating>
<name>Kobushi Abiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6451" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="113">7.27</rating>
<name>Hitou Nami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6452" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="138">6.39</rating>
<name>Fujiyoshi Harumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6575" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-05-01">
<rating votes="37">5.74</rating>
<name>Luke fon Fabre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character, the only son of a noble family in the kingdom of Kimlasca-Lanvaldear. After a kidnapping incident, all of his childhood memories were erased, causing him to be very selfish and ignorant of the real world. His only hobby is swordsmanship. Luke also possesses the ability to create a "hyperresonance" on his own, an extremely powerful ability when two fonists of the same type use their abilities in tandem.
As the anime progresses, Luke learns that he is actually the "replica" (clone) of Asch, the real Luke fon Fabre. This event, along with the abandonment of his friends, prompts Luke to change himself for the better.</description>
<picture>24166.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6581" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="14">4.73</rating>
<name>Ion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the Order of Lorelei, a neutral theocracy trying to calm the power struggle between Malkuth and Kimlasca-Lanvaldear. Though he is not a playable character, he accompanies Luke`s party for most of the game. He is calm in most situations, and can utilize Daathic fonic artes, break Daathic seals, and read the Score from fonstones, all of which can easily tire him out.
Later in the story, it is revealed that he is the 7th replica of the original Ion.</description>
<picture>24172.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7056" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="291">7.85</rating>
<name>Yuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuno, sometimes called "Yunocchi" by http://anidb.net/ch7057 [Miyako], is a young girl and main character in the story. She lives in the Sunshine Apartments, along with her close friends and neighbors Miyako, http://anidb.net/ch7058 [Hiro], and http://anidb.net/ch7059 [Sae]. Her friends think of her as a very nice person. Yuno dreams of being a great artist someday. Although she is a skilled artist overall, she considers painting and drawing her specialties. She rarely takes off a pair of X-shaped black hairpins.</description>
<picture>2085.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="7057" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="488">9.07</rating>
<name>Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyako is http://anidb.net/ch7056 [Yuno]`s close friend, classmate, and next door neighbor in the apartment building where they live. Yuno refers to her as Miya-chan. She has an active personality and is always trying to have fun with her friends. Her exuberance frequently borders on the childlike, but she is undeniably creative. She is very spontaneous and claims the word "plan" does not exist in her dictionary. She loves to eat and has frequently asked for Hiro`s leftovers when she is on one of her diets. She sometimes points out that http://anidb.net/ch7058 [Hiro] may be gaining weight, which earns her a punch on the head by Hiro. Miyako`s energy is frequently excessive and misplaced. Her rent is 5,000 yen cheaper than that of the other girls because her apartment is in poor repair, which is fortunate because she has less money than the other girls most of the time.</description>
<picture>2086.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="7058" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="218">7.33</rating>
<name>Hiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiro is a year older than http://anidb.net/ch7056 [Yuno] and http://anidb.net/ch7057 [Miyako], living directly under Yuno`s apartment. Although she tries to be a supportive senpai to the girls, she tends to worry excessively about her weight, causing her to go on diets for periods while occasionally binging on sweets. A childhood friend of http://anidb.net/ch7059 [Sae], she is one of her neighbor`s principal sources of support when she is involved with a deadline or other crisis.</description>
<picture>2087.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="7059" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-06-26">
<rating votes="199">7.05</rating>
<name>Sae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sae is an upperclassman and good friends with http://anidb.net/ch7058 [Hiro]. Her artistic specialties are photography and fiction writing; she writes fiction professionally under the pseudonym "Tachibana Aya" (橘文) and enrolled at the school specifically so she could learn how to illustrate her own work. Sae, who is tall, athletic, and generally mature, has a playful side that can be at the same time enigmatic and cunning; she has a habit of giving http://anidb.net/ch7056 [Yuno] just enough warning about potential problems for the younger girl to fail to avoid them. She also has a fondness for playing detective when faced with such anomalies as http://anidb.net/ch7057 [Miyako]`s apartment. She tends to get upset when Miyako refers to her as having masculine qualities. She also gets very uncomfortable when asked about her love life, frequently inventing a history for herself that even cursory examination would show to be absurd, while blushing furiously.</description>
<picture>2088.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="7060" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="243">8.55</rating>
<name>Yoshinoya-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoshinoya is http://anidb.net/ch7056 [Yuno] and http://anidb.net/ch7057 [Miyako]`s homeroom teacher and art instructor. She is buxom, exuberant, and a cosplay maniac. So much so, in fact, that she will frequently wear incredibly complicated things that are at times truly inappropriate. She has a fondness for modeling for her class, displaying her latest outfits whenever she can, and showing off in general. Moreover, she is shown wearing a pair of squeaking sandals in the anime series. It is later revealed that Yoshinoya still resides with her parents, and would often be criticized by them for not being mature. When asked her age, she will answer "eternally seventeen".</description>
<picture>2089.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="7106" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="27">7.61</rating>
<name>Fumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fumika is the main character in the anime series. She appears to be a young girl, though her real age is never mentioned. She works as a mail carrier from the afterlife realm of Shigo, delivering what are known as "shigofumi" to people in a Japanese city that she has been assigned to. These shigofumi are letters written by those who have recently died, and it is Fumika`s job to deliver the letters to whoever the dead wanted them to go to. Though typically the shigofumi mail carriers are people who have already died, and thus do not age, Fumika is different in that she ages at the same rate as a normal person, signifying that she has not died yet but is merely in a state of astral projection.</description>
<picture>25368.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7245" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="411">7.31</rating>
<name>Inuyasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>InuYasha is a hanyou (half-demon), the product of an inu-youkai (犬妖怪, dog demon) and a human. He wields Tetsusaiga, a supernatural sword made from one of his deceased father`s fangs. When properly wielded, the sword can destroy one hundred demons with a single swing. InuYasha can quickly recover from injuries that would be fatal to a human, largely due to his demonic blood. During the first night of each lunar month (new moon), InuYasha changes into a normal human with black hair and black eyes and loses his demonic powers.
InuYasha was bound to Goshinboku by Kikyo`s arrow for fifty years until Kagome freed him. InuYasha wears a special bead necklace that forces him to respond to Kagome`s command "Osuwari!", which translates to "Sit!" in English. In the English-dubbed version, "InuYasha, sit!" or "Sit, boy!" are sometimes used instead. Following the command, InuYasha is thrown to the ground. Kaede had placed the necklace upon InuYasha because he had threatened to kill Kagome if she refused to give the Jewel of Four Souls to him. As the series goes on, he begins to like Kagome more and more, shown when he will leave a battle to save her from being hurt.</description>
<picture>36855.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7321" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="358">7.40</rating>
<name>Sailor Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154979.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7571" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="631">8.66</rating>
<name>Hei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hei is the main protagonist and an elite Contractor with the Messier Code BK-201. In his team, Hei acts as the spy and assassin, swiftly dealing death without fail. Hei`s "mundane identity" is a gentle-hearted student from China named Li Shun Sheng (李舜生 (リ・シュンシェン), Ri ShunShen), but when "working" he takes on the role of a seemingly (at first) affectless and ruthless killer nicknamed "The Black Reaper"; this alias was earned based on stories of BK-201`s accomplishments as an assassin during the war at Heaven`s Gate.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>26352.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7577" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-01-31">
<rating votes="367">8.08</rating>
<name>Yin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26364.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7811" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="93">8.97</rating>
<name>Kitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kitarou is a youkai boy born in a cemetery, and aside from his mostly-decayed father, the last living member of the Ghost Tribe (幽霊族, yuurei zoku). He is missing his left eye, but his hair usually covers the empty socket. He fights for peace between humans and youkai, which generally involves protecting the former from the wiles of the latter. When questioned in the 2007 movie, Kitarou responds that he is three hundred and fifty years old.
Kitarou has an assortment of strange weapons at his disposal, including:
* * remote-controlled geta sandals

* * a detachable hand, also remote-controlled

* * a magic chanchanko vest which can protect its wearer from danger; it occasionally seems to act of its own accord, wrapping around enemies or aiding friends, even when Kitaro is not available to command it

* * spiny hairs which can be shot like arrows

* * another hair which can serve as an antenna for detecting spirit activity

* * a magical ocarina (usually used for calling Ittan Momen), which contains a baton, a whip and occasionally music which has the power to damage certain ghosts.

* * the power of electrocution, usually employed when an enemy has pinned or restrained him and he can no longer kick or use other weapons

</description>
<picture>26842.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7812" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Medama-oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Medama-oyaji is Kitarou`s father. Once a fully-formed adult ghost, he perished of a disease, only to be reborn out of his decayed body as an anthropomorphic version of his own eyeball. He looks small and fragile, but has a strong spirit and a great love for his son. He is also extremely knowledgeable about ghosts and monsters. He enjoys staying clean, and is often seen bathing in a small bowl. He has a great love for sake.</description>
<picture>26843.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9099" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-01-14">
<rating votes="550">8.23</rating>
<name>Lum</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lum (also referred to in some Western versions as Lamu - since her name in Japanese is technically pronounced "Ramu") is the second main protagonist of the series. She is a beautiful Oni alien who is capable of flying and generating electrical shocks and even lightning. She is extremely popular and is famous for ending her sentences with ~daccha (loosely translated as "yes?" or "you know?"). Except when in her school girl`s uniform, she usually wears a sexy outfit consisting of a tiger-striped bikini and knee-high go-go boots. While generally good-natured, sweet, faithful, and innocent, Lum also has a very hot temper and she is extremely jealous. Her dream in life is to live in a "Sweet Home with Darling" in which she keeps house and raises babies while Ataru, her "Darling," works a job. Unfortunately, Lum`s idea of "cooking" is to take very spicy ingredients like jalapenos, cayenne peppers and Tabasco sauce and irradiate them with an alien energy bazooka until they carbonize into inedible, crystallized nuggets. As an alien she has access to many bizarre gadgets whose use she really doesn`t understand all that well, leading to comic results. Differences between human and "Invader" physiology also drive many stories, like the time Lum`s horns begin to grow larger after she is bitten by a cow, or the time she becomes drunk by eating pickled plums.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28639.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10029" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="28">6.48</rating>
<name>Kaonashi</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>No Face (lit. "without face"), an odd spirit who takes an interest in Chihiro. Seeing No Face standing outside in the rain, Chihiro takes pity on the creature and lets him into the bathhouse to take shelter from the storm. At first, he is a strange, cloaked, masked wraith that merely breathes and smiles. No Face is a lonely being who seems to sustain itself on the emotions of those he encounters, particularly their emotional reception to his gifts. He is helpful to Chihiro because she helped him, whereas after observing the bathhouse staff`s reaction to gold and his own attempts to win them over with more gold, he reacts to their greed by becoming a grotesque monster which eats lots of food and some of the staff. After Chihiro feeds him the final piece of the medicine ball given to her by the River Spirit, No Face regurgitates everything he consumed, including the bathhouse staff members, all of whom are alive and well. Once he has emptied himself of these foreign influences and left the bathhouse, No Face reverts to his former state. At the end, he stays with Zeniba as a helper.</description>
<picture>30234.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11290" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="8">9.06</rating>
<name>Kanaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The artificial intelligence staff that Fumika carries is named Kanaka. The function of the staff is meant to aid the shigofumi mail carrier by keeping track of senders, receivers, the delivery area, and supplementing other usual tasks. The mail carrier can give the staff a numeral code pertaining to a program which can be activated and aid the mail carrier further, such as turning them invisible, or supplementing white wings on their back to enable them to fly, though there are time limits on these programs. The staffs carry their own personalities and have the ability to levitate. In the anime, Fumika`s staff Kanaka has a female voice and a loud, boisterous personality which directly contrasts Fumika`s otherwise placid disposition. Kanaka often gives Fumika her opinion on matters pertaining to who she is delivering letter to, though Fumika just goes along her business as usual either way. Despite technically not being alive, Kanaka still insists that "she" be referred to as a person, or in terms of what a person would do, such as while levitating or regenerating which she calls "standing" and "sleeping" respectively. Kanaka is prone to making mistakes while on the job, such as misplacing letters.</description>
<picture>42529.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11414" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="230">7.05</rating>
<name>Kuririn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuririn is introduced in Dragon Ball as a rival of the main character, http://anidb.net/ch2116 [Son Gokuu]. Later in the series, he develops a close relationship with him as well as his son, http://anidb.net/ch11419 [Gohan].</description>
<picture>66653.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12049" type="appears in" update="2009-10-01">
<rating votes="108">8.35</rating>
<name>Itoshiki Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13125" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="107">3.95</rating>
<name>Otonashi Meru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very shy girl who does not talk and only communicates via text messaging on her cell phone; she is notably and viciously abusive in her e-mails. Her family name, Otonashi, means "soundless", and her given name derives from the loan word "mail". Her e-mail address is "hazukashigariyasan", which means "full of shyness". She is called "MeruMeru" by her father. Aside from a few weak sounds and squeaks, she is essentially mute, and any attempt to speak will cause her to uncontrollably sputter in a horrific language. Her family also seems ridiculously rich, as her father is able to set up an audition for people to try and dub her voice in real time.
In the anime, her voice actress changes every episode and is chosen at random, and is credited with, at most, a short sequence of nonsense characters.</description>
<picture>38987.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13126" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="38">4.63</rating>
<name>Kudou Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13127" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="31">3.50</rating>
<name>Usui Kagerou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17812" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13129" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="10">2.86</rating>
<name>Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38991.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13673" type="appears in" update="2009-12-09">
<rating votes="18">4.09</rating>
<name>Mitama Mayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An evil-looking girl who compulsively commits malicious acts. Not wanting to be accused of reacting to stereotypes, people simply assume she is a good girl who only looks evil and whatever she did was not her doing. Just as most girls in the class, she has developed a crush on Nozomu, but can only express her love through harming him. Maria made the comment of her being a tsundere. Her name derives from mita mama yo (見たままよ), which means "What she is is exactly what she looks."</description>
<picture>40022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3131" picture="234931.jpg">Tanii Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13675" type="appears in" update="2009-12-09">
<rating votes="51">6.57</rating>
<name>Kaga Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A shy, insecure girl who constantly apologizes for trivial matters and things she didn`t even do. Her name in Eastern order sounds like kagai ("perpetrate"), and is most likely borrowed from former Morning Musume member Ai Kago.</description>
<picture>40028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13676" type="appears in" update="2009-12-09">
<rating votes="28">5.91</rating>
<name>Ookusa Manami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A married high-schooler who works multiple jobs to pay off her husband`s debts. Her name derives from okusama-nami ("a married person") It is revealed in episode 5 of Zan that her husband is unfaithful and she`s aware of it.</description>
<picture>40029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13767" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="69">7.95</rating>
<name>Chun-Li</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40630.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13841" type="appears in" update="2009-12-31">
<rating votes="1">5.80</rating>
<name>Ikkyuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The self-proclaimed "old friend" of Itoshiki Nozomu, who, like Nozomu, likes old things. It is later found out that they weren`t old friends (旧友) but rather "one day friends" (1日友) in elementary school. His name is a reference to the anime series Ikkyuu-san. He attempted to marry Rin, thus gaining an "old name" and becoming a member of an "old family", but Kafuka thwarted him in his advances.</description>
<picture>40805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13843" type="appears in" update="2009-12-31">
<rating votes="44">2.90</rating>
<name>Itoshiki Majiru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nozomu`s nephew, the son of Enishi. He was sent to live with Nozomu when his parents abandoned him. Although he is rather arrogant for his age, he is quite vulnerable to the psychological trauma caused by Nozomu`s students. His name becomes zekkou (絶交, "breach in a relationship") when compressed. It is hinted he has feelings for Nozomu`s student Kiri Komori but so seems to hide this and refer to her as big sister.</description>
<picture>40807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13844" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="9">5.99</rating>
<name>Kino Kuniya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Described in episode 10 of the second season as "Library committee member, hates losing. Supposed to appear as a rival character to Kudou Jun, but his strange clothes and interest in Kaga Ai are now his most notable traits." His fashion sense is terrible; a scene in the manga showed strange underwear hanging from his balcony. His name comes from the Books Kinokuniya chain.</description>
<picture>40808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13863" type="appears in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="4">4.35</rating>
<name>Koutei Penguin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40881.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14794" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="12">7.67</rating>
<name>Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiaki is Fumika`s coworker and superior, though unlike Fumika, Chiaki has already died. Chiaki died due to a car accident and thus retains the appearance of how she looked before she died, which happens to be very similar to Fumika, though Chiaki does not age. She says she is "over twenty-one-years-old" (and admits in that she died over `fifty years ago`), however looks roughly as old as Fumika is. She is assigned a different city in Japan than Fumika, and the two rarely ever meet on Earth, but do see each other more often when in Shigo. Chiaki has a bright personality and likes to express her emotions outwardly, whether they be related to frustration, or happiness. As observed by Fumika, Chiaki usually is not as diligent about her job as Fumika is, and if a delivery is too much of a pain, she will generally drop it, marking the letter with an invalid addressee.</description>
<picture>42533.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14795" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="4">7.82</rating>
<name>Matoma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matoma is the staff that Chiaki carries and like Fumika`s staff, helps her with her job. Matoma has a male voice and speaks in a monotonic tone. He is better at the job than Kanaka is and talks down to Kanaka for doing a poor job. Kanaka in turn needles Matoma by mocking him by twisting his name as in calling him `Tomato Juice`.</description>
<picture>42534.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29081" type="appears in" update="2017-10-23">
<rating votes="3">5.16</rating>
<name>Maedax G</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23822" picture="66280.jpg">Maeda-kun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30885" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="73">6.82</rating>
<name>Pegasus no Seiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73090.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="33064" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-06-05">
<rating votes="13">5.85</rating>
<name>Kodama</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kodama means "echo" (its literal meaning is a "tree spirit"). However, since its name is written in Katakana, not in Kanji, it could also mean "small ball" or "small spirit". They (there are many, in various sizes and shapes) are a kind of spirit who live in the forest. Although Kodama (a tree spirit) appears in many Japanese folktales, Kodama as a little white creature is Miyazaki`s creation.</description>
<picture>72863.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="33068" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-10-20">
<rating votes="8">6.73</rating>
<name>Rockman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178660.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="33078" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-06-05">
<rating votes="2">6.58</rating>
<name>Isozaki Ran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isozaki Ran is the protagonist in the story, she is introduced as a vivacious young lady having recently begun her first year in intermediate school where she engages in track and field as an extracurricular activity. Ran has always had a sense of insight about things that few other people can match. Ran is part of a traditional nuclear family (biological parents still married to each other) with an elder brother. She is in love with Rui.</description>
<picture>4260.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="33085" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Michael Jackson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72872.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="93694" update="2009-05-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あまい姫 / 発禁抄 / 原型の盾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sweet Princess / Banned Notes / Prototype Shield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amai Hime / Hakkinshou / Genkei no Tate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95845" update="2009-05-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">曰く, 過程の幸福は諸悪の本 / 予言省告示 / バラバラの名前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Say That the Pursuit of Happiness from a Process Is the Origin of Crime / A Notice from Ministry of Prediction / Names Ripped in Pieces</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iwaku, Katei no Koufuku wa Shoaku no Moto / Yogen Shou Kokuji / Barabara no Namae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95853" update="2009-05-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗中問答 / 負けたの草子 / 一本昔ばなし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mondou in the Dark / Storybook of Failure / A Book of Folktales</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anchuu Mondou / Maketa no Soushi / Ippon Mukashibanashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97320" update="2009-03-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111708" update="2009-11-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111709" update="2009-11-27">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111710" update="2009-11-27">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111711" update="2009-11-27">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
