<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6037" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>5</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-11</startdate>
<enddate>2008-10-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Genius Party Beyond</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Genius Party 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ジーニアスパーティービヨンド</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Genius Party Beyond</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Genialaus vakarėlio tęsinys</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6064" type="Same Setting">Fluximation</anime>
<anime id="2972" type="Other">Genius Party</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="713" approval="17" total="19">Manie-Manie: Meikyuu Monogatari</anime>
<anime id="5211" approval="5" total="5">Ani*Kuri15</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.genius-party.jp/beyond/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1522" type="Direction">Nakazawa Kazuto</name>
<name id="276" type="Direction">Morimoto Kouji</name>
<name id="10917" type="Direction">Tanaka Tatsuyuki</name>
<name id="1462" type="Direction">Maeda Mahiro</name>
<name id="20081" type="Music">Ifukube Akira</name>
<name id="5376" type="Character Design">Oohira Shin`ya</name>
<name id="1462" type="Character Design">Maeda Mahiro</name>
<name id="10917" type="Character Design">Tanaka Tatsuyuki</name>
<name id="1522" type="Character Design">Nakazawa Kazuto</name>
<name id="31510" type="Music">Juno Reactor</name>
<name id="738" type="Work">Studio 4C</name>
<name id="5376" type="Direction">Oohira Shin`ya</name>
<name id="21227" type="Music">Nozaki Minami</name>
<name id="276" type="Character Design">Morimoto Kouji</name>
<name id="21240" type="Music">Warsaw Village Band</name>
</creators>
<description>Five stories, five maestros, five styles and one common denominator: maximum creativity. Studio 4°C, the coolest label on the planet, invites us for the second time to an exclusive reunion of a talents with a group film, full of freedom and ingenuity, that goes from Mahiro Maeda`s classic anime, to Kazuto Nakazawa`s intricate urban sketches, Shinya Ohira`s bedlam of colour and Tatsuyuki Tanaka`s animated cyberpunk. And as if that wasn`t enough, Koji Morimoto, the studio big boss, is charge of putting the icing on the cake with fantafabulous piece of abstract poetry that would make a VJ die of ecstasy. The party of the year.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="799">6.76</permanent>
<temporary count="802">7.11</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>50439.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5010</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5842</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5846</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>7887</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5843</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5839</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6795</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.studio4c.co.jp/works/pages/26.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://studio4c.co.jp/works/en/pages/26.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Genius_Party#Genius_Party_Beyond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ジーニアス・パーティ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331465</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10475</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4552" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>superflat</name>
<description>Superflat is a postmodern art movement, founded by the artist Takashi Murakami, which is influenced by manga and anime. The term is used to refer to various flattened forms in Japanese graphic art, animation, pop culture and fine arts, as well as the "shallow emptiness of Japanese consumer culture". As self-proclaimed art movement, it was a successful piece of niche marketing, a branded art phenomenon designed for Western audiences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5257" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>psychedelic</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6093" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>short story collection</name>
<description>An anthology is a collection of literary works chosen by the compiler. It may be a collection of poems, short stories, plays, songs, or excerpts by different authors.
An omnibus format release is not just one continuous story, but several short stories. They may feature a different cast between each story, and the authors may differ.
In genre fiction, anthology is used to categorize collections of shorter works such as short stories and short novels, by different authors, each featuring unrelated casts of characters and settings, and usually collected into a single volume for publication. The complete collections of works are often called complete works or Opera Omnia (Latin language equivalent).
Source: EN Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="102688" update="2009-05-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2008-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Credits</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102689" update="2011-08-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2008-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="26">8.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">次元爆弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dimension Bomb</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigen Bakudan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102690" update="2011-08-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">GALA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gala</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gala</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102691" update="2011-08-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="25">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MOONDRIVE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moondrive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moondrive</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102692" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陶人キット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toujin Kit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toujin Kit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102693" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="24">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わんわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wanwa the Doggy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wanwa</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
