<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6055" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-08</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Stitch!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スティッチ!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7079" type="Sequel">Stitch! Itazura Alien no Daibouken</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3207" approval="1" total="4">Demashita! Powerpuff Girls Z</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.disneychannel.jp/dc/program/anime/stitch/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4245" type="Series Composition">Yonemura Shouji</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="1865" type="Character Design">Kanemori Yoshinori</name>
<name id="4880" type="Direction">Hata Masami</name>
<name id="5071" type="Series Composition">Kakihara Yuuko</name>
<name id="18197" type="Character Design">Shimizu Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="56909" type="Music">Suzuki Yoshihisa</name>
</creators>
<description>Stitch! is a new anime project from Walt Disney Animation Studios. It is an adapted version of the US animated feature film Lilo &amp; Stitch and the subsequent spin-off series. It takes place in the future after the film and started in Japan in October 2008. The show features a Japanese girl named Yuna in place of Lilo, and is set on a fictional island off the shore of Okinawa instead of Hawaii.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="90">2.96</permanent>
<temporary count="91">4.95</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>13211.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10252</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8963</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5027</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4596</identifier>
<identifier>xgqnhm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/stitch/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Stitch!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スティッチ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1505</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331384</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10420</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2681" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Okinawa</name>
<description>Okinawa Prefecture is the southernmost prefecture of Japan. It encompasses two thirds of the Ryukyu Islands in a chain over 1,000 kilometreslong. The Ryukyu Islands extend southwest from Kyushu (the southwesternmost of Japan`s four main islands) to Taiwan. Naha, Okinawa`s capital, is located in the southern part of Okinawa Island.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214299.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3714" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-10-21">
<name>Western animated cartoon</name>
<description>An anime series which originally started as a Western/American cartoon series or movie, but was later changed/adapted and remade specifically for the Japanese audience, and done through local anime studios within Japan.
See also: http://anidb.net/t4424 [American derived]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4148" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-11">
<name>late for school</name>
<description>A common device for a series opening or Establishing Character Moment. Things begin in a frantic rush which usually results in taking short cuts, such as eating breakfast on the run. The classic image is of someone running down the street with a slice of toast hanging out of their mouth, dragging their backpack with one hand while trying to put on their jacket or sweater one-handed with the other, bumping into important people in a manner that gets the plot started.
Basically, they`re never on time for school. While some are Heavy Sleepers, it would appear that they may have simply set their alarm clocks so as to give them insufficient time to get to class. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>161002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18272" type="main character in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Stitch</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stitch, an alien from outer space, one day ends up falling to an island located on Earth, called Izayoi. He discovers "The Spiritual Stone" on Okinawa and learns it can grant his wish of becoming the strongest in the universe...provided he does enough good deeds.</description>
<picture>36431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18273" type="main character in" update="2015-05-22">
<name>Uehara Yuuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuna is a young 9-year old 4th grader, elementary-school student who lives on a fictional island off the shore of Okinawa called Izayoi. Living on Izayoi, she learned and studies karate, living a rather normal life, but having to deal with minor problems living with her grandmother, Obaa. However, one day she meets a strange creature that has come from the depths of space, Stitch.</description>
<picture>173710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3794" picture="38865.jpg">Kumai Motoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75342" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-21">
<name>Piko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6925" picture="201846.jpg">Itou Miyako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="92584" update="2008-08-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92920" update="2008-09-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93724" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イチャリバチョーデー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ichariba Choodee (If We`ve Met Before, Then We`re Family)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93725" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イイコトカウンター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Good Deed Counter</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93726" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キジムナー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kijimuna (The Legendary Spirit)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95180" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ペイント妖怪むうん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Painting Monster, Muun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95181" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の電気ビリビリ・エイリアン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mysterious Lightning Biribiri Alien</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95182" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すきすき! エンジェル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lovely! Angel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95183" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スティッチ, ママになる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stitch Becomes a Mama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95184" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スティッチがいっぱい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stitch Lost!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95708" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お掃除エイリアン・フィリックス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cleaning Alien Felix</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95709" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワラッチがやってきた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go Warachi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96262" update="2009-01-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パイナップル工場は大パニック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Panic in the Pineapple Plant</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96516" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キツネ少女 ドローレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fox Girl Dolores</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97445" update="2009-03-18">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">眠れる森のエンジェル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sleeping Angel of the Forest</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97446" update="2009-10-25">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! スティッチ vs.ハムスターヴィール パート1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown! Stitch vs. Hamsterviel (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Stitch vs. Hamsterviel Part 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104004" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スティッチとサンタさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stitch &amp; Santa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104005" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにぎりルーベン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Riceball Rueben</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104006" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">火の玉ぼうや ダマッチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hinotama Boy Spirit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104007" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スティッチ, グータラになる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stitch Getting Lazy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104008" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スティッチ, アイドルデビュー?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stitch, Idol Debut?!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104009" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スティッチのうたじまん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stitch`s Singing Pride</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104010" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スティッチの暴走列車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stitch`s Rampage Express</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104011" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">教えて ジャンバ先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teachings from Jumba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104012" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スティッチのサプライズパーティー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stitch`s Surprise Party</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104013" update="2009-06-10">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キジムナー探検隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kijimuna Explorers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110895" update="2009-10-25">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! スティッチ vs. ハムスターヴィール パート2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown! Stitch vs. Hamsterviel (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Stitch vs. Hamsterviel Part 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110896" update="2009-10-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピーコからの挑戦状</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge from Piko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Piko Kara no Chousenjou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
