<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6064" restricted="false">
<type>Music Video</type>
<episodecount>14</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-09-20</startdate>
<enddate>2005-09-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fluximation</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Fluximation</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6037" type="Same Setting">Genius Party Beyond</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4887" approval="3" total="3">Global Astroliner Gou</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="271983">Nice, surreal, short pieces of animation.

If you want more of similar watch Dimension Bomb (from Genius Party Beyond) and Global Astroliner Gou.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://studio4c.co.jp/works/pages/19.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="738" type="Animation Production">Studio 4C</name>
<name id="276" type="Direction">Morimoto Kouji</name>
<name id="276" type="Chief Direction">Morimoto Kouji</name>
<name id="1522" type="Direction">Nakazawa Kazuto</name>
<name id="3670" type="Direction">Kitakubo Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="10921" type="Direction">Kanai Jirou</name>
<name id="9508" type="Direction">Fukushima Atsuko</name>
<name id="10917" type="Direction">Tanaka Tatsuyuki</name>
<name id="8475" type="Direction">Nakayama Daisuke</name>
<name id="7583" type="Direction">Ashino Yoshiharu</name>
<name id="8033" type="Direction">Nimura Hideki</name>
<name id="8630" type="Direction">Aoki Yasuhiro</name>
</creators>
<description>14 short music videos for Utada Hikaru`s album "Exodus".
Directed by http://anidb.net/cr276 [Morimoto Kouji], Kazuto Nakazawa, Hideki Himura, Hiroyuki Kitakubo, Jiro Kanai, Yoshiharu Ashino, Yasuhiro Aoki, Atsuko Fukushima, http://anidb.net/cr10917 [Tanaka Tatsuyuki], Daisuke Nakayama.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="273">5.36</permanent>
<temporary count="273">6.15</temporary>
<review count="1">8.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>9835.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5016</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://studio4c.co.jp/works/pages/19.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://studio4c.co.jp/works/en/pages/19.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="92126" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92127" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Devil Inside</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92128" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Exodus `04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92129" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">The Workout</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92130" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Easy Breezy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92131" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Tippy Toe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92132" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Hotel Lobby</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92133" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Animato</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92134" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Crossover Interlude</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92135" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Kremlin Dusk</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92136" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">You Make Me Want To Be A Man</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92137" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Wonder `bout</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92138" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Let Me Give You My Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92139" update="2008-07-27">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">About Me</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
