<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6073" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-12</startdate>
<enddate>2008-12-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Junjou Romantica 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Чистая романтика 2</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Чиста Романтика 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">纯情罗曼史2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">純情ロマンチカ2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Junjo Romantica 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9130" type="Sequel">Junjou Romantica (2012)</anime>
<anime id="10759" type="Sequel">Junjou Romantica 3</anime>
<anime id="5532" type="Prequel">Junjou Romantica</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8113" approval="44" total="44">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi TV</anime>
<anime id="8567" approval="8" total="9">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi 2</anime>
<anime id="10049" approval="2" total="2">Hybrid Child</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="322738">OK the yaoi is a bit uncomfortable to watch sometimes ... but the voices and the characters are so well developed this is a favorite of favorites.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://suzukisan.info/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="1482" type="Direction">Kon Chiaki</name>
<name id="10226" type="Original Work">Nakamura Shungiku</name>
<name id="4302" type="Series Composition">Nakase Rika</name>
<name id="5896" type="Music">Moka</name>
<name id="16961" type="Character Design">Kikuchi Youko</name>
</creators>
<description>The return of romance, drama, and pure-hearted romance. Junjou Romantica 2 (the sequel). Back to the beloved couples, and their perils in their forbidden relationships. Misaki Takahashi, from the main couple, thought that one Usami was a handful, until he meets another. Their relationship starts to fall down hill once again, but as always they find a way to make steamy love in the end. As for the other couples, ups and downs, lefts and rights occur, but all ends in sweet lovely bliss. Misaki and the Usami crisis, Hiroki with his pride, Shinobu with his age difference with his lover, Nowaki`s patience and love, Miyagi`s past-love and his present love, and Usagi-san and his family, these couples really got a lot of love and problems in their pure-hearted, forbidden romance.
With the return of love, drama, and pure-hearted romance, we return to the troubled couples, focusing on the parallels between each of their relationships. Misaki Takahashi thought that Haruhiko Usami was a handful, until a new love interest appears. This causes their relationship to once again head downhill, each hoping to find a way to reconcile in the end. For the other couples, episodes focus on Hiroki`s problems with his pride, Shinobu`s age difference from his lover, Nowaki`s patience and love, Miyagi`s past and present love, plus Usagi-san and his family issues. This all adds up to each of the couples having a lot of problems to overcome in their pure-hearted, forbidden love lives.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="809">7.32</permanent>
<temporary count="832">7.85</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>9889.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10183</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4814</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4359</identifier>
<identifier>cgfbhw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://suzukisan.info/romantica/index2.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://romantica.rightstuf.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Junjo_Romantica:_Pure_Romance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>純情ロマンチカ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1482</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331404</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10383</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2787" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-28">
<name>teacher x student</name>
<description>Suggests a relationship involving a teacher and their student, often times sexual in nature.</description>
<picurl>206646.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5794" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-01">
<name>forbidden love</name>
<description>This anime contains characters pursuing a romantic interest that their parents, grandparents, the police, the fire department, the neighbourhood watch association and local politicians do not approve of.
Potential relationships defined as such may be ones that are incestuous, violations of caste systems, or socially unsanctioned.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5804" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-19">
<name>piledriver</name>
<description>As you can see, the characters shirts were torn from a fight as they were previously wrestling. They seem to wrestle a lot in the show and most of the time you just see them doing the choke hold wrong and giving each other piledrivers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9518" type="main character in" update="2016-02-07">
<rating votes="51">3.89</rating>
<name>Takahashi Misaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9519" type="main character in" update="2009-06-17">
<rating votes="68">4.69</rating>
<name>Usami Akihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="5104" picture="29292.jpg">Hanada Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9520" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-17">
<rating votes="3">1.76</rating>
<name>Usami Haruhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9521" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-31">
<rating votes="5">7.28</rating>
<name>Aikawa Eri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="337" picture="223875.jpg">Namiki Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9523" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-17">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Asahina Kaoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9524" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-31">
<rating votes="4">1.87</rating>
<name>Sumi Keiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9525" type="appears in" update="2009-06-17">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Tanaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29104.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9543" type="appears in" update="2009-06-17">
<rating votes="27">5.74</rating>
<name>Kamijou Hiroki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29137.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9544" type="appears in" update="2009-06-17">
<rating votes="19">3.73</rating>
<name>Kusama Nowaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9545" type="appears in" update="2009-06-17">
<rating votes="18">6.98</rating>
<name>Miyagi You</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29139.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9546" type="appears in" update="2009-06-17">
<name>Tsumori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9582" type="appears in" update="2016-01-31">
<rating votes="19">4.99</rating>
<name>Takatsuki Shinobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A law student at a national university in Tokyo. He`s dating his sister`s ex-husband, who is 17 years older than him.</description>
<picture>29212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9584" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Usami Fuyuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9618" type="appears in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="5">6.21</rating>
<name>Takatsuki Risako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9645" type="appears in" update="2015-07-31">
<rating votes="5">8.12</rating>
<name>Usami Kaoruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29550" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="6">4.01</rating>
<name>Isaka Ryuuichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isaka Ryuuichirou is the senior managing director of Marukawa Publishing. He is acquainted with Sekaiichi Hatsukoi`s Ritsu`s parents and is a childhood friend of Junjou Romantica`s Haruhiko. He is 32 years old in the main time line. Isaka aspired to be a novelist, but his real talents lay in finding future best-sellers.
He appears in both Sekaiichi Hatsukoi and Junjou Romantica and is together with his assistant Asahina the main character of the short comics released with the Junjou Romantica DVDs, Junjou Mistake. Junjou Mistake takes place ten years before the main Romantica storyline.</description>
<picture>74519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="93504" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一度あることは二度ある</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Happens Once Will Happen Twice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichido Aru Koto wa Nido Aru</title>
<summary>Akihiko hates company parties and when he refuses to attend one thrown in his honor, Isaki doesn`t hold back on the dirty tricks. He tricks Misaki into going in order to get Akihiko to go. On the way to the party, Misaki ends up helping a man who seems ra
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725005</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93659" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">二度あることは三度ある</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Happens Twice Will Happen Thrice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nido Aru Koto wa Sando Aru</title>
<summary>When Haruhiko sends Misaki flowers, Akihiko starts getting jealous because Misaki refuses to say he loves him. Then, when Isaki pressures Misaki to stay away from Akihiko in order to protect his public image, Misaki himself starts to question their relati
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725007</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93660" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三度目の正直</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Third Time`s the Charm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sandome no Shoujiki</title>
<summary>With gifts arriving from Haruhiko daily, Masaki attempts to ask him to stop but Haruhiko doesn`t seem to be listening. Instead, he whisks Masaki away to the massive family mansion - an absolute lap of luxury. When Haruhiko offers to allow Masaki to live i
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725009</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94804" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">口は災いの元</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Casual Words Can Invite Terrible Misfortune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuchi wa Wazawai no Moto</title>
<summary>Feeling insecure about their relationship and looking for some way to connect, Nowaki asks Hiroki if he can call him the same friendly nickname everyone else does. When Hiroki flat out refuses, Nowaki`s feelings are hurt. Can he find some other way to bri
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725011</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94808" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘘から出た実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Many a True Word Is Spoken...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uso kara Deta Makoto</title>
<summary>Needing a little space, Misaki wants to hang out with his friend Sumi from school, but Akihiko is dead set against it. Is this unreasonable jealousy on Akihiko`s part or does Sumi really have more on his mind that just friendship with Masaki?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725013</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95098" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">百聞は一見に如かず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Picture Is Worth a Thousand Words</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyakubun wa Ikken ni Shikazu</title>
<summary>When Hiroki discovers Nowaki and Tsumori in a compromising position, he`s not sure what to think. Nowaki tries to explain, but Tsumori doesn`t seem to want to help clear up the matter. When Tsumori casually mentions that Nowaki is thinking of moving out,
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725015</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95188" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月に叢雲花に風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Into Each Life Some Rain Must Fall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki ni Murakumo Hana ni Kaze</title>
<summary>Akihiko has been acting very strangely lately - even going so far as to suggest that Misaki move out. When Misaki has a bit of déjà vu helping a lost old man at the train station, he discovers he`s not the only one having relationship problems. Could the
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725017</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95189" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋は思案の外</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Is Irrational</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi wa Shian no Hoka</title>
<summary>Shinobu`s sudden disappearance from Miyagi`s life has left him utterly confused. Why has he stopped coming around? It`s a single picture that holds the clues to everything, but can Miyagi come to terms with his past in order to move on?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725019</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95516" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一難去ってまた一難</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If It`s Not One Thing It`s Another</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichinan Satte Mata Ichinan</title>
<summary>Desperate to get Akihiko`s latest work completed, Aikawa begs Misaki to teach him what a "real date" is like for a college student. The date gets much more complicated when a present from Akihiko`s father for Misaki arrives and it puts Akihiko in a bad mo
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725021</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95627" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">縁は異なもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marriages Are Made in Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">En wa I na Mono</title>
<summary>Right after the TV reports that Haruhiko is getting married, his fiancé turns up on Akihiko`s doorstep, begging him to marry her instead! As if things weren`t complicated enough, Akihiko also turns up and it seems that it`s an arranged marriage and he doe
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725023</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95688" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">其の罪を憎んで其の人を憎まず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hate the Sin, Not the Sinner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Tsumi o Nikunde Sono Hito o Nikumazu</title>
<summary>A call for a family meeting seems to annoy Akihiko, but despite his numerous attempts to get out of it, he winds up going. Afterwards, Misaki and Akihiko head to a hot springs for a little relaxation, but wind up meeting up with Akihiko`s father instead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725025</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95904" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わり良ければ全て良し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All`s Well That Ends Well</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owari Yokereba Subete Yoshi</title>
<summary>Akihiko and Misaki head to the publisher to deliver Akihiko`s latest manuscript. When the two are pulled apart by business, Misaki is cornered by Haruhiko who is still determined to claim Misaki as his own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725027</identifier>
<identifier>junjo-romantica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172947" update="2015-10-29">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172948" update="2015-10-29">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
