<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="608" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-05-31</startdate>
<enddate>2002-11-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dorei Ichiba</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Slave Bazaar</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">奴隸市場</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">奴隷市場</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Slave Market</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Slave Bianca</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Annus Fabulosus - Le marché aux désirs !...</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4077" approval="1" total="3">Shojo Auction</anime>
<anime id="5541" approval="0" total="2">Soukou Kijo Iris</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.seddnet.com/products/dorei.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="776" type="Unknown Relation">Discovery</name>
<name id="1316" type="Original Work">Ruf</name>
<name id="6312" type="Music">Sano Hiroaki</name>
<name id="9967" type="Music">Nishizawa Takeshi</name>
<name id="19599" type="Character Design">Takizawa Jun</name>
<name id="19599" type="Direction">Takizawa Jun</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the game by http://anidb.net/cr1316 [ruf].
Looking for some flesh? Then you`ve come to the right place! Welcome to the slave market, where all of your perverted fantasies can be fulfilled... for a price!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="470">4.34</permanent>
<temporary count="478">6.30</temporary>
<review count="1">6.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>138282.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5387</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3385</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.seddnet.com/products/dorei.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1127</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2708" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>uncensored version available</name>
<description>There`s an uncensored version available of the porn anime this tag is added to, which in most cases means, that there was a region 1 DVD (R1 DVD = North America) release.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2711" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>urination</name>
<description>Urination, also known as micturition, voiding, peeing, weeing, pissing, and more rarely, emiction, is the ejection of urine from the urinary bladder through the urethra to the outside of the body. In healthy humans the process of urination is under voluntary control. In infants, some elderly individuals, and those with neurological injury or extreme psychological problems, urination may occur as an involuntary reflex. In other animals, in addition to expelling waste material, urination can mark territory or express submissiveness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2903" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-21">
<name>scat</name>
<description>Coprophilia, also called scatophilia or scat, is a sexual fetish involving feces. This anime depicts defecation in the context of said fetish, be it as minor as a burst of brown liquid caused by an enema or as major as actual ingestion of pieces of excrement.
Scatophilia is a fairly common motif in Japanese animated pornography, and has even spawned a fairly successful meme inside the fandom, in which http://anidb.net/a735 [Yakin Byoutou] (more commonly known in the western world as Night Shift Nurses) character http://anidb.net/ch28915 [Nanase Ren] appears on screen with the superimposed line: "how can you say you love her if you can`t even eat her poop?"
Because, really, how can you? How dare you?</description>
<picurl>126784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2905" parentid="2729" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-14">
<name>erotic torture</name>
<description>Erotic torture involves deliberately using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure. Examples include, among others, hot wax on skin, nipple clamps, electricity, extreme verbal and derogatory abuse, forced public exhibition, etc.
This is distinct from the common, non-erotic http://anidb.net/t6730 [torture], which is generally for the purpose of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or to apply coercion to compel action from the victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7221" parentid="7220" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>psychological sexual abuse</name>
<description>Psychological sexual abuse is the exercise of sexual coercion through non-physical means, such as verbal sexual behaviour, stalking, and emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7359" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-18">
<name>mansion</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7402" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>corrupt nobility</name>
<description>The nobility is characterized by decadence, sadism, and contempt towards the baseborn.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="55858" type="main character in" update="2013-05-16">
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<name>Myia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37225">Fujishiro Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55859" type="main character in" update="2013-05-16">
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<name>Bianca</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12970" picture="55683.jpg">Konoha Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55860" type="main character in" update="2020-03-13">
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<name>Cecilia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1804" picture="188441.jpg">Hokuto Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107895" type="main character in" update="2020-01-08">
<name>Cassius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242892.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107900" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Falco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242913.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108672" type="appears in" update="2020-03-12">
<name>Bytone</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35889" picture="150067.jpg">Jafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108673" type="appears in" update="2020-03-12">
<name>Sirene</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37225">Fujishiro Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108674" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-12">
<name>Ruka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37223" picture="24412.jpg">Haruno Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108675" type="appears in" update="2020-03-12">
<name>Doracus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244944.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108676" type="appears in" update="2020-03-12">
<name>Bougette of Savoia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244945.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6740" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2002-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Bianca</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bianca</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bianca</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15295" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2002-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cecilia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cecilia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15296" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2002-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Myia</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Myia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Myia</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
