<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6087" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-12-28</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Maria Holic</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">まりあ・ほりっく</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Maria†Holic</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Мария Холик</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Maria+Holic</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Марія†Голік</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">玛利亚狂热</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">m+h</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">まりあ†ほりっく</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Maria Holic</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">มาเรีย†โฮลิค</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8041" type="Sequel">Maria Holic Alive</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5083" approval="17" total="34">Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei</anime>
<anime id="4003" approval="15" total="24">Otome wa Boku ni Koishiteru</anime>
<anime id="8179" approval="4" total="10">Mayo Chiki!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="300614">desu yo~</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="181980">poor kanakon-san! ^^ watch this!! it`s funny as hell</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.mariaholic.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="3013" type="Character Design">Morioka Hideyuki</name>
<name id="1512" type="Direction">Miyamoto Yukihiro</name>
<name id="3527" type="Series Composition">Yokotani Masahiro</name>
<name id="3526" type="Original Work">Endou Minari</name>
<name id="59" type="Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="3013" type="Chief Animation Direction">Morioka Hideyuki</name>
<name id="3531" type="Music">Nishiwaki Tatsuya</name>
<name id="3528" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamamura Hiroki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr3526 [Endou Minari], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr12274 [Monthly Comic Alive].
http://anidb.net/ch1893 [Miyamae Kanako], a high school girl, who is allergic to boys, enrols in an all-girls school, hoping to find a female romantic partner. However, her ideal candidate, http://anidb.net/ch1892 [Shidou Mariya], turns out to be a mischievous cross-dressing boy, who together with his sarcastic maid http://anidb.net/ch1894 [Shinouji Matsurika], make life for Kanako really difficult.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3450">5.67</permanent>
<temporary count="3480">7.16</temporary>
<review count="5">6.43</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221984.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10200</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5030</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4281</identifier>
<identifier>trtvfk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mariaholic.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Maria_Holic</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>まりあ†ほりっく</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1532</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>332655</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10621</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2402" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-09">
<name>archery</name>
<description>Archery is the art, practice, or skill of shooting arrows with the use of a bow, from Latin arcus. A person who participates in archery is typically known as an archer.
While archery has been historically used for hunting, both for food and later, in a use that survives to this day, also as a sport, through most of pre-gunpowder human history its main use was for combat; archers were extremely important in warfare, in open field and siege alike, due to their ability to massively kill enemy armies with literal rains of arrows and to set things aflame with burning arrowheads. Proper easy of burning arrowheads could destroy the morale of an invading infantry division or set the entire defending fortress on fire, while non-burning arrowheads could destroy a large portion of the enemy infantry before it could even enter melee combat. Such was the destruction ability of archers that horse archers were the backbone of the both the Hun and Mongol hordes; the former brought terror to and helped the eventual demise of the Roman Empire, while the latter conquered such a large portion of Eurasia that historians coined the term Pax Mongolica (paralleling the Pax Romana) to describe their empire that at its apex spanned from modern-day Poland to the Middle East to Southern China, Korea and the southern parts of Russia.
With the discovery of gunpowder and the invention of firearms, archery was quickly rendered obsolete in warfare. Early firearms were not good in comparison to good archers, with drawbacks such as a vastly inferior rate of fire and high susceptibility to wet weather; nevertheless, they had longer effective range and, most importantly, required almost no practice to use properly in comparison to the many years that it took to train an archer; indeed, a popular saying used to go that "to make a good archer, one must start with his grandfather". Nevertheless, in the Far East archery is to this day considered an important subject in the studies of martial arts, and some Japanese schools have archery dojos ran by archery clubs. Additionally, archery saw an 18th century reemergence as a recreational activity in the West, becoming relevant as an elite class sport, specially for hunting but also at non-living targets, and eventually also becoming an Olympic competition.</description>
<picurl>145640.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2558" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>catgirl</name>
<description>A catgirl (nekomusume, 猫娘) is a girl that has a cat`s characteristics, a form of zoomorphism.
They can appear either as normal girls without any obvious cat traits —such as eyes, ears, paws, or a tail— or as girls who have one or more of these traits. In the former case they are usually cats that have become human through the means of magic. The feline features are added for moe and/or sexiness appeal, with the most common features being cat ears and tail. Nya~, the Japanese equivalent of meow, is often used by girls acting cute and is not a trait exclusive to catgirls.
Not to be confused with characters who simply are wearing a http://anidb.net/t1622 [cat ears accessory] (nekomimi, 猫耳) as a fashion accessory. Catgirls with cat ears should also be tagged with http://anidb.net/t2541 [animal ears].</description>
<picurl>150775.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2664" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-07">
<name>catholic school</name>
<description>A setting for this anime is a school run by the nuns and/or priests of the Church Of Rome.
Religious instruction may be an integral part of the plot. Religious icons - particularly crosses and crucifixes are usually prominent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3053" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-23">
<name>allergy to potential love interests</name>
<description>A character will be found responding to potential love interests, usually of the opposite gender, as if allergic to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3469" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-04-26">
<name>popularity fetish</name>
<description>At least one character in this anime obsesses with being or becoming popular with the other characters.
E.g. a school girl may want to become as popular as an idol (which could turn out to be not what she hoped for). Good school grades may also improve popularity, at least in fiction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3487" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-18">
<name>talks too fast</name>
<description>This character speaks with a pace so frenetic that it can get hard to follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3694" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>dear mother in heaven</name>
<description>A form of veneration of ancestors, where people call upon their ancestors for help, advice and similar in their everyday life like in other cultures upon God, Jesus, the Virgin Mary or various saints. The veneration of the spirit`s of one`s ancestors is an integral part of Japanese culture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3826" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-26">
<name>evil laugh</name>
<description>The thing all great evil villains do after saying/doing something evil.
Some notable examples of great evil villains with evil laughs: Dr. Evil, Dr. Horrible, The Joker, Lelouche, Light, and Mickey Mouse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5769" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>panels that require pausing</name>
<description>Panels that require pausing are image or text panels that interrupt regular animation and flash by so quickly that the viewer cannot recognize the image or read the text fast enough while playing at regular speed; they require pausing the video, or at least viewing it at a lower speed. Given the short screen time these panels are given, they are usually not relevant to the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="31" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-06">
<rating votes="350">7.97</rating>
<name>Minami Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minami Haruka is the oldest sister and in her second year of high school. She has been taking care of her younger sisters since she was young, and this fact has led to some misunderstandings with her classmates. Haruka is the most reliable among the three, but becomes infinitely lazy when she is by herself. She was called Banchou (gang leader) during her junior-high days.</description>
<picture>139649.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1159" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-06">
<rating votes="515">8.07</rating>
<name>Minami Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kana is the middle sister in her second year of junior-high school. Kana is an impulsive and lively girl who never thinks before acting. She often acts or talks impolitely without thinking, much to the annoyance of Chiaki. She has been mislead by Chiaki into thinking that Fujioka is challenging her. She generally does not get good grades in school, though she thinks that if she puts on Keiko`s glasses she will act and speak intelligently. She frequently invents random new holidays and also recruits Chiaki`s classmates into joining her silly escapades. "Kana" contains the kanji for "summer".</description>
<picture>139650.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1192" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-03-18">
<rating votes="65">7.18</rating>
<name>Fukuzawa Yumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fukuzawa Yumi is the main character of the series. In the beginning of the series, Yumi is bashful beyond words, very timid and unsure of herself. She first met http://anidb.net/ch1193 [Sachiko], the star of Lillian School and had her tie fixed by Sachiko, which mortified Yumi. Yumi`s friend, http://anidb.net/ch27888 [Takeshima Tsutaka], took a cute picture of this and wanted to display it in the school festival. Tsutako got Yumi to ask permission from Sachiko. Other characters often comment on how her emotions `show on her face`.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>215059.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1193" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-03-18">
<rating votes="80">6.57</rating>
<name>Ogasawara Sachiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ogasawara Sachiko is a student in her 2nd year at the Lillian Girls` Academy. Though prim, elegant and somewhat aloof, Sachiko has both a rough and a very sweet side. She is afraid of heights and dislikes men, to the point where she will do anything she can to avoid interacting or being near one. She is very protective of her petite sœur, http://anidb.net/ch1192 [Fukuzawa Yumi], and cares deeply about her. Unfortunately, she often has the same problem that Yumi does—she does not share most of her problems with her sœur, causing many misunderstandings.
Sachiko is slated to marry her cousin and fiancé http://anidb.net/ch15124 [Kashiwagi Suguru] after she graduates. This has caused her some distress since, because although she initially cared deeply for him, but he did not reciprocate. They now have a complicated relationship.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>215062.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1197" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-03-18">
<rating votes="65">5.86</rating>
<name>Toudou Shimako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toudou Shimako is http://anidb.net/ch1196 [Satou Sei]`s petite sœur at the beginning of the story and her successor later. Underneath her quiet, mannerly exterior lies a surprisingly strong resolve, calm personality and thoughtfulness.
During http://anidb.net/ch1193 [Sachiko]`s initial attempt to perform the sœur ritual on http://anidb.net/ch1192 [Yumi] in front of the entire student council body, Shimako was the only one who considered Yumi`s feelings of being forced to be one, and was brave enough to voice it out.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>215061.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1199" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-02-21">
<rating votes="22">6.22</rating>
<name>Nijou Noriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nijou Noriko is a young girl with a fascination with Buddhist statues and art. She enters Lillian Academy (a strictly Catholic institution) due to an unexpected turn of events. Due to this fact, she faces an astounding cultural shock (from the old-fashioned style school uniform to the students` mannerisms that she finds too antique and too "refined" to get accustomed to). Even in the novel`s narrative, Shimako is referred as "Shimako-san" from Noriko`s perspective, and not the usual "Shimako-sama" as default to all upper-classmen, and the fact that she hardly uses polite Japanese when talking to Shimako in private, also defines Noriko`s detachment from Lillian`s culture. She has a striaghtforward temper that contradicts her calm exterior and becomes Shimako`s petite sœur after Shimako enters her second year. Her very plain and jet-black hairstyle makes her look like a traditional Japanese doll, another stark contrast to Shimako`s "western doll" appearance.</description>
<picture>66258.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1200" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-03-18">
<rating votes="46">6.62</rating>
<name>Shimazu Yoshino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At the beginning of the series, Shimazu Yoshino is shown as frail girl who was constantly being cared for by her grande sœur, http://anidb.net/ch1201 [Hasekura Rei]. She was voted for the best petite sœur as everyone considered her to be soft and sweet. However, Yoshino is very independent and in some ways tomboyish, despite her sickly status and feminine appearance.
After her heart surgery, she became more energetic throughout the series and http://anidb.net/ch1192 [Yumi] began to see more of her fits of temper, which were usually directed towards Rei. In addition to being Rei`s petite sœur, Yoshino is also her cousin and next-door neighbor. She admires and loves Rei, but becomes upset with her every time she acts overprotective and fragile.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>215060.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1201" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-06-02">
<rating votes="31">6.11</rating>
<name>Hasekura Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hasekura Rei is a student in her 2nd year at the Lillian Girls` Academy and http://anidb.net/ch1200 [Shimazu Yoshin ]`s grande sœur and cousin. She is shown as very tomboyish on the outside, but is in fact quite gentle despite her appearances.
Rei enjoys reading shoujo novels, sightseeing, cooking, baking and sewing. She obsessively cares about Yoshino and often has to put up with her mood swings.</description>
<picture>215063.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1892" type="main character in" update="2015-09-03">
<rating votes="112">8.11</rating>
<name>Shidou Mariya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cross-dressing boy who attends Ame no Kisaki as a girl as a means to win the chairmanship of both the all-male and all-female schools where his late grandmother served as the ex-chairman for both. He deeply respects and loves his grandmother and does not care about actually winning chairmanship. He simply wishes to honour his grandmother`s request. He appears to genuinely care about others though this façade is often hidden through some excuse he has crafted for himself. When Kanako first meets Mariya, she is instantly attracted to his playful femininity and kind attitude. However, Mariya turns out to be quite sadistic in nature and generally adjusts his personality to reflect whatever situation he is in.</description>
<picture>20956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1893" type="main character in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="79">5.37</rating>
<name>Miyamae Kanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanako is the protagonist of the story. She is a second year high school transfer student to Ame no Kisaki. When a boy touches her, she breaks out in hives, giving her a fear of boys.</description>
<picture>20957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1894" type="main character in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="127">8.76</rating>
<name>Shinouji Matsurika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mariya`s maid. She is generally silent but is usually quite rude when she chooses to speak. She delivers the vast majority of her lines with a deadpan expression. The majority of her insults are directed at Kanako and Mariya. She refers to Kanako by such names as "Ms. Pig," "Eiffel Tower" and "Tokyo Tower" due to Kanako`s tall stature. When speaking to Mariya, Matsurika often delivers sharp remarks in regards to his cross-dressing tendencies. Matsurika also attends classes with Mariya.</description>
<picture>20955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1895" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="51">6.51</rating>
<name>Kiri Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An aloof and bespectacled student at Ame no Kisaki. Although she appears quite cold and dispassionate on the surface, she is actually a very caring and helpful personality. At the bequest of the teacher, she helps Kanako to overcome her initial troubles at the school, to the extent that she is willing to put her own reputation at stake by pretending to be Kanako`s lover; so as to avoid trouble from Ryuuken`s fans. She eventually becomes very close friends with Sachi.</description>
<picture>20963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1896" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="30">6.61</rating>
<name>Ishima Ryuuken</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The star of Ame no Kisaki due to her tall stature, good looks, kindness, and generally tomboyish nature. She has a great number of fans and her own fan club. She was supposed to be Kanako`s roommate at the dormitories only to be run out by Mariya later so that Mariya could keep a close eye on Kanako. Ryuuken`s fans cause mischief for Kanako because they are jealous of her friendship with Ryuuken.</description>
<picture>20965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1897" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="41">5.55</rating>
<name>Momoi Sachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bright and cheerful girl, Sachi quickly becomes friends with the newcomer, Kanako. She has orange hair, commonly tied in pigtails. She is good friends with Yuzuru. She seems to have access to hammer space, as she pulls numerous things out from her pockets, even things that would not fit.</description>
<picture>20964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1898" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="35">5.77</rating>
<name>Inamori Yuzuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A demure and friendly girl who has long been friends with Sachi. She is the best archer in the school`s archery club, of which Mariya is also a member.</description>
<picture>20962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1899" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="26">6.13</rating>
<name>Shiki Ayari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiki runs the school`s student council. She is Mariya`s and Shizu`s cousin, and has a long-standing rivalry with Mariya. She calls him `Flat Chest`, as he calls her `Fat Ass`. Apparently, the cause of the animosity between Mariya and Ayari happened because of a childhood incident where she had her dress ripped open supposedly by Mariya (and her underwear exposed. Because of that incident, she got called "Panda-Chang" after the mascot character printed on her underwear and all sorts of nicknames related to pandas. She blames Mariya for this incident and therefore holds a grudge towards him as a result.</description>
<picture>20961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1900" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="141">7.89</rating>
<name>Ryouchou-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An unusual young girl with cat ears who looks after the dormitories where many of the students live. She was nicknamed `God` for unknown reasons and the students do not dare disobey her for fear of vague, yet frightening threats. She has a pet dog, Yonakuni, who helps her take care of the place. Her rule of the dorm extends to manhandling Father Kanae after repeatedly demanding bribes so that he can see Kanako. She has an idiosyncratic speech pattern which makes her speak in a rather languid fashion and insert wherever grammatically possible the phrase `desu yo`.</description>
<picture>20960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1901" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-04">
<rating votes="22">3.70</rating>
<name>Yonakuni-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1902" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="22">5.23</rating>
<name>Kumagai Fumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1903" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="11">4.26</rating>
<name>Tsutsui Honoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="358" picture="174123.jpg">Takada Hatsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3096" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-06">
<rating votes="108">7.59</rating>
<name>Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruka`s classmate and a bit of an airhead. A member of the volleyball club. She tries to protect Haruka from Hosaka, a running gag, which always end with her remarking Hosaka as disgusting.</description>
<picture>139664.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3097" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-06">
<rating votes="122">7.46</rating>
<name>Atsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruka`s classmate. A member of the volleyball club. A very quiet girl, quite similar in character to Keiko.</description>
<picture>139665.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5514" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-03">
<rating votes="40">7.36</rating>
<name>Shidou Shizu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mariya`s twin sister. She attends an all boys school which was also run by the ex-chairman. She has a similar hatred/fear of males, and had similar experiences as Kanako, who she affectionately calls `Kana-chan`. Despite attending a boys school, she has the same hairstyle as Mariya, pigtails and all. Unlike Mariya, she appears to actually be the kind, innocent girl that Mariya attempts to portray.</description>
<picture>22294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5761" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-08">
<rating votes="28">6.45</rating>
<name>Cure Peach</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cure Peach is Momozono Love`s alter ego when transforming.
Attack: Pretty Cure! Love Sunshine!
PowerUp: Pretty Cure! Love Shinshine Fresh!</description>
<picture>22833.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5762" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-08">
<rating votes="27">6.33</rating>
<name>Cure Berry</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cure Berry is Aono Miki`s alter ego when transforming.
Attack: Pretty Cure! Espoir Shower!</description>
<picture>22834.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5763" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-08">
<rating votes="27">8.78</rating>
<name>Cure Pine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cure Pine is Yamabuki Inori`s alter ego when transforming.
Attack: Pretty Cure! Healing Prayer!</description>
<picture>22835.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6444" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="223">7.72</rating>
<name>Fuura Kafuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23898.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6445" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="262">8.14</rating>
<name>Kitsu Chiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23910.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6447" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="214">8.54</rating>
<name>Tsunetsuki Matoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23912.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6448" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="142">6.43</rating>
<name>Kimura Kaere</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23913.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6452" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="138">6.39</rating>
<name>Fujiyoshi Harumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23917.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7056" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="291">7.85</rating>
<name>Yuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuno, sometimes called "Yunocchi" by http://anidb.net/ch7057 [Miyako], is a young girl and main character in the story. She lives in the Sunshine Apartments, along with her close friends and neighbors Miyako, http://anidb.net/ch7058 [Hiro], and http://anidb.net/ch7059 [Sae]. Her friends think of her as a very nice person. Yuno dreams of being a great artist someday. Although she is a skilled artist overall, she considers painting and drawing her specialties. She rarely takes off a pair of X-shaped black hairpins.</description>
<picture>2085.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="7058" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="218">7.33</rating>
<name>Hiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiro is a year older than http://anidb.net/ch7056 [Yuno] and http://anidb.net/ch7057 [Miyako], living directly under Yuno`s apartment. Although she tries to be a supportive senpai to the girls, she tends to worry excessively about her weight, causing her to go on diets for periods while occasionally binging on sweets. A childhood friend of http://anidb.net/ch7059 [Sae], she is one of her neighbor`s principal sources of support when she is involved with a deadline or other crisis.</description>
<picture>2087.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="7059" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-06-26">
<rating votes="199">7.05</rating>
<name>Sae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sae is an upperclassman and good friends with http://anidb.net/ch7058 [Hiro]. Her artistic specialties are photography and fiction writing; she writes fiction professionally under the pseudonym "Tachibana Aya" (橘文) and enrolled at the school specifically so she could learn how to illustrate her own work. Sae, who is tall, athletic, and generally mature, has a playful side that can be at the same time enigmatic and cunning; she has a habit of giving http://anidb.net/ch7056 [Yuno] just enough warning about potential problems for the younger girl to fail to avoid them. She also has a fondness for playing detective when faced with such anomalies as http://anidb.net/ch7057 [Miyako]`s apartment. She tends to get upset when Miyako refers to her as having masculine qualities. She also gets very uncomfortable when asked about her love life, frequently inventing a history for herself that even cursory examination would show to be absurd, while blushing furiously.</description>
<picture>2088.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="7091" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-02-21">
<rating votes="28">5.38</rating>
<name>Matsudaira Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A distant relative and fan of Sachiko. She arrives at Lillian during Yumi`s Second Year. Touko is a member of the Drama club, and nicknamed Mechanical Drill by Satou Sei for her corkscrew pigtails. In the beginning of her first year Touko causes some strain in the relationship between Yumi and Sachiko. However, it is apparent later on in the year that she may become Yumi`s petite soeur.</description>
<picture>66250.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7991" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-10">
<rating votes="62">5.84</rating>
<name>Kanae Touichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The priest of the school Ame no Kisaki. He is the teacher for Modern Japanese and is very popular among the students because of his good looks. He gets a crush on every beautiful girl he sees and is currently "in love" with Mariya, Matsurika and Ayari. He seems to be concerned about Kanako because of her strange behaviour in his eyes. She is also the only one who failed in the Modern Japanese exams. Because of Mariya making up a story about how Kanako`s elder brother died and that he resembles her brother, he desperately wants to help her. He is similar to Kanako because he begins his sentences sometimes with "Skipped, Dear mama in heaven..." and is also prone to having long internal monologues (and generally looking too deeply into the most trivial of matters) and occasionally, fantasies. He also thinks much about what a person could mean when he or she is saying something. The similarity between Kanako and him is also that they both like beautiful girls. He is half-French.
source: wikipedia</description>
<picture>71358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9114" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="7">4.55</rating>
<name>Suzuki Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28601.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12628" type="appears in" update="2009-10-29">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Kohime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38036.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12629" type="appears in" update="2009-10-29">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Saneatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38037.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12631" type="appears in" update="2009-10-29">
<rating votes="8">7.65</rating>
<name>Tonomura-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="568" picture="65531.jpg">Sakuma Kumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12634" type="appears in" update="2011-05-10">
<rating votes="7">5.69</rating>
<name>Satsuki Chifumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10204" picture="37605.jpg">Itou Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12636" type="appears in" update="2009-10-29">
<rating votes="7">5.65</rating>
<name>Natsuru Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="642" picture="156264.jpg">Hazuki Erino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12639" type="appears in" update="2011-05-10">
<rating votes="5">7.31</rating>
<name>Enjouji Ayano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13125" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="107">3.95</rating>
<name>Otonashi Meru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very shy girl who does not talk and only communicates via text messaging on her cell phone; she is notably and viciously abusive in her e-mails. Her family name, Otonashi, means "soundless", and her given name derives from the loan word "mail". Her e-mail address is "hazukashigariyasan", which means "full of shyness". She is called "MeruMeru" by her father. Aside from a few weak sounds and squeaks, she is essentially mute, and any attempt to speak will cause her to uncontrollably sputter in a horrific language. Her family also seems ridiculously rich, as her father is able to set up an audition for people to try and dub her voice in real time.
In the anime, her voice actress changes every episode and is chosen at random, and is credited with, at most, a short sequence of nonsense characters.</description>
<picture>38987.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21618" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="8">7.87</rating>
<name>Hosokawa Kanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tall girl with a quiet (bordering on unapproachable - in the 14th novel, Noriko has described her as a "lone wolf") personality, and on top of that, a big fan of Yumi Fukuzawa, Kanako is introduced in the fourteenth novel, Suzukaze Satsusatsu (A Breath of Fresh Air). During the third season Kanako is actually more like a stalker than a fan and is treated as such when called the "Evil Spirit" who is following Yumi and the male acquaintances she makes from Hanadera. At first, Yumi was not aware of Kanako`s lack of acquaintances and social life, as Kanako actively interacts with her (Yumi has also admittedly felt pressure not to stumble and make mistakes in front of an under-classmen who admires her). She revealed a similar, or even stronger hatred towards men to that of Sachiko, apparently stemming from problems she has with her father (she calls men "the lowest possible form of life"). Her father had an affair and a baby with Kanako`s former senpai, Yuuko. Initially, she imagines Yumi as the living entity of a "perfect and pure" girl (i.e. one who would not involve herself with men), and Yumi admits to Rei that she feels a lot of pressure having to stay on her toes. When that fabricated image was shattered later on (Kanako claims that Yumi`s pure self was overtaken by another personality and is no longer her object of admiration, but someone she "couldn`t care less about"), Yumi quickly acts to repair their strained relationship, and finds out that in the end, Kanako still greatly likes her (Kanako had always, and still wants to take a photo alone with Yumi). Kanako later regains her own emotional balance upon her reconciliation with Yuuko. She is referred to by Marimite fans as Denpa. She is presented as one of the girls who may become Yumi`s petite sœur. She appears briefly in the second season, despite the events of her novel debut not occurring until the third episode of the third season. As of the fourth anime season, she is already close to the Yamayurikai, and, at 179 cm tall, has plans to join the Lillian Academy basketball team.</description>
<picture>66251.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29077" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="407">7.44</rating>
<name>Hatsune Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatsune Miku is a singing synthesizer application and its female character, developed by Crypton Future Media. It uses Yamaha Corporation`s Vocaloid 2 synthesizing technology. The name of the character comes from a fusion of the Japanese for first (初 hatsu), sound (音 ne) and future (Miku (ミク) sounds like a nanori reading of future, 未来, normally read as mirai), referring to her position as the first of Crypton`s Character Vocal Series. She was the second Vocaloid to be sold using the Vocaloid 2 engine and the first Japanese Vocaloid to use the Japanese version of the Vocaloid 2 engine. Her voice is sampled from Japanese voice actress, http://anidb.net/cr1673 [Fujita Saki]. Hatsune Miku has performed onstage as a projection.
Miku`s popularity has seen various references to her in anime. During an episode of http://anidb.net/a5576 [Zoku Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei], Miku is seen auditioning for the voice of http://anidb.net/ch13125 [Otonashi Meru] (Kagamine Rin and Len are referenced in the same episode). Miku`s voice is used in the last http://anidb.net/s10696 [ending theme] for the anime series http://anidb.net/a6182 [Akikan!]. In the http://anidb.net/a5932 [Lucky Star OVA], http://anidb.net/ch32 [Hiiragi Kagami] gets magically transformed into Miku cosplay. http://anidb.net/ch11062 [Kondou Mikoto] in the anime http://anidb.net/a6685 [Kampfer] appears dressed as Miku in episode seven. Miku also makes a cameo appearance in the anime http://anidb.net/a6176 [Sora o Kakeru Shoujo] as well as getting cosplayed by http://anidb.net/ch2254 [Kannagi Itsuki] in the second picture drama.</description>
<picture>84342.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="95643" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戯れの接吻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flirtatious Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tawamure no Seppun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95976" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">甘美な疼き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Sweet Twinge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanbi na Uzuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96286" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">倒錯の保健室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Infirmary of Perversion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tousaku no Hokenshitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96287" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">禁断の匂い / 乙女の秘蜜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Forbidden Smell / A Young Girl`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kindan no Nioi / Otome no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96288" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悦楽の代償</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Price of Pleasure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Etsuraku no Daishou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96289" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">被虐の若芽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Masochistic Young Buds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Higyaku no Wakame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96549" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疑惑の黒下着</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Suspicious Black Underwear</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giwaku no Kuro Shitagi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96550" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">穢された聖母・前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tainted Holy Mother, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kegasareta Seibo Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97116" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">穢された聖母・後編 / 妄想の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tainted Holy Mother, Part 2 / The End of a Fantasy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kegasareta Seibo Kouhen / Mousou no Hate ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97117" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">微乳の過ち / 伯林の恋文</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Flat-Chested Error / A Love Letter from Berlin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Binyuu no Ayamachi / Berlin no Koibumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97118" update="2009-02-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神への供物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Offering to God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami e no Kumotsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97119" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美少女だらけの水泳大会 ポロリもあるよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Swimming Competition Full of Pretty Girls: There Will Be Flying Tops</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bishoujo Darake no Suiei Taikai, Porori mo Aru yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99571" update="2010-03-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103873" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120717" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120718" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM (TV, CD, DVD)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125443" update="2010-11-24">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Information 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125444" update="2010-11-24">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Information 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125445" update="2010-11-24">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Information 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125446" update="2010-11-24">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Information 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125447" update="2010-11-24">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Information 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125448" update="2010-11-24">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Information 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125449" update="2010-11-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Club AT-Xインタビュー映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Club AT-X Interview</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Club AT-X Interview Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125450" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天の妃聖夜祭イベント映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special X`Mas Night: Ame-no-Kiseki Holy Night Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame no Kiseki Seiya Matsuri Event Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125462" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125463" update="2010-11-24">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125464" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125465" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125466" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125467" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125468" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125469" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125470" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125471" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125472" update="2013-07-21">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
