<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="611" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>1990-12-01</startdate>
<enddate>1995-07-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mamono Hunter Youko</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Demon Hunter Yohko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mamono Hunter Yohko</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">DHY</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">魔物ハンター妖子</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Devil Hunter Yohko</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Devil Hunter Yohko</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Yohko la chasseuse de démons</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Yoko: Cacciatrice di demoni</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Охотница на демонов Йоко</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="558" approval="2" total="2">Kishin Douji Zenki</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/1992-1990/works_movie_youko.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1962" type="Direction">Yamada Katsuhisa</name>
<name id="7537" type="Music">Watanabe Hiroya</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="6176" type="Character Design">Aoki Tetsurou</name>
<name id="5708" type="Work">Sai Haruo</name>
<name id="1962" type="Series Composition">Yamada Katsuhisa</name>
<name id="3729" type="Character Design">Abe Hisashi</name>
<name id="3729" type="Direction">Abe Hisashi</name>
<name id="1962" type="Chief Direction">Yamada Katsuhisa</name>
<name id="731" type="Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="116" type="Music">Oomori Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="4790" type="Character Design">Satou Yuuzou</name>
<name id="3568" type="Direction">Sakata Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="1921" type="Character Design">Oohashi Yoshimitsu</name>
<name id="4251" type="Original Plan">Mutsuki Juuzou</name>
<name id="59" type="Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch19171 [Mano Youko] may seem like a typical 16-year-old high school girl, who is athletic, pretty, and boy crazy. She lives in a nice house with her mother http://anidb.net/ch19264 [Sayoko] and her grandmother http://anidb.net/ch19262 [Madoka]. But once you get past that, Youko is hardly normal. Many of the female members of the Mano family have been Mamono hunters, fighting evil spirits and demons throughout history. Youko learns that she was able to escape an earlier attack because her powers have been manifesting, and that now she is indeed the 108th generation Mamono hunter.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="504">4.10</permanent>
<temporary count="510">6.24</temporary>
<review count="1">3.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>23980.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>372</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1280</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>129</identifier>
<identifier>zbsovc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/1992-1990/works_movie_youko.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Devil_Hunter_Yohko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>魔物ハンター妖子</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>151264</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3339" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-11">
<name>demon hunt</name>
<description>Demons are tracked down and probably killed in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3394" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>environmentalism</name>
<description>Environmental protection is a practice of protecting the natural environment on individual, organizational or governmental levels, for the benefit of both the natural environment and humans. Due to the pressures of population and technology, the biophysical environment is being degraded, sometimes permanently. This has been recognized, and governments have begun placing restraints on activities that cause environmental degradation. Since the 1960s, activity of environmental movements has created awareness of the various environmental issues.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4538" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>long episodes</name>
<description>Long episodes are regular episodes that are much longer than the standard 25-30 minutes, usually 45-60 minutes. 
Not to be used if a show has occasional 45-60 minute specials. Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="19171" type="main character in" update="2010-07-24">
<rating votes="8">7.36</rating>
<name>Mano Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The heroine of the anime. Yohko Mano is a typical schoolgirl who is crazy for handsome guys. Her grandmother gives Yohko the responsibility to be the 108th Devil Hunter and continue their family`s legacy of Devil Hunters. Now she fights as a devil hunter against demons that appear and interrupt her life and ruin her chances of ever getting with the guy of her dreams.</description>
<picture>3378.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19172" type="main character in" update="2010-07-24">
<rating votes="5">5.41</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Azusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azusa is the granddaughter of a friend of Madoka Mano`s. She is several years younger than Yohko. She wants to train as a mamano hunter under Madoka at the Mano Shrine, but that hasn`t happened yet. She was born in Komoridani, Kisshu. Azusa also has a box which she calls the "Mamono Hunter Starter Kit." This kit contains assorted goods such as toy ghosts, knives, and a mystic reference book entitled "All You Really Need To Know About Hyper-Space and Pan-Dimensional Travel."</description>
<picture>3377.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4960" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19261" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-24">
<rating votes="4">3.71</rating>
<name>Ogawa Chikako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Yohko`s classmate and best friend. Chikako enjoys eating and making money. She self-proclaims herself as Yohko`s business manager so that only she can decide when Yohko can practice her skills and for how much. Chikako is smart and seems to know much of what happens around her, particularly in school. She stores as much information as possible about her schoolmates in her little Cosio DK-J16 pocket organizer. She also claims to have a great intelligence network for finding information on people.</description>
<picture>50483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19262" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-24">
<name>Mano Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grandmother to Yohko Mano and mother of Sayoko Mano, Yohko`s mother. She was the former 107th Devil Hunter but now is too old to continue being a devil hunter, although she still has some skill and fight in her. She passes the title of Devil Hunter to Yohko to continue the family legacy.</description>
<picture>50485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3270" picture="30153.jpg">Mitsuya Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19263" type="appears in" update="2010-06-30">
<rating votes="3">7.06</rating>
<name>Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most beautiful girl at Yohko`s school who is actually to be the demon world`s resurrected queen.</description>
<picture>50494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19264" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-30">
<rating votes="3">4.74</rating>
<name>Mano Sayoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daughter of Madoka Mano and mother to Yohko Mano. She was supposed to be the 108th devil hunter but became pregnant with Yohko (Only virgins can become Devil Hunters). She had a very frank and open opinion on sex and even gave Yohko a package of condoms in the first episode. This attitude, like most things in the series, was later toned down greatly in subsequent episodes.</description>
<picture>50495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19265" type="appears in" update="2010-06-30">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Wakabayashi Osamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Osamu is one of Yohko`s classmates, he has a crush on her.</description>
<picture>50497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19266" type="appears in" update="2010-06-30">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Kando Hideki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hideki is an upper-classman of Yohko`s who she has a crush on. He becomes the sacrfice for the demon resurrection ceremony.</description>
<picture>50500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19268" type="appears in" update="2010-06-30">
<rating votes="2">7.64</rating>
<name>Gakuenchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The principal of Yohko`s school, who turns out to be a demon.</description>
<picture>50502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="542" picture="60897.jpg">Doi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19269" type="appears in" update="2010-06-30">
<rating votes="4">7.33</rating>
<name>Mano Ayako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Granddaughter of Chiaki Mano and cousin to Yohko Mano. She was trained by Chiaki Mano to defeat Yohko and become the true 108th Devil Hunter. Ayako shares a very similar appearance to Yohko, thus making them look like twins. However, Ayako has lighter hair and her eyes are a bit more narrow than Yohko`s, and her Devil Hunter uniform is black, not red. She is the wielder of the Whip of Destruction, which she uses at its full potential. Together with Azusa 2, she had planned to take the Devil Hunter title from Yohko and claim it as her own. However, they joined forces to fight a very powerful demon, one Ayako had accidentally released, which temporarily shook her confidence. Afterwards, Ayako decided she needed more training and left to improve herself, parting with her cousin on more amiable terms.</description>
<picture>3379.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19283" type="appears in" update="2010-07-24">
<rating votes="3">4.74</rating>
<name>Mano Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The very first Devil Hunter from the Mano Family. She is very skilled as a devil Hunter and is able to fend and defeat any demon, even the most powerful of all demons, Tokima. In several artworks, she is portrayed with a white devil hunter outfit with pink hair. In the anime however, she wears a red devil hunter outfit and has light green hair.</description>
<picture>50521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19284" type="appears in" update="2010-06-30">
<rating votes="3">3.66</rating>
<name>Azusa 2 Gou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sidekick to Ayako Mano. She looks very much like Azusa Kanzaki. Since she never mentioned her actual name, Madoka dubs her with the name "Azusa 2." She is very much like Azusa, both in appearance and in skill, which means that she too is a klutz at times and not very skilled in fighting. She does seem to have a bit more experience in combat, although not much of a difference compared to Azusa Kanzaki.</description>
<picture>50524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4960" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20145" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Makai no Koe</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The sinister voice of the demon world.</description>
<picture>153333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20146" type="appears in" update="2010-08-20">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Onra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The demon king who was awakened from construction company that was cutting down the forest in which he slept and eventually decides to take out his anger on Yohko and Azusa.</description>
<picture>3459.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20151" type="appears in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Biryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Thousands of years ago in another world/dimension Master Biryu fell in love with a woman named Yanagi. A dragon king named Ryu-o forbade love between creatures of Mother Earth and the Great Sea, so when he found out about the relationship between Master Biryu and Princess Yanagi, he seperated them and sealed them away for eternity. Ryu-o put Master Biryu in a Dragon Sphere hidden in the body of a demon.</description>
<picture>52235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20156" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">2.72</rating>
<name>Yanagi-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>From inside the orb of her hideous demon captor, appears the beautiful Princess Yanagi who nearly radiates elegance and grace. A Nymph of the Willows, she plays the flute, and is endowed with the power to form a protective shield, which even a very powerful demon would have quite a difficult time penetrating.</description>
<picture>3460.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20194" type="appears in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Obaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Master Biryu`s guardian. She sends Yohko mental images of Master Biryu in Yohko`s dreams making Yohko think that Biryu is interested in her. Lady Obaba then transports Yohko to her world/dimension in an effort to get Yohko to help free Master Biryu and Princess Yanagi.</description>
<picture>3462.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2040" picture="186173.jpg">Suzuki Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20263" type="appears in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Asakura Ryuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another one of Yohko`s crushes. He is the son of the president of the Asakura Company. Ryuichi is smart and athletic, according to Chikako. He`s also the one Tokima possesses in order to get into Yohko`s house and break the seal which constrains Tokima.</description>
<picture>3463.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20264" type="appears in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Tokima</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tokima is the demon who originally bridged the dimensional gaps between the demon plane and the human plane. He is very powerful, with the ability to control both the time and space continuums. He has fought and lost to every previous generation of Mamono Hunter, which explains the 107 scars on his body. After each such loss some of his power was sealed away by that particular Mamono Hunter.</description>
<picture>3464.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20342" type="appears in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Mano Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiaki is Madoka`s twin sister and Ayako`s grandmother.</description>
<picture>3466.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20343" type="appears in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Sano Yusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yusuke is a teacher at Yohko`s school. Yohko develops a crush on him.</description>
<picture>3467.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20967" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Ryuuou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Dragon King.</description>
<picture>53676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="287" picture="73062.jpg">Yanada Kiyoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20968" type="appears in" update="2010-08-21">
<rating votes="2">4.61</rating>
<name>Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mano Madoka became young again due to an accident in Volume 5.</description>
<picture>53677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66448" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Tateno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tateno is a basketball player at Yohko`s school. He is yet another guy who Yohko gets a crush on.</description>
<picture>153334.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2899" picture="79024.jpg">Miyazaki Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6751" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1990-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔物ハンター妖子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6752" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1994-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光陰覇王の乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell on Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouin Haou no Ran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6753" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1993-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー ミュージック クリップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Super Music Clip</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6754" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1993-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖子3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6755" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1992-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖子2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10642" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1995-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖子×2(二乗)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49673" update="2006-05-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152667" update="2013-08-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 6 Clean Closing</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152668" update="2013-08-21">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 5 Clean Closing</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152669" update="2013-08-21">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer Volume 6 Version 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152670" update="2013-08-21">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer Volume 6 Version 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152671" update="2013-08-21">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer Volume 6 Version 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152672" update="2013-08-21">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer Volume 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152673" update="2013-08-21">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152674" update="2013-08-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211901" update="2019-01-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
