<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6110" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-01-09</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Asu no Yoichi!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Yoichi of Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Ёити завтра</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Rytojaus Yoichis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Asu no Yoichi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ashita no Yoichi!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">明日的与一!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Yoichi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">AnY</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">明日のよいち!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Samurai Harem</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">High School Samurai</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7440" approval="5" total="14">Hyakka Ryouran: Samurai Girls</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="17">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="181980">u get what u see harem anime with lots of fan service</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="467099">its not bad its just your typical Harem check it out between better shows.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="83928">Less comedy and fanservice than I expected. It has a weak plot. Only for samurai fans who like a little comedy and/or fanservice.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="488554">the story get boring after few episode..
inconsistent chara develep imho is worst.
but still it`s a lil funny tho</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="133345">It`s a bit like Love hina</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="235338">Good anime to watch. Hope they would have a second season or OVA for this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="274546">promicing</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="226817">Take it as a comedy show. Pretty amusing.
ps: Kagome so kawaii neh~</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="74379">haven`t seen these sort of simple relaxing harem+comedy for a long time. defintely worth a watch if you`re into those genres.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="364775">Really funny and with much ecchiness, if you`re into stuff like that, you gotta watch this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="259124">I really like this setting. It contain classic chara types but thats the way i like it :) Great ep. 1 and ep. 2 XD</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/yoichi/</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Animation Work">AIC</name>
<name id="2382" type="Animation Character Design">Morishima Noriko</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="1636" type="Direction">Kujou Rion</name>
<name id="2383" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishii Yumiko</name>
<name id="3399" type="Music">Kikuya Tomoki</name>
<name id="8912" type="Original Work">Minamoto Yuu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr8912 [Minamoto Yuu], serialised in Monthly Shounen Champion.
Having been raised and trained for the past seventeen years as a traditional samurai bushi, http://anidb.net/ch3860 [Karasuma Yoichi] was surprised when his father suddenly announces that there nothing more that he could teach his son, but he arranges for Yoichi to continue training at a dojo owned by one of his father`s friends. So now, Yoichi must leave the tranquillity of his remote rural mountain life and move to the city to live with the family of his father`s friend. And if learning how to cope with city life was not hard enough, he finds himself living with four beautiful sisters, having to endure a `training` regiment more severe than he could ever have imagined.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3347">4.35</permanent>
<temporary count="3388">6.81</temporary>
<review count="4">5.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>13712.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4405</identifier>
<identifier>uqkpsf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/yoichi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Asu_no_Yoichi!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>明日のよいち!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1542</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>332636</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10622</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3975" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-22">
<name>delayed 16-9 broadcast</name>
<description>This anime was created with an aspect ratio of 16:9 (widescreen), but its initial Japanese TV broadcasts were cropped to 4:3 (fullscreen). At some point (usually 2-4 weeks) down the line, it was rebroadcast in 16:9.
Note: This tag does NOT apply to series created in 16:9, but only broadcast in 4:3 and not made available in 16:9 until their DVD/BD release. For those, use "Broadcast cropped to 4-3".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3860" type="main character in" update="2018-04-01">
<rating votes="26">6.14</rating>
<name>Karasuma Yoichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school sophomore who is also a young swordsman and has moved away from his mountain life to live with the Ikarugas in the city. He is a very active person who actively enjoys martial arts with swordsmanship in particular. Due to his early childhood in the mountains with his father, he does not know the current customs in Japan or to act around a girl. He is very honourable, which is shown when he addresses everyone with the dono honorific. However, due to constant misunderstandings, Ibuki, in particular, constantly attacks him under the assumption that he had done something perverted.</description>
<picture>215705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3861" type="main character in" update="2018-04-06">
<rating votes="35">7.06</rating>
<name>Ikaruga Ibuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school sophomore who becomes a self-appointed head of the Ikaruga family. She becomes a maternal figure for the Ikaruga family since their parents went overseas at an early age. She secretly likes Yoichi but is the first to attack him due to the many unusual events, which usually concern other girls. She is Assistant Instructor of Ikaruga Dojo, teaching Ukiha Kamikaze Swordplay. There are only 5 students in her dojo due to her violent nature. However, she treats children in a maternal fashion.</description>
<picture>215878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3862" type="main character in" update="2018-04-06">
<rating votes="50">7.94</rating>
<name>Ikaruga Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A freshman in high school, is Ibuki`s younger sister. She has a shy, tsundere personality and is acutely aware of her small breasts when compared to those of her siblings. It took a while for her to like Yoichi romantically and she tries to help him at times while saying it was for no particular reason. She is bad with household chores in general. She dislikes being compared to Ibuki as she is constantly overshadowed.</description>
<picture>215879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3863" type="main character in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="35">7.12</rating>
<name>Ikaruga Chihaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 3rd year junior high school student. She is the second youngest of the Ikaruga family and a professional cartoonist. She uses her siblings and Yoichi as a basis for her manga by manipulating the scenario`s surrounding them for the best results. She also seems to most knowledgeable about relationships out of the sisters as she flirts with Yoichi while poking fun at the others. She is the only person in the Ikaruga family to wear glasses.</description>
<picture>39043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3864" type="main character in" update="2019-12-31">
<rating votes="25">3.68</rating>
<name>Ikaruga Kagome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest of the Ikaruga family and an elementary school student. She is clumsy and does the washing up for the rest of the family. She has a shy personality and is very talented in cooking. She feels embarrassed by her breasts, so she wears a http://anidb.net/t1925 [sarashi] to cover them up.</description>
<picture>215880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8937" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="8">4.55</rating>
<name>Washizu Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Washizu (also known as Wa-san) is Ibuki`s classmate and a famous delinquent. At the beginning of the anime, Washizu was depicted as a loner, and the only friend he had was Torigaya. As the anime progressed, Washizu started being friendly to other people around him. Washizu has a crush on Ibuki, and sees Yoichi as a perverted pimp who plays around with many girls, including Ibuki. He despises him because of his misunderstanding of the relationship between Yoichi and Ibuki. However, he occasionally teams up with Yoichi to fight a common enemy.
Instead of confessing to Ibuki, he accidentally confessed to Ibuki`s sister, Ayame, and they started acting as a comic relief of the anime. They usually think together for how they could get close to their respective love interests (Ibuki for Washizu, Yoichi for Ayame).
"Washizu Vision" in the anime is Washizu`s misinterpretations of the situation, usually concerning Ibuki. They can also be Washizu`s fantasies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8938" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-09">
<rating votes="4">2.70</rating>
<name>Torigaya Keita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Torigaya is Washizu`s only friend until Washizu started opening himself to other people. He usually acts cocky and arrogant when he is with Washizu. He is very fond of children. In the anime, he unusually (and unexplainably) shrinks, which only Washizu notices.
Keita was actually female the whole time, with a boyish appearance. At the end of the anime, Keita unexplainably becomes completely feminine, which was extremely shocking to Washizu.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8939" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-21">
<rating votes="14">5.11</rating>
<name>Tsubame Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsubasa is the next heir of the Tsubame Tenryu Ryouge, a martial arts school threatening to collapse due to lack of funds, and was originally hired by Sakinomiya Ukyou to assassinate Yoichi.
She is a clumsy and shy girl, who dreams of having a normal life. She has a crush on Washizu, because he was the first one who treated her normally. But she gets hurt deeply after hearing Washizu saying that he hates martial arts.
She insisted to her subordinate Angela that she should go to the same school as Yoichi so she would have a good opportunity to assassinate him, although her true motive was to be a normal high school girl. In one incident, she slices a soccer ball heading towards her in front of her classmates due to her instincts and gets depressed because everyone became silent. Yoichi openly greets her to ease the tension of the scene, and everyone else follows suit. After school, Angela ripped Tsubasa`s clothes off in public. She turned into a deadly martial artist in a trace-like state due to her embarrassment. She attacks Yoichi at Angela`s orders. However, when Washizu interrupted their fight, Tsubasa broke out of her trance and fled the scene crying from humiliation. Later, she told Angela that she hates both martial arts and Angela. But the next day, she forgave Angela and started a ramen shop with her.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>39045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8940" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="25">7.55</rating>
<name>Takatsukasa Angela</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Angela is a 16-year-old girl, who is Tsubasa`s subordinate, who Yoichi described as being as tall as a model with a dynamic body. Initially Angela was hired by Sakinomiya Ukyou to assassinate Yoichi. She has been observing Tsubasa, because she thought that the next heir of Tsubame Tenryu Ryouge should assassinate Yoichi.
After she witnesses Tsubasa`s lack of interest in proceeding with the job, she ripped off Tsubasa`s clothes so she would turn into a deadly weapon. But the fight between Tsubasa and Yoichi was interrupted by Washizu. After Tsubasa left because of the embarrassment, Angela followed her and was in deep shock after hearing Tsubasa say that she hates both martial arts and Angela. She attempted to assassinate Yoichi that night by herself but that fails. Ahe explained everything to the Ikarugas about the assassination plot and her assassination attempt. Yoichi lectured her about her mercenary ways and that she should use her martial art skills with pride as a member of the Tsubame Tenryu Ryouge as well for the revival of her martial arts school. After that, she left the house and encountered Tsubasa, who had already forgiven Angela for her previous actions. Angela started a ramen shop with Tsubasa the next day. Angela also likes Yoichi romantically.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>39041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13097" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="2">3.58</rating>
<name>Yoichi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoichi`s father. He appears in person only in the first and last episode of the anime but does the voice over for previews in all of the episodes.</description>
<picture>39047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13098" type="appears in" update="2009-11-17">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Rouba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5639" picture="212814.jpg">Nitta Makiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13099" type="appears in" update="2009-11-17">
<rating votes="2">5.66</rating>
<name>Josei Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13100" type="appears in" update="2009-11-17">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Hittakuri Han</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38937.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13108" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Ojisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13117" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-11">
<rating votes="2">3.24</rating>
<name>Masayuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13118" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-18">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Yoshio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="6916" picture="187044.jpg">Sekiyama Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13119" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-18">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Hiroyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13120" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="2">4.07</rating>
<name>Masashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13132" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-02">
<rating votes="3">2.75</rating>
<name>Saginomiya Ukyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ukyou is the head of the Saginomiya clan. He has a crush on Ibuki and constantly attempts to kill Yoichi and forcefully kidnaps Ibuki.</description>
<picture>43969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13133" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38994.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13134" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Danshi Seito A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13135" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="2">5.67</rating>
<name>Danshi Seito B</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10865" picture="38995.jpg">Suzuki Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13136" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Danshi Seito C</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13137" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="3">6.12</rating>
<name>Hinagata Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13138" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Tenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4041" picture="26004.jpg">Miyasaka Shunzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13139" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="7">3.71</rating>
<name>Saginomiya Sakon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13140" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Onna Tomodachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5022" picture="170938.jpg">Tanaka Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13141" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Ikemen A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2328" picture="171565.jpg">Satou Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13142" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Ikemen B</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13143" type="appears in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="1">7.25</rating>
<name>Nuezume Jin`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2893" picture="240353.jpg">Yamaguchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13144" type="appears in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Mizunagi Uzumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13145" type="appears in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Mizunagi Shiomaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="565" picture="171984.jpg">Takagi Motoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13147" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Dokurou Leader</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6411" picture="44853.jpg">Aoki Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13148" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Ryokan no Joshou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10874" picture="223536.jpg">Sasai Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13150" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="2">4.26</rating>
<name>Asamigawa-tei Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2577" picture="22573.jpg">Misono Yukihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13151" type="appears in" update="2009-12-29">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Shitsuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6411" picture="44853.jpg">Aoki Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13152" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Youshou no Ukyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13153" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="2">6.67</rating>
<name>Saginomiya Oboro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39030.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13154" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="2">7.64</rating>
<name>Torigaya Keita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Torigaya is Washizu`s only friend until Washizu started opening himself to other people. He usually acts cocky and arrogant when he is with Washizu. He is very fond of children. In the anime, he unusually (and unexplainably) shrinks, which only Washizu notices.
In the end of the anime, he unexplainably becomes a girl, which was extremely shocking to Washizu.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>39035.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="96210" update="2015-08-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サムライ来る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Samurai Comes!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le samouraï arrive !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Primeira Espada Longa - O Samurai Chegou!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samurai Kuru !</title>
<summary>Karasuma Yoichi has lived all his life in the wilderness with his father, who has been training him in the ways of the samurai, living his life pretty much as in feudal Japan, with no intrusions from the modern world. After he manages to best his father one last time he is told to go out into the city and learn what he can there. The father sends a message to their distant relatives the Ikarugas who run a dojo in the city, and Yoichi is told to meet with them.
The modern world is baffling to the young samurai, who quickly gets into trouble as he goes through a shopping mall trying to find the Ikarugas. He beats up an arrogant punk who mocks his anachronistic appearance and chases down a thief, causing no small disturbance in the process. While doing this he runs into two of the Ikaruga sisters under somewhat compromising circumstances, but helps lost Kagome find Ibuki. He is arrested by the police but later released after apologising to everyone inconvenienced, as he is seen to be good-hearted. After Ibuki brings him home, the other Ikaruga sisters are surprised to see him.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96256" update="2015-08-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそ翼高(ヨッコー)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Yokko!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bienvenue au lycée Yokuryô</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Segunda Espada Longa - Bem-Vindo A Yokko!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso Yokkou</title>
<summary>The next morning is awkward for Yoichi as he tries to adjust to the Ikaruga household, and even more awkward when he transfers into school. Ibuki harshly admonishes him several times for strange behaviour that could be misinterpreted. The punk he defeated yesterday, named Washizu, goes to the same school, and challenges him to a duel, where he is again soundly defeated. When they get home Yoichi is struck by a sudden fever from the stress of trying to adjust so quickly to the modern world, and Ibuki goes out to get some groceries. Meanwhile, in uncharacteristic kindness Ayame tries to make rice porridge for him, which she does with Kagome`s help. Later, Ibuki returns and she apologises to Yoichi for her harshness and Yoichi does the same for his recklessness.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96275" update="2015-09-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">脱いだらすごいんです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amazing Without Clothes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elle est extraordinaire déshabillée !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Terceira Espada Longa - Despir E Queimar!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuidara Sugoin Desu</title>
<summary>A new girl has just transferred into Yoichi`s class, named Tsubame Tsubasa, who like Yoichi has lived her life until then in the mountains training her Tsubame Benten-style martial arts with Takatsukasa Angela. The two of them have been hired by a mysterious person to assassinate Yoichi, intending to use the payment to advance their school of martial arts, but Tsubasa has no wish to do so and longs for life as a normal girl, so rather than fighting him she befriends him, much to Angela`s consternation. One day, as Tsubasa is leaving school with Yoichi and Ibuki, Angela rips off her clothes, turning her into a deadly martial artist in a trance-like state due to her embarrassment, and so she attacks Yoichi. Before the fight escalates further Washizu interrupts, causing Tsubasa to break out of her trance and flee crying from embarrassment, and she resents Angela as a result.
Later that evening Angela herself attacks Yoichi, and tells her the reasons why she is trying to kill him, but he convinces her that is the wrong way, and that the pride they have in their art is the important thing. Later, she makes up with Tsubasa and they decide to work at a nearby ramen shop to make ends meet instead.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96486" update="2015-09-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちはやぶるちはや</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chihaya Being Chihaya</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chihaya fait semblant d`être Chihaya</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Quarta Espada Longa - Chihaya Fingindo Ser Chihaya!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chihaya Buru Chihaya</title>
<summary>Chihaya is having a block in her manga writing. Ibuki and Yoichi go for a spar in the dojo, with the small number of students and Ayame watching. After Yoichi damages her clothes she attacks him and her students become collateral damage. Ayame has a bath afterwards, and Chihaya comes by to see her, saying that she`ll check Yoichi out. She brings him into her room, showing him her manga drafts and explaining about her story, and then proceeds to come on to him. He kindly refuses her advances, but she tells him that she was just testing him. Ibuki saw them, and gives him a sound drubbing as usual. Chihaya however, later tells Ayame that Yoichi is a good man and she shouldn`t stop her feelings for him.
The next day Chihaya has supplementary review classes but has left her notebook at home, bringing her manga drafts instead, so Yoichi goes to her school to give it to her. He finds that she is being bullied by a group of students who cannot understand how she can be so passionate about her art. He confronts them and this escalates into a fight, and they are quickly defeated. Chihaya sees them beaten down and talks to them, saying that someday they`ll also find something they`ll be just as passionate about. Thus inspired by her experience of Yoichi she changes her manga character designs to resemble him more.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96535" update="2015-09-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの時君はワルかった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Back Then, You Were Badass</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tu étais méchant à cette époque-là</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Oitava Espada Longa - Desculpe Por Aquela Vez!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Toki wa Warukatta</title>
<summary>Washizu is seen helping an old man find his way, and quarrelling and losing to Ayame over a drink in a convenience store, and he is seen to have softened up since the days when he was the most feared delinquent in town. There is a great deal of misunderstanding between Washizu and Ayame over a love letter Washizu is trying to give Ibuki. Ayame comes by to deliver ramen for lunch and is shocked to see the two of them in an intimate pose, and so leaves without collecting payment.
A group of delinquents called Skull Union who were once beaten by Washizu see how he seems to have softened up since their defeat, and think that it is their opportunity to take him down. They enter the dojo and abduct Ayame, and while keeping her hostage they try to beat him up. He is unable to resist for Ayame`s sake, but eventually Yoichi comes by and frees her, and the two of them together manage to defeat the delinquents.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96536" update="2015-09-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スクミズ シロスク セパレート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Swimsuit, White School Swimsuit, Two-Piece Swimsuit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Maillots de bain scolaires, blancs et bikinis</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Sétima Espada Longa - Um Maiô Pela Metade!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sukumizu Shirosuku Separate</title>
<summary>Ibuki has won tickets to a private resort island, and she brings along her sisters, Yoichi, her students, Tsubasa, and Angela, and invited Washizu but he misunderstood the date of the outing. The resort island was actually a ploy by the mysterious masked man to once again assassinate Yoichi, and he has this time hired the Mizunagi brothers to do it, whose skill on the waters is unmatched. They get a trained seagull to attack the girls, and Yoichi tries to save them it looks like he is doing perverted things to them, although Angela understands what he was trying to do.
Later, Kagome refuses to take off her shirt to swim, which concerns Ibuki and Masashi, who say harsh things to her, so she walks off. Masashi goes after her, and they both fall into a pit that the Mizunagis have prepared. They are gone a long time so everyone goes looking for them. Kagome and Masashi find a tunnel out of the pit, which leads to a cliff, where Masashi falls. Yoichi, despite being unable to swim, dives in after him.
Kagome tosses Yoichi his wooden sword and a lifebuoy which he uses to stay afloat as the Mizunagis attack. Their first attack hits the cliff like a tidal wave, and Masashi nearly drowns, but Kagome dives in to rescue him. Yoichi is ready for the second attack and uses a special technique to deflect the oncoming wave, defeating the Mizunagis.
Later Kagome admits that she refused to go swimming because she was beginning to develop visible breasts, which she was shy about.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96537" update="2015-09-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わっさん来る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wassan Comes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Washizu arrive !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Sexta Espada Longa - Wa-San Chegou!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wassan Kuru!</title>
<summary>Washizu is still thinking of how to return Ibuki`s handkerchief, and eventually decides to do so by putting it in her shoe locker along with a note. However, he makes a big mistake and puts the handkerchief and letter in Yoichi`s locker instead. Yoichi meets him at the rooftop, who misinterprets the letter as signifying that he is interested in martial arts. But as Ibuki is also there he cannot deny it, and he winds up joining the Ikaruga dojo. At training he is considered a newbie beside all of the kids, and as such has to perform basic exercises. He starts off with push-ups, and winds up doing 400 and is nearly exhausted, but Yoichi says that as punishment he has to do a little more, and so the two of them wind up doing 1000 push ups in total. They later have dinner together as Chihaya has received a royalty check from her manga publisher and decides to treat everyone.
Meanwhile, the mysterious masked man has this time hired the assassin Nuezeme Jinjuurou to murder Yoichi, but the man proves to have a terrible sense of direction and goes further away instead.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96538" update="2015-09-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デートしようぜ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go on a Date!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sortons ensemble !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Quinta Espada Longa - Vamos Ter Um Encontro!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Date Shiyou ze!</title>
<summary>One day, Yoichi receives a love letter in his shoe locker from a pretty girl named Hinagata Yui, inviting him to go on a date. Ibuki, concerned that Yoichi might do something outrageous again goes on a "practice date" with him. Ayame, Chihaya, and Kagome watch them secretly. She has him change out of his robes into ordinary casual clothes and gets him to leave behind his wooden sword, and he notices her admiring a display with stuffed toy kittens. They go bowling and Yoichi proves to be ridiculously bad at it, and have lunch at the ramen shop where Tsubame works. As the day ends, as Yoichi is about to give Ibuki one of the stuffed kittens she was admiring earlier, she stumbles and while he tries to save her they both fall into a fountain. He gives her the stuffed kitten which makes her very happy, and she runs off to get a drink.
Yoichi then sees Hinagata, who asks him what his reply is to her letter. He thanks her and tells her that it made him happy, but he declines the offer, saying that a date must be between two people who love each other. Hinagata then produces a three-section staff and proceeds to fight him: she is yet another martial artist who has been hired to assassinate him. He manages to take her weapon from her and damages her clothes and she runs off. Meanwhile, a group of punks has accosted Ibuki at a vending machine and she beats them down.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96989" update="2015-09-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛んで火にいる夏祭り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Summer Festival: Plunging into the Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un flamboyant festival d`été</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Nona Espada Longa - Voe Para O Ardente Festival De Verão!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tonde Hi ni Iru Natsumatsuri</title>
<summary>It is another training day at the Ikaruga dojo, and Ibuki teaches the children while Washizu and Yoichi are paired. After getting beaten down Washizu washes his face at the pump with Torigaya, and decides to stop being so wishy-washy and declares his love for Ikaruga aloud. He meant Ibuki of course, but it is Ayame who hears him and misinterprets the declaration as being meant for her.
Afterwards, Torigaya points out that Ayame is actually in love with Yoichi, and so they hatch a plan at the upcoming summer festival to pair Ibuki with Washizu, Ayame with Yoichi, while Torigaya accompanies Chihaya and Kagome. The plan goes awry when Torigaya mistakenly switches the pairs, leaving Ibuki with Yoichi and Ayame with Washizu.
The mysterious masked man who has been trying to kill Yoichi, Saginomiya Ukyou, and his sister Sakon, appear at the festival. Ukyou is seen to have an obsession with Ibuki, and Sakon hatches a plan to send Yoichi and the Ikarugas to a hot spring resort they control.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96990" update="2015-10-01">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘湯で死闘!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Battle to the Death at a Hidden Hot Spring!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat mortel dans les sources secrètes !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Décima Espada Longa - Vida Ou Morte Nas Termas Secretas!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitou de Shitou!</title>
<summary>The Ikaruga sisters and Yoichi go to the hot spring inn, which despite being so isolated, is oddly very well-appointed. He meets Ukyou in the spring, who tells him how he is only causing trouble for the sisters and hasn`t really done anything for them. After dinner, the proprietress of the hot spring inn tells them of how there was a haunted cave behind the inn whose ghosts were frightening the guests. Yoichi and Ibuki go to investigate, belatedly followed by Ayame. The proprietress, who is really Sakon in disguise, drugs Chihaya and Kagome, so they fall asleep.
At the cave, Yoichi and Ibuki fall into a pit trap and are separated, and he sees what appears to be Ayame, who sets out to aggressively seduce him. The facts that she is behaving so substantially out of character and that her breasts are larger than he remembers tip him off, and he believes that she is a ghost attempting to deceive him. The false Ayame is again Sakon in disguise, and when Ibuki eventually finds them, she drugs the two of them, and so she and Ukyou manage to abduct Ibuki.
When Yoichi can move again he returns to the inn and is attacked by many of their former enemies and a large number of Saginomiya henchmen. The real Ayame joins him and helps him fight, and they rescue Chihaya and Kagome. They later find Ibuki, who seems to have lost her memories.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="97213" update="2015-10-01">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あすの与一!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoichi Fights On!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yoichi, jour après jour !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Décima Segunda Espada Longa - O Yoichi Do Futuro!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asu no Yoichi!</title>
<summary>Yoichi and the Ikarugas reach the Saginomiya residence, and are immediately attacked by Sakon and her henchmen. There are too many of them and eventually even Yoichi is overwhelmed by their numbers, until Washizu, Tsubasa, and Angela arrive to help.
Eventually they arrive face to face with Ukyou and Sakon, but Ukyou makes his escape to the roof of their mansion with Ibuki. Yoichi manages to reach him and they have a duel, and as dawn breaks and the other Ikaruga sisters arrive at the roof Ibuki somehow seems to regain her memories, but falls, but Yoichi and her sisters dive in after her, and he manages to use his skills to soften their landing.
Yoichi writes a letter to his father, telling him of the Ikarugas and how he realises that he still has so much to learn and will continue to remain with them.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="97214" update="2015-10-01">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いぶきさんはもらったよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Taking Ibuki</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ibuki est à moi</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Décima Primeira Espada Longa - O Que Ibuki-San Sofreu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ibuki-san wa Moratta yo</title>
<summary>The Ikaruga sisters and Yoichi return home and find that Ibuki has not just simply lost her memories, but has further reverted to the mental age of a four-year old. As such, she remembers Ayame and Chihaya but does not quite recognise them, but does not know Kagome at all, as she was not yet born when Ibuki was four, which breaks Kagome`s heart. The sisters find that Ibuki is incredibly immature, completely different from the strong elder sister they had come to rely upon.
Ayame later scolds Ibuki for accidentally throwing a scissors at Chihaya, which makes her cry and she runs outside, where she sees Washizu, who doesn`t quite understand why she is behaving so strangely, but he brings her to a playground and plays with her as she asks. The Saginomiya siblings visit, and they explain what had been done to Ibuki, saying that the drug used on her brought her mind back to the age when she was happiest, implying that she felt that caring for her sisters has been a painful burden for her. Ukyou tries to convince them to let him take Ibuki, and provides them with wealth and a comfortable lifestyle as compensation, and even offers Yoichi a place at the soon to be revived Tsubame Ben-Ten Dojo with Angela and Tsubasa, which he will provide with the necessary funding.
Everyone is tempted to consider the offer. However, Ukyou has one of his servants abduct Ibuki from Washizu, and Sakon lets on that her drugs brought Ibuki back to the mental age of four because that was what Ukyou specified. They very nearly accept the offers but Kagome`s sadness at being forgotten convinces them otherwise, and they go to the Saginomiya mansion to try to rescue Ibuki.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="98392" update="2010-01-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98393" update="2020-04-10">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112774" update="2010-01-08">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112775" update="2020-04-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112776" update="2010-01-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2009-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Symposium</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
