<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6129" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2008-10-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Initial D Extra Stage 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">頭文字D Extra Stage 2 旅立ちのグリーン</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Initial D Extra Stage 2: Tabidachi no Green</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">頭文字[イニシャル]D Extra Stage2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Initial D Extra Stage 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="631" type="Prequel">Initial D Extra Stage</anime>
<anime id="1724" type="Parent Story">Initial D Fourth Stage</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<creators>
<name id="769" type="Animation Work">ACGT</name>
<name id="6780" type="Character Design">Tanaka Jou</name>
<name id="6396" type="Original Work">Shigeno Shuuichi</name>
<name id="7092" type="Direction">Tominaga Tsuneo</name>
<name id="4619" type="Music">Katsumata Ryuuichi</name>
<name id="6435" type="Music">Umebori Atsushi</name>
<name id="767" type="Work">OB Planning</name>
<name id="6780" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Jou</name>
<name id="56708" type="Music">Dennis Martin</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch9273 [Iketani] missed an opportunity to see Mako and hates himself for never calling to say he was sorry. By chance he runs into her 6 months later, and the situation is awkward. Iketani does not have time to talk at that moment, so they arrange a second meeting. Iketani goes to the meeting place early, but an old man who was left behind from a tourist bus asks Iketani to take him to his destination instead. Iketani being a nice guy, can`t say no. Will he miss the meeting yet again?
Note: Aired as pay-per-view on SkyPerfecTV before actual DVD release.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="779">4.76</permanent>
<temporary count="787">6.70</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>13162.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10222</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5228</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/initial/initial.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.animax.co.jp/program/NN10001248</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.avexmovie.jp/wk/000082.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2355</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331852</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10776</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2766" parentid="2759" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>street racing</name>
<description>Seen The Fast and The Furious or played Need for Speed Underground series? This is it: people racing in illegal races on the streets with their own modified cars and maybe seeing the police chasing them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4258" parentid="2759" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>drifting</name>
<description>Drifting is a driving technique where the driver intentionally oversteers, causing loss of traction in the rear wheels, while maintaining control from entry to exit of a corner. A car is drifting when the rear slip angle is greater than the front slip angle, to such an extent that often the front wheels are pointing in the opposite direction to the turn (e.g. car is turning left, wheels are pointed right or vice versa).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5584" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>euro-beat</name>
<description>Euro-beat, as the name implies, is a music genre from Europe. It is a sub-genre of 80s Italo-disco (aka 80s Euro-disco). In Japan, this label is strongly tied to dance and para-para music.
A good example is the entire Initial D soundtrack.</description>
<picurl>169134.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9199" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-04">
<rating votes="168">8.59</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiwara Takumi is the main character in Initial D. Takumi has been driving up and down Akina mountain using a panda coloured Toyota Corolla Sprinter Trueno (AE86) since the age of 12, doing deliveries for his father`s tofu shop. Because of this, he has became a very skilled driver and after overtaking http://anidb.net/ch9257 [Takahashi Keisuke] he is thrown into the world of mountain pass racing.</description>
<picture>174502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9259" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-10">
<rating votes="83">1.91</rating>
<name>Takeuchi Itsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Itsuki Takeuchi is http://anidb.net/ch9259 [Takumi]`s best friend; he provides the comic relief in the series, and is generally quite loud and obnoxious. Itsuki works part-time at a gas station with Takumi and http://anidb.net/ch9273 [Iketani]; Itsuki plans to use the money he earns to buy an AE86 Corolla Levin (to complement Takumi`s AE86 Trueno) but mistakenly buys an inferior (less power, poor brakes, less chassis breaking, and worse suspension) AE85.</description>
<picture>160190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9273" type="main character in" update="2014-08-27">
<rating votes="37">6.43</rating>
<name>Iketani Kouichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iketani Kouichirou, one of http://anidb.net/ch9199 [Takumi]`s friends, works at a local gas station with both Takumi and http://anidb.net/ch9259 [Itsuki]. Itsuki admires him, as Iketani is leader of the local racing team, the Akina Speed Stars. Iketani drives a Nissan S13 Silvia. At first, Iketani thinks that the Speed Stars are the best drivers in Akina but later his boss Yuuichi tells Iketani of the mysterious driver of an AE86 who was the fastest driver in his time, and that he suspects that the driver is the owner of the local tofu shop.</description>
<picture>160189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32352" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-17">
<rating votes="24">7.28</rating>
<name>Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32366" type="appears in" update="2011-05-17">
<rating votes="11">7.04</rating>
<name>Tachibana Yuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32426" type="main character in" update="2014-09-06">
<rating votes="16">8.18</rating>
<name>Satou Mako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satou Mako is the driver of the Usui combination which she forms with her co-driver http://anidb.net/ch32427 [Sayuki]. She drives blue Nissan Sileighty (RPS13).</description>
<picture>160509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32427" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-06">
<rating votes="24">4.13</rating>
<name>Sayuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sayuki is the co-driver of the Usui combination which she forms with the driver http://anidb.net/ch32426 [Satou Mako].</description>
<picture>160510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49809" type="appears in" update="2012-10-11">
<name>Roujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Old man who was left behind by a tourist bus.</description>
<picture>126733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11009" picture="39517.jpg">Miyazawa Tadashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49810" type="appears in" update="2012-10-11">
<name>Iketani no Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iketani`s mother.</description>
<picture>126734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6871" picture="51988.jpg">Terase Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49811" type="appears in" update="2012-10-11">
<name>Chapatsu A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of men who challenged Mako.</description>
<picture>126735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2002" picture="21307.jpg">Katsu Anri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49812" type="appears in" update="2012-10-11">
<name>Chapatsu B</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of men who challenged Mako.</description>
<picture>126736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4719" picture="27542.jpg">Ikeda Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="92991" update="2013-06-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2008-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
