<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6153" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-01-07</startdate>
<enddate>2009-07-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hajime no Ippo: The Fighting! - New Challenger</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Боен дух: Нов претендент</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Боен дух: Нов противник</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ippo2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">神拳一步 New Challenger 第二季</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">HNI2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">はじめの一歩 The Fighting! New Challenger</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">더 파이팅 New Challenger</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">第一神拳 New Challenger</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9982" type="Sequel">Hajime no Ippo: The Fighting! - Rising</anime>
<anime id="1086" type="Prequel">Hajime no Ippo: The Fighting! - Kimura Tatsuya vs Mashiba Ryo</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="25">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="250429">This is the sequel to one of my favorite classics. Watch as local boxers, who have risen to be the best in Japan, face the world. Watch their struggle with training, tragedy and despair as dreams seem to be crushed, and laugh as they find time to rest and jest after intense national title defense matches. See the bonds created between fellow boxers in respect and feel the rage swell up from the cocky statements, taunts, and provocation from rivals.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="258497">It`s one of the best sport anime.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watch wich your own eyes ¬¬.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="309738">good character development and the best sport anime by far</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="344571">Very good anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="272616">if liked season 1 you must this one!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="181980">It`s Ippo!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="162513">I thought boxing was for thugs and brutes until I saw this masterpiece.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="180353">Highly recommended. The following of the best sport/boxing anime ever!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="135091">the best sports anime ever!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="160946">Hajime no Ippo is one of the very very few sports anime worth watching. 

I would be content to watch this show for the rest of my life.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="248240">One of the greatest Sport animes out there because of it`s comedy and awesome characters. This is a sequal. A third season is ongoing named Hajime no Ippo Rising.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="194756">Well worth watching, and very enjoyable.
You also do not need to have seen the first season to enjoy this (I watched this first, and started watching s1 as a result)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.vap.co.jp/ippo2/</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="3931" type="Original Work">Morikawa George</name>
<name id="3724" type="Series Composition">Fudeyasu Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="7932" type="Direction">Shishido Jun</name>
<name id="4393" type="Music">Hirano Yoshihisa</name>
<name id="4994" type="Character Design">Sugiura Kouji</name>
<name id="4994" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugiura Kouji</name>
<name id="6910" type="Music">Taniuchi Hideki</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch23 [Makunouchi Ippo] continues his boxing career still in search of what it means to be strong and fueled by the desire to fight his idol http://anidb.net/ch24 [Miyata Ichirou]. Along for the ride are pro boxers http://anidb.net/ch3 [Takamura], http://anidb.net/ch106 [Aoki] and http://anidb.net/ch107 [Kimura], each one aspiring to their own dreams.
Edited Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2867">8.88</permanent>
<temporary count="2934">8.65</temporary>
<review count="2">6.08</review>
</ratings>
<picture>15960.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10387</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5258</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4398</identifier>
<identifier>mcnooh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.vap.co.jp/ippo2/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1551</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>332635</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10750</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="183" parentid="2751" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-25">
<name>boxing</name>
<description>Boxing is a combat sport in which two people, usually wearing protective gloves, throw punches at each other for a predetermined set of time in a boxing ring.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-19">
<rating votes="467">8.88</rating>
<name>Takamura Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mamoru Takamura (鷹村 守, Takamura Mamoru?), voiced by Rikiya Koyama, is a strong boxer that has never lost a match. He has an incredible athletic ability that shows through in his strength. Takamura also has an insatiable appetite for women, which is only overshadowed by his obsession for victory. At one point, he single-handedly knocks out an adult bear while sustaining gashes on his arm and most notably on his chest. The weakened bear is eventually killed, and he is dubbed "The Bear Slayer", he honors it by wearing its pelt, and the scars proudly.
He originally is a delinquent that often gets into fights. Because of his strength, he often leaves the victims with serious injuries. He was disowned by his family due to a brawl initiated by Takamura that happened during a rugby match (with his older brother competing), when fans started booing Takamura`s brother, by the time the brawl was over, at least 20 people were beat up. After that incident, he continues to fight until he meets Coach Kamogawa. After weeks of training, and without a single spar, Takamura defeats his first opponent in 25 seconds of the first round by KO. His aspiration is to conquer the World Title in several weight classes, from Junior Middleweight and up.</description>
<picture>10685.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23" type="main character in" update="2014-09-19">
<rating votes="333">8.18</rating>
<name>Makunouchi Ippo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makunouchi Ippo is a shy fellow and gets bullied throughout highschool until one day he meets Takamura who introduces him into the world of boxing. This sparks a determination to find an answer to one question "How does it feel to be strong?".
Noticed by Takamura`s coach Genji Kamogawa, he starts training in the Kamogawa gym where he rapidly grows into a boxing prodigy.</description>
<picture>161203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="332" picture="47528.jpg">Kiyasu Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-19">
<rating votes="100">6.91</rating>
<name>Miyata Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyata a very skilled outboxer who specializes in counter punches. Considered by many to be a boxing prodigy, he uses the boxing style his father used. After his father was forced to retire, Miyata decides to take on his style of boxing to prove its worth, and to go above and beyond him. He begins at Kamogawa Gym, but after losing to Ippo, he later transfers to Kawahara Gym in hopes of one day facing Ippo in an official match. Miyata himself looked down on Ippo a little at first, but after he helped Ippo to buy new boots for their first match, he started to respect him more, developing a friendly rivalry.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>10688.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-08">
<rating votes="138">8.73</rating>
<name>Kamogawa Genji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head coach and founder of the Kamogawa gym. He fought as a prizefighter in Japan shortly after the end of the Second World War. Along with his friends, Ginpachi Nekota and Dankichi Hama, Kamogawa developed a style of fighting that both presumably became the forerunner of boxing in Japan and emphasized scientific theory in its techniques. In his prime, Kamogawa`s talents included the fearsome, yet self-destructive, Tekken (Iron Fist) blow which is a left hook body blow enough to knock someone down and an unyielding spirit which has been passed onto his students. As a coach, Kamogawa`s wealth of knowledge and experience has been tapped into on multiple occasions during training as well as in matches. He may seem to be a bit gruff towards his boxers, but maintains very strong relationships based on trust and spirit; i.e., he rescued Takamura from his life as a thug by introducing him to boxing. Although he rarely admits it aloud, he is extremely proud of his two best reliable straight-forward boxers, Takamura and Ippo.
Voiced by: Kenji Utsumi</description>
<picture>14338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-19">
<rating votes="143">8.56</rating>
<name>Aoki Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoki Masaru is Ippo`s senpai and Kimura`s best friend. Aoki provides much of the gym`s comic relief and exercises one of the world`s most unusual fighting styles. A few of his signature techniques include the fan-favorite Frog Punch, double punch, an untorqued (ineffective) corkscrew punch, and the utterly ridiculous Lookaway. In the past, he and Kimura were the toughest high-school thugs around, but now Aoki`s real job is at a ramen restaurant. Due to the numerous times being dumped by the pretty girls in high school, he`s developed a taste for women with unattractive faces. He has fought for the Japanese lightweight championship and shares an apartment with his girlfriend, Tomiko, a friend of Kumi Mashiba whose nice personality and good body more than compensate for her less-than-stellar face. Aoki seems to be based off of hardcore fight fan hero Emanuel Augustus for his offbeat fighting style and record. His current record stands at 10-6-4, with 6 KOs.</description>
<picture>10686.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-19">
<rating votes="97">7.82</rating>
<name>Kimura Tatsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ippo`s senpai and Aoki`s best friend. He is the smooth, collected type and a romantic at heart, but trains as hard as anyone. His style incorporates a fast left and faster footwork. In training for his bid for the Japanese junior lightweight championship against Ryo Mashiba, he developed a devastating vertical combination known as the Dragon Fish Blow. In the past, he and Aoki were the toughest high-school thugs around, but now Tatsuya`s real job is at his family`s flower shop. His current record stands at 16-5-3, with 8 KOs. After losing to Ryo Mashiba, he announced his retirement from boxing. Shortly after, unable to stay away from boxing, he returned saying he`d spell his name in katakana (タツヤ, Tatsuya) instead of kanji (達也,, Tatsuya).
Voiced by: Keiji Fujiwara</description>
<picture>10687.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="111" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-08">
<rating votes="103">7.21</rating>
<name>Mashiba Kumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kumi is Ryo Mashiba`s sweet-natured, but hard-working and willful younger sister, and as such understands him better than anyone else. She will do almost anything to support her brother and make him happy, including going to his matches even though she doesn`t like to see him get hurt.
Kumi tends to be modest and shy, but she will stand up for her brother and friends at a moments notice.
Voiced by: Sanae Kobayashi</description>
<picture>14389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3424" picture="24518.jpg">Hirata Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="112" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-19">
<rating votes="83">7.57</rating>
<name>Mashiba Ryo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known by ringnames such as the "Executioner" or "Shinigami (God of Death)" by those who watch his matches, Mashiba is one of the most intimidating boxers in the series. He effectively combines an inhuman reach and the offensive Detroit version of the Hitman stance that was used by the American boxer Thomas Hearns who ruled 5 classes of boxing weights by this style to create a devastating whip like technique known as the Flicker Jab to eat away at his opponent`s guard and resolve. Those fortunate and/or skilled enough to make it through his barrier-like Flicker still have to deal with his power-packed Chopping Right, which cuts down those who would deal damage up-close.
Voiced by: Masahiko Tanaka</description>
<picture>10689.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="284" picture="225436.jpg">Tanaka Masahiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="115" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-08">
<rating votes="46">4.83</rating>
<name>Yagi Haruhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The manager of Kamogawa Gym and a part-time trainer. Friendly and knowledgeable, "Yagi-chan" (as his pupils affectionately call him) is also in charge of securing match posters, selling tickets, and anything else involving the gym`s finances. He knows a great deal about boxing himself, having been a boxer at Kamogawa Gym once. Additionally, although Yagi was not a skilled boxer nor a good second member, but he is a master fisherman who can outfish anyone.
Voiced by: Toshihiko Nakajima</description>
<picture>14394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="117" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-08">
<rating votes="20">5.09</rating>
<name>Miyata no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichiro Miyata`s father and coach, and the one who passed on to him the love of boxing. Formerly a Japan and OPBF champion in his prime, when Ichiro was a very young boy he lost soundly to Randy Boy and had his jaw fractured, so he chose to retire despite having the chance to make a comeback. As a witness of his father`s fall from grace, Ichiro decided to take on his style and become the best with it.</description>
<picture>14395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="125" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-07">
<rating votes="38">6.56</rating>
<name>Makunouchi Hiroko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiroko is Ippo`s widowed mother. She is a very kind and strong willed woman who cares for her son a great deal. She started running the fishing business after her husband, Kazuo, died after saving his friend Sakuma. Though she refuses to attend any of Ippo`s matches because she doesn`t want to watch him get hurt, she supports his boxing wholeheartedly because she knows how much joy it has brought to his life and how it has helped him with his self-esteem. Since Kazuo`s death, Ippo and Hiroko have been more or less alone in the world; so the strength of their family bond is no surprise.</description>
<picture>14400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3200" picture="24192.jpg">Terauchi Yorie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="421" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="26">5.74</rating>
<name>Umezawa Masahiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate of Ippo`s, Umezawa was the leader of a group of students who would regularly bully him. Together with his two flunkies, he made a habit of beating Ippo up, until the day that Takamura stopped him. After an initial failure to confront the fledgling boxer, Umezawa soon began to cheer Ippo on in his matches, and eventually took a job at the Makunouchi family fishing business to help out when Ippo`s mother became ill. His ultimate goal, however, is to become a manga artist, and he eventually left his job to pursue it. In spite of all they went through in high school, the two are now the best of friends.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>14717.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="423" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="45">6.48</rating>
<name>Fujii Minoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A reporter for a boxing magazine who has been following Ippo`s career since his fights with Miyata. Occasionally he drops by with information concerning opposing fighters in upcoming matches for the Kamogawa gym members.</description>
<picture>14719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="338" picture="17174.jpg">Ono Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="431" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-10">
<rating votes="58">7.35</rating>
<name>Sendou Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An aggressive mid-range fighter, his specialty punch is the "Smash". He resides in the Naniwa Ward of Osaka, where his is known as "Rocky" and the "Naniwa Tiger." His "Rocky" nickname was influenced by his power boxing style similar to that of Rocky Marciano, the only heavyweight champion in history to retire undefeated. In a recent interview with Shounen Magazine, Hajime no Ippo`s manga-ka, Jyoji Morikawa said that Hidekazu Akai was also one of his models for Sendo. Like Sendo, Akai was from Osaka and was nicknamed the Naniwa Rocky.
Voiced by Masaya Onosaka</description>
<picture>14727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="853" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-30">
<rating votes="17">5.89</rating>
<name>Yamada Naomichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His initial nickname was "Geromichi" (a Japanese pun based on the fact that he threw up after every part of training). While in public he is awkward and uncomfortable, Naomichi puts everything into his training for his hope for strength and self-confidence.</description>
<picture>15170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="948" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-05">
<rating votes="26">2.93</rating>
<name>Shinoda Tomoyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the trainers at the Kamogawa Gym. Because he oversees the training of some of Kamogawa boxers, he is normally a second to some of them during their matches.
Voiced by: Seiji Sasaki</description>
<picture>15291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3441" picture="149777.jpg">Sasaki Seiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8558" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="14">1.35</rating>
<name>Bryan Hawk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raised in the toughest parts of New York, Bryan Hawk is an incredibly talented fighter that earns the title of WBC Junior Middleweight Champion.
He has a borderline psychotic personality and a contemptuous attitude.</description>
<picture>3001.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12521" type="appears in" update="2009-10-24">
<rating votes="6">7.85</rating>
<name>Kamogawa Boxing Gym</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>37728.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12522" type="appears in" update="2009-10-25">
<rating votes="3">5.25</rating>
<name>Kawahara Boxing Gym</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>37820.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12530" type="appears in" update="2009-10-24">
<rating votes="8">2.44</rating>
<name>Otowa Gym Kaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12531" type="appears in" update="2009-10-24">
<rating votes="2">3.43</rating>
<name>Hachinohe Kentou Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Hachinohe Boxing Association.</description>
<picture>37741.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12532" type="appears in" update="2009-10-24">
<rating votes="10">6.05</rating>
<name>Hachinohe Kentou Kai Kaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12539" type="appears in" update="2009-10-24">
<rating votes="8">3.56</rating>
<name>Kawahara Gym Kaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37746.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12580" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-23">
<rating votes="48">8.51</rating>
<name>Date Eiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At an age swiftly approaching thirty, Date is an old-timer for a boxer, but is nevertheless the man that Ippo looks up to. Years ago, he lost his World Title Match to the champion, Ricardo Martinez, who was defending his title for the 2nd time. He was knocked out in the 2nd round, and among other injuries, got a scar on the bridge of his then-fractured nose.
Date gave up boxing after that in order to settle down with his wife Aiko (a woman from a rich family who sacrificed a lot to be with him, and who just had a miscarriage at that time) and raise a family. But Date was a born boxer -- he found he could not contain his combative nature for long, and after Aiko told him that she wanted their son Yuuji to see his dad fight, he picked his career back up to the top. Date is strong in every way, but his greatest weapon is the Heartbreak Shot, a corkscrew blow to the heart that immobilizes the opponent.
He is the sole boxer to have defeated Ippo in the ring, making Kamogawa throw the towel.
After this fateful match, Date went after the WBA title - a rematch with Ricardo Martinez, who was making his 18th title defence - but lost by K.O. in the 10th round. The injuries he received in this fight included broken hands and a fractured jaw, and seriously limited Date`s chances of making a return to the ring. He has, however, passed on his dream to Ippo. Currently, he trains other boxers at the Nakadai Gym. Morikawa Jouji stated in an interview that Date was modelled after former OPBF Champion Ozaki Fujio.
At the time of his retirement, Date held a record of 23-2-0 with 17 KO`s. He was the former OPBF Featherweight Champion as well as a two-time JBC Featherweight Champion and has twice been the #1 contender to Ricardo Martinez`s WBA Featherweight Title.</description>
<picture>10690.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="260" picture="17083.jpg">Aizawa Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12625" type="appears in" update="2009-10-28">
<rating votes="8">4.46</rating>
<name>Nakadai Gym Kaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12626" type="appears in" update="2009-10-28">
<rating votes="6">5.93</rating>
<name>Okita Keigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boxer at Nakadai Gym who preceded Ippo as the Rookie of the Year. Okita, an exceedingly serious young man, idolizes Eiji Date to the point of mimicking his style and special techniques. Date`s favor of the relatively inexperienced Makunouchi Ippo inflamed Okita`s jealousy, and he challenged Ippo to a match. Though confident that his special "corkscrew blow", a punch copied from Date, would carry him through the fight, Okita was soundly defeated by Ippo in the first round. Later, he was seen as one of Date`s assistants during his fight with Ippo. It is also shown that he lost to Shimabukuro Iwao before Iwao`s Japanese title match with Ippo.</description>
<picture>37995.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12632" type="appears in" update="2009-10-29">
<rating votes="8">3.08</rating>
<name>Kida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch24 [Miyata]`s manager.</description>
<picture>38047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12659" type="appears in" update="2009-10-30">
<rating votes="8">3.27</rating>
<name>Naomichi no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3240" picture="45305.jpg">Yokoo Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12687" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-01">
<rating votes="29">5.43</rating>
<name>Tomiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="653" picture="18181.jpg">Tsuda Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12691" type="appears in" update="2009-11-02">
<rating votes="15">5.99</rating>
<name>Date Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38218.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12692" type="appears in" update="2009-11-02">
<rating votes="12">5.22</rating>
<name>Date Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38219.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2039" picture="41388.jpg">Wakabayashi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12790" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-23">
<rating votes="23">7.79</rating>
<name>Nekota Ginpachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Making his home a lonely shack up in the mountain forests, Nekota is http://anidb.net/ch61 [Kamogawa]`s best friend of over fifty years. Occasionally, http://anidb.net/ch61 [Kamogawa] will visit him in the mountains, once taking http://anidb.net/ch23 [Ippo] and the others there to train for upcoming fights. While a meddling old geezer who tends to overstay his welcome, he is nonetheless loyal, good-hearted and trustworthy to the boys at the http://anidb.net/ch12521 [Kamogawa Gym]. Nekota proved a far greater technical boxer than even http://anidb.net/ch61 [Kamogawa]; but as a result of their constant spars, he developed the beginning stages of punch-drunk syndrome. Despite this condition, Nekota took it upon himself to challenge an arrogant American military officer, Ralph Anderson, in a boxing match to boost Japanese morale. Though Nekota had the upper hand, Anderson won by throwing an illegal rabbit punch, which resulted in permanent mid-brain damage.</description>
<picture>38406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="201" picture="17016.jpg">Nagai Ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12791" type="appears in" update="2009-11-06">
<rating votes="16">6.04</rating>
<name>Hachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hachi (lit. eight) is Nekota`s pet dog. He is a very friendly dog that goes wherever Nekota does. Nekota even snuck him into Korakuen Hall for Ippo`s title fight against Sendo.</description>
<picture>38407.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13109" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-23">
<rating votes="50">5.71</rating>
<name>Iimura Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 23-year-old sportswriter who works alongside http://anidb.net/ch423 [Fujii]. Iimura`s calm indifference and sharp wit serve often to put off those who would judge her only for beauty, but she is an avid boxing fan and, though less experienced than some, an outstanding journalist.</description>
<picture>38966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13219" type="appears in" update="2009-11-23">
<rating votes="2">3.43</rating>
<name>Kinoshita Boxing Gym</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>39212.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13223" type="appears in" update="2009-11-29">
<rating votes="6">5.19</rating>
<name>Sanada Kazuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Handsome and highly intelligent, Sanada`s full-time job is as a doctor at the same hospital in which http://anidb.net/ch111 [Kumi] works. Before moving up to the Featherweight division, he had a very successful reign as the JBC Jr. Featherweight Champion, defending the title five times. He is the pupil of http://anidb.net/ch61 [Kamogawa Genji]`s old nemesis, http://anidb.net/ch13222 [Hama Dankichi], and in a fight, he uses his immense knowledge of human physical capabilities to predict his opponents` moves. His specialties include two of http://anidb.net/ch13222 [Dankichi]`s inventions: the "Hien" (飛燕) -- named after a model of highly maneuverable Japanese fight plane, it`s an unpredictable left jab known in English as the Swallow -- and the "Tsubame Gaeshi", a piercing double uppercut known in English as the Swallow`s Return.
After his failed attempt to obtain the Featherweight Championship from Ippo, he retires from boxing to continue his work as a doctor. Sanada`s character is fairly reminiscent of mid-1980s boxer "The Fighting Physician" Dr. Terry Christle, who had been the Irish national Middleweight champion and chief sparring partner of Marvelous Marvin Hagler during his training for his super fight against Sugar Ray Leonard. Christle had earned his Ph.D at the Royal College of Surgeons in Ireland, but before embarking on a medical career had wanted to give boxing a try, ultimately retiring in 1987. At the time of his retirement, Sanada held a record of 13-2-1 with 9 knockouts.</description>
<picture>39179.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13356" type="appears in" update="2009-11-30">
<rating votes="3">2.11</rating>
<name>Sakaguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boxing promoter for the OPBF.
He has a personal vendetta against Miyata for defeating his champion client Arnie Gregory. He is currently promoting Randy Boy Jr. as part of his revenge. He is short, high strung, and greatly resembles an Asian Don King. His nationality is unknown, but he can speak fluent English. Even his own boxers seem to dislike him as shown by Arnie firing him and Randy constantly ignoring him or telling him off. After Randy`s loss to Ichiro Miyata, Sakaguchi nullified their contract. Shortly after Takamura`s title defense the same night he accidentally struck Sakaguchi (who he thought was responsible for his less than stellar defense) and Sakaguchi has since stated that he will never return to Japan. Mr. Sakaguchi possesses some of the same mannerisms, personality traits, and even haircut as promoter Don King.</description>
<picture>39487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13357" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="3">4.54</rating>
<name>Arnie Gregory</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arnie Gregory is an Australian boxer nicknamed "The Crocodile", his punches, especially hooks, are very powerful. He also uses a technique against counterpunchers called Bloody Cross.
He was the OPBF Champion but lost his title to Miyata. He was KO`d by Miyata`s Jolt Counter when Miyata was almost done. He fired his manager, Mr Sakaguchi, before the end of his match with Miyata because of Sakaguchi thinking of boxing as nothing more than a way of making money and thus failing to understand the feelings of the fighters.</description>
<picture>39488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13358" type="appears in" update="2009-11-30">
<rating votes="5">6.78</rating>
<name>Wanpo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wanpo is one of http://anidb.net/ch12791 [Hachi]`s sons. http://anidb.net/ch12790 [Nekota] gave him to http://anidb.net/ch23 [Ippo] soon after http://anidb.net/ch23 [Ippo] won the Japanese Featherweight Championship. His name is a combination of English and Japanese to form a pun on http://anidb.net/ch23 [Ippo]`s name, which literally means "one step". One pronounced using Japanese syllables is Wan (ワン, One).</description>
<picture>39492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13388" type="appears in" update="2009-12-01">
<rating votes="16">7.81</rating>
<name>Ricardo Martinez</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The longtime reigning WBA Featherweight Champion, Martinez is considered the only active Super Champion in the world. Having made quick work of Date and sixty other unlucky opponents, Martinez is undefeated and seemingly invincible, as he demonstrated to Ippo in a one-sided sparring match. His strength, speed, ability, and reflexes are almost otherworldly. Martinez is also touted to have "the world`s best jab", a jab with no shoulder movement and a very powerful snap. Though he rarely deigns to speak to his opponents, Martinez respects boxers who manage to last more than a round or two against him. The boxer he respects most is Date, as Date pushed him further than anyone else ever had in their rematch. Even so, Martinez`s face was not even swollen up from their rematch, whereas Date`s injuries were so bad that he had to retire. Martinez currently holds a record of 68-0 with 64 KO`s. Martinez`s style, demeanor, and career is based on retired world champion Ricardo Lopez, who defended the WBC strawweight title 22 times and is the third champion history to retire undefeated.</description>
<picture>39516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2730" picture="22755.jpg">Sugawara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13389" type="appears in" update="2009-12-01">
<rating votes="3">3.73</rating>
<name>Bill Stewart</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5977" picture="30601.jpg">Omoro Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13529" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="5">5.56</rating>
<name>Hammer Nao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13534" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-18">
<rating votes="15">5.49</rating>
<name>Itagaki Manabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most recent addition to the roster, the charming Manabu has a prodigy`s talent and was the captain of his high school`s boxing team. Cheerful and a lover of bad puns (as are the rest of his family), Manabu is a fierce outboxer with extremely high speed and reflexes and whose fighting style is uncanny in its resemblance to Miyata`s. His most powerful technique is a furious hail of mid-power blows known as the Hedgehog or Porcupine, which was employed in an East Japan Rookie Kings showdown with his longtime nemesis, Kyosuke Imai. Outside of boxing, Manabu is employed as an assistant at the Makounouchi family`s fishing business. Itagaki`s character is based on retired world champion Oscar de La Hoya for his prodigy-like natural ability and good looks, whom Itagaki has admitted to idolizing in the manga. His current record as the Rookie King of his class stands at 11 Matches 10-1-1 (W-L-D), with 8 KOs.</description>
<picture>10691.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13535" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="3">3.93</rating>
<name>Badei Maguramo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39692.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13599" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="3">5.36</rating>
<name>Imai Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The longtime rival of http://anidb.net/ch13534 [Itagaki Manabu], Imai was the one boxer who managed to thwart Itagaki in his high-school days. They fought a total of three times in the amateur ring; each time Imai was victorious. His build, KO pattern, and even hairstyle are remarkably similar to those of Itagaki`s senpai, Makunouchi Ippo. Imai is ordinarily cool and composed, bearing a poker face even in the heat of battle. It seems the only people who can rouse him out of this perpetual calm are Ippo, Itagaki, and Itagaki`s sister Nanako -- with whom Imai is very much smitten.</description>
<picture>39825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13601" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="3">2.77</rating>
<name>Makino Fumito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2328" picture="171565.jpg">Satou Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13602" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="3">2.24</rating>
<name>Makino no Trainer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10999" picture="171547.jpg">Katsunuma Kiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13603" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Sayama Boxing Gym</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="13604" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="3">3.24</rating>
<name>Arman Alegria</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11050" picture="39835.jpg">Morikawa Ryuuta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13605" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="3">3.93</rating>
<name>Morris West</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13606" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="3">2.12</rating>
<name>Morris no Second</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1406" picture="18432.jpg">Suzuki Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13614" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="3">3.93</rating>
<name>Takamura Suguru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13616" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="3">5.19</rating>
<name>Takamura Kyouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13618" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="3">3.78</rating>
<name>Takamura Wataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="435" picture="188447.jpg">Matsumoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13619" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="4">2.92</rating>
<name>Miguel Zale</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13620" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="3">3.93</rating>
<name>Yi Yonsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39866.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13656" type="appears in" update="2009-12-08">
<rating votes="3">3.52</rating>
<name>Itagaki Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3362" picture="69121.jpg">Fukuda Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13657" type="appears in" update="2009-12-08">
<rating votes="3">4.71</rating>
<name>Itagaki Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="309" picture="17145.jpg">Sonozaki Mie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13658" type="appears in" update="2009-12-08">
<rating votes="5">4.98</rating>
<name>Itagaki Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch13534 [Itagaki Manabu]`s younger sister. A flirtatious "genki" girl, Nanako is 16 years old and extremely interested in boys, harboring a particular taste for fighting men. She develops a crush on Ippo shortly after Itagaki introduces them, and finds herself competing with Kumi and Iimura for his attention.</description>
<picture>39973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13660" type="appears in" update="2009-12-08">
<rating votes="3">3.93</rating>
<name>Baraki Haseo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39976.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="96092" update="2009-01-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96178" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる一歩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Step</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratanaru Ippo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96179" update="2009-01-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96180" update="2009-01-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96206" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Bloody cross -血の十字架-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bloody Cross</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bloody Cross -Chi no Juujika-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96356" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界の力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">World Class Strength</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai no Chikara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96357" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界への胎動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Towards the World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai e no Taidou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96358" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束の場所へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Promised Place</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku no Basho e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96920" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追い続ける背中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Figure to Chase After</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oitsuzukeru Senaka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96965" update="2009-02-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔の降臨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Devil`s Advent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma no Kourin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97090" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魂の一撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spirit For One Last Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamashii no Ichigeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97211" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">受け継ぐ資格</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inheritance Qualifications</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uketsugu Shikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97265" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">噛ませ犬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cannon Fodder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamase Inu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97392" update="2014-04-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一歩VSハンマーナオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ippo vs. Hammer Nao</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ippo vs. Hammer Nao</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97450" update="2010-01-07">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロの条件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Requirements For A Pro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pro no Jouken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97681" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イッポ・オン・ザ・ビーチ2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ippo on the Beach 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ippo on the Beach 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98642" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Parody Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98837" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二つのスパーリング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sparring Between the Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatsu no Sparring</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99349" update="2009-04-08">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">板垣, デビュー戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Itagaki`s Debut Fight!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itagaki, Debut-sen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99686" update="2009-04-14">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極限の減量</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Extreme Weight Management</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokugen no Genryou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99687" update="2009-04-14">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">野生児</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wild Kid</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yaseiji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99688" update="2009-04-14">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二羽の鷹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Hawks</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Niwa no Taka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99913" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="11">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">王様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The King</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ou-sama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99914" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">支える手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Supporting Hand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasaeru Te</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99915" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケンカバトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brawl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenka Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99916" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BATTLE OF HAWK!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of Hawk!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Battle of Hawk!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99917" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界J・ミドル級タイトルマッチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Junior Middleweight World Title Match</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai J Middle-kyuu Title Match</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99918" update="2009-04-27">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一触即発</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Critical Situation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isshokusokuhatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104291" update="2009-06-19">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銅像をどうぞ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Please Accept This Bronze Statue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Douzou o Douzo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104894" update="2009-07-03">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">New Challenger</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Challenger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">New Challenger</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
