<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6169" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-07-09</startdate>
<enddate>2009-09-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ookami to Koushinryou II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Spice and Wolf 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Spicy Wolf II</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Волчица и пряности II</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Aktar ve Kurt II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ookami to Koushinryou 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">狼與辛香料II</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">狼与香辛料II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">SW2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">saw2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">SaWII</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">S&amp;W2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">S&amp;WII</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">otk2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">狼と香辛料II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Spice and Wolf II</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">늑대와 향신료 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6465" type="Prequel">Ookami to Koushinryou II: Ookami to Kohakuiro no Yuuutsu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="21">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="392207">too much flirting and less conflict... the first season is better...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="281568">This is highly recommended!!!
The art is fantastic, the writing is excellent and the characters are memorable.  The characters  relationships don`t regress like some other anime sequels but they stay true to their characters the whole way through and it adds to the believability of the story.  If you like intelligent and intricate storytelling like DeathNote then watch this and part 1.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="369287">Pretty cool:)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="402522">It has a very unique mood. Slow paced but very intresting if you are into medieval times, + this anime shows the most realistic picture of the age.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="306093">want to see it .. all episoded in a row ...!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="208300">My all time favourite anime series. If you like Middle ages setting and beautiful sceneries. Check this one out!
10/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="261604">Can`t wait!!!!! MUST SEE!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="320325">You can`t die until you see this, and the first season, its a MUST see...if you die before then I am very very sorry for you!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="183015">With the exception of medieval economics, this is the best story about pair relationship among anime genre. No harem. No tsundere. I love it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="446193">It`s every bit as good as its parent, and dreams for continuation much like its continuation. Spice and Wolf II continues the story of the lovable [i]Holo[/i] and her silver-tongued companion Lawrence as the viewer sees their relationship and the characters themselves grow.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="428629">a classic sequel to what to be the greatest romantic old love story....this anime rocks....a must see for those loves classic/western stories/romance ,,,,please watch the 1st season first...</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.spicy-wolf.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="1417" type="Character Design">Kobayashi Toshimitsu</name>
<name id="1417" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kobayashi Toshimitsu</name>
<name id="1558" type="Music">Yoshino Yuuji</name>
<name id="3211" type="Direction">Takahashi Takeo</name>
<name id="1432" type="Original Work">Hasekura Isuna</name>
<name id="20046" type="Animation Work">Marvy Jack</name>
<name id="1417" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kobayashi Toshimitsu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr1432 [Hasekura Isuna], continuation of the first season: http://anidb.net/a5406 [Ookami to Koushinryou].
Following http://anidb.net/ch2818 [Kraft Lawrence] (Spice) an experienced travelling merchant and his sharp-tongued 600-year-old pagan deity companion http://anidb.net/ch29 [Holo] (Wolf) on their journey to return to Yoitsu, Holo`s home in the north. A tender relationship has blossomed between the characters, as they make deals, travel between cities, encounter religious fanatics, overcoming the daily toils of a travelling merchant.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5800">8.49</permanent>
<temporary count="5850">8.33</temporary>
<review count="3">7.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>233306.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10269</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5341</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6884</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4469</identifier>
<identifier>tsktzo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.spicy-wolf.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Spice_and_Wolf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>狼と香辛料</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1686</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334105</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11457</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2380</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2009/ookami_to_koushinryou2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-08">
<name>ambitious</name>
<description>having a strong desire for success or achievement; wanting power, money, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2439" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>PIC NEEDS IMPROVEMENT</name>
<description>This entry has a poor picture and needs to have it replaced by a higher-quality alternative. Causes may include: it is too small; its colours or lighting are bad; it has excessive compression or other encoding issues; it is from non-anime sources (anime/char); the face is hard to see (char/creator); the hair/eye/skin colours do not match the anime (char); it does not represent their usual appearance (char); among others. If you can, please swap a better picture in and remove this tag. Thank you.</description>
<picurl>224875.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3423" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>religious persecution</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3932" parentid="6073" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-11">
<name>older female younger male</name>
<description>This tag indicates that this anime has a male and female lead, and the female is older. If the main cast is greater than two people, then the use of this tag would indicate a romantic relationship between those two.
In case of harems it translates to:
a) majority of the girls are older than the guy
b) the lead girl (or her main rival) is older than the guy</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4271" parentid="2876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-29">
<name>corrupt church</name>
<description>An official religion (not cult or sect) has become evil or was evil to begin with, and tends to be highly influential with political leaders, to strengthen / enforce the church`s power over the people.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4642" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-08">
<name>economics</name>
<description>Economics is the social science that studies economic activity to gain an understanding of the processes that govern the production, distribution and consumption of goods and services in an economy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29" type="main character in" update="2017-12-29">
<rating votes="2235">9.20</rating>
<name>Holo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Holo is a wolf harvest deity originally from a land in the north known as Yoitsu. She made a promise with men from a town called Pasroe where she would ensure the town would have good wheat harvests year after year. However, as time went on, the townspeople slowly started to forsake Holo and did not rely on her as they once did. As such, Holo escapes from town in Lawrence`s wagon and started traveling with him to see how much the world has changed since she has been in Pasroe. Holo has chosen the form of a girl younger than Lawrence, though she still retains her large white-tipped wolf tail, and ears. Her true form is that of a very large wolf which many people revered and feared.
She refers to herself as the "Wise Wolf of Yoitsu" (ヨイツの賢狼, Yoitsu no Kenrou). She is typically very haughty and self-sufficient, though due to her isolation for hundreds of years in Pasroe, she came to feel very lonely, and sometimes shows a more fragile side of herself. She relies on Lawrence for company as she fears loneliness, which is something that Lawrence is very aware of and tries to comfort her in his own way. Holo is also very aware of the different time spans that she and Lawrence have, as a human lifespan is like a blink of an eye for her kind. Holo is shown to be quite scared of that fact but hides it with jokes. She has a peculiar way of speaking, modeled after that of the oiran high-class courtesans. She is fond of delicious food and alcohol, but especially loves apples. She takes pride in her tail and takes special care of it, constantly combing and maintaining it.</description>
<picture>209420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2818" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="252">8.11</rating>
<name>Kraft Lawrence</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kraft Lawrence, who chiefly goes by his surname, is a twenty-five-year-old travelling peddler who goes from town to town buying and selling various things in order to make a living. When he was twelve, he became an apprentice to a merchant relative, and set out on his own at eighteen. His goal in life is to gather enough money to start his own shop, and he has already been travelling for seven years while gaining experience in the trade. He meets Horo one night and eventually agrees to her travelling with him. She helps him by providing her wisdom which helps to increase his profits and get him out of jams. As the series progresses, both Lawrence and Horo demonstrate a growing affection toward each other.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>42502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12412" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-20">
<rating votes="18">7.76</rating>
<name>Dian Rubens</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dian Rubens is an alchemist, who is in the process of chronicling pagan tales and beliefs so as to print them in books. She also carries information about Horo`s birthplace Yoitsu. According to Horo, Dianna is not human, but a bird even bigger than Lawrence. She fell in love with a traveling priest and spent a few years helping him build a church but left because he noticed that she never seemed to grow old and became suspicious.</description>
<picture>37467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12413" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-20">
<rating votes="20">1.43</rating>
<name>Fermi Amati</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amati, who just like Lawrence mainly goes by his surname for business, is a young man who works as a fish broker. Amati is an honest personality, so much in fact that he`s titled as a "white knight". He becomes infactuated by Horo the moment they meet.</description>
<picture>37472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13835" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="16">5.72</rating>
<name>Fleur Bolan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cloaked and shrouded in mysteries, Fleur (or Eve as she introduces herself) is a merchant from the port town of Renos. Due to events in the past, this trader is wary of just about everyone. Although hard to approach, Eve is talkative under the right circumstances and has a keen eye for people and business alike. She is in fact a fallen noble that was once sold as slave to another merchant after her family`s fall. She organized a secret smuggling operation with the church then left it after she felt that they don`t need her cooperation anymore then made a contract with Lawrence.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>42501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14776" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="12">6.69</rating>
<name>Mark Cole</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An old friend of Lawrence who owns his own street stall in Kumerson. He used to be a travelling merchant, but met his future wife, Adele, when in Kumerson, and decided to settle down and become a shopkeeper. He has a 2-year-old child. A young boy named Lant helps him at his stall.</description>
<picture>42504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14777" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="8">5.14</rating>
<name>Eu Lant</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy who works in Mark`s street stall. He is a quick worker who learned the fundamentals of trading and life from Mark.</description>
<picture>42503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4860" picture="211311.jpg">Sasajima Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14778" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="7">4.12</rating>
<name>Arold Eklund</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A quiet, elderly man who works as an inkeeper.</description>
<picture>42505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4688" picture="29259.jpg">Hirota Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14779" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="7">4.54</rating>
<name>Rigolo Deidre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The town chronicler. Lawrence and Holo go to him for information about Holo`s hometown.</description>
<picture>42506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2258" picture="21881.jpg">Uchida Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14780" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="10">4.41</rating>
<name>Merta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A nun who takes care of Rigolo</description>
<picture>42508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14882" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-08">
<rating votes="8">4.54</rating>
<name>Gi Batos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Rowen Trading Company who chiefly handles precious metals. He does business with the "heretical" alchemists and is a friend of Diana.</description>
<picture>42690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="325" picture="223404.jpg">Akagi Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14883" type="appears in" update="2010-02-08">
<rating votes="3">5.33</rating>
<name>Adele Cole</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mark`s wife.</description>
<picture>42691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4217" picture="151698.jpg">Yanagisawa Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14884" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-08">
<rating votes="19">7.25</rating>
<name>Helena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a clever bartender who knows a lot about the town`s business dealings and gossip.</description>
<picture>42692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="431" picture="23201.jpg">Nakayama Sara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14885" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-08">
<rating votes="6">2.03</rating>
<name>Lutz Eringin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The representative of Helink Trading Company who makes the deal with Lawrence and Fleur considering their "selling Holo" scheme.</description>
<picture>42693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4185" picture="224827.jpg">Ushiyama Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14886" type="appears in" update="2010-02-08">
<rating votes="2">5.24</rating>
<name>Kolker Kues</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18803" picture="223601.jpg">Namura Yukitarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40277" type="appears in" update="2012-01-07">
<rating votes="1">4.11</rating>
<name>Diana no Tsukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diana`s messenger.</description>
<picture>79565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12636" picture="42695.jpg">Mizobe Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40278" type="appears in" update="2012-01-07">
<rating votes="1">4.11</rating>
<name>Monogoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Beggar.</description>
<picture>79566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="98372" update="2009-03-28">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104880" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と嵐の前の静寂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and the Calm Before the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Arashi no Mae no Seijaku</title>
<summary>Instead of taking Holo to the festival as planned, Lawrence is taken by fellow merchant Batos to meet Dianna Rubens, an alchemist, to learn more about Yoitsu. She tells Lawrence of a legend about the bear that destroyed Yoitsu and also of a large wolf near the town of Renos who called herself Holo of Yoitsu. Later when sharing a drink with Mark, Lawrence becomes jealous of Amati, fearing he may be trying to steal Holo away from him. When they both return to the inn, Holo reveals how she lied to Amati, telling him she travels with Lawrence because she owes him a large debt. She also recounts how Amati and a crowd of other festival-goers haggled over pieces of pyrite, greatly inflating their price.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="104881" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼とふとした亀裂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and an Inadvertent Rift</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Futoshita Kiretsu</title>
<summary>Lawrence and Holo travel to Kumerson, where a pagan festival is taking place. Upon arrival, they meet Fermi Amati, a young merchant and Lawrence`s fellow guild member. Amati, who seems smitten with Holo, helps them get a room in the trading company, where Holo drinks too much on the first night and has a hangover the following morning, during which Lawrence sells the nails in his cart to his friend Mark. That night, Lawrence asks Holo a few questions about towns neighboring Yoitsu and ascertains that it will probably take another year or two to reach it. Lawrence suggests that they can split up once they reach the town of Niohira, since it would only take Holo two days to reach Yoitsu from there, but he quickly regrets his lack of tact.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105132" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と埋まらない溝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and the Gap That Cannot Be Filled</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Umaranai Mizo</title>
<summary>In front of the Merchant Guild, Amati challenges Lawrence, proclaiming he will pay for Holo`s falsified debt of 1,000 silver coins and then propose to her, certain that she will leave Lawrence. Lawrence researches Amati, discovering that his plan to pay back the debt relies on the sale of pyrite. Back at the inn, Holo discovers and reads a letter for Lawrence containing an explanation of the legend about the bear that destroyed Yoitsu. When Lawrence returns, she claims that he knew Yoitsu was destroyed the entire time and he has now grown tired of her. Her fit of rage prompts Lawrence to leave the inn.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105473" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と浅知恵の末路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and the End of Shallow Thinking</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Asajie no Matsuro</title>
<summary>Lawrence realizes that he has to drop the price of pyrite or risk losing Holo to Amati. After receiving the information on Amati`s assets, Lawrence finds Amati and proposes a deal based on credit (essentially, a naked short on pyrite), which will result in profit for Amati if the price of pyrite rises or losses if the price of pyrite falls. Amati accepts the deal after Lawrence appeals to his chivalry and causes him to doubt that Holo will agree to his marriage proposal. Unable to enlist Mark`s help to purchase the pyrite necessary to pull off the deal, Lawrence turns to the alchemists in the belief that they should have a large amount of pyrite that he can purchase.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105669" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と希望と絶望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf, Hope and Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Kibou to Zetsubou</title>
<summary>To gain access to the alchemists` quarter, Lawrence asks Batos for a password to meet Dianna. Upon his arrival, Lawrence is told that the pyrite has already been sold on credit. Dianna, however, agrees to sell Lawrence pyrite instead and tells him that she will handle negotiations and contact him upon their completion. The next morning, Lawrence goes to the exchange with Amati and receives fourteen gold coins, equivalent to 300 silver coins, in accordance with their deal. The price of pyrite continues rising, worrying Lawrence.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="106051" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="20">9.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と信ずべき神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Trustworthy God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Shinzubeki Kami</title>
<summary>Lawrence participates in the pyrite market, selling small quantities several times to combat the rapidly rising prices, but to no avail. Lawrence`s original plan falls through when Dianna`s messenger informs him that the negotiations did not go as planned. In despair, Lawrence all but gives up before he is spurred on by Mark`s apprentice, Lant. When Lawrence goes to sell his remaining pyrite, Holo also sells a large bag purchased from Dianna, revealing that she was attempting to help Lawrence from the beginning. The market quickly turns to selling, dropping the price of pyrite and causing Amati huge losses. He fails to fulfill his portion of his challenge to Lawrence and gives up his marriage proposal to Holo as a result. Holo and Lawrence realize what they mean to one another and the two grow closer as they decide to continue traveling together to find Yoitsu.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="106342" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と無謀な商談</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Reckless Negotiation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Mubou na Shoudan</title>
<summary>Lawrence and Holo go see Ligro and are at first awed by the magnificent garden behind his house encased in large glass windows. Ligro brings them downstairs where Holo picks out a few books containing old legends from the north for Lawrence to carry back. Lawrence and Holo spend an enjoyable night together, though Holo later confesses that she is afraid of being separated from Lawrence at the journey`s end. After Holo goes to sleep, Lawrence chats with Eve about her business ventures, but she surprises him by asking whether he would like to sell Holo.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="106343" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と蠱惑的な旅人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and a Fascinating Traveler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Kowakuteki na Tabibito</title>
<summary>Holo and Lawrence visit the port in Renos, where they sit down for a meal. Holo uses her sharp senses and informs Lawrence that foreign fur merchants are unable to sell their wares, resulting in some unrest. However, she becomes inebriated from the meal and has to rest. Lawrence, meanwhile, visits a local bar to gather information and learns that the entire town is on edge due to some issues with the fur trade. After dinner, Lawrence goes to talk with the innkeeper but is interrupted by the arrival of the mysterious cloaked stranger, who introduces herself as Eve Bolan. She and Lawrence briefly chat, and she tells him that they should chat further if their interests coincide.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="106344" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と戯れの日々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Playful Days</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Tawamure no Hibi</title>
<summary>Lawrence and Holo make their way to the chilly port town of Renos, known for its wood and fur. As he enters the town, Lawrence is given a tablet to identify him as a foreign merchant, allowing him to trade in the town. Intrigued by the town`s history and legends, Lawrence decides to investigate. They settle into the local inn, where the innkeeper tells them about people who may be able to help them, including a man named Ligro, who was part of a strange gathering witnessed by Lawrence and Holo upon entering the town. They also meet a mysterious cloaked stranger, who Lawrence mistakes as male. Holo corrects him and jokingly chides him for having eyes for another woman.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108229" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と孤独な微笑み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Lonely Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Kodokuna Hohoemi</title>
<summary>Eve explains the plan to Lawrence: they will sell Holo to gain cash, which they will then use to buy the fur in town. The fur will then be sold in turn at a profit, and Holo will be bought back. After Lawrence explains it to Holo, she also agrees to the plan, hoping Lawrence will be more selfish and use the profit to achieve his dream. Later, Lawrence`s digging around town reveals that Eve is trading in salt and that the church in town is aiming to become more powerful in the region and Eve had a disagreement with the bishop but Lawrence and Holo resolve to go with Eve`s plan nonetheless.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108373" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と別れの決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and the Decision to Part</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Wakare no Ketsui</title>
<summary>The trading company wishing to purchase Holo proposes to pay with 60 gold coins instead of 2,000 silver coins because of their inability to procure the necessary silver, and Lawrence agrees to the deal. While celebrating the deal, Eve reveals she had been purchased and married to a merchant. She tells Lawrence and Holo to cherish their experiences together. Back at the inn, Holo suggests they should end their journey after she is sold since Lawrence has almost realized his dream of becoming a shop owner, and Lawrence`s efforts to dissuade her fail. The next morning, they return the books borrowed from Ligro, pausing to converse with a nun residing in Ligro`s home. Suddenly, Eve arrives and says there has been a coup d`état, leaving them surrounded by a rebellion.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108439" update="2013-10-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼ととめどなき涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf and Endless Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Tomedo Naki Namida</title>
<summary>Even in light of the chaos caused by the coup, Eve and Lawrence decide to continue with their plan. While Eve goes to reserve a ship, Lawrence leaves Holo with the traders and receives the gold according to the deal. However, when he meets with Eve in the inn, Lawrence decides to pull out. Eve threatens to murder him, since he discovered Eve had a cunning plan involving the Church to earn a huge amount of money. Eve knocks him out, but leaves him a deed to an inn, which he then uses to buy back Holo. In the face of Holo`s apparent fury, Lawrence declares his decision to forgo his dream and keep traveling with Holo as well as stating his affection for her.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="109200" update="2010-04-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109201" update="2010-04-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111605" update="2010-07-10">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2009-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わっちと"すとれっち"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stretching with Holo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wacchi to Stretch</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111614" update="2010-09-07">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わっちと"おべんきょう"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Studying with Holo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wacchi to Obenkyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118967" update="2019-04-18">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending of Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121976" update="2019-04-18">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2009-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オーディオドラマ『黒狼の揺り籠 (前編)』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio Drama: Black Wolf`s Cradle (First Part)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Audio Drama: Kuro Ookami no Yurikago (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121977" update="2019-04-18">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オーディオドラマ『黒狼の揺り籠 (後編)』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio Drama: Black Wolf`s Cradle (Last Part)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Audio Drama: Kuro Ookami no Yurikago (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
