<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6172" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2008-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bihada Ichizoku</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Battle for Beauty</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">美肌一族</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/bihada/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1383" type="Animation Work">Omnibus Japan</name>
<name id="9790" type="Character Design">Azuma Miho</name>
<name id="7817" type="Direction">Katou Michiya</name>
<name id="34766" type="Series Composition">Kurozumi Hikari</name>
</creators>
<description>There is a World Beautiful-Skin Competition (WBC) to which the 3 billion woman of the world aspire to win. Carrying on the 300-year legacy of the competition are twin Bihada sisters, Sara and Saki.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="146">2.96</permanent>
<temporary count="148">5.03</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>13489.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10011</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4908</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4378</identifier>
<identifier>kkslrz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/bihada/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>美肌一族</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1516</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>332043</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10529</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="74215" type="main character in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="2">5.79</rating>
<name>Bihada Sara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>171084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2987" picture="23718.jpg">Shouji Umeka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74709" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-23">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Bihada Rumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2049" picture="228615.jpg">Soumi Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74710" type="main character in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Yuutenji Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172461.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74711" type="appears in" update="2015-04-23">
<rating votes="1">1.02</rating>
<name>Bihada Kenya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3099" picture="24698.jpg">Kakegawa Hirohiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74713" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-23">
<name>Yuutenji Tatsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43062" picture="172469.jpg">Kano Eikou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74714" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-10">
<name>Kamata Masao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74715" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-23">
<name>Shiratori Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74716" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-23">
<name>SMK</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74717" type="appears in" update="2015-04-23">
<name>Neko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="410" picture="228116.jpg">Aoki Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74788" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-26">
<name>Minamoto Tsuyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42742" picture="171015.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74968" type="appears in" update="2015-05-05">
<name>Chousokabe Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56995" picture="228084.jpg">Sakurai Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75080" type="appears in" update="2015-05-10">
<name>Jikkyou Ana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2025" picture="23203.jpg">Oota Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75081" type="appears in" update="2015-05-10">
<name>Barano Sayuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="93333" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">華麗なる美肌家の一族</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beautiful Bihada Family</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kareinaru Bihada Ke no Ichizoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93651" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美と宿命のプレリュード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prelude of Fate and Beauty</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bi to Shukumei no Prelude</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93738" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祐天寺帝国の陰謀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yuutenji Empire`s Conspiracy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuutenji Teikoku no Inbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93921" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私, 仕事に生きますわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I, Working for Survival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watakushi, Shigoto ni Ikimasuwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93922" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私, キレイになりますわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Will Be Beautiful</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watakushi, Kirei ni Narimasuwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="94810" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私こそ美肌家の娘ですわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am the True Daughter of the Bihada Family</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watakushi Koso Bihada Ke no Musume Desuwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95275" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙の回転スキンケア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Revolting Tears - Skincare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida no Kaiten Skincare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95536" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と憎しみのエチュード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Etude of Lova and Hatred</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Nikushimi no Etude</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95596" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と美が壊れるとき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When Love and Beauty Get Destroyed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Bi ga Kowareru Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95652" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎のワールド美肌チャレンジ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Heated Word Bihada Challenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Word Bihada Challenge</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95726" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">骨肉の頂上決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Battle of the Twins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotsuniku no Choujou Kessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95733" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紗羅よ立て, 君は美しい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stand up Sara, You Are Beautiful</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sara yo Tate, Kimi wa Utsukushii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168189" update="2015-04-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
