<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6226" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>2009-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Slap Up Party: Arad Senki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">アラド戦記~スラップアップパーティー~</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Arad Senki: Slap Up Party</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">地下城与勇士 -阿拉德战记</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">slap up party</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スラップアップパーティ -アラド戦記-</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14559" type="Other">Dixia Cheng Yu Yongshi: Dungeon and Fighter</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1523" approval="9" total="12">Ragnarok The Animation</anime>
<anime id="9269" approval="7" total="13">Ixion Saga: Dimension Transfer</anime>
<anime id="13246" approval="2" total="9">Tate no Yuusha no Nariagari</anime>
<anime id="24" approval="1" total="5">.hack//Sign</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.sup-arad.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="17590" type="Direction">Ikezoe Takahiro</name>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="10717" type="Animation Work">GK Entertainment</name>
<name id="10763" type="Character Design">Nagasaku Tomokatsu</name>
<name id="15684" type="Series Composition">Yamanobe Kazuki</name>
<name id="10763" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nagasaku Tomokatsu</name>
<name id="13809" type="Music">Nakatsuka Takeshi</name>
<name id="41639" type="Original Work">Nexon</name>
<name id="54870" type="Original Work">Neople</name>
</creators>
<description>* Adapted from the MMORPG Arad Senki originally developed in South Korea under the name Dungeon &amp; Fighter, where NHN Japan says is it the most popular action RPG.
The anime will follow the adventures of Baron, a man living on continent of Arad in the year 981 after "the cursed light of Kazan" has fallen across the land. Thanks to the curse, one of his arms has become possessed. After finding a sword that has been possessed by the spirit Roxy, he embarks on a quest to unravel the secret of the curse and meets various people who also join his party.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="404">3.66</permanent>
<temporary count="410">6.18</temporary>
<review count="1">8.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>14015.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10232</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4657</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4475</identifier>
<identifier>awklqj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/contents/arad/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/arado/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dungeon_Fighter_Online</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アラド戦記#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1606</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>333420</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10484</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2009/arad</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6191" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>card games</name>
<description>A card game is any game using playing cards as the primary device with which the game is played, be they traditional or game-specific. Countless card games exist, including families of related games (such as poker). A small number of card games played with traditional decks have formally standardized rules, but most are folk games whose rules vary by region, culture, and person.
Many games that are not generally placed in the family of card games do in fact use cards for some aspect of their gameplay. Similarly, some games that are placed in the card game genre involve a board. The distinction is that the gameplay of a card game primarily depends on the use of the cards by players (the board is simply a guide for scorekeeping or for card placement), while board games (the principal non-card game genre to use cards) generally focus on the players` positions on the board, and use the cards for some secondary purpose.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6098" type="main character in" update="2009-04-12">
<rating votes="2">4.20</rating>
<name>Baron Abel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6099" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-12">
<rating votes="5">5.46</rating>
<name>Ryunmei Ranka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="313" picture="158104.jpg">Nogawa Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6100" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-12">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Kabenshisu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6101" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-12">
<rating votes="3">5.81</rating>
<name>Ixia Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1931" picture="238837.jpg">Tsuji Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6102" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-12">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Jeda Raxpa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6103" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-12">
<rating votes="1">7.25</rating>
<name>Ilbek</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6104" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-12">
<rating votes="3">8.35</rating>
<name>Hilia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6105" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-12">
<rating votes="1">7.25</rating>
<name>Halsen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6106" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-12">
<rating votes="3">8.35</rating>
<name>Roxie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6107" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Weri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2935" picture="219973.jpg">Tsubuyaki Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="98425" update="2009-03-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遭遇! 鬼の剣士と愛のガンナー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter! The Demon Swordsman and the Gunner of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souguu! Oni no Kenshi to Ai no Gunner</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99651" update="2009-04-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一発昇天!? 戦うプリースト ジェダ参上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Shot Death!? Fighting Priest Jeda Visits</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ippatsu Shouten!? Tatakau Priest Jeda Sanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99652" update="2009-04-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪徳商法!? ツボ商人 ダンジンの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unscrupulous!? Vase Merchant Danjin`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akutokushouhou!? Tsubo Shounin Danjin no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99653" update="2009-04-13">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陰謀!? エルブンガードシャッフル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conspiracy!? Erbinger Dochabru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inbou!? Erbinger Dochabru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99654" update="2009-04-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">災難!? かけ出しメイジの事情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Disaster!? The Novice Mage`s Circumstances</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sainan!? Kakedashi Mage Jijou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99655" update="2009-04-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決闘! 地下の最強格闘家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel! Strongest Fighter Underground</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kettou! Chikano Saikyou Kakutouka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102271" update="2009-05-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">守銭奴! 雑貨屋カンナの儲け話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Slave Of Wealth! The Story Of Earning Money At The Storehouse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shusendo! Zakkaya Kanna no Mouke Hanashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102272" update="2009-05-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家庭崩壊!? 風拳VS雷拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A family break-down !? Wind fist vs Thunder fist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katei Houkai!? Kaze Kobushi VS Kaminari Kobushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102273" update="2009-05-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壮絶! メカニック大戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heroic! Battle of the mechanics</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souzetsu! Mechanic Dai Sensou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102274" update="2009-05-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走! 鬼の瞳にも涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rampage! The Tears of a Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou! Oni no Hitomi ni mo Namida</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104157" update="2009-06-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">摩訶不思議! 眠れる国のクニック族</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unbelievable! The Tribe Of The Sleeping Kingdom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makafushigi! Nemureru Kuni no Knick Zoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104318" update="2009-06-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! 魔の稜線 (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intense Fight! The Spine Of The Demon Mountain - 1st Installment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Ma no Ryousen (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104755" update="2009-06-27">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誘惑!? 雪山に舞うお騒がせ姉妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Temptation!? Dance In The Snowy Mountain. The Two Sisters Who Caused A Huge Uproar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuwaku!? Yukiyama ni Mau Osawagase Kyoudai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104756" update="2009-06-27">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! 魔の稜線 (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intense Fight! The Spine Of The Demon Mountain - 2nd Installment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Ma no Ryousen (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104915" update="2009-07-04">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">発進!? 空飛ぶ帆船パルト!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Set Sail!? The Sailboat That Sails In The Sky!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hasshin!? Soratobu Hansen Paruto!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105082" update="2009-07-12">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ときめき! 二人の距離は...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Heart Beats! Distance Between Two People...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokimeki! Futari no Kyori wa...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105163" update="2009-07-18">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白熱! 対決の荒波</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Hot! The Fierce Wave Of A Confrontation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakunetsu! Taiketsu no Aranami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105502" update="2009-07-24">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パラレル! カペッチョの恩返し / アラド王国の休日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cabecho`s Repayment/Public Holiday Of The Kingdom Of Arad</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Parallel! Kapeccho no Ongaeshi / Arad Oukoku no Kyuujitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105726" update="2009-08-01">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カオス! 容疑者バロンの長い夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chaos! The Long Long Night Of Baron, The Suspect</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chaos! Yougisha Baron no Nagai Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106125" update="2009-08-07">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">争乱! ウエストコーストの燃える空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chaotic Fight! The Burning Sky Of The west Coast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souran! West Coast no Moeru Sora</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106304" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会! 伝説の剣士アガンゾ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion! The Legendary Warrior, Aganzou!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai! Densetsu no Kenshi Aganzo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106305" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦慄! 光のジグハルト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Horror! Sieghart Of Light!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senritsu! Hikari no Sieghardt</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106306" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">集結! 登れ 天城へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gather! Go Up The Castle Of The Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuketsu! Nobore Amagi e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108262" update="2009-09-05">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">始まり! 悲しみはあの光から</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beginning! The Sorrow Comes From The Light!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari! Kanashimi wa Ano Hikari kara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108450" update="2009-09-11">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! 大陸の空の上で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Battle! Above The Continent`s Sky!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Tairiku no Sora no Ue de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108451" update="2009-09-11">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならパーティー これにて終幕!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell Party, This Will Be The Last!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Party Kore nite Shuumaku!!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
