<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6234" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-01-24</startdate>
<enddate>2010-03-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hetalia: Axis Powers</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Axis Powers Hetalia</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Хеталия и страны Оси</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Военизирана Хеталия</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">黑塔利亚 Axis Powers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Hetalia</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヘタリア Axis Powers</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hetalia: Axis Powers</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7448" type="Sequel">Hetalia World Series</anime>
<anime id="7461" type="Side Story">Ginmaku Hetalia: Axis Powers - Paint It, White (Shiroku Nure!)</anime>
<anime id="8948" type="Other">Hetalia: Axis Powers Fan Disc</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="504638">Hetalia is exactly what you`re looking for if you are in for a strange mix of low-commitment educational series with funny and stereotypical characters. Episodes with 5 minutes that almost have no connection to each other, the main goal of this show is to teach world history in the funniest and silliest way. A bunch of bishounen characters representing a country stereotypically being put into the weirdest situations to explain historical events - what could possibly go wrong?</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://hetalia.com/top.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="3720" type="Series Composition">Hiramitsu Takuya</name>
<name id="4220" type="Original Work">Himaruya Hidekazu</name>
<name id="4221" type="Music">Conisch</name>
<name id="8144" type="Direction">Bob Shirahata</name>
<name id="5503" type="Character Design">Kawanami Masaaki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a popular web-released manga series by http://anidb.net/cr4220 [Himaruya Hidekazu].
Cynical gag story set in Europe in the years between WW1 and WW2 (1915-1939), using exaggerated caricatures of the different nationalities as portrayed by a gaggle of bishounen boys. For example, the http://anidb.net/ch5841 [Italia] Veneziano character is into pasta and women. The http://anidb.net/ch5842 [Doitsu] (German) bishi loves potatoes and sausages, and Nippon is an otaku boy. Installments of the manga have jumped back and forth in setting from the ancient times to modern-day geopolitics.
The title comes from the Japanese words for "useless" (hetare) and Italy (Italia).
Note: Japan`s Kids Station television network has officially canceled its planned broadcast of the Hetalia Axis Powers anime series "due to various circumstances." The series was distributed by Japanese retail anime chain Animate, via cel phone delivery and internet streaming.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1625">5.44</permanent>
<temporary count="1638">6.80</temporary>
<review count="3">7.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>52849.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10179</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5060</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4417</identifier>
<identifier>acixrv</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4488</identifier>
<identifier>jkujpg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hetalia.com/top.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hetalia#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Axis_powers_ヘタリア</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1531</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>332647</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10744</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>HetaliaOfficial</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2675" parentid="2831" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Russia</name>
<description>Russia, officially known as the Russian Federation, is a sovereign country in Eurasia. Russia is the largest country in the world by area, covering more than one-eighth of the Earth`s inhabited land area, and the ninth most populous. The European western part of the country is much more populated and urbanised than the eastern; about 77% of the population live in European Russia. Russia`s capital Moscow is one of the largest cities in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2691" parentid="2641" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-21">
<name>World War II</name>
<description>World War II, or the Second World War (often abbreviated WWII or WW2), was a global military conflict which involved most of the world`s nations, including all great powers, organised into two opposing military alliances: the Allies and the Axis. The war involved the mobilisation of over 100 million military personnel, making it the most widespread war in history. In a state of "total war," the major participants placed their entire economic, industrial, and scientific capabilities at the service of the war effort, erasing the distinction between civilian and military resources. Over seventy million people, the majority civilians, were killed, making it the deadliest conflict in human history.
The start of the war is generally held to be September 1, 1939, with the invasion of Poland by Nazi Germany and subsequent declarations of war on Germany by most of the countries in the British Empire and Commonwealth, and by France. Many countries were already at war before this date, such as Ethiopia and Italy in the Second Italo-Abyssinian War and China and Japan in the Second Sino-Japanese War. Many who were not initially involved joined the war later, as a result of events such as the German invasion of the Soviet Union, the attacks on Pearl Harbor and British colonies, and subsequent declarations of war on Japan by the United States, the Netherlands, and British Commonwealth.
In 1945, the war ended in a victory for the Allies. The Soviet Union and the United States subsequently emerged as the world`s superpowers, setting the stage for the Cold War which continued for the next 46 years. The United Nations was formed in the hope of preventing another world conflict. The acceptance of the principle of self-determination accelerated decolonization movements in Asia and Africa, while Western Europe itself began moving toward integration.
------
About the picture
Top left: Battle of Wuhan
Top right: Second Battle of El Alamein
Middle left: Battle of Stalingrad
Middle right: German dive bombers over Eastern Front winter 1943-1944
Bottom left: Wilhelm Keitel signing German Instrument of Surrender
Bottom right: Invasion of Lingayen Gulf</description>
<picurl>40430.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2807" parentid="2831" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>France</name>
<description>France, officially the French Republic, is a country whose territory consists of metropolitan France in western Europe, as well as several overseas regions and territories. The metropolitan area of France extends from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea, and from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean. The overseas territories include French Guiana in South America and several islands in the Atlantic, Pacific and Indian oceans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214343.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2810" parentid="2831" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Italy</name>
<description>Italy, officially the Italian Republic, is a unitary parliamentary republic in Europe. Located in the heart of the Mediterranean Sea, Italy shares open land borders with France, Switzerland, Austria, Slovenia, San Marino and Vatican City.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2811" parentid="2831" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Germany</name>
<description>Germany, officially the Federal Republic of Germany, is a federal parliamentary republic in central-western Europe. It includes 16 constituent states, and has a largely temperate seasonal climate. Germany is the most populous member state of the European Union. Germany`s capital and largest metropolis is Berlin, while its largest conurbation is the Ruhr, with its main centres of Dortmund and Essen.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214345.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2814" parentid="2832" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Canada</name>
<description>Canada is a country located in the northern part of North America. Its ten provinces and three territories extend from the Atlantic to the Pacific and northward into the Arctic Ocean. Canada is sparsely populated, the majority of its land territory being dominated by forest and tundra and the Rocky Mountains. Its capital is Ottawa, and its three largest metropolitan areas are Toronto, Montreal, and Vancouver.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214271.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3342" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-19">
<name>Nazis</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5841" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="61">6.40</rating>
<name>Italia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bright and energetic nation that progressed from being the kin of Roma Antiqua, widely recognised as the strongest nation in the world, to being clumsy and irresponsible. Personified as being carefree, cowardly and lackadaisical (noted by his collection of white flags he uses to surrender), he often depends on Germany to resolve issues. Nods to Italian culture include his artistry and recurrent portrayal of pasta and pizza. He has an older brother, who represents southern Italy and who is commonly known as Italy Romano.</description>
<picture>59514.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5842" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="57">7.82</rating>
<name>Doitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hard worker and lover of rules. He sticks to them rigidly and trains his troops to do the same. Despite this, he has formed a close relationship with the carefree Northern Italy. He notes at one point that he has a crazy boss.</description>
<picture>59516.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5843" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="45">6.93</rating>
<name>Nihon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hard-working, serious, skilled with his hands, and needs time to adjust to other people. He is inexperienced in the outside world, but does his best to learn all he can. Generally quiet, he sometimes seems to have the attitude of an old man.</description>
<picture>59515.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5844" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="33">5.06</rating>
<name>America</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raised by England and having fought for his independence, America became a country of pioneers. He is an energetic country who loves sticking his nose into other people`s business. He sees everything in a positive light, is quick to take action, and he always has his own idea of doing things. He also has immense physical strength and courage, although he has a crippling fear of ghosts, particularly when they are vague blobs of light in pictures. Strangely, a grey named Tony appears in his house from time to time without him minding it at all. America is frequently seen clutching a hamburger and flashing a thumbs up. America also has a penchant for coming up with elaborate inventions that never go anywhere.</description>
<picture>59509.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5845" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="48">7.85</rating>
<name>Igirisu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A nation that was once a pirate and tormented Spain, the United Kingdom is a gentleman who is known for having terrible cooking skills (although America enjoys his food), a foul mouth, and huge eyebrows. He does not get along well with France or Russia, and can sometimes be cynical, particularly towards his somewhat estranged sibling America. Despite being mocked by the other nations for it, England is a strong believer of unicorns, faeries, and magic, going so far as to literally curse his enemies. England cannot hold his liquor well and is a very unhappy sort of drunk. He once formed an alliance with Japan because he felt lonely. He is classified as a tsundere character.</description>
<picture>59510.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5846" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="36">6.71</rating>
<name>France</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Once a large nation, but after Napoleon Bonaparte had died, he was no longer good in war and instead attracted tourists to his country with his wine. He has an intense rivalry with England, and loves to argue with him over trivial topics. France is infatuated with most of the nations, often touching them inappropriately. He has been known to streak naked and makes blatant sexual comments at every opportunity. France maintains a bit of facial hair because he feels it makes him look like a big brother. He is constantly pictured with a rose, whether he is carrying it or using it as a censor.</description>
<picture>59511.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5847" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="78">8.26</rating>
<name>Russia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite having the cruelty of a child, Russia is the tallest of all the nations. He adores vodka and sunflowers. His primary hate is "General Winter", despite using the cold to his advantage in war. Russia has a kind and gentle face, but has mentally cracked from the strain of his bloody history. The other nations are mortified by him, particularly Lithuania, whom he loves to both physically and emotionally abuse. Occasionally, he stalks others while in a panda costume. Russia promises that eventually "everyone will become one with Russia". He also frequently says "KolKolKolKol" to nations he is threatening. Russia is almost always seen carrying a section of pipe. He is classified as a yandere character.</description>
<picture>59512.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5848" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="34">5.27</rating>
<name>Chuugoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the oldest nations and is regarded as the eldest brother among the East Asian nations. He is extremely superstitious and religious. Slightly disturbed of Russia. He has certain tastes for things and gets irritated if a food has a certain pattern of tastes. He is also a big fan of Hello Kitty and tends to end his sentences with the Japanese suffix -aru.</description>
<picture>59513.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5849" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="21">6.35</rating>
<name>Austria</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2889" picture="75539.jpg">Sasanuma Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5850" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="8">3.32</rating>
<name>Spain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59959.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5851" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="11">7.83</rating>
<name>Poland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2884" picture="23111.jpg">Tanaka Kazutada</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5852" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="10">2.91</rating>
<name>Greece</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22931.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="171" picture="23121.jpg">Kousaka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5853" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="10">7.00</rating>
<name>Belarus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="685" picture="24841.jpg">Takano Urara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5854" type="appears in" update="2013-03-11">
<rating votes="9">6.45</rating>
<name>Estonia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Estonia is described as "The wisest of the Baltic brothers and the most lucky as well." He is very high-tech, and is the owner of the strange "mochis", which are small, round, white creatures; each of them is like a certain country, with the four that are usually shown being America, Italy, Canada, and England. Of the three, it is he who tends to stand up to Russia the most.</description>
<picture>22933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="171" picture="23121.jpg">Kousaka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5855" type="appears in" update="2013-03-11">
<rating votes="3">4.76</rating>
<name>Latvia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Latvia is the youngest of the three states. He gets bullied the most by Russia due to his blunt nature, but is also the most dependent on him. He is very short, which Russia often points out to him. Latvia believes he could have grown more if Russia would not push down on his head when annoyed, which lead Russia to attempt to stretch him instead. He is shown to also drink quite a lot of alcohol, despite his young age.</description>
<picture>22934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="589" picture="186167.jpg">Takeuchi Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5856" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="6">6.38</rating>
<name>Roma Teikoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10476" type="appears in" update="2010-02-16">
<rating votes="7">6.28</rating>
<name>Canada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An easygoing, softhearted and gentle young man.
The polar bear Kumajirou is always with him. They`ve been together for so long without even knowing about each other, so he can`t remember his name.
He hates being mistaken for America, so he tries to show the appeal for Canada in various ways, but...
He hates fighting, but his neighbor is his neighbor, so when will he be able to live in peace...?</description>
<picture>43101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12585" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-16">
<rating votes="28">6.05</rating>
<name>Chibitalia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2980" picture="147242.jpg">Kanada Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12591" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-27">
<rating votes="7">4.18</rating>
<name>Shinsei Romano Teikoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4741" picture="45560.jpg">Konno Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14093" type="appears in" update="2010-01-13">
<rating votes="18">7.66</rating>
<name>Hungary</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14094" type="appears in" update="2010-01-13">
<rating votes="4">4.84</rating>
<name>Liechtenstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41461.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14095" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-13">
<rating votes="12">5.73</rating>
<name>Swiss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14096" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="15">5.83</rating>
<name>Romano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59960.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14099" type="appears in" update="2013-03-11">
<rating votes="8">7.51</rating>
<name>Lithuania</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lithuania, the eldest, was once a superpower that ruled much of Eastern and Middle Europe with Poland, but their empire collapsed. He has always fought off other countries, including Russia and the Teutonic Knights (the younger version of Prussia). Lithuania is shown to be good friends with both Poland and America, having lived in the latter`s house for a while before the Great Depression. He has a crush on Belarus, not noticing when she glares at him and, one time, not even noticing when she broke all of his fingers.</description>
<picture>41466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="589" picture="186167.jpg">Takeuchi Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14100" type="appears in" update="2010-06-02">
<rating votes="2">2.00</rating>
<name>Belgium</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41467.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14101" type="appears in" update="2013-03-11">
<rating votes="4">8.82</rating>
<name>Sweden</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sweden appears to be scary and often intimidates those around him, although he is actually friendly. He has a tendency to leave vowels out of his statements, making what he says difficult to decipher. He has a fondness for Finland, calling him "m` wife".</description>
<picture>41468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7049" picture="32044.jpg">Sakai Keikou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14102" type="appears in" update="2013-03-11">
<rating votes="4">5.18</rating>
<name>Finland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Finland is a cheerful nation who has a particular fondness for Christmas because of the belief that Santa Claus lives in Lapland, which is a major region in northern Finland. He and Sweden escaped from Denmark`s house together, traveling back to their homes together as well. He considers all the Nordics to be brothers, and he and Sweden are shown to be the peacekeepers between them.</description>
<picture>41469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14103" type="appears in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="3">7.92</rating>
<name>Sealand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sealand is unofficially the smallest nation in the world. Dressed in a sailor suit, Sealand is the youngest and smallest character in the series. He was created after England made him, but left him in the middle of the sea and forgot about him. However, nobody recognizes Sealand as a nation in his own right. As a result, he has to try other ways of getting noticed. For example, he once went to a meeting disguised as Canada. In the film Paint it, White, Sealand is shown that he has the ability to run across water and jump great heights, being able to jump from sea-level to his platform in a single leap. He refers to England as jerk England or British jerk.</description>
<picture>41472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14127" type="appears in" update="2010-01-14">
<rating votes="4">7.09</rating>
<name>Bulgaria</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14128" type="appears in" update="2010-01-14">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Egypt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41519.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14129" type="appears in" update="2010-01-14">
<rating votes="2">2.45</rating>
<name>Cuba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16236" type="appears in" update="2010-03-30">
<rating votes="3">2.69</rating>
<name>Chibi America</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16992" picture="46181.jpg">Iwamura Aiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16298" type="appears in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="4">5.69</rating>
<name>Ukraine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1888" picture="228611.jpg">Masuda Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="96509" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="10">1.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<summary>When the nations gather to solve the world’s problems, U.S.A. presents his solution to global warming - and it’s a pretty stupid one. Then everyone argues for a while, just before a flashback to WWI.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96808" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<summary>Germany is prowling the woods of WWI in search of the enemy, when he happens upon a crate of tomatoes. Just as he opens the wooden box, Italy attacks! I’m only kidding. Italy mostly just lays around.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="96809" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<summary>WWI is over, but Italy won’t quit pestering Germany. In fact, with WWII right around the corner, Italy pledges his undying devotion to his gruff friend, and a delightful Axis of Bromance is born.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="97057" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<summary>Italy and Germany have a new BFF: Japan. After a “getting acquainted” soak in the hot springs, Japan shows the guys his value as an ally by - actually, he doesn’t really do much. But he seems very polite.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="97153" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<summary>Germany, Japan, and Italy are on a deserted island, and they’re making the most of such a pleasant environment. Especially Italy, who uses the free time to make white flags and sand sculptures of pasta.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="97263" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<summary>Japan, Germany, and Italy roast marshmallows on the beach. The three guys may feel like the night belongs to them, but they are far from alone. Actually, marshmallows sound pretty good right now. BRB.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="97356" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<summary>U.S.A. takes a break from stuffing hamburgers into his face just long enough (barely) to reveal his plans for attacking the Axis. Meanwhile, much to Germany’s delight, Italy’s got an obnoxious brother.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="97428" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<summary>Since Italy’s kind of a moron, he keeps getting captured by the Allies. But since he’s kind of annoying, he keeps getting sent back to the Axis. And in a shocking turn of events, Japan answers a telephone!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="97675" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<summary>The Allies get together to split up their responsibilities for the coming war, which really just means: U.S.A. decides he’ll be the hero and everyone else will act as his support. Meanwhile, isn’t France dreamy?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="98434" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<summary>France is devastated upon learning he wasn’t invited to the second meeting of the Allies, and as he reflects on the - I’m sorry, can you excuse me for a second? It seems chibi Italy is wearing Hungary’s dress.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="99341" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<summary>The moment of truth arrives in Chibitalia: will Italy accept the adorable Holy Roman Empire’s offer? And while the Allies prepare for WWII, U.K. totally hangs out with a unicorn.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="99689" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<summary>First, a scene from after the war: France asks U.K. to marry him. It has something to do with the Suez Canal. Next, a scene set before the war shows the Axis prepping to take on U.K.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="99835" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<summary>U.K. is aggravated after losing to Germany, so the lad uses the dark arts to get his revenge. In a scary room, he chants a summoning spell and unleashes - Russia, the weirdest of all world powers!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="99964" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<summary>The Allied assault on the Axis begins! And ends! And then it begins again! And ends again! What’s with all the false starts and sudden stops? It’s kind of hard to explain. Just watch the episode.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="99965" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<summary>U.S.A. is ready to clean out his cluttered storage room, but he may not have what it takes to let go of so many memories. Actually, he may need to worry more about letting go of some hamburgers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="99966" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<summary>A walk down memory lane reveals the moment when China found tiny, young Japan sitting all alone in the woods.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="99967" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<summary>Italy and Germany enjoy soaking in the rays of the sun, but Japan isn’t thrilled about the prospect of exposing himself. Of course, a quick glimpse at his library proves he’s not totally against nudity.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="99968" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<summary>Germany goes to the supermarket to buy sausages. Ordinarily that wouldn’t be exciting, but during this trip he manages to encounter every mildly-offensive stereotype ever associated with every nation ever.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="101613" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD1 Credits</title>
</episode>
<episode id="101614" update="2010-03-29">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102488" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
<summary>U.K. unveils the secret weapon he plans to use in order to claim revenge against U.S.A. - a chair! An EVIL chair! An EVIL chair that Russia keeps sitting in at all the wrong moments!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102489" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
<summary>A flashback into the past reveals the reasons why U.S.A. might sometimes appear to be lacking in good taste. Also, the long and winding tale of Liechtenstein and Switzerland comes to an end.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102490" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<summary>Tension arises when Switzerland and Liechtenstein encounter Austria at the grocery store. Meanwhile, the Axis boys discover that their deserted island isn’t actually all that deserted.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102491" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<summary>Switzerland questions why his sis, Liechtenstein, cut her hair. Everyone else questions if she’s actually a little boy. Later, Germany is confused when he overhears an awkward situation involving Italy and a bed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102492" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
<summary>As Holy Roman Empire prepares to leave for war, little Italy gets emotional and gives the departing nation a meaningful gift. Well, really, I’m just assuming it’s meaningful. Because, otherwise, it’s just silly.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102493" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
<summary>Sealand has a lot of heart, but as the teeny-tiniest nation in the world, he’s having a tough time getting the other countries to recognize that he even exists.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102494" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<summary>A tale of two weapons: First of all, Italy shouldn’t be messing around with hand grenades. Can we all agree on that? Next, U.S.A. takes a trip down memory lane when he finds an old musket in his storage room.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102495" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<summary>The Allied forces gather for a meeting. Here’s a list of the three most interesting things that happen: 1) China shows up late. 2) Canada has a bear in his lap. 3) OMG, AXIS SPY.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="103424" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD2 Credits</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103425" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">America`s Storage Cleaning Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105573" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 27</title>
<summary>The Allies get their hands on a valuable source of information that could reveal the inner-workings of the Axis gang: Germany’s diary! And it’s all about Italy. Seriously, like every page.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105936" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 28</title>
<summary>The Axis falls under Allied attack once again! But then something strange happens - a jolly visitor arrives bearing gifts, allowing enemies to put aside their differences if only for one night.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="106108" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD3 Credits</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106205" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 29</title>
<summary>Russia knows no fear, as evidenced by his willingness to jump out of an airplane without a parachute. The Baltics, however, seem to be more than a little uneasy around Russia.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="106458" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
<summary>During a sleepover at Japan’s place, U.K. makes a new pal while soaking in the bath. This new pal is green and might actually be a hallucination. Or, he might actually exist. We may never know.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108071" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
<summary>In this very informative episode of Hetalia Axis Powers, the gang shares stories of how the Christmas season is celebrated - or not - in their homelands. Note to self: avoid Russia during the holidays.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108176" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
<summary>Germany stirs from his slumber to find the Roman Empire on his bed. It turns out Germany is a big fan of his visitor’s work - and misses him very much. How sweet.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108500" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 33</title>
<summary>Germany and Italy spend a beautiful night by the campfire, and when a shooting star flashes through the sky, Germany makes a wish. Actually he makes a lot of wishes, and they’re all about Italy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108562" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 34</title>
<summary>Germany goes sightseeing in sunny Italy, a lively land where music and laughter drift on the breeze. Surprisingly, he doesn’t hate it. Later, the Allied boys explore their artistic sides.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108658" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 35</title>
<summary>It’s time for the G8 summit, but Canada is missing. When he finally shows up, the rest of the… Wait. Who the crap is this Canada guy? Later, France catches Olympic fever - and loses his pants.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108800" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 36</title>
<summary>With spring still many months away, U.S.A. and Japan make preparations to survive the harsh winter. And by preparations, I mean that Japan buys manga and ice cream while U.S.A. almost freezes to death.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="109155" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 37</title>
<summary>Russia’s heading over to Germany’s place for a sleepover, and he’s worried about what to wear. Italy’s got some concerns, too. If his friends make new friends, will he be pushed aside?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="110703" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 38</title>
<summary>Germany addresses Italy’s abandonment issues and offers his little friend a treaty to put him at ease. Okay, it’s not really a treaty at all. It’s actually a pinky swear.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="110780" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 39</title>
<summary>In the New World, adorable baby U.S.A. is caught in the middle of a very intense custody battle between France, Finland, and a few other blonde guys!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="110942" update="2009-10-26">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD4 Credits</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110943" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 40</title>
<summary>Everybody still wants little baby U.S.A. all to themselves! It’s France and his buddies versus U.K. and his gang. Who will earn the right to be called big brother by the New World’s cutest newborn?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="111214" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 41</title>
<summary>It’s an episode of psychological combat! While U.S.A. tries to come up with ways to mess with his opponents’ heads, France takes it upon himself to spread scandalous rumors about Germany.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="111324" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 42</title>
<summary>Russia introduces the world to his sisters, the busty, bouncy Ukraine and the very intense Belarus. It’s an unusual family, to say the least.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="111499" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 43</title>
<summary>The saga of Russia’s sisters continues! Things haven’t been the same since the collapse of the Soviet Union. As a result, Ukraine is jiggling her way across Europe in search of new friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="111592" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 44</title>
<summary>Liechtenstein’s a little too laid back about her borders, so Switzerland decides to teach her about the peril of strangers. Later, Japan and U.S.A. work on becoming better friends. And there’s cake! Cake’s awesome!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="111796" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 45</title>
<summary>During a tender moment of reflection, Liechtenstein recalls the heartbreaking circumstances surrounding her first meeting with Switzerland: a boy who would become like a brother to her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="111893" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 46</title>
<summary>U.K. develops a serious case of hair envy - and an aversion to scissors - in the wake of another humiliating encounter with France and his gorgeous, golden locks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="112068" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 47</title>
<summary>England and France pay a visit to Poland and his pretty new pony; America’s astonishing rate of growth comes as quite a shock to jolly old England.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="112231" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 48</title>
<summary>A self-inflicted rocket wound leaves England hovering on the verge of death, but America wants to be paid back before the old chap kicks the bucket.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="112324" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 49</title>
<summary>France drops by to visit Japan, who’s as isolated as ever, and there’s nothing in the world that’s going to make the guy come out of his room to greet his charming visitor. Well, except maybe a cute kitty.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="113033" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 50</title>
<summary>America swings by to show Japan a fortune telling game. Later, when the rest of the guys want to celebrate the fact that he’s coming out of his shell, Japan chooses a quiet night at home instead. Big shock, right?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="113354" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 52</title>
<summary>It’s an episode of mistaken identities in more ways than one when Holy Roman Empire and Italy go skinny-dipping. Later, everybody thinks Canada is everybody but Canada!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="113355" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 51</title>
<summary>America’s totally freaked out by scary movies, but due to his heroic inclinations, he refuses to stop watching them! Japan thinks loaning him some horror video games might toughen him up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119280" update="2010-06-25">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode P1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126175" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 8 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126176" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 7 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126177" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 6 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126178" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 5 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126179" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 4 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126180" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 3 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126181" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 46-52</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126182" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 40-45</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126183" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 34-39</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126184" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 27-33</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126185" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 20-26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126186" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 14-19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126187" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 8-13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126188" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 1-7</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
