<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6235" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-01-12</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ride Back</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">رايد باك</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Ride Back</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">背骑少女</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ライドバック</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">RideBack</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2351" approval="8" total="9">Dead Heat</anime>
<anime id="4196" approval="6" total="12">Air Gear</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="27">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="128900">easy nice anime ....</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="83971">simply amazing</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="75610">If you like Motocycles you will like this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="344883">i like the anime, its fun</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="144215">Excellent!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="311686">cool</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="250692">...just finished watching the series and I was pleasantly surprised at how well they mixed the sub plot of a government uprising with a "regular" girl`s struggle to get back on her feet. My favorite part is the melding of her dancing background with the motorcycle mecha (`ride back`). It is a treat to see and definitely not too shabby for an anime action junkie ^_^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="256742">&lt;br /&gt;Ima　&lt;br /&gt;Tokei ga tsugesari kisetsu wa meguri&lt;br /&gt;Ano egao shiru kokasunnde mo&lt;br /&gt;Kokoro o sou anata o wasurenai&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Mou nido to aenakutatte)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warai ao sashin o taoshitemo&lt;br /&gt;Afuredasu omoi o kakushite mo&lt;br /&gt;Kokoro wa wasurenai&lt;br /&gt;Anata to no kioku</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="334021">WOW!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="200365">This is a must see! The whole thing just captivates you and you can`t stop watching it! If you haven`t started yet, you rather wait until all eps have aired and then watch them in one go, because this show is pure infatuation! An all-time fav!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="414904">This is awesomeness at it`s best. From time to I find shows that simply just BLOW YOU AWAY and that`s one of them. Must see for sure!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.rideback-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="3500" type="Series Composition">Takayashiki Hideo</name>
<name id="4549" type="Direction">Takahashi Atsushi</name>
<name id="7839" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tasaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="10163" type="Original Work">Kasahara Tetsurou</name>
<name id="7839" type="Character Design">Tasaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="9792" type="Series Composition">Iizuka Ken</name>
<name id="18474" type="Music">Wada Takafumi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr10163 [Kasahara Tetsurou].
In a future world where an organization called the GGP has taken control of the world, http://anidb.net/ch2377 [Ogata Rin] had a promising career as an up-and-coming ballet dancer, but suffered a serious injury and decided to quit.
Years later in college she comes across an unusual club building and soon finds herself intrigued by a transforming motorcycle-like vehicle called a Rideback. She discovers that her unique ballet skills with balance and finesse make her a natural on a Rideback. However, those same skills also get her into serious trouble with the government.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2615">6.41</permanent>
<temporary count="2645">7.59</temporary>
<review count="6">6.52</review>
</ratings>
<picture>33394.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8049</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4618</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4403</identifier>
<identifier>hcbafn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.rideback-anime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rideback</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>RIDEBACK</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1541</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>332639</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10746</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="125" parentid="362" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>ballet</name>
</tag>
<tag id="362" parentid="2793" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-24">
<name>dancing</name>
<description>Dance is when people move their body to music. There are many kinds of dance, like ballet or waltz. Dancing can be done for fun but can be also an art.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3166" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-18">
<name>political unrest</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3252" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>history is written by the victors</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3664" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>futuristic motorcycle</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2377" type="main character in" update="2009-06-16">
<rating votes="22">8.13</rating>
<name>Ogata Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Her parents were Yuki and Munetatsu, and due to her mother being a talented dancer, was therefore expected to be their natural successor, having participated in dancing competitions from a young age. However, in 2017, she fractured her left foot while dancing and subsequently decided to stop dancing, later enrolling in the theatre department of Musashino University, where she first comes across Rideback.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>24917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2995" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="4">7.04</rating>
<name>Hishida Haruki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2996" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="10">7.37</rating>
<name>Kataoka Tamayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Third year student in the French literature department and a senior to both to Rin and Haruki. The Rideback champion of Japan.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>24920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2997" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="4">3.99</rating>
<name>Uemura Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Childhood friend of Rin`s.</description>
<picture>24919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2998" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="3">6.39</rating>
<name>Okakura Tenshirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head of the Rideback team. Possessing a strict character.</description>
<picture>24918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6868" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="6">6.05</rating>
<name>Kiefer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6869" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="4">5.04</rating>
<name>Uchida Suzuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="435" picture="188447.jpg">Matsumoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6870" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="3">5.59</rating>
<name>Kawai Douta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6871" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="2">3.48</rating>
<name>Ogata Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="403" picture="74821.jpg">Horie Kazuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6872" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="8">7.19</rating>
<name>Yoda Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6873" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="4">1.07</rating>
<name>Romanov Karenbach</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6874" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="11">5.32</rating>
<name>Yokoyama Misao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6875" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="3">5.76</rating>
<name>Kataoka Ryuunosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6876" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="2">2.73</rating>
<name>Kataoka Nanfuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6877" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="2">2.73</rating>
<name>Yamamoto Tsutomu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6878" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-14">
<rating votes="2">2.73</rating>
<name>Satou Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="96265" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">深紅の鉄馬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crimson Iron Horse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shingou no Detsu Uma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96402" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">珠代上等!? S.L.F~スプレッド・レッグス・フォーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge from Tamayo!? S.L.F - Spread Legs Form</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamayo Joutou!? S.L.F.: Spread Legs Form</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96403" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして旗(フラッグ)はふられる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And There`s the Flag</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Flag wa Furareru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96495" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しょう子, 危機一髪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Close Call for Shoko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouko, Kiki Ippatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96520" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎のライドバック少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious RideBack Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Rideback Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96522" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電光石火ライド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lightning-Fast RideBack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Denkousekka Ride</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96523" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">罪とX</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crime and Punishment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumi to Batsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96928" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="12">3.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">GET RIDE! 選ばれし者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Ride! The Chosen One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Get Ride! Erabareshimono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96929" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陽だまりの庭で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Sunny Garden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hidamari no Bade</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97136" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光の舞台へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Stage of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari no Butai e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97137" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Master of the war</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Master of the War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Master of the War</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97138" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">曇りのち雨ときどき...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cloudy Followed by Occasional Rain...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kumori Nochi Ame Tokidoki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="101603" update="2009-05-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="101604" update="2009-05-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">3.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163595" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163596" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">TAF2009-PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2 (TAF2009)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163597" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">TAF2008-PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1 (TAF2008)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163598" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 6 (30 s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163599" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5 (30 s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163600" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4 (15 s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163601" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3 (15 s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163602" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (15 s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163603" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (15 s)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
