<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6262" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-12-29</startdate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Touhou Niji Sousaku Doujin Anime: Musou Kakyou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">東方アニメプロジェクト・夢想夏郷</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Touhou Unofficial Doujin Anime: A Summer Day`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">A Summer Day`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Сон в летний день</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="synonym">Neoficiální fananimace Tóhó: Sen letního dne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">touhou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">東方二次創作同人アニメ 夢想夏郷</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7982" type="Alternative Setting">Anime Tenchou x Touhou Project</anime>
<anime id="8624" type="Alternative Setting">Gensou Mangekyou: The Memories of Phantasm</anime>
<anime id="12338" type="Alternative Setting">Hifuu Katsudou Kiroku: The Sealed Esoteric History</anime>
<anime id="8664" type="Other">Touhou PVD</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://maikaze.com/musoukakyo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="22087" type="Original Work">Zun</name>
<name id="10637" type="Direction">Tokine</name>
<name id="10637" type="Music">Tokine</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Project Touhou franchise owned by http://anidb.net/cr28439 [Team Shanghai Alice].
Gensokyo: A world that quietly exists next to our own world, separated only by a mythical boundary. A Utopia, in which humans and other beings, like elves, youkai, and gods live together in peace. Each year there is a large festival at the Reimu Hakurei shrine by the shrine maiden who protects the Gensokyo boundary. The shrine is then filled with many of Gensokyo`s inhabitants, as the summer draws near. — from intro
In the Hakurei shrine warehouse the not so helpful, klutzy, http://anidb.net/ch4161 [Ibuki Suika] and shrine maiden http://anidb.net/ch4158 [Hakurei Reimu] are the only ones working on the preparations for the upcoming festival. Suika is then sent off to do the shopping, when Reimu notices the disappearance of the shrine`s, actually her saisen (coin box). Journalist http://anidb.net/ch4160 [Shameimaru Aya] who suddenly shows up, suggests the box may indeed have been stolen, strangely enough since it is always empty. Aya goes into detective mode, quickly summoning mage http://anidb.net/ch4159 [Kirisame Marisa], who is supposed to help find the missing saisen. As it turns out many other things have mysteriously disappeared the night before.
Much work still lies ahead of Reimu... and who or what is the shadowy figure among the trees near the shrine?
— written by foo2
Note: This is an unofficial fan-made anime.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="783">5.20</permanent>
<temporary count="788">6.86</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>16326.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9874</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>30547</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://maikaze.com/musoukakyo/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2802" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-14">
<name>action game</name>
<description>Any game where reflexes are the key to the gameplay, violence is optional.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4770" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-17">
<name>fan-made</name>
<description>Produced by an unofficial entity, totally unrelated to any commercial production studio/company (maybe even a group of friends with an idea, access to some equipment, a very tight budget, and lots of spare time). "Made for fans by fans" in its purest form.
Don`t expect big-bucks animation, top-notch voice actors or overly-elaborate scripts, but sometimes you can get a very nice surprise from that kind of productions, so don`t write them off that fast!
In Japan, this kind of of productions is also known as "doujin" (同人) - self-published works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4158" type="main character in" update="2009-03-01">
<rating votes="64">7.88</rating>
<name>Hakurei Reimu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The shrine maiden of the Hakurei Shrine, a remote building far in the east where the boundaries of Gensokyo and the human world overlap. Reimu is very easygoing— some would say lazy— and hates to train. As such, even though she`s naturally talented, her offensive and magical abilities are only average. However, she has a strong sense of duty, and if it`s for the sake of Gensokyo she can overcome almost any obstacle through sheer perseverance. Her main abilities are flying in the sky, good intuition, and getting along with everyone; even those who were once her enemies.</description>
<picture>20139.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4159" type="main character in" update="2009-03-01">
<rating votes="47">6.96</rating>
<name>Kirisame Marisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marisa is a human magician who lives in a cluttered house in the Forest of Magic. She is friends with Reimu and visits her often, but otherwise is solitary and spends most of her time researching magic. She is also an avid collector stuffing her house with various items, and would go "borrowing" things from others without returning them. She is selfish, sometimes violent, and has a disagreeable manner. Underneath, though, she is honest and a hard worker. This makes it strange that she is friends with Reimu, whose powers are purely from talent while she had to work very hard to get her own to the same level. Her ability is high-level destructive magic.</description>
<picture>20140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4160" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-01">
<rating votes="11">7.39</rating>
<name>Shameimaru Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aya is a reporter and photographer who runs Gensokyo`s one-woman newspaper, the Bunbunmaru Shinbun. She has a serious character, at odds with her reporting; she loves rumours and her newspaper is filled with gossip about the girls of Gensokyo, sometimes on the verge of being a tabloid. To Reimu`s irritation, however, she rejects the stories of a certain shrine maiden saving Gensokyo as unverifiable. Not one to show off, she rarely fights of her own volition, though she has contempt for those she thinks are weak.</description>
<picture>20141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4161" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-01">
<rating votes="21">8.19</rating>
<name>Ibuki Suika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who insists that she is an oni, even though Gensokyo supposedly doesn`t have any. Suika and Yugi Hoshiguma were once part of the four devas of the mountains, long ago before the oni retreated underground. As an oni, she loves drinks, feasts, and competition. Despite her small size, she is strong in strength, speed, and mystic powers; she is also several hundred years old. Using her ability to control density, she can gather people to form a banquet, or she can scatter herself to become mist.</description>
<picture>20142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4162" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-01">
<rating votes="54">7.67</rating>
<name>Remilia Scarlet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Remilia is the vampiric mistress of the Scarlet Devil Mansion who claims to be descended from Vlad III Dracula although she is not. She is known as the Scarlet Devil as when she feeds, the blood of her victims stains her dress red. Apart from her unpleasant needs, she`s hardly malicious enough to deserve such a title; merely childish, even though she`s over five hundred years old. Although being a vampire is normally a lonely life, she has a good relationship with her many employees (including Sakuya and Meiling).</description>
<picture>20159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1931" picture="238837.jpg">Tsuji Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4163" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-01">
<rating votes="44">8.27</rating>
<name>Izayoi Sakuya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakuya is the only human living in the Scarlet Devil Mansion, yet she is also the head maid. Though she looks about sixteen like the other girls, Sakuya has the ability to slow, stop and possibly reverse time. She seems to have been serving Remilia for a long time and may be far older than she looks. Her talents are cooking, knife throwing and time manipulation.</description>
<picture>20160.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4164" type="main character in" update="2010-11-26">
<rating votes="43">8.34</rating>
<name>Patchouli Knowledge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A scholar who is a friend of Remilia Scarlet. She resides in the library of the Scarlet Devil Mansion, and is the de facto librarian. In fact, she rarely leaves it and is somewhat of a hikikomori. She has command over the seven elements (which the Japanese days of the week are named after, making her the "One-week Wizard") and is in theory an extremely powerful magician. However, her constitution is very poor and asthma often prevents her from reciting her spells. She has a tenuous relationship with Marisa, who tends to carry off her books without asking.</description>
<picture>5430.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4165" type="appears in" update="2009-03-01">
<rating votes="15">5.77</rating>
<name>Hong MeiLing</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Chinese girl serving as the door guard of the Scarlet Devil Mansion. Canonically, she is known to be a very humanoid youkai who practices martial arts, but is generally friendly towards humans.</description>
<picture>20144.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36859" type="appears in" update="2011-09-21">
<rating votes="50">8.23</rating>
<name>Konpaku Youmu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36860" type="appears in" update="2011-09-21">
<rating votes="18">7.95</rating>
<name>Saigyouji Yuyuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36862" type="appears in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="8">8.92</rating>
<name>Yakumo Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36864" type="main character in" update="2011-09-21">
<rating votes="13">6.59</rating>
<name>Alice Margatroid</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39890" picture="161176.jpg">Oomori Nichika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50028" type="appears in" update="2012-10-23">
<rating votes="2">6.69</rating>
<name>Yagokoro Eirin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59399.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50029" type="appears in" update="2012-10-23">
<rating votes="6">7.95</rating>
<name>Inaba Tewi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59398.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50030" type="appears in" update="2012-10-23">
<rating votes="2">7.81</rating>
<name>Houraisan Kaguya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59400.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50031" type="appears in" update="2012-10-23">
<rating votes="8">7.02</rating>
<name>Reisen Udongein Inaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59397.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="95691" update="2008-12-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95981" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢想夏郷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Summer Day`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Musou Kakyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96885" update="2009-02-08">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Parody</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119309" update="2011-08-22">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview - Bad Apple</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125927" update="2017-08-27">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125928" update="2012-10-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132587" update="2011-08-22">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2 Teaser Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="142229" update="2012-08-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">予定調和</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pre-Established Harmony</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yotei Chouwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144910" update="2017-08-27">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144911" update="2012-10-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161777" update="2015-07-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2014-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢想夏郷2.5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Summer Day`s Dream 2.5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Musou Kakyou 2.5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186426" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">綻びのデジャヴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blooming Deja Vu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokorobi no Dejavu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190530" update="2017-08-27">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190531" update="2017-08-27">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190532" update="2017-08-27">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
