<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6283" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-02-12</startdate>
<enddate>2009-02-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Street Fighter IV: Aratanaru Kizuna</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Street Fighter IV: The Ties That Bind</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Uliczny wojownik IV: Więzy</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">sf4</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ストリートファイターIV 新たなる絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Street Fighter - Round One: Fight!</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Street Fighter - Round One Fight</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7321" type="Sequel">Super Street Fighter IV</anime>
<anime id="313" type="Prequel">Street Fighter II: The Movie</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="241158">I don`t think this was so bad as some may suggest. It`s a story in the world of Street Fighter - evil organizations try to chase down the vagabond Ryu who is trying to master Setsu no Hado, Ken, Guile, Chun Li and Sakura investigate the organization and team up to do sth about it. It`s a somewhat entertaining film if you like the world of Street Fighter and enjoy seeing the characters do their thing.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="738" type="Animation Work">Studio 4C</name>
<name id="1595" type="Music">Fukasawa Hideyuki</name>
<name id="9665" type="Direction">Kanai Jirou</name>
</creators>
<description>Throughout the world, fighters have begun to suddenly disappear - all of them masters in their particular combat discipline. http://anidb.net/ch5076 [Guile] and http://anidb.net/ch13767 [Chun Li] are assigned to investigate the situation and find out what they can. Meanwhile, http://anidb.net/ch13775 [Cammy]`s Delta Red team has investigations of its own to make, as a mysterious force seems to have torn a hole in the Amazon jungle. At the same time, a secret agent seems to be tracking http://anidb.net/ch5047 [Ryuu], and it`s not long before everybody else`s eyes are on the legendary and elusive fighter. But Ryuu has a problem of his own: is he really able to control the power of the Dark Hadou that dwells inside him?
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="399">3.06</permanent>
<temporary count="405">5.73</temporary>
<review count="2">3.24</review>
</ratings>
<picture>19192.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10659</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5369</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Street_Fighter_IV#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ストリートファイターIV#.E3.82.B9.E3.83.88.E3.83.AA.E3.83.BC.E3.83.88.E3.83.95.E3.82.A1.E3.82.A4.E3.82.BF.E3.83.BCIV.E3.80.9C.E6.96.B0.E3.81.9F.E3.81.AA.E3.82.8B.E7.B5.86.E3.80.9C</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2802" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-14">
<name>action game</name>
<description>Any game where reflexes are the key to the gameplay, violence is optional.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5047" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="51">9.01</rating>
<name>Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryu is a pretty simple guy. He wears the same outfit wherever he goes - white gi, black belt, red headband, period - and he has the same aim wherever he goes as well. He wants to fight whoever he thinks can make him a stronger fighter.</description>
<picture>21382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5076" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-20">
<rating votes="9">8.97</rating>
<name>Guile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13766" type="main character in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="26">9.27</rating>
<name>Ken Masters</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Street Fighter 2 V voice actor: 羽賀研二</description>
<picture>40634.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1926" picture="156610.jpg">Kishi Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13767" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="69">7.95</rating>
<name>Chun-Li</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13769" type="appears in" update="2015-10-20">
<rating votes="5">6.94</rating>
<name>Mike Bison</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mike Bison is depicted as an African American boxer wearing blue trunks with white trim and a torn white shirt under a blue tank top. He wears red boxing gloves and boxing shoes. His hairstyle consists of short hair cut in an odd pointing style in the front, similar to Mike Tyson`s haircuts from the time Street Fighter II was made. Although usually removed when these illustrations are published outside Japan, some character illustrations feature his Japanese name, "Bison" on the waistband of his trunks. In Street Fighter IV, the waistband now reads "Champion".
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picture>40592.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13774" type="appears in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="9">7.68</rating>
<name>Balrog</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13775" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="27">8.62</rating>
<name>Cammy White</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40639.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13778" type="appears in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="20">8.05</rating>
<name>Gouki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2339" picture="151715.jpg">Taketora</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="97007" update="2009-02-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>2009-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
