<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="630" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2003-09-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Uchuu no Stellvia</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Stellvia of the Universe</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Cosmic Stellvia</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Космическая Стеллвия</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">우주의 스텔비아</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Стелвіа всесвіту</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">宇宙的星路</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">SotU</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">su</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Stellvia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">UNS</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">宇宙のステルヴィア</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Stellvia</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="192" approval="28" total="42">Mugen no Ryvius</anime>
<anime id="7443" approval="25" total="39">Mouretsu Pirates</anime>
<anime id="445" approval="18" total="23">Stratos 4</anime>
<anime id="1" approval="15" total="30">Seikai no Monshou</anime>
<anime id="1139" approval="4" total="5">Futatsu no Spica</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="240459">You can now watch Stellvia in BD-720p, with [R-B]`s external subs. Time to rewatch it AGAIN guys.
For those who don`t know the series - it`s EPIC.
One of the finest examples of the "save the world in realistic setting" genre.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="293766">Stellvia is one of three mechina anime`s I have watched and really enjoyed. I found this series to be really unique because it intermingles a high school setting with a sci-fi twist. Fair amount of drama and suspense, good character development, and the climax of this anime was outstanding! Highly recommended in my standings. =)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="376567">I think this one is highly watchable. Story is quite unique and carried well all the way to the climax. It has some unexpectedly good drama also. The main character wasn`t nearly as annoying as Shinji :D I think the only downside was well-below-average animation. As someone else noted here before, it has this good old majestetic hardcore scifi feeling :D</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/stellvia/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3333" type="Character Design">Uno Makoto</name>
<name id="3613" type="Series Composition">Satou Tatsuo</name>
<name id="719" type="Original Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="3613" type="Direction">Satou Tatsuo</name>
<name id="1905" type="Music">Nagaoka Seikou</name>
</creators>
<description>In 2167, a supernova explosion engulfed the Earth with a wave of electromagnetic energy, turning the sky green and causing countless disasters. After recovering from that first wave, humanity started putting up defences to protect itself, and by the year 2356, a network of six orbiting space stations, the Foundations, now guards the Earth from a second supernova wave that is expected to arrive later that year. Each Foundation houses a high school for promising young space cadets, and eager 15-year-old http://anidb.net/ch2780 [Katase Shima] has just been accepted to Stellvia, the second Foundation. Making friends, going to class, learning to pilot a light spacecraft — it is all part of the high school experience, hundreds of miles above Earth aboard space station Stellvia.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2739">6.95</permanent>
<temporary count="2772">7.78</temporary>
<review count="10">6.98</review>
</ratings>
<picture>38953.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>74</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1200</identifier>
<identifier>dqwdjq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/stellvia/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Stellvia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>宇宙のステルヴィア</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>241173</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5964</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="389" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>crybaby</name>
<description>Someone whose feelings are very easily hurt, often by trivial matters.</description>
<picurl>162105.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="601" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>bicycle</name>
<description>A bicycle, often called a bike or cycle, is a human-powered, pedal-driven, single-track vehicle, having two wheels attached to a frame, one behind the other. A bicycle rider is called a cyclist, or bicyclist.
Souce: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>172772.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2665" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>school sports festival</name>
<description>To show off the students in sports clothing — in ecchi anime the female students in particular — a sports festival (or athletic meet) is quite popular in your typical anime with school setting. Here the protagonists can show their skills in diverse athletic competitions.
Note: This festival may also, though very rarely, take place at a kindergarten or preschool.</description>
<picurl>161025.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2781" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>first kiss</name>
<description>The first kiss plays a role in this anime. Especially for the female cast this can be quite an important moment, so that stealing ones first kiss is serious for them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2909" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>karaoke</name>
<description>Obligatory national pastime for students in any anime with school setting. Amateur singing to subtitled music videos.
The word itself is a compound of the Japanese words for "empty orchestra".</description>
<picurl>160894.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4304" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-04-26">
<name>anti-climactic end</name>
<description>The story in this anime and the character development were building up so some special point, and the viewer will probably have been looking forward to this resolution. But the ending was a let-down.
This may have several reasons, e.g. it may simply be "bad" story-telling, or the animation studio ran out of money and had to prematurely end the story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4667" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-20">
<name>hard science fiction</name>
<description>Hard science fiction is a category of http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] characterised by an emphasis on scientific accuracy, technical detail, or both. The term is not defined precisely, and is often seen as an approximate way of describing works. Stories revolving around scientific and technical consistency were written as early as 1860s and 1870s; http://anidb.net/cr5973 [Jules Verne] is generally considered the creator of the genre. Although not always accurate in his scientific depictions, and though Verne himself denied writing as a scientist or seriously predicting machines and technology of the future, the attention to detail in his work became an inspiration for many future scientists and explorers.
Nowadays, the term http://anidb.net/t7086 [soft science fiction] is also often used to refer to science fiction stories which lack scientific focus or rigorous adherence to known science; the categorization "hard science fiction" thus represents a position on a broad continuum ranging from "softer" to "harder". There is a degree of flexibility in how far from "real science" a story can stray before it leaves the realm of hard science fiction; some authors scrupulously avoid such technology as faster-than-light travel, while others accept such notions but focus on realistically depicting the worlds that such a technology might make possible. In this view, a story`s scientific "hardness" is less a matter of the absolute accuracy of the science content than of the rigour and consistency with which the various ideas and possibilities are worked out. Furthermore, later discoveries do not necessarily invalidate the label of hard science fiction; the designation remains valid even when a crucial plot element is later discovered to be incorrect.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5463" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-25">
<name>boarding school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5963" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-12">
<name>utopia</name>
<description>"Paradise". Portrays a peaceful, united civilization striving for perfection. This may include the world living as one in peace or just an isolated society, at peace with all their surroundings and anything that exists on the outside is irrelevant. In these conditions, humans may have obtained balance with technology which now exists merely to enhance human living standards. Advanced science and technology allow the absence of death and suffering and/or changes in human nature and condition. Technology has affected the way humans live to such an extent that normal functions such as sleep, eating or reproduction are replaced by artificial means (which may include a society comprised of a single gender). A healthier, more intelligent race has been bred. Many or all people exist with traits and special talents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2780" type="main character in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="16">3.58</rating>
<name>Katase Shima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The heroine of the story is Shima (or `Shipon (しーぽん)` as she is dubbed by Arisa) who joins the Stellvia foundation`s space program so that she could "see the stars while looking forward, rather than having to look up". In the beginning, she fluctuates between complete confidence in her abilities and believing she couldn`t do anything. The series depicts her as extremely diligent, although she is also a natural genius.
[Spoiler]As the series progresses, she learns to understand her mistakes and not think that she has to be perfect or else fail. For instance, after a rocky start to her training, during which she was dead last in her class at piloting, she takes the advice of Kouta Otoyama and realizes she was trying to keep track of far too much information on her ship displays. Her piloting improves dramatically as a result. Shima is offered to be the 5th member of the Big 4, after passing the test. Despite her early setbacks as a pilot, her programming abilities are top notch from the very start, and she eventually combines the two in order to become even more formidable in the cockpit. She is called Shipon because the first time she piloted one of the Biancas she flew around like a ping-pong ball.[/Spoiler]
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>28805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2781" type="main character in" update="2012-05-04">
<rating votes="7">2.91</rating>
<name>Otoyama Kouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouta is an enigmatic character. He and Shipon develop a romantic relationship but there`s still a lot about him that remains unknown. He has an older sister who runs an astronomical observatory in Japan. He often gives advice which is as enigmatic as himself.
[Spoiler]He consistently achieves rank C in every class, without exception, regardless of how easy or hard the subject is. And when he was warned of the possibility of Ayaka attacking Shipon during training, he displays extraordinary piloting abilities beyond what his ship should have been capable of handling. Another example would be during a simulator-game where Rinna scored Rank A, Shima scored Rank B, he had scores Rank S. When Shima asks why Kouta does not do the best during class, especially since he is capable of it, he merely says: he wonders why also. Pierre once remarks "Talented hawks hide their talons" when referring to Kouta`s skills.
On a different note, James was curious of Kouta`s `vision` and said he was chosen by the universe.[/Spoiler]
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>42141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2782" type="main character in" update="2010-01-29">
<rating votes="11">5.79</rating>
<name>Arisa Glennorth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arisa is Shipon`s best friend at the Stellvia foundation. They meet on the shuttle going to the station from Earth at the beginning of the term, and find themselves rooming together and in the same class as well. Though Arisa is nowhere near Shipon in academic or piloting ability, she finds Shipon to be an inspiration to improve herself, and calls Shipon her "Star of Hope". Later in the series, she begins focusing on becoming a mechanic, rather than a pilot.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>42140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2783" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-10">
<rating votes="4">6.06</rating>
<name>Kazamatsuri Rin`na</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rinna is a transfer student from the Ultima foundation, and considers Shipon to be both a friend and chief rival. Rinna is a few years younger than Shipon and most of the other students, but because there are few children at Ultima (it being the newest of the foundations, and still incomplete), she has little to do with herself but play with simulators. As a result, she`s far better at piloting and zero-G movement than most people years older than her.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>47652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2784" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-21">
<rating votes="8">7.41</rating>
<name>Fujisawa Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yayoi is one of the older students in Shipon`s class. Yayoi had been in Stellvia`s training program 2 years before, but left after a flight training accident. [Spoiler]She was saved by Ayaka Machida, but it turned out the "accident" was also intentionally caused by Ayaka in the first place.
Recognizing the signs of another "accident" when Ayaka took Shipon out to train alone, she warns Kouta of what might be about to happen. Kouta is able to prevent another tragedy.
Despite the attacks on herself and Shipon, Yayoi defends Ayaka when it looked like she might face expulsion from Stellvia. Some viewers argued that Yayoi and Ayaka`s relationship might be romantic in nature.[/Spoiler]
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>33643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2785" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="5">6.65</rating>
<name>Kayama Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akira is a quiet and somewhat taciturn member of Shipon`s class as well as Yayoi`s roommate. Though she becomes irritated easily when around people too much, she learns to enjoy spending time with Yayoi, Shipon, Alisa and the others of their group. [Spoiler]Late in the series, she starts dating JoJo.[/Spoiler]
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>48401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2786" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-22">
<rating votes="6">4.75</rating>
<name>Machida Ayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the "Big 4" of Stellvia, (older students who are at the top of their classes), Ayaka is shown as competitive in the extreme. She has something of an inferiority complex which drives her to be the absolute best, and she can`t tolerate seeing others better than her.
[Spoiler]Two years in the past, when Yayoi was her classmate, she arranged an accident to ensure her own position at the top of the class. Things went a little out of hand, however, and it looked like Yayoi might lose her life, so Ayaka rescued her. Yayoi was hospitalized and traumatized, and left Stellvia for a time. Now with Shima Katase looking like she would surpass Ayaka as well, the same thing almost happened. Had Yayoi not returned to Stellvia and recognized the danger Shipon might be in, Ayaka might have seriously injured or even killed her. Due to Yayoi`s defense, Ayaka was not expelled from Stellvia, but was suspended for a time.
After Yayoi forgives Ayaka for nearly causing her to lose her life, the two become very close. Ayaka seems to have strong feelings for her classmate and friend Kent Austin who is also one of the Big 4. Although in the last episode it appeared that she was closer to Yayoi than Kent.[/Spoiler]
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>48399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2787" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="3">4.16</rating>
<name>Richard James</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Richard is the Head Teacher of Stellvia`s Space Academy. He is also the one who conducted the entrance interview for Shima. He is avuncular and usually takes the optimistic view of events. Richard also encourages his peers to put more trust in the prep students when events put them in critical situations. Richard plays a lot of chess with Hutter.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>48398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="710" picture="228657.jpg">Hori Katsunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2788" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="5">3.09</rating>
<name>Carl Hutter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hutter is a teacher at Stellvia`s Space Academy. He appears unemotional and calm at all times. Usually, Hutter plays the Devil`s Advocate against Richard James` optimism. He helps Shima with her confidence towards the end of the series. He is revealed to have a more exotic origin later on in the series.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>42211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="284" picture="225436.jpg">Tanaka Masahiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2789" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="3">4.58</rating>
<name>Shirogane Jinrai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirogane is another teacher at Stellvia`s Space Academy; he appears to teach programming. He is particularly enthusiastic about the school`s athletics carnival and Astroball, (a game that has some similarities with Lacrosse), which he played in his student days at Stellvia. Passionate and determined, Jinrai is intent upon having the students` voices heard when no-one will listen. Jinrai has feelings for the flirtatious school nurse Ren.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>48405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2790" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="3">4.98</rating>
<name>Leila Barthes</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Instructor in charge of Pilot Training at Stellvia. She used to be an elite pilot, and spent some time wallowing in despair after losing the "elite" tag. However, she recovers from this(after an incident on a space station that was under construction) and choses to become an instructor at Stellvia. She is tough toward the students because she wants them to succeed, she has a loving smile toward the childlike attributes of her students and is very scary when she is mad.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>48400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2791" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-23">
<rating votes="3">3.71</rating>
<name>Renge Ren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A nurse at Stellvia. Ren is very flirtatious and early on in the series dates different men, which causes Jinrai to become jealous. She also works closely with the pilots, especially Kouta, who she assists with training for missions. She seems to also have feelings for Jinrai.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>48438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2792" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="3">2.76</rating>
<name>Joey Jones</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another of Shipon`s classmates, Jojo (as he is called) is loud and enthusiastic. He is not very good in his studies nor pilot training and sometimes get needled because of it. Nevertheless, he is not all bad apples. [Spoiler]He eventually starts dating Akira later on in the series. He sometimes has some rather good things to say that are very influential, he tries to cheer Akira up one time when she is depressed at the gap between her and the top students.[/Spoiler]
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>42213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2793" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="2">1.29</rating>
<name>Takida Pierre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another of Shipon`s classmates, Pierre is good looking and a big talker, but doesn`t seem to have a lot more than that going for him. He likes to hit on virtually every girl he lays eyes on, even Rinna in one episode. He shows particular interest in Yayoi, though it`s not clear what her feelings for him may be. [Spoiler]He confesses his feelings to her and was turned down, but Yayoi later hints he might still have some hope.[/Spoiler]
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>48408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2794" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="2">2.61</rating>
<name>Odawara Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another of Shipon`s classmates, he is seen hanging out with Joey and Pierre. Others call him by his nickname, Dai, which is another reading for his given name in kanji (大). [Spoiler]In the last few episodes he becomes very serious and says some very influential things which is broadcast through the solar system as the last sounds from Stellvia before the inevitable end.[/Spoiler]
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>26822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2795" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-11">
<rating votes="4">6.45</rating>
<name>Najima Gable</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gable Najima is one of the http://anidb.net/ch2798 [Big 4]. She usually quotes something of http://anidb.net/cr3515 [Shakespeare] and sometimes the bible.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>42212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2796" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="2">3.60</rating>
<name>Kent Austin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the Big 4. He usually tries to stir Ayaka up with information that could be potential competition for her with no intention of any of it leading to the "accidents" arranged by Ayaka. He gets Shipon and her friends out of a spot of trouble at the beginning when he saw them as he was passing by. Kent seems to like Ayaka more than just a friend. Though he doesn`t try to make anything out of it.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>48406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7068" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2797" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="2">3.81</rating>
<name>Shoujin Ritsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the Big 4. Devoted to training, he is described as being a "Ninja" by Shipon. Shoujin is very quiet and reserved, rarely speaking. He merely nods and "hmm"`s when in agreement.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>48407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2798" type="appears in" update="2009-01-31">
<name>Big 4</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="2804" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="3">6.32</rating>
<name>Katase Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shima`s mother.</description>
<picture>48404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2139" picture="25822.jpg">Kasahara Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2805" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="3">4.05</rating>
<name>Katase Umihito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shima`s father.</description>
<picture>48402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2806" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-22">
<rating votes="3">4.89</rating>
<name>Katase Masato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shima`s younger brother.
In the end of the series, he is shown grown up, and joining Stellvia too</description>
<picture>48403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18039" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-23">
<rating votes="3">4.36</rating>
<name>Otoyama Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12246" picture="41028.jpg">Sakuma Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18078" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-23">
<rating votes="3">4.36</rating>
<name>Mia Glennorth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18079" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-24">
<rating votes="2">3.60</rating>
<name>Orihara Michio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18080" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-24">
<rating votes="3">2.30</rating>
<name>Juno Myor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13050" picture="171761.jpg">Shibuya Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89456" type="appears in" update="2017-05-23">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kazamatsuri Natasha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4770" picture="76766.jpg">Suzuka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89457" type="appears in" update="2017-05-23">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kazamatsuri Tamotsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1985" picture="21285.jpg">Hayashi Kazuo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6979" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6985" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とまどい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hesitation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomadoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7242" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ごめんなさい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Sorry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gomen Nasai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7441" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">がんばります</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Do My Best</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ganbarimasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7513" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きっかけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opportunity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikkake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7688" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まけません</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Won`t Lose</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makemasen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7801" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">くやしいよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frustration</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuyashii yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7913" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Me?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi Desuka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8035" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いってきます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Going</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ittekimasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8037" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかえりなさい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome Back</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okaerinasai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8320" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほんとうのあなた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Real You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hontou no Anata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8393" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こくはく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuhaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8533" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふゆやすみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Winter Vacation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuyuyasumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8682" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆめとげんじつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream and Reality</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume to Genjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8778" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わかりません</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Don`t Understand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakarimasen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9052" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うたがいのなかで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Doubt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utagai no Nakade</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9345" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たたかい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9669" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とおいこえ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distant Voice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tooi Koe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9670" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なきんぼ おこりんぼ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cry Baby, Hot-head</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakinbo Okorinbo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10024" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みらいをきみに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let There Be A Future You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai o Kimi ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10292" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みえないかべ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invisible Wall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mienai Kabe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10395" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれのみち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Their Own Path</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Michi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10652" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">だからあなたがいる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s Why You`re There</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dakara Anata ga Iru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10828" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたたびのやみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Darkness Falls Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatabi no Yami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11283" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11373" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きらめきはこえ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining Voice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirameki wa Koe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39413" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118460" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening Ep 26</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
