<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6303" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-01-18</startdate>
<enddate>2012-04-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ai no Kusabi (2012)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">間の楔 (2012)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="793" type="Alternative Setting">Ai no Kusabi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="271366">Love the original and the novels are some of the best examples of yaoi fiction to date. This new version is amazing, retold in stunning detail and despite our beloved voice of Iason Mink, I highly recommend viewing this reproduction if you`re a fan of the original. You`ll fall in love all over again!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="375005">if you have seen the orginal or read the books then you should totally watch this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="33393">The animations is amazing! I`m so glad they chose to do an OVA of this! This isn`t a fluffy shounen ai story but it`s an amazing love story and definitely the most amazing animation you`ll find in any anime of this series.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20120814042713/http://ainokusabi.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Animation Work">AIC</name>
<name id="2163" type="Character Design">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="3987" type="Direction">Akiyama Katsuhito</name>
<name id="2163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="17073" type="Original Work">Yoshihara Rieko</name>
<name id="17073" type="Series Composition">Yoshihara Rieko</name>
<name id="4642" type="Music">Takahashi Tetsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>The story is set in the future on the planet named Amoi which is controlled by a supercomputer named Jupiter. Among the mostly male human population, the blond-haired elite class is allowed to temporarily keep slaves as luxury pets. One elite member, http://anidb.net/ch25159 [Iason], encounters a lower class slum mongrel named http://anidb.net/ch25160 [Riki] and decides to forcibly take him as a pet which is unusual and taboo in elite society. However, Iason keeps Riki longer than it is socially approved, and rumors abound about their possible relationship.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="258">5.11</permanent>
<temporary count="263">6.59</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>16280.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10568</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5784</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4624</identifier>
<identifier>muchog</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20120814042713/http://ainokusabi.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20130813172032/http://www.anime-int.com/works/ainokusabi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>間の楔#OVA_.E7.AC.AC2.E6.9C.9F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340871</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1282" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>pet</name>
<description>A domestic animal kept for pleasure or companionship.</description>
<picurl>221616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2145" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-21">
<name>chain</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2868" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-20">
<name>racism</name>
<description>Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of an ethnically different background based on the pseudo-scientific belief that biological differences between peoples form so-called "races" and that one`s own "race" is superior to another, possibly also holding that members of different "races" should be treated differently. Some definitions include only consciously malignant forms of discrimination, and some views include discriminatory behaviors and beliefs based on cultural, national, ethnic, caste, or religious stereotypes. In works of fiction, this may also include similar actions against other sentient species.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2884" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>psychoactive drugs</name>
<description>Psychoactive drugs are chemical substances that affect the function of the central nervous system, altering perception, mood or consciousness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3190" parentid="6083" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-28">
<name>master-slave relation</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3664" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>futuristic motorcycle</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5804" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-19">
<name>piledriver</name>
<description>As you can see, the characters shirts were torn from a fight as they were previously wrestling. They seem to wrestle a lot in the show and most of the time you just see them doing the choke hold wrong and giving each other piledrivers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="25159" type="main character in" update="2010-11-18">
<rating votes="17">8.55</rating>
<name>Iason Mink</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iason is not just any Blondie - he is the most perfect, superior and powerful of all of them, the one who talks directly with Jupiter and carries out Jupiter`s commands. He is the head of the Syndicate, Tanagura`s black market for pet trade. He is in love with Riki, a mongrel from the slums, which casts a literally dark shadow over his seeming perfection. Iason becomes interested, obsessed, and finally falls in love with Riki. He has an elegant and calm manner that hides a passionate, ruthless and unforgiving nature. For Riki, Iason is willing to flaunt and break all taboos.</description>
<picture>59494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25160" type="main character in" update="2010-11-18">
<rating votes="12">4.64</rating>
<name>Riki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Riki, or "Riki the Dark" has been called the `charisma` of the slums. He was the leader of Bison, a gang in Ceres, and eventually became Iason Mink`s pet, which had a crushing effect to his human pride. Riki is proud, rebellious, fierce and defiant, but his experiences change him. Some men living in the slums feel he has lost his spark. He is torn between his pride and the feelings he has for Iason that he is unwilling to acknowledge.</description>
<picture>59495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25161" type="main character in" update="2010-11-18">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Guy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A former pairing partner of Riki`s. (He, too, is overly obsessed about Riki.) When Riki was the leader of the Bison gang, Guy was his second-in-command, and Guy assumes the leadership when Riki vanishes.</description>
<picture>59496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36187" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-02">
<rating votes="4">3.39</rating>
<name>Katze</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36188" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-02">
<rating votes="4">1.19</rating>
<name>Kirie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36189" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-02">
<rating votes="7">5.22</rating>
<name>Raoul Am</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="133131" update="2012-01-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">petere 檻獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Petere: Caged Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Petere Kanjuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133132" update="2012-02-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">pardo 折翼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pardo: Broken Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pardo Setsuyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133133" update="2012-04-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">congressus 邂逅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Congressus: Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Congressus Kaikou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133134" update="2012-04-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">retino 淫縛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Retino: Bondage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Retino Inbaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178943" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178944" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178945" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178946" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178947" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178950" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 4 Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178951" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 4 Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178952" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3 Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178953" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3 Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178954" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2 Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178955" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2 Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178956" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1 Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178957" update="2016-07-17">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1 Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
