<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6311" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-03-27</startdate>
<enddate>2009-06-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kin`iro no Chord: Secondo Passo</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Златната корда: Втора стъпка</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">La Corda D`Oro: Secondo Passo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">金色のコルダ ~secondo passo~</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4509" type="Prequel">Kin`iro no Chord: Primo Passo</anime>
<anime id="10210" type="Other">Kin`iro no Chord: Blue Sky</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.corda-primopasso.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="845" type="Animation Work">Yumeta Company</name>
<name id="930" type="Original Work">Koei</name>
<name id="7768" type="Animation Character Design">Fujioka Maki</name>
<name id="7768" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujioka Maki</name>
<name id="8937" type="Direction">Ochi Koujin</name>
</creators>
<description>Following the intraschool competition at Seiso Academy, budding music student Kahoko meets brusque boy Eto, the new school board director Akihiko Kira, and the mysterious transfer student Aoi Kaji.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="396">4.83</permanent>
<temporary count="399">6.79</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>22050.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10592</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5717</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4441</identifier>
<identifier>xtptnu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.corda-primopasso.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>La_Corda_d'Oro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>金色のコルダ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1570</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>333045</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10852</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1015</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>la-corda-doro-primo-passo-and-secondo-passo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8388" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="4">5.43</rating>
<name>Yunoki Azuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azuma is a third year student. He appears to be a very considerate and kind to others, and is considered a prince in school because of his good looks, perfect grades, and charming personality. Azuma comes from a well-brought family of traditional Kado background and he is extremely capable in traditional Japanese rituals and customs, like Ikebana (the art of flower arranging), tea ceremonies, and traditional gardening. Born as the third son of the family, he is strictly forbidden to outshine his older brothers. For that reason he was forced to give up piano when he was young and turn to flute instead.</description>
<picture>27538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13242" type="main character in" update="2009-12-03">
<name>Tsuchiura Ryoutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13243" type="main character in" update="2018-05-20">
<rating votes="4">8.02</rating>
<name>Hino Kahoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66038.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1436" picture="18822.jpg">Takagi Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13244" type="main character in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="7">9.50</rating>
<name>Tsukimori Ren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13261" type="main character in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="1">8.22</rating>
<name>Shimizu Keiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13262" type="main character in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="3">7.99</rating>
<name>Hihara Kazuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13263" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="1">7.56</rating>
<name>Fuyuumi Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3710" picture="25089.jpg">Satou Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13264" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-25">
<name>Lili</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63059" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="1">6.53</rating>
<name>Amou Nami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1888" picture="228611.jpg">Masuda Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68246" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-26">
<name>Etou Kiriya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="96796" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<summary>Even though the music contest within the school has ended, Kahoko has continued her own violin practice. Kahoko, like many of the other contestants, resume their practice to once again perform and compete against each other.  After encountering a lower classman, Kiriya Etou, some very cold and harsh words were exchanged...why was he so cold...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>524222</identifier>
<identifier>la-corda-doro-primo-passo-and-secondo-passo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="101970" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<summary>With the pressure of appearing on stage Kahoko doubts her abilities on stage. It will take the help of her friends to bring her back from the edge.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>529756</identifier>
<identifier>la-corda-doro-primo-passo-and-secondo-passo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
