<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6317" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-12-22</startdate>
<enddate>2001-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kanzen Shouri Daiteiou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Perfect Victory Daiteiou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Eldran Series 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Daiteiou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">完全勝利ダイテイオー</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3961" type="Character">Nekketsu Saikyou Gozaurer</anime>
<anime id="4486" type="Character">Zettai Muteki Raijin Ou</anime>
<anime id="5816" type="Character">Genki Bakuhatsu Ganbaruger</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="7902" type="Character Design">Kondou Takamitsu</name>
<name id="6665" type="Series Composition">Kitajima Hiroaki</name>
</creators>
<description>When an alien force attacks Earth, a giant sword falls onto the campus of Paradise Elementary School, transforming it into a flying vessel. The fate of the planet lies with one group of kids who must pilot powerful mecha to stop the invaders before it`s too late!
Source: Anime-Planet
Note: originally planned as a TV anime series, but ended up being a promotional video for its manga serialisation on magazine Monthly Daiteioh.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="62">3.03</permanent>
<temporary count="62">4.61</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>169506.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7157</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9221</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352123</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6004" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>development hell</name>
<description>Due to unforeseen circumstances, the production or release of this anime has been pushed back, stalled, or cancelled one or more times from when it was first announced.
While some of them have eventually been completed, others might have only had a trailer released or have been changed into another format (e.g. a TV series turned into an OVA).
Common reasons for a work to become stuck in development hell include creative differences, legal issues, financial problems, scheduling conflicts or the death of an involved creator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="96175" update="2009-01-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2001-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
