<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6321" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-11-29</startdate>
<enddate>2008-02-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Saa Ikou! Tamagotchi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">さあイコー! たまごっち</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Let`s Go! Tamagotchi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">さぁイコー! たまごっち</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3083" type="Other">Anime TV de Hakken! Tamagotchi</anime>
<anime id="7018" type="Other">Eiga de Toujou! Tamagotchi Doki Doki! Uchuu no Maigotchi!?</anime>
<anime id="7078" type="Other">Tamagotchi!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="151293">Cuteness overload. Exactly somethin that all tamagotchi fans would love. So do I</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gyao.jp/bkids/tamago/</url>
<creators>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="4464" type="Animation Character Design">Ichiishi Sayuri</name>
<name id="5374" type="Series Composition">Matsui Aya</name>
<name id="1051" type="Original Plan">Bandai</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
</creators>
<description>Tamagotchi is an anime series focusing on the lives of Mametchi, Memetchi, Kuchipatchi, ChaMametchi, and their friends.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="43">2.21</permanent>
<temporary count="43">4.20</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>16862.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10957</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6798</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gyao.jp/bkids/tamago/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>たまごっち#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1293</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329576</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14215</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="997" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>association football</name>
<description>Football is a sport that involves kicking a ball in order to score a goal, while the other team tries to stop you by kicking the ball in the other direction to score a goal of their own. In the United States, this sport is known as soccer; the inappropriately titled "American" football (which in fact is played with the egg-shaped "ball" being carried around) is some kind of rugby for babies.</description>
<picurl>40031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="31572" type="main character in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="8">5.12</rating>
<name>Mametchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31573" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="6">7.27</rating>
<name>Memetchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31574" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="6">7.27</rating>
<name>Kuchipatchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12373" picture="223463.jpg">Yaguchi Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31577" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-26">
<name>Flowertchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10854" picture="38961.jpg">Sasaki Hinako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31578" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-26">
<name>Makiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2890" picture="23182.jpg">Sugiyama Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31579" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-26">
<name>KuroMametchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="402" picture="17249.jpg">Katou Nanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31580" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-26">
<name>Gozarutchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2364" picture="151724.jpg">Furushima Kiyotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="96219" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">朝からごりっぱ! たまごっちスクール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asakara Gorippa! Tamagocchi School</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96220" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">まめっちのビックリ新発明!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96221" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">めめっちのぐるぐるピンチ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96222" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぱっちの森のある一日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96223" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">チームでたいこー! まめっちvsくろまめっち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96224" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-01-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパーヒロインちゃまめっち!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96225" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おぼえてる? ふらわっち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96226" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モテモテ!? くろまめっち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96227" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねつれつ! まめっちファンくらぶ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96228" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ごっち大王は笑わない?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96229" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ごりっぱ先生のバースデー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96230" update="2009-01-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2008-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">たまごっちタウンのないしょばなし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
