<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6323" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-04-12</startdate>
<enddate>2009-06-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hatsukoi Limited</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Hatsukoi Gentei</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">First Love Limited</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">初恋限定</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">HatsuLimi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">初恋限定.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hatsukoi Limited</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Компания «Первая любовь»</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5276" approval="63" total="70">KimiKiss Pure Rouge</anime>
<anime id="100" approval="12" total="14">Boys Be...</anime>
<anime id="5909" approval="11" total="25">Toradora!</anime>
<anime id="3067" approval="6" total="14">Ichigo 100%</anime>
<anime id="2165" approval="2" total="2">School Rumble</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="161487">very lovely</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="35101">If you like love-polygon type of anime, this is one of the best out there! A funny yet a bit romantic type of anime. Must watch!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="293290">Good. But just 12 EP is to short.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="543820">For me (still new at this) the animation was superb and the characters were all enjoyable. Episode #9 was extremely moving. I hope there is more out there like this series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="332327">Love this!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="433379">Seriously, a must see for romance and comedy!!!Great character development, although the main character`s development had some unfinished business T_T 
I will rewatch it soon!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.j-hatsukoi.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="2932" type="Character Design">Shitaya Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="1521" type="Direction">Yamakawa Yoshiki</name>
<name id="2931" type="Music">Nijine</name>
<name id="2932" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shitaya Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="3391" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hasegawa Shin`ya</name>
<name id="9774" type="Series Composition">Kunisawa Mariko</name>
<name id="6307" type="Original Work">Kawashita Mizuki</name>
<name id="8360" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamakawa Kouji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr6307 [Kawashita Mizuki].
Being an adolescent girl is just one problem after another. Middle-schooler http://anidb.net/ch6556 [Arihara Ayumi] receives a note from a high-schooler, a very large and intimidating boy, http://anidb.net/ch6565 [Zaitsu Misao], asking her out. Frightened and intrigued, she doesn`t know what to do!
This has been described as a series of vignettes in the everyday lives of a junior high school girl named Ayumi and seven other junior high and high school girls, as they fall in and out of love and deal with girl issues.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2540">6.41</permanent>
<temporary count="2555">7.49</temporary>
<review count="3">6.88</review>
</ratings>
<picture>29284.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10286</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6882</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5150</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4450</identifier>
<identifier>uxkbdv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://jcstaff.co.jp/sakuhin/nenpyo/2009/04_hatsukoi/hatsukoi.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hatsukoi_Limited</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>初恋限定。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1581</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>333417</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10837</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3694" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>dear mother in heaven</name>
<description>A form of veneration of ancestors, where people call upon their ancestors for help, advice and similar in their everyday life like in other cultures upon God, Jesus, the Virgin Mary or various saints. The veneration of the spirit`s of one`s ancestors is an integral part of Japanese culture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3718" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>love between enemies</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4761" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-11">
<name>love letter</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime receives a love letter, usually stashed away in their school shoe locker. Or in other cases a girl might directly give the love letter to the boy she loves.
Plot device to further the relationship between characters, may also be used as comedic element creating awkward situations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5104" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-11-22">
<name>vignetted picture</name>
<description>In photography and optics, vignetting is a reduction of an image brightness or saturation at the periphery compared to the image center, usually caused by faulty optics.
Although vignetting is normally unintended and undesired, it is sometimes purposely introduced for example in comics, animation or video games as a creative, false camera effect, such as to draw attention to the center of the screen.</description>
<picurl>43292.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5285" parentid="3411" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>street fighting</name>
<picurl>211275.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5546" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-07-28">
<name>complete manga adaptation</name>
<description>Anime ends, then manga ends</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6556" type="main character in" update="2013-01-20">
<rating votes="14">5.06</rating>
<name>Arihara Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 2nd year middle school second year. Ayumi is one day asked out by http://anidb.net/ch6565 [Misao Zaitsu]. Though she claimed she would accept any offer, she is consistently unsettled by Zaitsu`s monstrous appearance. However, she shows she can be somewhat caring as well as crafty. She is 152cm (4`9") tall and runs the second fastest in her class. She`s also unusually strong for her size and build, as demonstrated when she knocked out Misao with a single kick. She falls in love with Misao`s younger brother http://anidb.net/ch6561 [Mamoru] after he carries her to the infirmy. At the end, she is trying to decide between the two Zaitzu brothers, whether to choose the one who likes her (Misao) or the one she likes (Mamoru). She shares a strong resemblance to http://anidb.net/ch28486 [Chinami Hashimoto], a character from another of Kawashita`s work, Strawberry 100%.</description>
<picture>27786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6557" type="main character in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="34">8.49</rating>
<name>Enomoto Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of http://anidb.net/ch6556 [Ayumi]`s friends, Kei is apparently very popular with guys due to her "mature" face. However, she sees the attention she receives as a hassle, and believes confessions of love are just a chore if the feeling isn`t mutual. She openly admits that looks are a major factor in choosing a relationship, but carries a love-hate (mostly hate) relationship with http://anidb.net/ch6562 [Kusuda].</description>
<picture>27775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6558" type="main character in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="16">5.78</rating>
<name>Bessho Koyoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another one of http://anidb.net/ch6556 [Ayumi]`s friends, Koyoi has an open brother complex with her brother http://anidb.net/ch6571 [Yoshihiko]. Once http://anidb.net/ch6565 [Misao] starts hanging around, she, along with http://anidb.net/ch6560 [Nao], stop walking home with Ayumi. She is also in the same grade as Ayumi. Since her brother likes http://anidb.net/ch6567 [Misaki], a popular and attractive girl, she regards her as a "Final Boss" that she must defeat. She also quotes that Misaki`s chest is a "truly evil power."</description>
<picture>27787.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6559" type="main character in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="16">7.15</rating>
<name>Dobashi Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seemingly the most level headed out of the group, Rika seems to enjoy teasing others. A well known tom-boy, she excels in athletics and has been stated to be domineering. She is in the same grade as http://anidb.net/ch6556 [Ayumi]. She became close to tennis player http://anidb.net/ch6563 [Terai] when he started physical training with her, and over time became attracted to him, but didn`t give him that impression at first, thinking that was all there was to have a relationship.</description>
<picture>27789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6560" type="main character in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="12">5.47</rating>
<name>Chikura Nao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another one of http://anidb.net/ch6556 [Ayumi]`s friends, Nao is somewhat envious of http://anidb.net/ch6557 [Kei]`s attention. Along with http://anidb.net/ch6558 [Koyoi], she stops walking home with Ayumi for fear of http://anidb.net/ch6565 [Misao]. She is in her 2nd year of middle school. Being a member of the art club, she came to admire the artist who made the painting of a Sakura tree, http://anidb.net/ch8890 [Renjou Yukito], and after meeting him, asked him to assist her in making her own painting. However, upon his graduation, he left Japan, leaving her broken hearted. When she learned about http://anidb.net/ch6564 [Hiroyuki Sogabe]`s feelings towards her, she became close to him. She shares a strong resemblance to http://anidb.net/ch21615 [Misuzu Sotomura], a character from another of Kawashita`s works, http://anidb.net/a3067 [Ichigo 100%].</description>
<picture>27788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6561" type="main character in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="10">5.25</rating>
<name>Zaitsu Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cheerful boy who dreams of being a paramedic, http://anidb.net/ch6556 [Ayumi] falls for Mamoru quickly when he offers to take her to the nurse. Although he is in Ayumi`s class, Ayumi only realizes that he is in fact http://anidb.net/ch6565 [Misao]`s younger brother a day after she meets Misao. He is somewhat taken back by Ayumi; he believes she is more fearsome than she may appear. Furthermore, despite Ayumi`s feelings, Mamoru has a crush on his next door neighbor http://anidb.net/ch6567 [Misaki Yamamoto]. He later runs away with http://anidb.net/ch6562 [Kusuda] and http://anidb.net/ch6564 [Sogabe] after he was turned down by Misaki. He then has a change of heart after realizing he made Ayumi cry due to his actions. He shares a passing resemblance to Kojima, a character from another of Kawashita`s work, Lilim Kiss, as well as http://anidb.net/ch8848 [Manaka Junpei] from http://anidb.net/a3067 [Ichigo 100%].</description>
<picture>27796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6562" type="main character in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="12">4.69</rating>
<name>Kusuda Etsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kusuda is a pervy friend of http://anidb.net/ch6561 [Mamoru]`s. His talent is putting girls to sleep with stupid puns. He doesn`t see much in http://anidb.net/ch6556 [Ayumi], but he is very interested in http://anidb.net/ch6567 [Misaki]; he is nearly obsessed with her. He seems undaunted by http://anidb.net/ch6557 [Kei]`s good looks, and with his "Kappa" face, they tend to bicker a lot. He runs away from home with Mamoru and http://anidb.net/ch6564 [Sogabe] because he regrets saying he hates Kei.</description>
<picture>27794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6563" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="7">4.76</rating>
<name>Terai Haruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the tennis club at school, Terai has little athletic ability. However, with http://anidb.net/ch6559 [Dobashi]`s assistance, he manages to become a somewhat decent athlete. During that time, he has fallen for Dobashi, but due to her (inadvertent) teasing, plus the fact that she avoided holding hands with him (to which she revealed that she found it embarrasing to do so), he is unsure of their relationship.</description>
<picture>27795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6564" type="main character in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="8">5.83</rating>
<name>Sogabe Hiroyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a friend of http://anidb.net/ch6562 [Kusuda]. Sogabe is a bit of a delusional character, as well as a little narcissistic. He likes http://anidb.net/ch6560 [Nao] and tries to get close to her to create an opportunity for her to confess to him. He shows his insecurities when Nao shows interest towards http://anidb.net/ch8890 [Yukito Renjou], an artist and graduated student from their school. He runs away from home because of this (although only for two days) with Kusuda and http://anidb.net/ch6561 [Mamoru].</description>
<picture>28269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6565" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="10">6.81</rating>
<name>Zaitsu Misao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>With a monstrous face and a huge body, Misao is feared by anyone who sees his face or knows his name (with the exception of his childhood friend and neighbor, http://anidb.net/ch6567 [Misaki Yamamoto]). As expected, he is a capable fighter with plenty of enemies. However, he is also unexpectedly shy; being unable to convey his feelings through words, he writes his confession on a note, and he is unable to bring himself to even say http://anidb.net/ch6556 [Ayumi]`s name. He fell for Ayumi when he saw her picture while looking through http://anidb.net/ch6561 [his brother]`s class photos. After Ayumi made him realize that he scares her, he decided to watch over her at a distance.</description>
<picture>27797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6566" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="9">5.10</rating>
<name>Arihara Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch6556 [Ayumi]`s older brother Yuuji can be somewhat callous and rude. For example, he steals her cookies and barges into her room without knocking. The opposite to http://anidb.net/ch6558 [Koyoi], he has a sister complex, for which he claims the love is purely brotherly. Like all other guys at his school, he cowers at hearing the name of http://anidb.net/ch6565 [Misao Zaitsu], and is under the impression that his sister has fallen for Misao.</description>
<picture>27792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6567" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="60">9.17</rating>
<name>Yamamoto Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A first year in high school, Misaki is close friends with http://anidb.net/ch6569 [Meguru] and http://anidb.net/ch6568 [Yuu], as well as the next door neighbor and childhood friend of the Zaitsu brothers. She has a very open relationship with her neighbors, and even comes into http://anidb.net/ch6561 [Mamoru]`s room through his window, and is the only character in the series who`s not afraid of http://anidb.net/ch6565 [Misao] (in fact she often has casual conversations with him). She somehow knows submission techniques, and can perform them instinctively in her sleep. Though she claimed she had no interest in relationships at the moment, she developed an interest for http://anidb.net/ch6566 [Yuuji Arihara] when he shoved a lollipop in her mouth (showing an example to his friend, Yoshihiko Bessho). But although she likes Yuuji, she is not used to feeling vulnerable around boys, because she`s usually cool and level headed.</description>
<picture>27772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6568" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="7">5.75</rating>
<name>Enomoto Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuu is good friends with http://anidb.net/ch6569 [Meguru] and http://anidb.net/ch6567 [Misaki], and is also http://anidb.net/ch6557 [Kei]`s older sister. She is a cheery girl who never hesitates to make friends. Although she appears to be a little ditsy, she carries an avid interest for just about everything, making her very knowledgeable on a variety of subjects. As a result, she, like her sister, garners a lot of attention from many guys. However, whether its being oblivious or just nonchalant, she doesn`t seem to mind being friendly with all of them. She also seems to be younger than her little sister, because of her small size and child-like innocence.</description>
<picture>27790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6569" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="11">6.27</rating>
<name>Watase Meguru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meguru is a close friend of both http://anidb.net/ch6567 [Misaki] and http://anidb.net/ch6568 [Yuu]. In middle school, she was a national champion in swimming, making her a reserve candidate for the Olympics. However, Meguru quits swimming when she enters high school because her breasts grow too large and attract too much attention when she`s in her swimsuit. Unfortunately, those who are attracted don`t include http://anidb.net/ch8891 [Takei], whom Meguru secretly likes. She also wears small bras in attempt to make her breasts look smaller. Her friends encourage her to to not be ashamed of them, and not hiding them. She eventually joins the school swimming team, at first to save the team from closure (due to the fact that it had only five members and one of them quit) and taking the position as team manager, and, after some prodding from Takei, eventually as one of the swimmers.</description>
<picture>130748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6570" type="appears in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="6">3.84</rating>
<name>Kyuuma Nanoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nanoka is a first year in highschool, and http://anidb.net/ch6569 [Meguru]`s self-proclaimed rival in swimming since middle school. She shows up to challenge Meguru to a swimming race and beats her, making Meguru unsure of herself, and is also influential in getting her back into swimming. Her small stature makes people think she is a primary school student. Meguru calls her Q-chan, a nickname Nanoka hates.</description>
<picture>130747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6571" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="6">5.16</rating>
<name>Bessho Yoshihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A first year in high school, Yoshihiko is http://anidb.net/ch6558 [Koyoi]`s older brother, with whom she is smitten. However, he does not return her level of affection, and is often annoyed by it. He is in love with http://anidb.net/ch6567 [Misaki], whom, to his dismay, likes his friend http://anidb.net/ch6566 [Yuuji], but they are in friendly terms such that she often confides in him about boys.</description>
<picture>27793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8890" type="appears in" update="2009-06-10">
<rating votes="7">4.68</rating>
<name>Renjou Yukito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An artist, whom drew the Sakura painting which Nao is inspired at. He used to attend the middle school which Nao goes to. Presently, he goes to a prestigious high school called Kaitei High School and is in his graduating year. He became close to Nao after she finds out he made the painting she often looked at. Upon his graduation though, he left Japan. (Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>28270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8891" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="9">5.78</rating>
<name>Takei Gengorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gengorou is an upperclassman who tries to persuade http://anidb.net/ch6569 [Meguru] to join the swimming club at every opportunity. He challenges Meguru to a backstroke contest (to persuade her to join the team) and loses. Takei is Meguru`s childhood friend - it is mentioned that they`ve taken swimming together since they were children. He finally succeeds in getting Meguru to join the swimming club as a star player after he admits to liking her as a girl rather than merely as a champion swimmer.</description>
<picture>28271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9780" type="appears in" update="2009-07-26">
<rating votes="11">5.42</rating>
<name>Fudoumiya Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10754" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="9">5.62</rating>
<name>Andou Soako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A second year middle school student, Soako is the heroine of the special episodes of Hatsukoi Limited. The first introduction of Soako is when she is late for school. Unfortunately for Soako, in her lateness, she has forgotten to put on underwear. The story follows her throughout the day, and all the problems that she has. She was, however, helped by http://anidb.net/ch6561 [Mamoru], which made her fall for him (to http://anidb.net/ch6556 [Ayumi]`s dismay).</description>
<picture>32068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11371" type="appears in" update="2009-08-27">
<rating votes="2">3.77</rating>
<name>Taiiku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The physical education teacher for Ayumi`s class.</description>
<picture>33943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4041" picture="26004.jpg">Miyasaka Shunzou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="97353" update="2009-03-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美少女Aと野獣Z</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beauty A and the Beast Z</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bishoujo A to Yajuu Z</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99595" update="2011-01-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とまどいダイビング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confused Diving</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomadoi Diving</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99596" update="2009-04-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界の誰より大好きな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love You More Than Anybody Else in the World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai no Dare yori Daisuki na</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99597" update="2009-04-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆらめきアンバランス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wavering Unbalance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yurameki Unbalance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99598" update="2009-09-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">となりの山本さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yamamoto-san from Next Door</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tonari no Yamamoto-san.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="100122" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="100123" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="101867" update="2009-05-06">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その思い出には満開の</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Full Bloom for Those Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Omoide ni wa Mankai no</title>
</episode>
<episode id="101868" update="2009-05-06">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チョコレート・ボマーの憂鬱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of the Chocolate Bomber</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chocolate Bomber no Yuuutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="101869" update="2009-05-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キスをしようよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiss o Shiyou yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="101870" update="2011-01-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪が降り出すその前に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Before It Snows</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki ga Furidasu Sono Mae ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103913" update="2009-06-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カッパファイト!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kappa Fight!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kappa Fight!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104200" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハツコイリミテッド.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Love Limited</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsukoi Limited</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104201" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年達の逃避行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boys` Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounentachi no Douhikou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105537" update="2009-09-16">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">限定少女. 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limited Girl 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gentei Shoujo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105538" update="2009-08-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">限定少女. 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limited Girl 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gentei Shoujo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108082" update="2009-08-27">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">限定少女. 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limited Girl 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gentei Shoujo 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110928" update="2009-11-08">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2009-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">限定少女. 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limited Girl 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gentei Shoujo 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111274" update="2011-01-09">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2009-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">限定少女. 5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limited Girl 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gentei Shoujo 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112105" update="2017-11-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112106" update="2017-11-26">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2009-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112425" update="2011-01-09">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">限定少女. 6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limited Girl 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gentei Shoujo 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125476" update="2017-11-29">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125477" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="en">After Talk</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125478" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125479" update="2010-11-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
