<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6325" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-04-25</startdate>
<enddate>2009-04-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann: Lagann Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gurren-Lagann Movie: Lagann Arc</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">극장판 천원돌파 그렌라간: 나암편</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Гуррен Лаганн: Арката Лаганн</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">ttgl movie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 天元突破グレンラガン 螺巌篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gurren Lagann the Movie: The Lights in the Sky Are Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Gurren Lagann. Película 2: Las luces del cielo son estrellas</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5783" type="Prequel">Gekijouban Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann: Gurren Hen</anime>
<anime id="4575" type="Full Story">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="156781">just the ending of the regular series minus all the crap.. in its pure form it is awesome</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="357163">Your mind, your body, and your soul will be blown away</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="418726">If you liked the first series then you will love this movie even more trust me on this</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="379739">OH, SHI-
Just when you thought it couldn`t get any better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="136296">Breathtaking.  Somehow, it utterly surpasses the original series.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gurren-lagann-movie.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="718" type="Animation Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="3078" type="Character Design">Nishigori Atsushi</name>
<name id="718" type="Original Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="1568" type="Original Work">Nakashima Kazuki</name>
<name id="155" type="Direction">Imaishi Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="1414" type="Music">Iwasaki Taku</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the re-edited second part of the story from the television series http://anidb.net/a4575 [Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann].
Background: In the distant future, people build their homes and raise domestic animals in subterranean caverns called pits. A boy named http://anidb.net/ch469 [Simon] happens to find a small, shiny drill that unlocks not only a more promising, but also a quite dangerous future for humankind. Together with the reckless, charismatic leader http://anidb.net/ch468 [Kamina] and the trigger-happy http://anidb.net/ch470 [Youko], they battle against ever more powerful gigantic robots — the Gunmen — on the planet`s surface. The Spiral King`s Four Supreme Generals are merciless in their quest to wipe mankind from the surface of the planet though. One such fierce battle costs Kamina`s life. Simon is crushed by this, but saving http://anidb.net/ch471 [Nia Teppelin], a discarded daughter of the Spiral King, gives Simon hope again...
After destroying the Four Supreme Generals, Simon and his many human followers confront http://anidb.net/ch1561 [Lordgenome], the Spiral King, and defeat him. The parting words of the 1000-year-old Lordgenome, who calls himself the guardian of mankind, have an ominous ring to them though, for he warns the humans about leaving the planet for space where far greater danger awaits. Never-the-less mankind thrives in the following years, rebuilding civilization on the planet`s surface. A time of prosperity. The warning to avoid conquering space has been forgotten...
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1988">8.68</permanent>
<temporary count="2006">8.22</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224529.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10576</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4565</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gurren-lagann-movie.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gurren_Lagann#Anime_films</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>天元突破グレンラガン#.E5.8A.87.E5.A0.B4.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5555</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>333018</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10898</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11155</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1393" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-08">
<name>drill</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3313" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>evolution</name>
<description>Evolution is change in the heritable characteristics of biological populations over successive generations. Evolutionary processes give rise to biodiversity at every level of biological organisation, including the levels of species, individual organisms, and molecules.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64170.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3327" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-08">
<name>manly</name>
<description>Masculinity is possessing qualities or characteristics considered typical of or appropriate to a man.
Typical characteristics associated with masculinity are: courage, a strong physique, competitive, strong willed, and a sense of honor.
Very important for being considered masculine however is the ability to inspire respect from your fellow brethren and/or being perceived as a virile man by the opposite sex.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3874" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>bridge bunnies</name>
<description>A term and English nickname describing the attractive girls who manage the various functions aboard a ship`s/starship`s bridge area. 
Although it originated in reference to characters from Macross, it does not exist among Japanese fans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7086" parentid="2846" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>soft science fiction</name>
<description>Soft science fiction is a type of science fiction in which the science presented is scientifically inaccurate or unimportant to the story, in contrast to http://anidb.net/t4667 [hard science fiction]. Its elements generally present themselves via artistic licence.
This is not to be confused with social science fiction, confusingly also called "soft science fiction", which is science fiction concerned with the "soft sciences" (social sciences), as opposed to the "hard sciences" (natural sciences).</description>
<picurl>222752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="468" type="appears in" update="2016-10-26">
<rating votes="1619">8.82</rating>
<name>Kamina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamina is a young man from Jeeha village who dreams of leaving the village and go to the surface, which he saw as a child. He`s very passionate about his goals, expressing his wishes through energetic speeches, which seem to affect all those who hear them.
As the leader of the "Gurren Brigade", he convinces Simon to aid him in his plan to drill through the roof of the village and get to the world above, but the plan fails and he is imprisoned. After defeating an invading Gunmen, he leaves the village with Simon and Yoko, in the cockpit of a tiny but powerful Gunmen Simon unearths and Kamina names "Lagann".
Kamina is extremely impulsive, and sometimes acts with little regard for his life. His plans are rarely well thought-out, often relying solely on brute strength and determination to win, but for some strange reason or another, they seem to work most of the time. It is revealed that Kamina`s impulsive confidence is mostly a show to give Simon the courage to act. He believes that in reality, all he can do is give Simon the motivation to "reach the heavens"; he couldn`t do it himself.</description>
<picture>14764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="469" type="main character in" update="2016-10-26">
<rating votes="660">7.68</rating>
<name>Simon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Simon is a fourteen year-old digger from Jeeha village. Although he is initially looked down upon because of it, Simon excels at drilling through the ground, and the drill quickly becomes his trademark symbol. One day, he finds a mysterious drill-shaped item, which is later revealed to be the "Core Drill", for a head-shaped Gunmen he also finds buried in the soil. With the help of the small Gunmen, Kamina, and Yoko, he fights off a much larger Gunmen that falls into the village. In the process of defeating the invader, they reach the surface world. Prior to the time-skip, Simon is mostly depicted as merely following Kamina`s lead and often acting as a counter-balance to Kamina`s impulsiveness. An unfortunate accident forces Simon to mature and take up a leadership role within Team Dai-Gurren.</description>
<picture>14766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="470" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-16">
<rating votes="1477">8.55</rating>
<name>Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl from Jeeha`s neighbouring village of Littner, who had been chasing the Gunmen which entered Jeeha village. She wields an extensive arsenal of firearms and has previous experience fighting Gunmen. She uses her marksmanship from afar to assist Kamina and Simon, while they pilot their respective Gunmen.</description>
<picture>14767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="471" type="main character in" update="2008-12-10">
<rating votes="530">6.69</rating>
<name>Nia Teppelin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nia is a mysterious young girl found by Simon sleeping in a capsule in the middle of a dump site. She has had no prior contact with humans except her father. She is very curious, pure and innocent, because of a sheltered childhood in a peaceful environment away from all the battles occurring in the outside world, and because she had only recently gained sentience. During her travels with Team Dai-Gurren, she discovers the harsh realities of the world and has a very close relationship with Simon throughout the story.</description>
<picture>14768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="472" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-29">
<rating votes="224">1.74</rating>
<name>Rossiu Adai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy from another underground village, Adai, in which the people worship the Gunmen as gods. A modest but intelligent person, he`s often seen looking after the young Gimmy and Darry. When the twins are chosen to leave the village, he decides to go with them, thus the trio joins Team Gurren. Before he leaves, the village elder gives him a book that seems to withhold some secrets from humanity`s past, with the task to find someone able to read it, as no one in his village can decipher its content. After Kamina`s death, Rossiu temporarily begins piloting Gurren in his place, though initially has trouble, due to Simon`s breakdown</description>
<picture>14771.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="508" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="184">6.95</rating>
<name>Kittan Bachika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kittan Bachika is the oldest of the Black Siblings. During his first encounter with Team Gurren, he mistakenly confuses Kamina for a Beastman. This is reconciled, when it is discovered that Kamina is piloting the Gunmen, Gurren. Shortly after, the two teams (the Black Siblings and Team Gurren) come into contact with the sixteen-headed enemy Gunmen, whom the Black Siblings had crossed paths with earlier. After the eventual defeat of the enemy Gunmen, the two teams part ways.</description>
<picture>14807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="514" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="102">3.22</rating>
<name>Kinon Bachika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinon is the second oldest of Kittan`s younger sisters. After Team Dai-Gurren`s capture of Dai-Gunzan, she takes up a position within its control tower, monitoring the radar. She seems to be the calmest and smartest member of the Black Siblings.</description>
<picture>14812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1503" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-19">
<rating votes="299">8.29</rating>
<name>Viral</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Viral is a member of the Human Eradication Army, who regards Kamina as a strong rival. Though being among the more humanoid of the Beastmen, his DNA contains aspects of shark and feline genetics. He pilots Enkidudu, which mainly utilizes swords and a powerful laser. He is extremely loyal to Lordgenome and the four supreme generals, and he does his best to serve them. After Kamina`s death, he continues to fight Gurren-Lagann, thinking that Kamina is still alive, and he is shocked once he learns the truth. He is given the gift of immortality by Lordgenome, so that he could spread his legacy. After the fall of the empire, he resurfaces and causes an uproar with his Gunmen, calling Simon out to fight him. He is later taken into custody, and pilots Gurren during the battle against the Anti-Spirals. Viral thus becomes a `reformed villain` of sorts. It is also shown that his deepest desire is to get married and have children, but cannot do so as Beastmen lack the spiral energy necessary for reproduction. In the epilogue, he becomes the captain of the Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren and an emissary for Earth.</description>
<picture>16029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1541" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="93">5.91</rating>
<name>Darry Aday</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darry Aday is a girl from Aday Village, who used to be cared for by Rossiu. She is Gimmy`s twin sister and has a good bond with him. As a young girl, she was shy and quiet and used to cling to a plush doll, which she carried with her at all times. After the timeskip, however, she is much more confident and has left her old personality behind. As a Grapearl pilot, she is careful, calm and perceptive, and puts more thought and planning into her actions than Gimmy.</description>
<picture>16077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1543" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="79">3.78</rating>
<name>Gimmy Aday</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gimmy Aday is a boy from Aday Village, who used to be cared for by Rossiu. When new children were born into the village, the population exceeded its limit of 50, which mandated that two people be removed and sent to the surface. Since Gimmy and Darry had no parents, the village elder chose them to leave the village, however, Rossiu decided to go with them. The pair of twins have a very good bond with each other, and were often left to their own devices around Dai-Gurren, except when they were with older girls, such as Yoko or Nia. After the timeskip, Gimmy and Darry become important Grapearl pilots, often fighting together. Gimmy tends to be more impulsive and reckless, which sometimes puts the duo in trouble.</description>
<picture>16078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1544" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="88">6.20</rating>
<name>Kiyal Bachika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest of the Black Siblings.</description>
<picture>16079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1545" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="74">5.94</rating>
<name>Kiyoh Littner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The oldest of Kittan`s younger sisters.</description>
<picture>16080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1546" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="35">5.25</rating>
<name>Dayakka Littner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dayakka Littner is the former leader of Littner Village, abandoning his post, when most of Littner joined Team Dai-Gurren. His Gunmen is the Dayakkaiser, but after the seizure of Dai-Gunzan, he acted as the captain of Dai-Gurren during battles, while Kiyoh piloted the Dayakkaiser in his stead.</description>
<picture>16081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1561" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="83">7.58</rating>
<name>Lordgenome</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A seemingly cruel and ruthless tyrant who employs legions of creatures known as Beastmen to systemically eradicate all human-kind on the planet surface, commanding his armies from a gigantic funnel-shaped castle called Teppelin.</description>
<picture>16099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="481" picture="127294.jpg">Ikeda Narushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1580" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="212">5.63</rating>
<name>Leeron Littner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leeron Littner, or simply "Ron", is the village mechanic of Littner, who is able to repair and scavenge the various Gunmen he and his group encounter. Quite knowledgeable, and very flamboyant, Leeron was the first one to join Kamina, Simon, and Yoko on their quest to defeat the Beastmen. He has become the main technician for Team Dai-Gurren, as well as being in charge of coordination and communication between the Gunmen during battle from Dai-Gurren. His ability to learn and adapt is incredibly great, seeing as he once mentioned that he didn`t even know how to read before becoming a mechanic.</description>
<picture>16119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1681" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="27">8.10</rating>
<name>Lordgenome Head</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seven years later, Rossiu recovered Lordgenome`s brain and regrows the likeness of Lordgenome`s head from a tissue sample collected from the Spiral King`s corpse. This is done because Lordgenome`s memories could not be accessed directly from a normal computer, so a special "Bio-Computer" had to be built to allow Lordgenome to relay his memories personally to the curious. Once activated, the bemused Bio-Computer explains the existence of the Anti-Spirals to Rossiu, and later serves as a power source for Arc Gurren when the Mugan have overrun Kamina City. The Bio-Computer`s information later proves invaluable, helping to prevent the moon drop and provide the means to reach the Anti-Spiral`s pocket dimension.
However, though programmed without a personality, Lordgenome eventually regains self-awareness and assumes the identity of the man he used to be, joining as navigator of the newly recommissioned Chouginga Gurren just to finally come face to face with the Anti Spiral. Once Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann is formed, Lordgenome uses the Super Spiral Space`s power to temporary recreate his body to serve as one of the thirteen key pilots. He then later detaches Lazengann Overload to block the Grand Zamboa`s Infinity Big Bang Storm and wilfully sacrifices himself to convert the massive attack and himself into a galaxy-sized drill of Spiral Energy that Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann absorbs to ensure Lordgenome`s intent of paving a path for the spiral beings of future generations.</description>
<picture>16222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="481" picture="127294.jpg">Ikeda Narushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1821" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="31">8.03</rating>
<name>Koko-jii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Old Coco is a mysterious, silent old man who leads Team Gurren to the hot springs resort in episode six.
Although he tricks the group into entering the Beastmen`s trap, he helps Kamina later on by letting him onto the Beastmen Gunmen. He then gets caught up with Team Dai-Gurren, and now follows it around, although nobody seems to notice him. He seems to be incredibly hard to notice, to the point of saving Nia in episode eleven, and disappearing again before anyone realises he is gone. The timeskip reveals that he is in fact a Beastmen who was in charge of taking care of Nia, and continued to do so after she was no longer the princess of Teppelin.</description>
<picture>16413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1822" type="main character in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="55">7.20</rating>
<name>Messenger Nia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>For most of the third arc, Nia serves as the messenger from the Anti-Spirals to the humans, during the Earth`s Human Extermination System.
After the Anti-Spiral data awakens within her and converts her into an Anti-Spiral virtual lifeform, becoming an emotionless and serious person, the exact opposite of how Nia was beforehand. As the messenger, she wears a dark skin-tight suit, covered with a green line pattern resembling something like a circuit board, and the previously red irises of her eyes have become black.
After becoming a messenger on the birth of the 1 millionth human, she possesses the power to travel between spatial dimensions, jump between positions instantly and intercept most methods of communication. She appears before Simon several times over the course of the arc, to repeatly tell him that all efforts against the Human Extermination System is futile while increasing the odds against mankind. But it was when she is the only thing keeping the Gurren Lagann from the "moon"`s control system, Simon points out to her that all her actions and appearances before him were in fact the act of her true feelings of her former self, who urges Simon to keep fighting, allowing Nia to have the strength to return to her former self while ending the Human Extermination. However, she is transported back to the Anti-Spiral homeworld so the data on Team Dai Gurren can be extracted from her for analysis, resulting in the rescue attempt that begins the fourth and final arc.</description>
<picture>16414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1823" type="main character in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="69">2.61</rating>
<name>Anti-Spiral</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Anti-Spiral is the ultimate villain of Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann, and the central antagonistic presence for the final two story arcs. He first appears as a disembodied voice in episode twenty four, but is formally introduced in episode twenty six. His physical form is a chaos of arbitrary human concepts fluctuating on a black silhouette, with cartoonish gestures and exaggerated expressions.
Anti-Spiral is both the leader and collective mental manifestation of the "Anti-Spiral Race" after they seal themselves away to purge their race of Spiral energy. The highly advanced technology bequeaths onto him extensive, almost supernatural powers, which manifest in the form of red energy. With these abilities he is able to manipulate physical and chemical laws (going as far as altering probability), which he does regularly both offensively and as a form of intimidation. The Anti-Spiral is the nemesis of Lordgenome, being responsible for Lordgenome`s madness after explaining the nature of Spiral Nemesis to him.
Beyond what is known of the Anti-Spirals, little is known of the Anti-Spiral personally. He has the mannerisms of a scientist, suggesting he had a hand in both the creation of Anti-Spiral technology and the decision to undergo the millennia-long battle against the Milky Way`s spiral beings. The Anti-Spiral is very proud and holds deep contempt for spiral beings, specifically Simon, frustrated him that across all of time, spiral beings still resist limiting their populations and continue to defy the resolution of his race and their ideology.</description>
<picture>16415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="482" picture="17466.jpg">Kamikawa Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1824" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-25">
<rating votes="20">7.16</rating>
<name>Leite Jokin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leite Jokin is the chief engineer of Team Dai-Gurren and Leeron`s direct subordinate. She is a skilled and ingenious mechanic, an ideal work partner for the naturally gifted Leeron. Her central duties revolve around maintaining Dai-Gurren`s spiral engine, which appears less technologically sophisticated in Fortress-class Gunmen thus requiring additional fuel beyond spiral energy. Her personal trademarks are her lab coat and a cigarette she holds in her mouth.
In Part III, Leite`s role in the story is expanded from a virtual background character to an important member of the supporting cast. She is married to Makken, who she affectionately calls "Oto-chan" or "Daddy", and the two have three children. Leite and Makken operate a small business servicing mechanical equipment and automotive vehicles, though on occasion they get contracts to develop weapons from the New Government. She and Makken have great faith in Simon and his capacity as a decision maker; their loyalty to him urges them to resist Rossiu by rebuilding the scrapped Gunmen of Team Dai-Gurren, refitting them with spiral weaponry capable of damaging Mugann. Leite also refits Gurren Lagann`s power pack to allow it to reach escape velocity, but opts out of the Battle of Earth to stay with her children on the surface [5]. When Team Dai-Gurren is reformed, she assumes her old post as engineer of the gang`s flagship, the Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren. She eventually ends up as one of the fourteen pilots of Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann, battling Grand Zamboa to both avenge Makken`s death at the hands of Anti-Spiral Kantai and for the freedom of the entire galaxy.</description>
<picture>29961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1825" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="9">6.21</rating>
<name>Makken Jokin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makken is a fairly silent man who is an important part of Team Dai-Gurren, but has rarely spoken or gotten much screen time whatsoever. He has his own Gunmen, Moshogun, which is based on an ancient samurai.
After the timeskip, Makken is married to Leite with three children. Sadly, he is killed in the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, after sacrificing himself to stop a large Anti-Spiral missile from destroying the Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren.
In the epilogue, a memorial site, in the form of a sword, is seen in his honour right alongside Kamina and the other members of Team Dai-Gurren.</description>
<picture>27556.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1826" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="10">5.57</rating>
<name>Zorthy Kanai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zorthy Kanai appears at the end of episode seven as a new addition to Team Dai-Gurren. His most recognisable quality is his smoking habit, which is unique to every other character in the series. The name of his Gunmen is the Sozoshin.
Zorthy is killed during the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals.</description>
<picture>27550.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1827" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="14">6.08</rating>
<name>Iraak Coega</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iraak Coega is a member of Team Dai-Gurren. He pilots a Gunmen that serves Youko as a mobile rifle platform. Together, they assaulted Dai-Gunzan with the rest of the Team Gurren. The name of his Gunmen is Ainzer.
Iraak is killed during the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, after he and Kid attempted to avenge Zorthy.</description>
<picture>27555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1828" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="11">6.88</rating>
<name>Kid Coega</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kid Coega is another new member of Team Dai-Gurren. His Gunmen utilises two pistols to attack enemies, the Kid Knuckle.
Kid is killed during the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, when he and Iraak attempt to avenge Zorthy`s death.</description>
<picture>27552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1829" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="13">4.42</rating>
<name>Jorgun Bakusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jorgun Bakusa and Balinbow Bakusa are the towering, twin brothers of Team Dai-Gurren, piloting the two-faced Gunmen, Twin Boukun. The two are always hyped and normally speak in manly grunts and monosyllabic phrases. They sport differently coloured sunglasses, which can be used to tell one brother from the other — Jorgun wears red shades, while Balinbow sports blue ones. After the timeskip, the two were appointed Directors of the Public Affairs Department, in which they were responsible for the human population count.
Jorgun and Balinbow are killed in the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, after saving Gimmy and Darry`s lives.</description>
<picture>16421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1830" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="31">1.92</rating>
<name>Balinbow Bakusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jorgun Bakusa and Balinbow Bakusa are the towering, twin brothers of Team Dai-Gurren, piloting the two-faced Gunmen, Twin Boukun. The two are always hyped and normally speak in manly grunts and monosyllabic phrases. They sport differently coloured sunglasses, which can be used to tell one brother from the other — Jorgun wears red shades, while Balinbow sports blue ones. After the timeskip, the two were appointed Directors of the Public Affairs Department, in which they were responsible for the human population count.
Jorgun and Balinbow are killed in the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, after saving Gimmy and Darry`s lives.</description>
<picture>16420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5410" picture="222917.jpg">Douzaka Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1831" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="70">3.44</rating>
<name>Attenborough Cortitch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Attenborough Cortitch is a hyperactive, impulsive, trigger-happy man, who is the gunner of Dai-Gurren`s control team. He tends to fire at enemies or move Dai-Gurren without warning. After the timeskip, he joins Leeron`s science team and still appears to have his hyperactive nature. After Team Dai-Gurren moved to Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren, he assumed the same position he had before at the weapons control. Curiously, this trait became one of Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann`s attacks. He randomly showed up in the series one day, later it was confirmed that he sneaked into some bozo`s luggage, and that is how he joined Team Dai Gurren.</description>
<picture>16423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1832" type="appears in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="9">5.80</rating>
<name>Tetsukan Littner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tetsukan Littner is a member of the control team for Dai-Gurren. He is in charge of monitoring the condition of the ship. After the timeskip, he becomes a part of Leeron`s science team. Also due to being attracted to the fast-food restaurants that were built in the new city he became obese.</description>
<picture>27871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1833" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="14">5.84</rating>
<name>Gabal Docker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gabal Docker is Team Dai-Gurren`s helmsman, in charge of Dai-Gurren`s steering and manoeuvring.</description>
<picture>16422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1834" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="11">5.48</rating>
<name>Cybela Kuto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cybela Kuto is mainly seen at a computer, where she can communicate with Grapearls or do analysis tasks. Later, she joins Team Dai-Gurren, assuming a position at Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren`s bridge.</description>
<picture>16419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1835" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="8">3.97</rating>
<name>Guinble Kaito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guinble Kaito, along with Kinon, seems to be one of the more important members of Rossiu`s intelligence team. He and Kinon often accompany Rossiu, and stayed with him on Earth to watch out for the city while the rest of Team Dai-Gurren headed into space for their final battle against the Anti-Spirals.</description>
<picture>16418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2134" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-03">
<rating votes="154">7.99</rating>
<name>Boota</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The unofficial mascot of Team Dai-Gurren, Boota is a small pig-mole from Giha village, whom Simon keeps as a pet. Boota is characterized by his sunglasses and star pattern surrounding his tail. No matter how many years pass, Boota`s physical appearance does not change much. Although he can`t talk, he can understand humans, and even has near-human intelligence. His favorite spots to stay are between Youko`s breasts or on Simon`s shoulder.</description>
<picture>16989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12879" type="appears in" update="2010-04-10">
<rating votes="13">6.45</rating>
<name>Tsuuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Viral`s wife in the universe created by the Anti-Spiral`s Alternate Space Labyrinth for him.
Since his deepest desire was it to have a family but he was unable to because of his lack of spiral energy, his wish manifisted in this universe almost trapping him and the rest of Dai-Gurren-Dan.</description>
<picture>46106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12880" type="appears in" update="2010-04-10">
<rating votes="4">4.54</rating>
<name>Memu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Viral`s daughter in the universe created by the Anti-Spiral`s Alternate Space Labyrinth for him.
Since his deepest desire was it to have a family but he was unable to because of his lack of spiral energy, his wish manifisted in this universe almost trapping him and the rest of Dai-Gurren-Dan.</description>
<picture>46107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81067" type="appears in" update="2016-03-22">
<rating votes="3">9.30</rating>
<name>Super Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>After Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann had been destroyed by the Granzeboma, Team Dai-Gurren split its power into pieces to form their own separate Tengen Toppa Gunmen, including Tengen Toppa Lagann`s head becoming Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann. The rest of said team was composed of a Tengen Toppa Gunmen for all surviving members, as well as Nia. After a lengthy battle, Lordgenome sacrificed himself to absorb the Anti-Spiral`s Infinity Big Bang Storm and create a mass of Spiral Power, which Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann absorbed and combined into the Super Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann. It only appears in the second movie, and never appeared in the original television series.</description>
<picture>63638.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="97388" update="2009-05-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>130</length>
<airdate>2009-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="200534" update="2018-05-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
