<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6327" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>2009-09-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bakemonogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ghostory</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Монстрассказы</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Истории о Чудовищах</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Monstrų Istorijos</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">บาเกะโมโนกาตาริ</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Истории за Чудовището</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Потвороповідь</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Бакемоноґатарі</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Монстроповідання</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Оповідання про монстрів</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">化物語</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">داستان از ما بهتران</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">باکمونوگاتاری</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">bakemono</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BMG</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">化物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bakemonogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Bakemonogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Истории монстров</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">괴물 이야기</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ปกรณัมของเหล่าภูต</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Canavar Hikayeleri</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">化物语</title>
<title xml:lang="x-kot" type="official">바케모노가타리</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8658" type="Sequel">Nisemonogatari</anime>
<anime id="9453" type="Prequel">Nekomonogatari (Kuro): Tsubasa Family</anime>
<anime id="11827" type="Side Story">Koyomimonogatari</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7238" approval="137" total="277">Arakawa Under the Bridge</anime>
<anime id="6613" approval="110" total="222">Katanagatari</anime>
<anime id="5083" approval="66" total="133">Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei</anime>
<anime id="13900" approval="55" total="77">Seishun Buta Yarou wa Bunny Girl Senpai no Yume o Minai</anime>
<anime id="4032" approval="14" total="29">xxxHOLiC</anime>
<anime id="6014" approval="11" total="42">Ef - a Tale of Melodies.</anime>
<anime id="6773" approval="10" total="40">Dance in the Vampire Bund</anime>
<anime id="3651" approval="8" total="56">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu</anime>
<anime id="5052" approval="8" total="28">Mokke</anime>
<anime id="8852" approval="8" total="21">Tasogare Otome x Amnesia</anime>
<anime id="5909" approval="7" total="70">Toradora!</anime>
<anime id="10360" approval="6" total="15">Mekakucity Actors</anime>
<anime id="1015" approval="5" total="41">Shingetsutan Tsukihime</anime>
<anime id="5113" approval="5" total="28">Mononoke</anime>
<anime id="12116" approval="4" total="7">Kubikiri Cycle: Aoiro Savant to Zaregotozukai</anime>
<anime id="270" approval="3" total="13">The SoulTaker</anime>
<anime id="1551" approval="2" total="20">Boukyaku no Senritsu</anime>
<anime id="8742" approval="2" total="17">Kokoro Connect</anime>
<anime id="10439" approval="2" total="13">Terra Formars</anime>
<anime id="9749" approval="2" total="12">Grisaia no Kajitsu</anime>
<anime id="7568" approval="1" total="7">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai</anime>
<anime id="8889" approval="1" total="2">Sasami-san@Ganbaranai</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="101">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="40085">Good but "slightly" overrated here in the recommendations. Dialog (which is non-stop throughout the eps) is ok. Characters are enjoyable. Stories are interesting enough. It has substance and the comedy is good. You`ll either love or hate the art-film like visual style of this show though. I`m not a fan of it at all. If you are or you can get used to it then it`s worth a watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="140370">Amazing graphics and animation with and unpredicted sequence of events that can leave anyone surprised. However because of its long talks and abstract animation some may not enjoy it. 

In the end you will either love it or hate it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="88664">This was fantastic watch and left me aching for more. Onto the sequels now!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="326975">Good anime. If you want an anime that builds mostly on the character conversations, and have a decent story too, this is the show for you. And those who say this show has a lot of fanservice, they obviously hasn`t seen a show that really has lot of fanservice.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372950">It`s one of a kind, not really. The art of this Anime lies within. If you really watch it, you will know it. But be warned, if you are just a dragon ball-otaku, get the **** out :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="414436">If you are intelligent enough to think about the dialog and understand it is a must see indefinitely.
One of my personal favorites.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="293766">Bakemonogatari is a very unique anime. The story is original, it`s filled with specific cultural beliefs, and the art style made a whole new genre in it`s own! Descent amount of drama and suspense. Nice sense of fluency of the story, (even though it`s a little repetitive, it never gets old), and just a really interesting story. It`s something new, and not in a bad way.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="103240">i was blown away by this anime instantly. i can not comprehend how can someone create such a wonderful piece of art. but take it with a grain of salt its my love for this anime talking though i cant imagine that some one would hate this one for any reason.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="475892">excellent story, doesn`t have lots of action, but development is superb. build-up of characters is wonderfully thought-off. most characters` back stories are actually excluded from this anime, but can be found in the other installments (nisemonogatari, kizumonogatari) and the "series" will become much better if you watch them all, not only limiting oneself to bakemonogatari. strongly recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="539481">10 stars to the background music!
Fun and action with special animation. I think that they had empty pockets and used the money they had for animation in a fantastic way.

Since it is a novel they made the right choice of stuffing some of the story in frames(thus not cutting story out and leaving viewers confused). The frames are almost too short to read by catching them with pausing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="465944">absolutely fantastic.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="632413">Recommended for You who like an anime with an tsundere chara, vampire, loli, and ghost with a mystery disclosure.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="332605">Great art and stories (5 arcs). Mostly good animation. Sweetest OP in a while (EP 10).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="155853">Bakemonogatari was a nice surprise. Entertaining coming of age/romance anime masked as a ghost-detective story, with nice humor, well written dialog, interesting characters and a surreal touch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="380021">Best ever seen in this gategory!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="292889">Great visuals , great story , great female lead. definitly a "Must see".</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="332060">My most favorite anime ever.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="181980">nice art + story</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="253278">holy sh•t.  Yeah great art, animation, directing and story.  Highly recommend.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="313818">one of the BEST animes ever made, and if some ppl don`t recognize it`s greatness they should quit watching animes, Super ultra interesting plot, characters are so freaking GREAT, outstanding conversations (which makes most of the anime this interesting) it has one of the most vivid plots and dialogs i`ve ever seen. It has to be in "TO WATCH" list in every mind. just GREAT!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="321267">Wonderful script</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="317829">Great animation and a decently fresh plot. Possibly one of the best animes of this summer, you won`t want to miss Bakemonogatari.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="578181">An excellent series for anyone who`s a fast reader and can deal with SHAFT`s style. Don`t pause to read the title cards, it messes with the atmosphere of the show.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="375769">Its a must see in all ways</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="157861">Beautiful animation!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="342505">it`s a great anime i tottaly love it.  and about the  abuse  coments... GUYS everyone has a taste on his own...  if u had time to watch animes then u had no better work to do... so please stop complaining! P.S. sorry for my broken english.. :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="333203">one of my alltime favorites</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="378687">Very enjoyable story and animation style.  Worth watching more than once.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="377192">Very interesting anime!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="5315">One of the most original, interesting, and exciting anime ever created. It`s like the combination of FLCL and His/Her Circumstances. Very amazing masterpiece!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="233579">Real masterpiece. Great characters, interesting dialogs, great art.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="410813">Interesting characters, great music, great story, great animation.
Must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="365975">I fell love with Senjougahara at first sight and with anime on second.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="417732">Show is great. It takes you in with first moments and you are kept entertained up until the end.

Must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="201805">just amazing artistic to the minimal detail</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="134578">Simple, yet entertaining.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="217023">I loved this anime to death.
so awesome.
must see.
Characters are great, I love the interaction between main characters, and how at the end, there`s no question of how the main characters relate to each other, or how they feel.
that being said, I`m sad that there prob won`t be a sequel.
Excellent use of non standard animation.
I can`t say enough good things about this anime...
and episode #12 = My favorite all time episode of any anime, ever.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="106859">Great show. I personally love it, but it`s definitely the type of thing one will either love or hate.  If you  don`t mind shows with lot captions and text like His and Her Circumstances or the last part of EVA; and if you like show where the focus is on the conversations that the characters have rather than on action then you should definitely check this one out.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="204142">Awesome story.  A unique visual style, spectacularly drawn.  Hilarious comedy, and great characters.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="242116">Definitely a good one. One little thing that bugs me is the intro though since you cant read so much text without pause :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="463604">GREAT!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="448871">Interesting from start to the end. Characters are absolutely the best thing in this. They build as the anime goes on. There wasn`t too much dialog, in my opinion. And this series have so cute girls that it`s allmost illegal</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="229165">awesome animation. great caracters, and funny moments. not apt for chirdren. mesmerizing for me 10/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="522273">Amazing series. Dialogue driven but fast paced. The jokes are good. Most of all the story is awesome. Really liked metaphors and character development. The supernatural component was also nicely included. A must watch series for all.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="550129">Excellent animation, nice plot and characters. Your eyes will be pleased for sure.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="115911">Probably one of the best anime, or any type of show I have ever seen, the story is well made, long story short, its simply awesome. I`ve enjoyed watching, it is a MUST SEE definitely. Story was great Can`t get enough of it. :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="297053">A must see anime, very good style and story</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="614621">This series shows that animation is one of the fine arts...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="387237">The almost pretentious artsy style can kind of get in the way sometimes, but that doesn`t change the fact that this is still a must-see anime.

Very unique plot... it will have you question your own life, reality and existence.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="612872">Simply LOVED IT NO WORDS go for it it was a theme which i was looking for days</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="325333">Bakemonogatari is simply a masterpiece in each way! No true anime fan should miss it!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.bakemonogatari.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="530" type="Music">Kousaki Satoru</name>
<name id="59" type="Series Composition">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="59" type="Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="6433" type="Direction">Oishi Tatsuya</name>
<name id="3529" type="Character Design">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="3529" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="5970" type="Original Work">Nishio Ishin</name>
<name id="26229" type="Series Composition">Tou Fuyashi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a series of light novels written by http://anidb.net/cr5970 [Nishio Ishin] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr6436 [Vofan].
http://anidb.net/ch8962 [Araragi Koyomi] is a third year high school student who is almost human again after having briefly become a vampire. One day, a classmate named http://anidb.net/ch8963 [Senjougahara Hitagi], who infamously never talks to anyone, falls down the stairs into Koyomi`s arms. He discovers that Hitagi weighs next to nothing, in defiance of physics and common sense alike. Despite being threatened by her, Koyomi offers her help, and introduces her to http://anidb.net/ch8967 [Oshino Meme], a middle-aged homeless man who helped him stop being a vampire.
Note: Episodes 13-15 (Tsubasa Cat parts 3-5) were not part of the initial TV broadcast and premiered on the anime`s official website.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9975">8.47</permanent>
<temporary count="10110">8.35</temporary>
<review count="6">8.74</review>
</ratings>
<picture>79083.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10196</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5081</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6948</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4435</identifier>
<identifier>tjmgsl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bakemonogatari.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>化物語</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1685</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334106</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11458</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B06XP34Y5F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2760" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>basketball</name>
<description>Basketball is Netball for men, the real game that encourages dribbling and other such uncouth behaviour that was sanitised out of the ladies` version. However, it is itself woozy compared to Ulama, as the losing side are seldom publicly sacrificed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2964" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>OP variety</name>
<description>Several OP sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique OP for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3196" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-19">
<name>photographic backgrounds</name>
<description>Real-life backgrounds, with the possible addition of a few 2D elements are shown / used in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3696" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-28">
<name>off-model animation</name>
<description>Anime shows tend to most often run on an already tight budget; some have even tighter ones. Thus, over the years it became a norm to invest more time and money into the first and last episode, leaving many episodes in the middle to stand severe budget restrictions. This sometimes results in episodes which particularly stand out due to the drop in artwork or animation quality; bar some basic framework, they often have little in common with the rest of the series.
One clue to upcoming off-model animation is the noticeable addition of many Korean names in the production credits, as farming out more animation to Korean artists is a nearly universal indicator of a production company trying to save money in all possible ways.
This effect is often called yashigani, after the infamous http://anidb.net/e4682 [fourth episode] of http://anidb.net/a403 [Lost Universe], Yashigani Hoburu. Another prominent term describing the same effect is "QUALITY animation", with capital letters meant to show contrast to actual quality. http://anidb.net/a4531 [Yoake Mae yori Ruriiro na: Crescent Love] is another legendarily terrible offender: the TV airing of its http://anidb.net/e63752 [third episode] had a perfectly spherical ball in place of what should be a cabbage; the "cabbage" was so egregious that it became closely associated with the anime itself, to a point the show would henceforth be nicknamed "Cabbage Love" among Western viewers.
One should not confuse the yashigani effect with art shifts that stem from guest staff, changes in main staff, intentional art shifts, and similar effects. Another effect one shouldn`t confuse this one with is the so-called DVD/BD enhancement, which is when a studio scrambles to meet the deadline for a TV airing and airs a half-finished episode but eventually fixes it for a disk release; for example, http://anidb.net/cr792 [Shaft] is particularly infamous for its disk enhancements, to a point it has become known as "Shafting", and they prominently feature intentionally weird character models, but they don`t often leave bad artwork on the disk release. Additionally, it should also not be confused with intentional lack of detail on background plane characters; this effect is instead when even the foreground has art quality shifting over time due to the aforementioned budget restrictions.</description>
<picurl>29532.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3915" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>child abuse</name>
<description>Story depicts child abuse, which is a very complex and dangerous set of problems that include child neglect and the physical, emotional, and sexual abuse of children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4606" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>slide show animation</name>
<description>The entire anime or parts of it show sequences of still images. Sometimes used in low budged animations for action scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5769" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>panels that require pausing</name>
<description>Panels that require pausing are image or text panels that interrupt regular animation and flash by so quickly that the viewer cannot recognize the image or read the text fast enough while playing at regular speed; they require pausing the video, or at least viewing it at a lower speed. Given the short screen time these panels are given, they are usually not relevant to the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5781" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-01">
<name>exorcism</name>
<description>Eviction of demons or other spiritual entities from a person or place which they are believed to have possessed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7222" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-30">
<name>groping</name>
<description>Groping is the act of subjecting another person to unwanted sexual touching.</description>
<picurl>68310.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7238" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>attempted rape</name>
<description>Attempted rape is an unsuccessful attempt at http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape]. For AniDB purposes, generally an "unsuccessful" attempt is where both fellatio and penetration did not occur. Discretion should be applied on a case-by-case basis.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8962" type="main character in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="1150">7.98</rating>
<name>Araragi Koyomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Araragi Koyomi, the main character of the story, is a third year high school student who is close to failing every class except maths.
Shortly before the story begins, he was attacked by vampire during spring break, and became a vampire himself. Although http://anidb.net/ch8967 [Oshino Meme] helped him become human again, there are a few lingering side effects; he can see in the dark, and he heals faster than the average human. He is still scared of morning sunlight even though it no longer has any effect on him.</description>
<picture>28404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8963" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1976">8.57</rating>
<name>Senjougahara Hitagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hitagi, the main character of Hitagi Crab, is a weak-looking girl with an "incurable disease". She is in the same class as http://anidb.net/ch8962 [Koyomi], but he has almost never heard her speak.
When she was in the first year of high school, she encountered a mysterious crab, after which she became weightless. Ever since, she has avoided contact with everyone else, threatening everyone who discovers her secret. She called herself a tsundere and always speaks in an abusive style.</description>
<picture>31036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8964" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-27">
<rating votes="480">7.88</rating>
<name>Hachikuji Mayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayoi, is a fifth-grade elementary school girl. She always carry a big backpack, wears a hairband and ponytails.</description>
<picture>28405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8965" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-08">
<rating votes="799">6.94</rating>
<name>Hanekawa Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsubasa, is http://anidb.net/ch8962 [Koyomi]`s classmate and the class president. Koyomi describes her as "the class president of all class presidents".</description>
<picture>27221.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8966" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="571">7.13</rating>
<name>Kanbaru Suruga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suruga is http://anidb.net/ch8962 [Koyomi]`s underclassman, ace of the school`s basketball team and one of http://anidb.net/ch8963 [Hitagi]`s acquaintances from back in junior high school.
Immediately after she entered senior high school, she became aware of Hitagi`s secret and was threatened by her, just like Koyomi was.</description>
<picture>17576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8967" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-08">
<rating votes="202">8.15</rating>
<name>Oshino Meme</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meme is a middle-aged man who lives in an abandoned building. Being an expert in the apparitions field, he solves http://anidb.net/ch8962 [Koyomi]`s and others` problems, albeit with compensation.</description>
<picture>129235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8968" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-22">
<rating votes="473">7.07</rating>
<name>Sengoku Nadeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nadeko is http://anidb.net/ch8962 [Koyomi]`s sister`s friend back in elementary school. She always wears a waist pouch; always cast her eyes downward, have her bangs covering her eyes, not talk much and can be easily amused.</description>
<picture>28407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10291" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="1069">8.75</rating>
<name>Oshino Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who lives with Meme in the abolished building. She appears to be an eight year old girl, but she was originally a beautiful vampire who had lived for more than 500 years. After the events at the end of Koyomi Vamp, she was left in a weakened condition with no powers or traces of her original personality and therefore have to abandon her "Kiss-shot Acerola-orion Heart-under-blade" name. She was named Shinobu by Meme at the beginning of Hitagi Crab, suggesting her kanji name Shinobu (忍), having "heart" (心) under "blade" (刃), matches with her original personality.</description>
<picture>46747.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10342" type="appears in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="458">6.98</rating>
<name>Araragi Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karen, the main character of Karen Bee, is one of Koyomi`s sisters. She`s older than Tsukihi and always doing outdoor activities.</description>
<picture>61484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10343" type="appears in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="330">6.51</rating>
<name>Araragi Tsukihi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukihi, the main character of Tsukihi Phoenix, is one of Koyomi`s sisters. She`s the youngest of Araragi family. Unlike her sister, Karen, she is always doing indoor activities.</description>
<picture>61485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11423" type="appears in" update="2009-08-30">
<rating votes="21">2.67</rating>
<name>Kanbaru Suruga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34089.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11876" type="appears in" update="2010-06-30">
<rating votes="253">7.79</rating>
<name>Black Hanekawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanekawa Tsubasa turns into Black Hanekawa whenever she falls into stress. She is the embodiment of all of Hanekawa`s frustrations in life and is dangerous and violent.</description>
<picture>36430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11973" type="appears in" update="2009-09-26">
<rating votes="13">3.45</rating>
<name>Senjougahara Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20157" type="appears in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="320">9.10</rating>
<name>Kiss-shot Acerola-orion Heart-under-blade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52246.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58165" type="appears in" update="2019-08-25">
<rating votes="21">2.57</rating>
<name>Episode</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140476.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="104682" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Promo 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104683" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="3">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Promo 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104713" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="52">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひたぎクラブ 其ノ壹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hitagi Crab, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Caranguejo Hitagi - Primeira Parte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitagi Crab Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>On the day after the Golden Week holiday, third year high school student Koyomi Araragi finds himself saving a classmate, Hitagi Senjyogahara, by catching her when she slips on the stairs and comes tumbling down from above. He discovers that she`s impossibly light, as if she has no physical weight whatsoever….
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610921</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104913" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="47">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひたぎクラブ 其ノ貳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hitagi Crab, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitagi Crab Sono Ni</title>
<summary>On the day after the Golden Week holiday, third year high school student Koyomi Araragi finds himself saving a classmate, Hitagi Senjyogahara, by catching her when she slips on the stairs and comes tumbling down from above. He discovers that she`s impossibly light, as if she has no physical weight whatsoever….
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610923</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="105076" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="45">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まよいマイマイ 其ノ壹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mayoi Snail, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoi Maimai Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>Koyomi meets Mayoi Hachikuji, an elementary school girl who is frantically comparing the town map displayed in the park to the memo in her hand. Learning that Mayoi has lost her way en route to a relative`s home, Koyomi offers to help, only to be violently rebuffed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610925</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="105127" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="39">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まよいマイマイ 其ノ貳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mayoi Snail, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoi Maimai Sono Ni</title>
<summary>Koyomi meets Mayoi Hachikuji, an elementary school girl who is frantically comparing the town map displayed in the park to the memo in her hand. Learning that Mayoi has lost her way en route to a relative`s home, Koyomi offers to help, only to be violently rebuffed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610927</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="105499" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="44">8.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まよいマイマイ 其ノ參</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mayoi Snail, Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoi Maimai Sono San</title>
<summary>Koyomi meets Mayoi Hachikuji, an elementary school girl who is frantically comparing the town map displayed in the park to the memo in her hand. Learning that Mayoi has lost her way en route to a relative`s home, Koyomi offers to help, only to be violently rebuffed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610929</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="105713" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="35">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">するがモンキー 其ノ貳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suruga Monkey, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suruga Monkey Sono Ni</title>
<summary>Suruga Kanbaru, the school’s biggest star who has led the underwhelming girls’ basketball team to the national championships, begins to inexplicably stalk her upperclassman, Koyomi Araragi. When Hitagi Senjyogahara hears about this, she reveals that back in middle school, she was once so close to Suruga that they were known as the "Valhalla Combo."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610933</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="105714" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="38">7.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">するがモンキー 其ノ壹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suruga Monkey, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suruga Monkey Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>Suruga Kanbaru, the school’s biggest star who has led the underwhelming girls’ basketball team to the national championships, begins to inexplicably stalk her upperclassman, Koyomi Araragi. When Hitagi Senjyogahara hears about this, she reveals that back in middle school, she was once so close to Suruga that they were known as the "Valhalla Combo."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610931</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106165" recap="true" update="2015-07-28">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">化物語SP</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 05.5 - Special Recap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakemonogatari SP</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106297" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="37">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なでこスネイク 其ノ貳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nadeko Snake, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nadeko Snake Sono Ni</title>
<summary>Meme Oshino has given Koyomi Araragi the task of heading to an abandoned temple on top of a mountain on the outskirts of town, and placing a talisman on the main shrine. Koyomi invites Suruga Kanbaru to accompany him, and the two are on their way up the deserted mountain path towards the shrine, when they pass a young girl running down, her hat pulled low over her head.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610939</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106298" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="36">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なでこスネイク 其ノ壹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nadeko Snake, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nadeko Snake Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>Meme Oshino has given Koyomi Araragi the task of heading to an abandoned temple on top of a mountain on the outskirts of town, and placing a talisman on the main shrine. Koyomi invites Suruga Kanbaru to accompany him, and the two are on their way up the deserted mountain path towards the shrine, when they pass a young girl running down, her hat pulled low over her head.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610937</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106299" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="36">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">するがモンキー 其ノ參</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suruga Monkey, Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suruga Monkey Sono San</title>
<summary>Suruga Kanbaru, the school’s biggest star who has led the underwhelming girls’ basketball team to the national championships, begins to inexplicably stalk her upperclassman, Koyomi Araragi. When Hitagi Senjyogahara hears about this, she reveals that back in middle school, she was once so close to Suruga that they were known as the "Valhalla Combo."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610935</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106381" update="2009-08-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106382" update="2014-05-26">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108140" update="2009-08-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108141" update="2009-08-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108430" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="34">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つばさキャット 其ノ壹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsubasa Cat, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubasa Cat Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>June 13th. The students are busy after class, getting ready for the last School Festival of their high school days, which will be held during the upcoming weekend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610941</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="108431" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="68">9.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つばさキャット 其ノ貮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsubasa Cat, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubasa Cat Sono Ni</title>
<summary>June 14th. The students are busy after class, getting ready for the last School Festival of their high school days, which will be held during the upcoming weekend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610943</identifier>
<identifier>bakemonogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="108496" update="2017-08-30">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109104" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="30">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つばさキャット 其ノ參</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsubasa Cat, Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubasa Cat Sono San</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109108" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112088" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112089" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112090" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112091" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112092" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112780" update="2014-05-26">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112781" update="2014-05-26">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112782" update="2015-07-28">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112783" update="2014-05-26">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112785" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112786" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112787" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116319" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116560" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="29">7.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つばさキャット 其ノ肆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsubasa Cat, Part 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubasa Cat Sono Yon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117236" update="2017-08-30">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 5a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117333" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117334" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117335" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117336" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118941" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="32">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つばさキャット 其ノ伍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsubasa Cat, Part 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubasa Cat Sono Go</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120106" update="2010-11-15">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 TL notes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120107" update="2010-11-15">
<epno type="6">O3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2 TL notes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120519" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120520" update="2015-07-28">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 5b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121170" update="2010-11-15">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Intro Ep 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122218" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo Episode 15 B</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122219" update="2011-08-14">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo Episode 15 A</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125136" update="2018-09-12">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
