<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="634" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>27</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>2003-10-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Air Master</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">AirMaster</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Въздушен майстор</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Airmaster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">AM</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">エアマスター</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Air Master</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Air Master</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="618" approval="6" total="13">Ikkitousen</anime>
<anime id="3352" approval="2" total="2">Natsuki Crisis</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="291289">Well Directed Action;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="98714">one off the best fighting anime ever</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="388003">The first time I actually liked the leading character who was a woman!! Characters are all epic, and the action this show had was awesome.

Please be a good sport and pick this anime, and WATCH IT!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="336446">Maki rulez XD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="348518">I have enjoyed this better then Grappler Baki</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="408084">This remotivated my martial arts training. Definate Must See for the martial arts + anime fans!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.vap.co.jp/airmaster/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1147" type="Original Work">Shibata Yokusaru</name>
<name id="1834" type="Animation Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="2208" type="Character Design">Umakoshi Yoshihiko</name>
<name id="4539" type="Direction">Nishio Daisuke</name>
<name id="3465" type="Series Composition">Yokote Michiko</name>
<name id="2208" type="Chief Animation Direction">Umakoshi Yoshihiko</name>
<name id="4393" type="Music">Hirano Yoshihisa</name>
</creators>
<description>Aikawa Maki, 16 years old, is a first year senior high school student known as the Air Master. An invicible street fighter. Most of the time, she is just like a normal girl but she`s a different person when she`s out in the streets.
Once a gymnast of Japan, Maki is now establishing and reviving the legend of "airborne street fighting" as an Air Master. A fighting style based on one`s jumping strength and movement while airborne. So she can once again feel the excitement of being a gymnast, she seeks the strongest opponents to battle.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1805">4.89</permanent>
<temporary count="1848">6.96</temporary>
<review count="8">6.24</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10893.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>82</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>230</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1198</identifier>
<identifier>ipbrof</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.vap.co.jp/airmaster/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Air_Master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>エアマスター</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>241165</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2384" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-22">
<name>prodigy</name>
<description>Character is very good at everything he/she does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2487" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>charismatic</name>
<description>Charisma is a compelling attractiveness or charm that can inspire devotion in others.&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5285" parentid="3411" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>street fighting</name>
<picurl>211275.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13779" type="main character in" update="2009-12-25">
<rating votes="20">8.69</rating>
<name>Aikawa Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Formerly a gymnast who trained under her now-deceased mother, Maki uses her acrobatic skills in her fighting style to increase her freedom of movement. Maki has the ability to replicate nearly any move she gets hit with or sees. Since her relationship with her father is conflicted, she lives alone. Maki seems to enjoy street fighting for the `rush` rather than any sense of revenge or honor. When not fighting, Maki tends to stick out in a crowd due to her unusual height (6 feet, which is very tall for a teen Japanese girl) and appearance, preferring to follow her quartet of friends quietly. Her younger sister comments that Maki is somewhat simple minded. Maki is reluctant to deal with several people obsessed with her. She becomes vulnerable to attack, for a moment, when she gets approached in any romantic way, especially with Julietta Sakamoto. Her signature moves are the "Air Spin Driver" and the " Air Cutter"; she is later shown to master the art of Air Flow.
[source: wiki]</description>
<picture>40589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15330" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="7">4.47</rating>
<name>Kawamoto Michiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Michiru is a friend of Maki. She also has a crush on Shinnosuke, but becomes upset when he admits his love for Maki. She is a fan of the model Nono Rakuko. Yuu and Michiru make a great duo and are seldom seen apart.</description>
<picture>43735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15331" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="8">4.75</rating>
<name>Takigawa Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuu is a friend of Maki and shares some of the same interest as Renge. She is a fan of the singer Uzumi Mika. She is taking karate lessons and also has a crush on Shinnosuke, and sometimes she fights with Michiru about Shinnosuke.</description>
<picture>43736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3128" picture="24744.jpg">Suzuki Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15332" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-06">
<rating votes="9">4.57</rating>
<name>Nakanotani Mina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Maki`s shyer friends, who goes to a presumably rich, private school. Mina has ridiculously exaggerated, large breasts, normally used as a source of humor rather than fan service, and she is extremely self conscious about it. In addition to this, Mina is hopelessly in love with Maki, who is not sure how to handle the matter, making this the main reason her friends make fun of her. However, like Maki, she has her share of admirers as well; including Reiishi Mishima and many members of Kinjirou`s Black Suit gang. She has been a fan of Nanjou Remon`s novels since she was a kid.</description>
<picture>43737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15333" type="appears in" update="2010-02-27">
<rating votes="4">3.84</rating>
<name>Tokita Shinnosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A guy who challenges Maki early on, but later temporarily joins the group. He seems to have a crush on Maki. He fights with a long staff that can separate into three parts connected with a chain. He seems to know the art of the Drunken Fist.</description>
<picture>43738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15334" type="appears in" update="2011-08-31">
<rating votes="4">4.67</rating>
<name>Fukamichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The man who runs the street fighting tournament, and who gave his name to the ranking system (Fukamichi Rankings). He decides who is qualified to be in the Tournament rankings. He watches the fights and have videos of them streamed to his laptop, which he then broadcasts all over the world on the internet. He does not participate in the fights but, he`s been shown to be extremely strong and fast. He has a younger brother, Nobuhiko Fukamichi, who participates in the competition. He has a hobby of critiquing restaurants and posting the results on the internet.</description>
<picture>50773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15335" type="appears in" update="2010-02-27">
<name>Emiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2128" picture="216210.jpg">Kiuchi Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15336" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="13">1.55</rating>
<name>Inui Renge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The group`s extremely short friend. Renge has a penchant for eating obsessively, yet she is always thin (Although, sometimes, when she eats a lot, she is shown to have a belly). Renge is the stereotypical, overexcited kid, with a tendency to whine, but she mostly serves as a cheering squad. She later acquires a kitten that she carries with her most of the time. Much to her friends surprise, she has two younger sisters named Men-Men and Mikan, who both look identical to Renge. She is good friends with Tsukio, and usually gives him money for breakfast. Her features resemble that of `Astro Girl`.</description>
<picture>43739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15337" type="appears in" update="2010-02-27">
<rating votes="4">4.66</rating>
<name>Kitaeda Kinjirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinjirou Kitaeda is one of the rivals of Maki Aikawa, he`s the leader of a gang called "The man in black justice league".
Kinjirou can look badass, but he`s homossexual, he`s boyfriend is a big guy called Nagato, that always punching the girls who get close to "Kin".</description>
<picture>43740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15338" type="appears in" update="2010-02-27">
<rating votes="7">9.12</rating>
<name>Sakamoto Julietta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A scruffy but handsome ghost writer who becomes obsessed with Maki (romantically), while the latter is totally uninterested in him and finds his behavior very creepy. He is a smooth talker but prone to overly aggressive declarations of love, sometimes bordering on assault, towards Maki, who he calls "My Jenny". He tends to always kiss her and declare his love for her when they`re together, even during their fights, throwing her off balance. This is usually done for comedic effect. He has three women who are head over heels for him: Uzumi Mika (a famous singer), Nono Rakuko (a famous model), and Nanjou Remon (a famous novelist). He ignores them all since he`s fixed on marrying Maki and making her move in with him. Maki is physically capable of beating him down in his insane-like "distracted" state of mind (Julietta rarely gets serious with anyone—he`s got "Maki" on his mind,if ya know what I mean); however, she did have a hard time with him at first. If Julietta, who defeated the 3rd ranked Yoshitoku Konishi (without going serious), were to get serious with Maki, who lost to the 4th ranked Fukamichi fighter... it is in no way clear who the "winner" would be. He can take a huge beating and still be able to fight. In a fight with another opponent he once had both his legs and one of his arms broken but he was still able to fight. Sakamoto usually only fights with extremely fast and devastating kicks. He usually leaves his hands in his pockets while fighting even though he has a powerful punch. It`s said his strength is legendary on the street. He becomes rank seven in the Fukamichi Rankings after defeating Nobuhiko Fukamichi in a single kick, though Julietta`s rank does not do justice to his fighting ability, as he defeats Yoshitoku Konishi, the third place holder, without going serious.</description>
<picture>43741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15339" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-27">
<rating votes="11">7.91</rating>
<name>Sakiyama Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A wanna-be future model (later a female wrestler) with an obsessive one-sided rivalry with Maki. She later becomes a moderately good fighter, and accomplishes things by sheer force of will and determination. She is loud and over dramatic, and during extended fights is essentially a Berserker powered by her own rage, and she will not admit defeat unless violently knocked out. A running gag in the show is how most characters refer to her by her full name in a dramatic fashion, probably due to her tendency to do the same. When enraged, her appearance has been compared to the Devilman. Due to a childhood "accident", she`s deaf in her right ear.</description>
<picture>43742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="542" picture="60897.jpg">Doi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15340" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="2">5.42</rating>
<name>Saeki Shiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maki`s estranged father. Maki was born when he was fifteen, which would make him around thirty-one years old. He`s a four-time pro-fighting champion. He runs a dojo and raises Maki`s half-sister, Miori. He gets beaten by Sakamoto, but they become friends later on.</description>
<picture>3944.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15341" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="5">3.82</rating>
<name>Saeki Miori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maki`s somewhat bratty younger half-sister. Her martial-artist father is the same as Maki`s, so she shares some of her older sister`s fighting ability, but none of her gravity-defying gymnastic skill, which Maki evidently got from her mother. In her first appearance, she suddenly attacks Maki. She is about the same height as Renge, though she is younger. She decides to move in with Maki. She later idolizes Sanpaguita Kai.</description>
<picture>3945.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="13940" picture="171402.jpg">Hirotsu Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15342" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="3">3.15</rating>
<name>Sampaguita Kai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Though she is not initially involved in the street-fighting tournament Maki joins, Sampaguita Kai was one of her most difficult opponents. Using a similar fighting style to Maki, Kai faces her in a tag-team match during a women`s wrestling tournament. She becomes obsessed, like a number of Maki`s earlier opponents, with beating Maki. She`s the younger sister of Lucha Master, who taught her how to fight ever since she was young. Kai gained the ninth rank within the Fukamichi Rankings after beating Shun Yashiki, however she is narrowly defeated by Kinjiro Kitaeda, which leaves her ranked ten. Kai`s signature move is the "Izukaya Bomber", which involves a clothesline takedown; she learns this move from her former mentor/wrestling partner Hayase Mio.</description>
<picture>154206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2901" picture="23286.jpg">Ishizuka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15343" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="4">5.33</rating>
<name>Lucha Master</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lucha Master is, as the name implies, a masterful wrestler, styled after Mexican Luchadores. He always wears a mask, and he is the first major challenge Maki faces. He is one of only three characters who can use a similar sort of aerial combat to Maki. He is the older brother of Sanpaguita Kai, another character with a similar fighting style. Lucha Master is ranked twenty-first within the Fukamichi Rankings.</description>
<picture>3941.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15344" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="4">2.83</rating>
<name>Taketsugu Tsukio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another early opponent. He has a furious punch( similar to a jackhammer), but is not as fast as some of the other street fighters. Maki often overlooks him, especially since, after his first appearance, Lucha Master quickly showed up, and this makes him furious. Tsukio is ranked twenty-second within the Fukamichi rankings...</description>
<picture>3942.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3400" picture="24480.jpg">Uemura Kihachirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15345" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="2">6.78</rating>
<name>Mishima Reiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sort of hanger-on to Tsukio Taketsugu, Reiichi is both a coward and a klutz. Though he could only fight well with a bike, using it like it`s part of his own body, he`s still only a moderately skilled street fighter.</description>
<picture>3943.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15346" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="2">3.80</rating>
<name>Yashiki Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukio`s younger cousin. Originally 9th place in the Fukamichi Tournament but, after losing his rank to Kai, he decided to beat the 8th place holder. He`s a ki manipulator. He has a technique where he uses his ki to create an osmotic punch, which strongly pressures the insides of an opponent`s body resulting in a loss of a massive amount of liquid within their body, rendering them incapacitated. Since he uses his ki for this technique, he can only use it a certain amount of times until he rests to build up his ki again. He teaches this technique to Kaori Sakiyama.</description>
<picture>154207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15347" type="appears in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="4">5.56</rating>
<name>Minaguchi Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is ranked number four, and the only one to defeat Maki. Her full fighting style emphasizes on counter attacks as well as cutting and stabbing techniques with her hands. She starts her fight as a calm and collected individual. Though Maki sees through her and knows that she likes to fight.</description>
<picture>81269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15348" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<name>Konishi Yoshitoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The 3rd place holder in the Fukamichi Rankings. Konishi believes he has attained perfection and specializes in grappling and submission techniques. He is shown to easily beat Shiro Saeki who is also proficient in submission techniques, and fight on par with and eventually "defeat" Sakamoto Julietta (who, sadly, rejects the notion of practice, training, or "going serious").</description>
<picture>154205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66853" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<name>Ogata Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66854" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<name>Kawahara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66855" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">2.83</rating>
<name>Cary</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66856" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">1.91</rating>
<name>Komada Shigeo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66857" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">3.80</rating>
<name>Sawamura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66858" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">3.84</rating>
<name>Yuukorin-oneesan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="120" picture="192488.jpg">Ogura Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66859" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<name>Sayama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66860" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="1">3.49</rating>
<name>Gouda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66861" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="1">3.49</rating>
<name>Byoubou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="292" picture="68967.jpg">Nishi Rintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66862" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">2.10</rating>
<name>Baba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66863" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">2.86</rating>
<name>Akiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66864" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">4.22</rating>
<name>Seriguchi Tomiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1917" picture="151688.jpg">Natsuki Rio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66865" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">3.84</rating>
<name>Kusaka Shizuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2890" picture="23182.jpg">Sugiyama Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66866" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="3">4.20</rating>
<name>Nono Rakuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3834" picture="25805.jpg">Toyoshima Machiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66867" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="3">5.27</rating>
<name>Ishige Masami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="458" picture="171388.jpg">Inoue Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66868" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">2.86</rating>
<name>Utsumi Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2139" picture="25822.jpg">Kasahara Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66869" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="3">3.24</rating>
<name>Hayase Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1659" picture="223004.jpg">Katsuragi Nanaho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66870" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">1.91</rating>
<name>Fukamichi Nobuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2799" picture="23198.jpg">Matsuno Taiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66871" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="1">3.49</rating>
<name>Hanai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66872" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">3.80</rating>
<name>Tachibana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4030" picture="77664.jpg">Ryuutani Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66873" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="2">2.55</rating>
<name>Nagato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="7052" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛べ! エアマスター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly! Air Master</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobe! Air Master</title>
<summary>Maki Aikawa is tall, with a nice model-like figure, but is also quiet and looks like an ordinary high school girl. However, her unique life style includes being a street fighter within the dark alleyways and back streets of Tokyo. To date, she remains undefeated against both men and women. And with a unique arsenal of aerial techniques allowing her to knock out opponents at will, people began to call her the Air Master.One day, she encountered a scene where several girls (also known as a ko-gal group) who attended Tomato High School were being picked on by a boy. Seeing this, Maki came to their assistance and ended up fighting him and knocking him out. The gallery of people, who held witness to this, started yelling that she was the Air Master. Another street fighter of high spirit who refers to himself as Lucha Master, was also at the scene and immediately challenged her. And with that, a high-level street fight began spontaneously!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511648</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="7459" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吠えろ! 崎山香織!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Howl! Kaori Sakiyama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoero! Sakiyama Kaori!!</title>
<summary>From the scene that took place the other day, several girls (also known as a ko-gal group) immediately began to voice their acceptance in having Maki join their circle of friends. The group include Yuu, Michiru, Mina, and Renge. Maki was nicknamed Maki-chan.The ko-gal group planned an outing to a pool where they could showoff some new and very revealing bathing suits. A few days later, each of them were modeling their new bathing suit. During the pool outing, a girl named Kaori Sakiyama also noticed the girl and became jealous, challenging the entire group to a swimming match.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511650</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="7500" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">挑め! 時田伸之助</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge! Shinnosuke Tokita</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idome! Tokita Shinnosuke</title>
<summary>Yuu, Michiru, Mina, Renge, and Maki went to Shibuya. When on the street, a young man named Shinnosuke Tokita whose goal was to beat the Air Master, presented his challenge. This man who challenged Maki carried a Sansetsukon, a deadly weapon that he had trained with since the age of five.Before the fight with Shinnosuke could commence, Kaori Sakiyama shows up unexpectedly to challenge Maki to the first fight.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511652</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="7589" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目立て! 月雄と麗一</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stand out! Tsukio and Reiichi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Medate! Tsukio to Reiichi</title>
<summary>After battling together, Shinnosuke was so impressed with Maki`s abilities, he decided that he too wants to become a street fighter. Mina senses Shinnosuke`s feeling toward Maki and becomes jealous.During that night, the fighters of Shibuya were surprised at the number of ladies as well as a child (Renge)who turned out. Shinnosuke faced a number of challengers who were easily beaten. After giving a look as though he hadn`t really faced any worthy competition, a young boy on a BMX named Reiichi suddenly appeared to present a challenge.Soon, another fighter who was also Reiichi`s best friend appeared. This fighter whose name was Tsukio was well built with thick arms and had defeated many fighters night after night and yearned for a chance to battle with the Air Master. But first came the battle with Shinnosuke!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511654</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="7946" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">唱(うた)え! 坂本ジュリエッタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sing! Julietta Sakamoto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utae! Sakamoto Julietta</title>
<summary>Maki is confronted by a man named Julietta Sakamoto who Tsukio knows and calls a strong man. Approaching Maki, he begins to whisper words of love into her ear and gently kisses her hand. Maki is quite surprised while her friends Yuu and Michiru drop their jaws at the sight of this. Renge uncontrollably eats a snack that was given to her by Julietta. And as for Mina, she blurts out "I am Maki`s lover!" Maki and her companions are completely caught off guard by the actions of Julietta. And as for Maki who wants to fight Julietta, she knows to get involved further might be a dangerous risk of a different sort.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511656</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8189" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノってけ! 摩季</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ride it! Maki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Notteke! Maki</title>
<summary>Maki`s involuntary encounter with Julietta Sakamoto left her confused. She spaces out and decided not to go to school because something still doesn`t feel right. She wants the challenge of battle but knows it is not possible. Mina begins to worry about Maki who did not come to school and decides to visit her, even thought she does not know her address. Michiru, Yuu, Shinnosuke and the very strangely dressed Renge follow Mina. Renge casts a strange spell and impressively locates Maki. As they begin to approach Maki, she`s walking through the rain without an umbrella while appearing to be gathered in deep thought they were unable to call to her. After leaving a letter for Julietta in his mailbox, Maki went to the gym of fighter named Shiro Saeki. It seems like there is a long history between Maki and Shiro. At the same time, Julietta, who had received the letter from Maki, was very excited about its contents.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511658</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8416" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二度と言わせるな!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Won`t Let Me Say That Again!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nido to Iwaseru na!</title>
<summary>Maki challenges Julietta to a fight. The appointed time is three o`clock and that`s when she wakes up. "I overslept!" said Maki. However, the man who arrived at the appointed place on time was Maki`s father, "Shiro Saeki". Without Maki`s presence, Shiro challenges Julietta to a fight, but to Julietta, Shiro was not the one he was eagerly waiting for. Julietta begins to plant a sequence of kicks that were filled with fury. As Maki proceeds as quickly as possible to the appointed place, she is stopped on route and challenged to another fight by a girl named Miori Saeki. The girl is in fact Maki`s half-sister who has a similar passion for battle. Maki, who is seriously in a hurry, arrives at the appointed place by quickly throwing off Miori. Miori then follow Maki to the appointed place to witness the unexpected defeat of their father. Finally, the full-out battle of Maki and Julietta begins!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528874</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8571" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">轟け! 中ノ谷美奈</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resound! Mina Nakanotani</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todoroke! Nakanotani Mina</title>
<summary>The beach! Maki, Mina, Yuu, Michiru, and Renge had come to hang out and sun bathe together. Of course, Mina and her unbelievable breasts stood out conspicuously to attract the attention of anyone who passed by.While at the beach, Renge decided to enter Mina in the beach queen contest without ever telling her. Mina, who is very large breasted and a natural for such a competition is also very shy and at first, refuses to participate. However, Maki encourages Mina to partake and she agrees and then becomes determined to win the contest.At the same time, another competition, "The Beach Wrestling Queen Tournament," was being held at the same place. The tournament`s previous winner with consecutive victories is a fighter that uses aerial killing techniques who does not appear to be an amateur. While watching the event, Maki is approached by a woman named Shizuna who hands her a flashy mask to encourage her to become a participant. Furthermore, a woman who calls herself "Supermodel of the future," who has already established a reputation for herself by fighting on shows, also appears to compete!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511662</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8726" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">進め! 黒正義誠意連合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go! Black Alliance of Justice and Sincerity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Susume! Kuroseigiseiirengou</title>
<summary>A group of high school students in their school uniforms came to Tokyo on a field trip. They call themselves the "Black Alliance of Justice and Sincerity". While the Black Alliance enjoy fighting, they also have aspiration of becoming Japan`s number one fighting group. Immediately, they begin to challenge the students of the Tokyo area. To their surprise, the Tokyo students present little challenge and are defeated quite easily. Quickly gaining confidence, the Black Alliance begin to say that the people of Tokyo are weak. However, while still in Tokyo, the members of the Black Alliance noticed Mina Nakanotani, who is famous throughout Japan for having such a well-endowed figure. The members of Black Alliance are overjoyed and immediately start to dance wildly when seeing Mina in real life. Rudely, they push Mina`s companion , Maki, out of the way for an opportunity to have a picture taken with her. At the end of the photo shoot, the Black Alliances suddenly abduct Mina and run away from the scene. Renge, another companion of Mina begins to panic at what had just happened and turns to their other friend Maki, to apprise her of the situation. Maki is nowhere to be found!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511664</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="9699" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃えろ! 北枝金次郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blaze! Kinjiro Kitaeda</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moero! Kitaeda Kinjirou</title>
<summary>Although the kidnapped Mina was rescued from the hands of the Black Alliance, Tsukio, Reiichi, and Shinnosuke are soon overwhelmed by the growing number of the Black Alliance. Tsukio realizes that they would soon be annihilated and orders Shinnosuke and Reiichi to flee from the scene carrying Mina. However, they are soon cornered by the growing number of Black Alliance members. At the same time, there is a man with a dignified look sitting in a cafe` calling out the leaders of the Black Alliance. He is the president of Black Alliance of Justice and Sincerity "Kinjiro Kitaeda," also known as "Kin-chan." In realizing what has done, Kinjiro becomes agitated and hit one of his members with all his might! And finally, Maki arrives to find Mina! At last, the fight of Black Alliance of Righteousness and Sincerity vs. Maki starts!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511666</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="9777" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たたみこめ! 摩季対金次郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beat it in! Maki Vs. Kinjiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatamikome! Maki tai Kinjirou</title>
<summary>Maki`s anger erupted into a violent rage when she saw Mina! After defeating several of the Black Alliance members, Maki is challenged to a fight by their leader, Kinjiro, who is also known as "Kin-chan." As Maki and Kinjiro prepare to battle drawing closer to each other, Nagato, another member from the Black Alliance, steps in gesturing that he want to be the next to fight the Air Master. Maki quickly accepts Nagato`s challenge. Julietta, who was sitting nearby noticed Maki and proceeded to approach her, to his surprise, Nagato quickly lands a kick to Julietta`s body. Before the final fight between Maki and Kinjiro can even start, a fierce battle between Nagato and Julietta takes place!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511668</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="10102" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">名のれ! ファミレスラーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Make Yourself Known! Fami-Wrestlers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanore! Famiwrestlers</title>
<summary>Kaori Sakiyama continues to knock down her opponents one after another when street fighting. Impressed by Sakiyama`s sense of fighting, Tomiko, a professional woman wrestler asks her to join a wresting tag team called Fami-Wrestlers. During there conversation, Sakiyama tells Tomiko about Maki. Tomiko finds it hard to believe that a young high school student could be stronger than Sakiyama and challenges the Air Master to a fight where she is easily defeated and received injuries that will take a month to heal. By force of circumstance, the Fami-Wrestlers became a combination of Sakiyama and Maki. The opponent they meet at the ring on the day of the match, "Matoba," seems to be acquainted with Sakiyama from her own high school days. As Matoba, a former acquaintance whispers something into Sakiyama`s ear, Sakiyama`s disposition immediately changes. A fierce battle is about to begin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511670</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="10170" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">輝け! スカイスター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sparkle! Sky Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayake! Skystar</title>
<summary>An out-of-this-world tag team is born! And they`re called the Fami-Wrestlers! Ignoring the matches listed on the card, this duo starts attacking one team after another! Kaori Sakiyama grabs a mic in the stunned crowd and gives an all-out performance! Feeling she should stop their fighting, a blood-thirsty pro wrestler named Mio Hayase appears. Sakiyama yells to her over the mic, "you look like you poisoned the princess in the dragon castle and switched places with her!" No one can stop Sakiyama from egging on the fight! Or so they thought. Mio hits Sakiyama in the head and she collapses. Sakiyama`s body may be completely worn out, but she rushes in through spirit alone! Due to Sakiyama`s energy and yelling, Maki gets fired up and enters her battle mode! Everyone expects the super-strong pro wrestling duo of Mio Hayase and Sanpagita Kai to win and the bell rings! Mio is shocked at Maki`s strength and quickly tags Kai. Kai says, "let me see who you really are!" when she stops to protect Mio and the letters SS are written on her back!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511672</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="10234" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突きぬけろ! カイと摩季</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly Through! Kai and Maki!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukinukero! Kai to Maki</title>
<summary>Air Master vs. Sky Star, the mid-air battle extravaganza has finally begun! But Kai is a cut above Maki when it comes to the ring. Maki is about to collapse! But then, Sakiyama yells from ringside, "What the hell are you doing in there?!" But then Maki is smacked! Mio, Kai and the spectators are all stunned. Sakiyama is screaming to kick Kai and Mio`s butts! Sakiyama goes to unleash her Hua Jing on Kai but it misfires. Then Kai and Mio explode in a magnificent combination attack! Sakiyama and Maki are knocked into their corner. Kai hits with her Missile Kick and Mio unleashes her special attack, the Izakaya Bomber, on the back of Maki`s head. Mio and Kai sandwich her with an Izakaya Bomber. Mio taunts Maki, saying this is what pro wrestling is really like, but Sakiyama smirks back saying this is perfect for her. Hearing that, Kai decides to unleash an attack that employs her true spirit as a pro wrestler. The match is approaching its climax!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511674</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="10655" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">征服せよ! 女帝ゴキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conquer! Empress Cockroach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seifuku Seyo! Jotei Goki</title>
<summary>After the pro wrestling event, everyone slowly starts to change. Shinnosuke makes a resolution in his heart and leaves on a solitary voyage. Maki, on the other hand, is rendered completely dumb after the match. She isn`t giving off the same aura she had while in the ring! Dumbfounded by this, Kaori Sakiyama begins to preach to Maki and confesses that she was fired from her job. Kaori then drags Maki to work the same part-time job she took up. Her job is to play the villain in the High Rangers hero show at the amusement park. Maki is up there, dumb as ever, with a bunch of wannabe fighters on stage. Then, the enemy leader that Sakiyama is playing, Empress Cockroach, enters the stage! Sakiyama is a natural to play this role and the children are likewise truly frightened. She kicks Maki to the side as the show heats up. Maki seems to be wondering what the heck she is doing on stage and then she comes attacking out of nowhere! Now the real hero show will begin!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511676</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="10703" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦え! 深道ランキング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fight! Fukamichi Ranking</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakae! Fukamichi Ranking</title>
<summary>A mysterious man calling himself Fukamichi suddenly appears in front of Tsukio and Reiichi asking them to join the Fukamichi Ranking. Tsukio is annoyed at his attitude but invites Lucha Master to take his place. Right when they think the fight is about to start, Fukamichi calls out the 36th ranked fighter in the Fukamichi Ranking and he defeats Lucha Master in one second. The three of them are disappointed and shocked by this. While this is going on, a man who says he is in the Fukamichi Ranking appears before Kai and Mio. This man is named Yashiki. He appears to want to fight the Air Master. He is ranked number nine and appears quite confident in his fighting abilities. Kai doesn`t really understand what the Fukamichi Ranking is all about but she says to Yashiki that if he wants to fight the Air Master, he has to beat her first. Then Yashiki busts out an osmosis attack like Kaori Sakiyama`s, and a strong one at that! Kai is knocked down in one blow! Miori is stunned by what is happening before her and she called out for her sister, Maki! The mysterious street fighting story of the Fukamichi Ranking is underway!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511678</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11054" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">集え! ストリートファイターズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gather Round! Street Fighters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsudoe! Street Fighters</title>
<summary>Maki`s strength is fully tested by the Fukamichi Ranking. Maki easily defeats the 17th ranked fighter but waiting at the side is a dangerous looking fighter, her opponent. He says "Welcome to the Sniper Karate course." There is also a man who has come to Tokyo after hearing of Maki`s spectacular fights. The leader of the Ranking, Fukamichi himself, invited him and it`s none other than Kinjiro Kitaeda. Instead of fighting a rematch with the Air Master he opts to join the Fukamichi Ranking. Nagato overhears Fukamichi say "Kinjiro Kitaeda, I want you," while recruiting him. Nagato says "What did you just say to Kin-chan?" Nagato is in a blind rage of jealousy due to those words. Fukamichi, who just came to recruit him, is unfazed and taunts Nagato. This doesn`t look like it`ll end smoothly!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511680</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11943" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コスプれ! 駒田シゲオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cosplay! Shigeo Komata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cosplay! Komada Shigeo</title>
<summary>A cosplaying man named Shigeo Komata, his clothes are ragged and he has a crew cut like someone out of a video game. Though he based his attacks on a video game character, his power is not to be taken lightly! For this reason, he is number six in the Fukamichi Ranking. Maki definitely sees that he`s not someone who will be beaten if she doesn`t give 100%. At the same time, Kinjiro Kitaeda is fighting the 10th ranked fighter upon Fukamichi`s instructions. He`s being swiftly punched by his nimble opponent, but he responds with "There`s no soul in your punches" and knocks him out in one blow. Fukamichi watches this all happen and even sees Yashiki, the 8th ranked fighter who can use the osmosis attack, be quickly overcome. We have a new rival here, folks! Meanwhile, Maki is reluctantly going to have her rematch with Shigeo. She is thinking up a special attack to finally beat him while watching a movie with Mina. A move to beat an opponent in one split second... Maki has an idea!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528836</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11944" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍べ! 尾形小路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lurk in the Shadows! Koji Ogata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinobe! Ogata Kouji</title>
<summary>Maki and Kai will have real Fukamichi Ranking battles. Fukamichi gives them both locators to find the other person, to be worn on their wrists. Though it`s an incredible device to help you locate your opponent, Maki can`t figure out how to work it at all! Fukamichi is amazed how dull she is besides for her fighting skills. Though she can`t figure it out, she ends up in a dilapidated building. The locator shows her opponent is close by and then he shows up! His name is Koji Ogata. He`s dressed oddly and his unusual movements confuse Maki. His attack style is Ninjutsu! Maki can`t figure out his attacks and his being hit over and over. Fukamichi sees this and says, "For Maki Aikawa, it`s only a matter of time." Like he`s signaling the final blow, Ogata sends out this shrill whistle sound. Maki continues to be hit. Then, Ogata begins to look like multiple people! Is that possible?! Maki`s in trouble!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511682</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11945" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶつかれ! カイ対金次郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strike! Kai vs. Kinjiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Butsukare! Kai tai Kinjirou</title>
<summary>Kai is walking along a large road following the locator that Fukamichi gave to her. Slowly but surely, she approaches her opponent. Miori is alongside and her and is completely emotionally attacked to Kai. Her opponent happens to be Kinjiro Kitaeda, or Kin-chan! As soon as they realize who their opponent is, they start into a full-out battle! Izakaya Bomber vs. Chi Punch. Or more so, Sky Star Pro Wrestler vs. the Spirited Right Puncher!" They`re in the middle of a busy street with cars and people around, plus it`s broad daylight. A large gallery of people form to watch them find each other un affected by their surroundings. Though Kin-chan is looking for the Air Master, he cannot hide is surprise at her toughness. The tension between the two grows! Kinjiro tries to end it with his ultra-fast right while Kai is trying to show him her "way of life." The fight between these two is one for the ages! They`re in a dead heat! Which one will win?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511684</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11946" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しゃべらせろ! 深道(弟)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Make Him Talk! Fukamichi (Little Brother)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shaberasero! Fukamichi (Otouto)</title>
<summary>The man who appeared in front of Julietta was the younger brother of the ringleader of the Ranking`s younger brother, Fukamichi. Nobuhiko challenges Julietta to a fight. He thought Julietta Sakamoto would be unable to fight and he mistakenly feels happy. Fukamichi watches the fight on the monitor excitedly, with bated breath. He then sees his brother get knocked out and his head stuck into the ceiling. The fight ended while he was still introducing himself. Then, Kinjiro, whose left arm was destroyed in the fight against Kai, stumbles into a clinic. He says crazy things to the doctor like, "please reset the bone now," and "just make it so I can throw five more punches." His requests ignored and being told to be admitted in the hospital, Kinjiro leaves in search of another doctor. Just then, he meets a girl nurse named Shizuna. She tells him to come with her because she can fix his arm and then leads him into a strange basement. Kin-chan feels like something strange is about to happen to him!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511686</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11947" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">打ち上げろ! 炎のランカー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Launch It! The Flame Fighter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchiagero! Honoo no Ranker</title>
<summary>Deciding to follow the invitation of Shizuna, who said she could fix his arm, Kinjiro follows her to a mysterious basement and passes out. The pain and fatigue had pushed him to his limits. Shortly afterward, when he awakes, he feels that his pain threshold had been raised and his body feels strange. He then realizes that he`s been turned into a Shizuna-man! By the way, what`s a Shizuna-man? Thinking his outfit looks stupid, Kin-chan takes off the pieces of the Shizuna-man armor one by one as Shizuna scowls at him like some sort of monster. Then, he realizes that he can use his left arm. Though he dislikes the outfit, he`d rather have that than not be able to use his arm. Reluctantly he strips down to the bare minimum amount of armor and goes to defeat the Air Master once again. Around the same time, the younger Fukamichi brother appears once again, this time challenging Maki to a fight. But this time he doesn`t show himself and begins a fight in a showy blast of fireworks on top of a roof. At the same time, Kin-chan is out to challenge the Air Master. But this time Fukamichi declares that his opponent is the 4th ranked Minaguchi. Kinjiro suddenly gets angry proclaiming, "I won`t just do as you want me to!"
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532172</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="13581" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">切り裂け! 皆口由紀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Slash Through! Yuki Minaguchi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirisake! Minaguchi Yuki</title>
<summary>Kin-chan loses to Yuki Minaguchi. His right arm is back to full function but he`s overwhelmed by Yuki`s strength. Her next opponent is the Air Master. All the Fukamichi Ranking fans across the country have been awaiting this battle as the fight begins in earnest. Both Maki and Yuki try to end the fight with their special attack right at the start. But, they both notice the other`s attack and dodge. Yuki smiles happily at Maki and for the first time Maki feels terror throughout her body. The difference in emotion is apparent in the fight and Maki is handily being beaten. About to accept her own defeat, Maki suddenly hears Kaori Sakiyama`s loud yells! "Are you running away?! What will you do then?!" Maki, beaten ragged, stands up against Yuki saying, "I won`t... lose. Fighting is all I know."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511690</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="13582" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">焼け! 肉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Grill It! Meat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yake! Niku</title>
<summary>It`s been ten days since the showdown between Maki and Yuki Minaguchi. Maki has been out of it, not sure if she feels good or bad. At Maki`s father, Saeki Shiro`s dojo, a man calling himself Konishi shows up. He says he won`t use his bat and challenges Saeki. The truth is that Konishi is a judo master calling himself the Submission Hunter. The way he speaks is very odd. Honestly speaking, he`s a strange guy. The fight begins quickly but what is surprising is the rate at which he knocks out Saeki`s knees. When asked about his real background, Konishi admits to being in the Fukamichi Ranking. Wanting to know more, Saeki invites him out to a Korean barbeque restaurant. Konishi thought they`d talk while eating but Saeki isn`t letting him eat the meat at all. This irritates Konishi. Their conversation doesn`t work well either. Finally, Saeki admits that he can`t enjoy eating his meal to the max when dining with a guy. As their conversation creeps further into absurdity, Renge shows up, bedazzled by the smell of the Korean barbeque.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511692</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="13583" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壊せ! 小西対ジュリエッタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Break! Konishi vs. Julietta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kowase! Konishi tai Julietta</title>
<summary>"I will defeat you. I will become a perfect dazzling star in the night sky tonight!" declares Konishi. While standing up to Julietta`s random power, Konishi keeps telling himself to remain cool. Konishi breaks Julietta`s right leg with his left arm! You can hear the ligament snap in the quiet of the evening park! Konishi prepares for him to submit. However, for some reason, Julietta`s right leg comes flying in! And faster than before! How can this be? His ligament was torn! In any case, this is true. Konishi, telling himself to stay cool even more than before, stops trying to guard Julietta`s kicks and tries to tackle him instead. If he uses all five of his senses at once he`ll tackle him and defeat him! While this is going on, Maki is practicing attacks blindfolded with Miori at their home. Maki learns to be able to sense her surroundings. And then, Maki learns to feel the air...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511696</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="13584" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">感じろ! 闘いの風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Feel It! The Wind of the Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanjiro! Tatakai no Kaze</title>
<summary>A few days after being completely defeated by the woman, Yuki Minaguchi, Kinjiro Kitaeda puts on a new Shizuna-man outfit dubbed Shizuna-man Version 2. But once Nagato saw him in that armor, the atmosphere suddenly changes. He doesn`t seem like the normal, passionate Kin-chan... Wanting to test out Shizuna-man Version 2, Shizuna takes Kin-chan directly to a park that night. Kin-chan starts to realize his power, but somewhere in his heart he feels uneasy. But, he cannot conceal the greatness of the power he`s received. But something is different... His opponent is Lucha Master, who is giving him all he`s got in return. What happened to the fight he expected?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511698</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="13585" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛べ! 相川摩季</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly! Maki Aikawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobe! Aikawa Maki</title>
<summary>"Win, Maki." Maki Aikawa tosses her body away during the fight and realizes the true essence of fighting. She thinks. She searches. That is why she`s so strong when at full power. Her opponents all know this well. The people she encounters all experiences this and changed forever. She allows them to change. Kaori Sakiyama represents one such people. From meeting with Maki, a fire was lit inside her heart and her passion level rose. She was also the first friend that Maki, someone who has lived her life fighting every day, has ever known. She`s no longer a lonely fighter. She has a friend who worries about her. Maki then thinks of all her friends, Yuu, Michiru, Renge, Mina... How they all cheer her on. Maki can fight full-on because she has friends in her corner. She`ll continue to meet people, friends and enemies. People are able to grow and feel despair from the people they meet. But no matter what, she`ll continue on. It`s because she`s continued on that she`s made it to the place she`s currently in. The person she encounters here is called an Eternal. She doesn`t know if he`s aiming for the top or not. Nevertheless, Maki flies through the air with all her power. She`s the Air Master!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511700</identifier>
<identifier>air-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
