<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="638" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>150</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2006-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Konjiki no Gash Bell!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Golden Gash Bell!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gash Bell tv</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Златовласый Гаш Белл!!, Золотой Режущий Колокольчик!</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Златният Гаш Бел!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kngb</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gash Bell</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">金色のガッシュベル!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Zatch Bell!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Zatch Bell!</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Zatch Bell!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">갓슈벨</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Zatch Bell!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1676" type="Side Story">Gekijouban Konjiki no Gash Bell!! 101 Banme no Mamono</anime>
<anime id="2776" type="Side Story">Gekijouban Konjiki no Gash Bell!! Mecha Vulcan no Raishuu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2921" approval="20" total="21">Ueki no Housoku</anime>
<anime id="7934" approval="12" total="19">Beelzebub</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="243684">A shounen, that actually makes sense while trying to make as much nonsense as possible.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="210496">Very melon / 10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="319095">No way around this!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/GB/</url>
<creators>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="7780" type="Direction">Nakamura Tetsuharu</name>
<name id="4449" type="Direction">Kaizawa Yukio</name>
<name id="3467" type="Series Composition">Yamatoya Akatsuki</name>
<name id="5275" type="Original Work">Raiku Makoto</name>
<name id="127" type="Character Design">Ootsuka Ken</name>
<name id="5442" type="Series Composition">Hashimoto Hiroshi</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
<name id="127" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ootsuka Ken</name>
<name id="733" type="Work">Yomiko Advertising</name>
<name id="1834" type="Work">Toei Animation</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch11209 [Takamine Kyomaro]`s lazy life suddenly turns upside down as a mysterious kid named http://anidb.net/ch11208 [Gash] appears in his room, claiming to be his 14th birthday gift.
Gash has no memory of his past and doesnt know anything about his own identity and his only belonging is a red book that is written in a non human language.
However,By saying "Zakeru", kyomaro accidentaly triggers Gash to release a huge amount of lightening through his mouth.
Shocked, Kyomaro decides to act normally in order not to ruin his own peaceful life, but when other creatures like Gash try to find and attack him, Kyomaro tries to defend Gash and win over attackers by using the words in the book.
It turns out, there are 99 other creatures like Gash in this world and they`re seeking power by knocking down each other. Who will stand out?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1027">5.94</permanent>
<temporary count="1057">7.35</temporary>
<review count="3">7.61</review>
</ratings>
<picture>178011.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2290</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7430</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>250</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10732</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1187</identifier>
<identifier>gvchjc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/GB/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>金色のガッシュベル!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>金色のガッシュ!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>53</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240810</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5970</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3245" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-05">
<name>strategy</name>
<description>Instead of blindly running into a battle or trap, at least one of the protagonists devises a clever strategy to significantly improve the odds of victory.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3833" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>there can be only one</name>
<description>The long-term plot of the program revolves around a group of characters whose numbers are being slowly whittled away by one means or another, usually by killing each other. In the case of some reality shows, this is a process of elimination intended to result in a single winner. In other shows, this is a dramatic device, designed to generate tension and conflict with which to drive the overall plot of an episode or Story Arc (if any); in these cases it is sometimes combined with Anyone Can Die to especially heighten the resulting excitement, even when the apparent main character may be protected by Contractual Immortality. Compare Gotta Kill Them All.
Named for one of the catchphrases that came out of the Highlander franchise.
Source: TVTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11208" type="main character in" update="2009-08-15">
<rating votes="13">7.17</rating>
<name>Gash Bell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="4838" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11209" type="main character in" update="2009-08-15">
<rating votes="14">5.21</rating>
<name>Takamine Kiyomaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33236.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11211" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-15">
<rating votes="14">5.71</rating>
<name>Mizuno Suzume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33264.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1940" picture="21213.jpg">Akiya Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28978" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-22">
<rating votes="10">8.53</rating>
<name>Parco Folgore</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Parco Folgore and his Mamodo Partner Kanchomé are friends and allies of Kiyo Takamine and Zatch Bell. Folgore is a superstar and film hero from Milan, Italy, known for his two hit songs Chichi o Moge! (チチをもげ, lit. Grope the Breasts!) and Muteki Folgore! (無敵フォルゴレ, lit. Invincible Folgore!). Chichi no Moge! was changed to Hey Hey Let`s Dance all Day by Viz Media and Muteki Folgore to Iron Man Folgore. Although appearing perverted, cowardly, and weak, Folgore is a person with high morale standards and is more insightful then he seems. In the past, Folgore was a short tempered and vicious man who was feared in town due to his ruthless nature. His parents threatened him with a shotgun to leave home out of fear. Folgore later changed his personality after watching a hippopotamus and oxpecker living in mutalism and developed his comedic personality. Kanchomé`s appearance is that of a young boy wearing a blanket sleeper, with large eyes and a duck bill. His personality tends toward childish and abrasive, often crying and whining like an infant. He greatly admires Folgore, believing him to be invincible. Kanchomé`s spells involve transformation and illusions. He later gains the ability to create clones with inhuman strength and a spell that can trap his opponents in an illusionary world giving him full control over their senses. Kanchomé`s book was burned by an attack by Clear Note.</description>
<picture>66144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28985" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Nicole</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4205.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1934" picture="186186.jpg">Aida Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32529" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-21">
<rating votes="3">4.91</rating>
<name>Sherry Belmond</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4188.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32530" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Hyde</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4192.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="5342" picture="224845.jpg">Urawa Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32531" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="2">6.14</rating>
<name>Brago</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10401" picture="38335.jpg">Kojima Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32532" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="2">3.29</rating>
<name>Takamine Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4182.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="321" picture="17158.jpg">Yamazaki Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32545" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Takamine Seitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4184.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32556" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Kubozuka Eita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4193.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32557" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Kaneyama Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4191.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32558" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Raycom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4207.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3794" picture="38865.jpg">Kumai Motoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32559" type="appears in" update="2016-06-30">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Nakamura Mariko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3875" picture="25549.jpg">Hanioka Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32560" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<name>Gofure</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32561" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<name>Gofure (Koinu)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4186.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3875" picture="25549.jpg">Hanioka Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32563" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<name>Naomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11253" picture="40616.jpg">Mizowaki Shihomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32564" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<name>Kamakirijoe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4187.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="10401" picture="38335.jpg">Kojima Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32565" type="appears in" update="2015-02-24">
<name>Sherry no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3947" picture="25762.jpg">Shou Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32566" type="appears in" update="2011-11-30">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Coco</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4189.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32567" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<name>Zoffis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4190.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3250" picture="24693.jpg">Fujita Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32568" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Kanchome</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32569" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-21">
<rating votes="7">6.62</rating>
<name>Umagon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4195.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32570" type="appears in" update="2015-02-24">
<name>Akiyama Shin`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32571" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Eshuros</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4197.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32572" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4198.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32573" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Seibee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4199.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32574" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Kolulu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4200.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32575" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Fein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4201.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32576" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Haruhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4202.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32577" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Sugina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4203.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="32327" picture="86564.jpg">Misaki Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32578" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Hosokawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4204.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3370" picture="74440.jpg">Yamaguchi Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32580" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Yamanaka Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4206.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32581" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Mars</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4208.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32582" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<name>Rembrand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4209.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="9608" picture="35858.jpg">Nakata Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50565" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-12">
<rating votes="9">6.17</rating>
<name>Ooumi Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50566" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-12">
<rating votes="9">4.04</rating>
<name>Tio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82683" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-06-27">
<name>Li-en</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="394" picture="17239.jpg">Ikezawa Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82684" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-06-27">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Nakata Sabae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82685" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-06-27">
<name>Patie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82686" type="appears in" update="2016-06-27">
<name>Rops</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82687" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-06-27">
<rating votes="1">8.64</rating>
<name>Sunbeam Kafka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82688" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-06-27">
<name>Wonrei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82689" type="appears in" update="2016-09-15">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Elle Chivas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64192.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82690" type="appears in" update="2017-01-03">
<name>Apollo Genesis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82697" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Momon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4665" picture="27220.jpg">Takahashi Naozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82698" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Riya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10876.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82700" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Zaruchimu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63948.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="132" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82701" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Raushin Mou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64099.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82702" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Adler</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64150.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82703" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Esukaruro Run</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82704" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Gyaron</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82705" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Jedeyun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82706" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Harry Jet</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82707" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Fango</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4838" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82708" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Kazu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64040.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82709" type="appears in" update="2016-07-20">
<name>Keith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82710" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Cherish</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82711" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Buzarai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64039.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="8359" picture="174120.jpg">Sasaki Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82712" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Bern</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64038.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5021" picture="188516.jpg">Taki Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82713" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Kyle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64101.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82714" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Chita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63947.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82715" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Riou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3645" picture="25834.jpg">Yamamoto Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82716" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Rein</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82717" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Arishie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82718" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Rodeaux</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82719" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Arth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64147.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82720" type="appears in" update="2016-07-20">
<name>Elly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4838" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82721" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Karudio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82722" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Grab</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82723" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Coral Q</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64151.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="9800" picture="36489.jpg">Koujiro Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82724" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Sauzaa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64148.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82725" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Jido</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82726" type="appears in" update="2016-06-29">
<name>Ted</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82727" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Alumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82728" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Nikolaus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64105.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4707" picture="27477.jpg">Tamaki Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82729" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Maestro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10885.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82730" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Majirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2413" picture="22272.jpg">Mizuta Wasabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82731" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Retsusai Monmon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4101" picture="26184.jpg">Adachi Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82732" type="appears in" update="2018-04-08">
<name>Dalia Anje</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82733" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-06-28">
<rating votes="1">8.64</rating>
<name>Riddles-hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="599" picture="226547.jpg">Naya Rokurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82734" type="appears in" update="2016-07-20">
<name>Demoruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188873.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82735" type="appears in" update="2016-07-05">
<name>Pamun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10879.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4020" picture="28744.jpg">Matsuoka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82736" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Lance</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="29934" picture="79157.jpg">Azumi Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82737" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Weil</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82738" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Kido</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82739" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Kinoyama Tsukushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82740" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Albert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82741" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Elizabeth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64149.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82742" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Dalmos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82743" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Victoream</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82744" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Mohawk Ace</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10884.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="5887" picture="203017.jpg">Nagano Yoshikazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82747" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Danny</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82748" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Iwashima Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3702" picture="25829.jpg">Numata Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82749" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Psycho Jungle</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82750" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Second Site</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3157" picture="24155.jpg">Nishimatsu Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82751" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Dinosaur Arm</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82753" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Tsuaoron</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82754" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Telepathy Radar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4422" picture="228398.jpg">Iida Toshinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82755" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Denshin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82756" type="appears in" update="2016-06-29">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Big Boin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82758" type="appears in" update="2016-07-18">
<name>Wonderful to the Future</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="29934" picture="79157.jpg">Azumi Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82759" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Gensou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82760" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Ururu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63949.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82762" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Pyonko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82763" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Erujo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64092.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3420" picture="228543.jpg">Fujita Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82764" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Dogmos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10897.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3998" picture="33313.jpg">Fujimoto Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82765" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Francoise Cardin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64090.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="26181">Yamanaka Rieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82766" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Henrika Abbott</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64089.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5021" picture="188516.jpg">Taki Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82767" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Borubora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64091.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12415" picture="41837.jpg">Ishikawa Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82768" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Paul Khan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64088.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="66" picture="216211.jpg">Bifu Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82769" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Geryuosu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64152.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="42105">Shibayama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82770" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>John Owen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64098.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4423" picture="26687.jpg">Okuda Keijin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82771" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Takahashi Mamiko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82773" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Gustav</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64153.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82774" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Jeff</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82775" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Jeff no Sofu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4478" picture="26750.jpg">Matsuoka Fumio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82776" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Vincent Barry</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10883.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82777" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Jiji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3284" picture="24296.jpg">Kitamura Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82778" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Layla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82779" type="appears in" update="2016-07-05">
<name>Gurisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63933.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3285" picture="193568.jpg">Kimotsuki Kaneta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82780" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Nyarurato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63950.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="23531" picture="222835.jpg">Yukiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82781" type="appears in" update="2016-07-05">
<name>Noritou Hassamii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4004" picture="77763.jpg">Masutani Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82782" type="appears in" update="2016-07-05">
<name>Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3253" picture="24232.jpg">Kameyama Sukekiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82783" type="appears in" update="2016-07-05">
<name>Endouki Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63932.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82784" type="appears in" update="2016-07-04">
<name>Hibiki Shion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3834" picture="25805.jpg">Toyoshima Machiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82785" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Kalura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187951.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="82786" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Marlene Yanenz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187952.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="82787" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Belgim E.O</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82788" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Garionto</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2248" picture="170362.jpg">Kawashima Tokuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82789" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Garza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63946.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82790" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Circus no Danchou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82791" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Zabasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1659" picture="223004.jpg">Katsuragi Nanaho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82792" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<name>Baransha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82793" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Bago</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82794" type="appears in" update="2016-08-09">
<name>Furito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64061.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82795" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Lili</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3713" picture="25079.jpg">Mine Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82796" type="appears in" update="2016-08-09">
<name>Lucica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64060.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2792" picture="26717.jpg">Kawata Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82797" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Jem</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64100.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82798" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Zeon Bell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10882.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="685" picture="24841.jpg">Takano Urara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82799" type="appears in" update="2016-07-20">
<name>Dufort</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188870.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82800" type="appears in" update="2016-06-29">
<name>Yopopo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10877.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3271" picture="171421.jpg">Emori Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82801" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Babiru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82802" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Gorudou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2143" picture="178043.jpg">Kayumi Iemasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82803" type="appears in" update="2016-06-29">
<name>Lupa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10775" picture="38758.jpg">Sakurai Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82804" type="appears in" update="2016-06-29">
<name>Leopardon Papipurio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2005" picture="188512.jpg">Yamazaki Michiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82805" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Jill</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="628" picture="188442.jpg">Dodo Asako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82806" type="appears in" update="2016-07-11">
<name>Hige</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63951.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82807" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Professor Dartanian</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82808" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Malyl Carnoy</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82809" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Tremor Mole</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187959.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="82811" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Seiu Ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187961.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="82812" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Aruvin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="385" picture="215702.jpg">Tsukada Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82813" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Steng</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82814" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Bartolo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="287" picture="73062.jpg">Yanada Kiyoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82815" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Ryukku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64102.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82816" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Robunos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10895.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4838" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82819" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Sekkoro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3936" picture="245652.jpg">Mita Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82820" type="appears in" update="2016-07-21">
<name>Hiromi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63999.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82821" type="appears in" update="2017-04-07">
<name>Baba Anan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2040" picture="186173.jpg">Suzuki Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82822" type="appears in" update="2016-06-28">
<name>Cook</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82824" type="appears in" update="2016-06-29">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Zoboron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187978.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="82838" type="appears in" update="2016-06-30">
<name>Miss Wriggle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188004.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="82839" type="appears in" update="2016-06-30">
<name>Suzuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26181">Yamanaka Rieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82845" type="appears in" update="2016-07-02">
<name>Natsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188060.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="82894" type="appears in" update="2016-07-05">
<name>Maril Cullanoa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82895" type="appears in" update="2016-07-05">
<name>Oren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188156.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="385" picture="215702.jpg">Tsukada Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82906" type="appears in" update="2016-07-07">
<name>Barutoro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10881.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="287" picture="73062.jpg">Yanada Kiyoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82916" type="appears in" update="2016-07-10">
<name>Kikuropu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="66" picture="216211.jpg">Bifu Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82917" type="appears in" update="2017-01-03">
<name>Igirisu Shinshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83581" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Furigaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64041.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="66" picture="216211.jpg">Bifu Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83582" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Gerhart</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64042.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83887" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Dorouma Kotarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3289" picture="203640.jpg">Yasuhara Yoshito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83888" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Kogorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64085.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38419" picture="141689.jpg">Nakayama Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83889" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Tooyama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64087.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="242" picture="238968.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83891" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Torowa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64093.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20322" picture="186181.jpg">Shiga Katsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83892" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Ozzie Bryant</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190238.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="83893" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Tsuvai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64094.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83894" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Divitto Cole</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2802" picture="176252.jpg">Shingaki Tarusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83895" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Faust</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64095.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83896" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Natsuo P. Costner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="646" picture="186183.jpg">Satou Haruo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83897" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Fire Elbow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64096.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="83898" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Rocket Foot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64097.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="83899" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Unko Tin Tin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190247.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="83901" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Lightning Eye</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64103.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="83902" type="appears in" update="2016-08-19">
<name>Blizzard Thing</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64104.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="84824" type="appears in" update="2016-09-16">
<name>Gantsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="84825" type="appears in" update="2016-09-16">
<name>Billy Ferris</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="7898" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔界から来た電撃少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lightning Boy From Another World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`enfant éclair qui venait d`un autre monde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makai Kara Kita Dengeki Shounen</title>
<summary>A boy named Zatch Bell arrives at Kiyo Takamine`s house and reveals that Kiyo`s father sent him to train Kiyo. Zatch gives Kiyo a letter from his father which reveals that Kiyo`s father found an amnesic Zatch unconscious in the forest and with him was a red book in a mysterious language. While arguing with Zatch, the book glows red and Zatch shoots lightning out of his mouth destroying Kiyo`s wall. At school, Kiyo annoyed with Zatch`s presence sends Zatch to the rooftop to deal with "bullies". Zatch finds Suzy Mizuno on the rooftop and coincidentally, also finds a bully. The bully proceeds to beat up Zatch. Kiyo intervenes but is also beaten. Later, a mysterious flying skateboarder named Eido comes from the sky and knocks out the bully by blasting wind with his hand. He then demands Suzy to be his girlfriend and attacks Kiyo and Zatch. Kiyo notices that a child like Zatch is the one using the wind techniques. Kiyo reads "Zaker" from Zatch`s red book and Zatch fires lightning Eido, scaring them away. In the distance, a mysterious pair reveal the Mamodo battle has begun.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="8535" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷結呪文ギコルvsザケル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Freezing Spell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sortilège des glaces</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyouketsu Jumon Gikoru VS Zakeru</title>
<summary>Kiyo is on the way to school with Zatch when they notice a lake has been frozen. Kiyo notices a man named Hosokawa holding a light blue book with a child named Reycom. On the way home, Kiyo notices Suzy on television in the middle of a bank robbery committed by Hosokawa. Kiyo, hesitant to help her, is persuaded by Zatch to save Suzy. Kiyo bikes there and he and Zatch are launched from a bike into the bank. Kiyo attempts to get Zatch to fire lightning by reading "Zaker" from Zatch`s book but nothing occurs. Hosokawa demands Kiyo`s book and threatens to shoot Suzy. Kiyo wanting to save Suzy, shouts "Zaker" and Zatch simultaneously fires lightning from his mouth causing Hosokawa and Reycom to fly out of the bank. At home, Kiyo realizes the book responds to the user`s emotions. Kiyo realizes Zatch has become stronger and notices another page of Zatch`s book has become read-able.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="8683" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第2の術ラシルド!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Second Spell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le deuxième sortilège</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Ni no Jutsu Rashirudo!</title>
<summary>At school, the bank incident causes Kiyo to become popular with the students. On the way home, Kiyo and Zatch are attacked by Hosokawa and Reycom. Hosokawa reveals that he wants to use Zatch`s powers for his own gain. In the midst of the battle, Kiyo is frozen to the ground. Hosokawa takes Kiyo`s book but is unable to read it. Hosokawa grabs Zatch and attempts to fire a "Zaker" at Kiyo but nothing occurs. Kiyo realizes that only the people chosen to read the book are able to cast the spells. Zatch manages to retrieve the book and return it to Kiyo. Kiyo reads the second spell "Rashield" which summons an electric shield from the ground. The shield catches Reycom`s icicles and reflects it back with the addition of lightning on the icicles towards him. One of the reflected ice shards comes in contact with Reycom`s book causing it to burn. When the book is burned into ashes, Reycom disappears along with it.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9194" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">100人の魔物の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Mamodo Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La grande bataille de Mamodos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyaku Nin no Mamono no Tatakai</title>
<summary>Zatch realizes from the battle that he was the cause of the lightning attacks. The next day, Kiyo spots Zatch trying to boast about his ability to fire lightning. They get into an argument and Zatch runs away. Zatch later meets and befriends a dog which accompanies him to Kiyo`s house. At home, Kiyo is visited by the mysterious pair from before. They reveal Zatch is a Mamodo from the Mamodo World and when the book of that Mamodo is burned, the Mamodo is sent back to the Mamodo world. It is also revealed that every thousand years, a Mamodo battle occurs and the last one remaining on Earth becomes the next Mamodo King. They then demand Kiyo to surrender his book saying it would only bring trouble. Zatch, overhearing this, leaves with the dog. He runs into a mysterious man who uses a spell revealing the dog was actually a Mamodo.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9497" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い刺客ブラゴとシェリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dark Mamodo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Mamodo Noir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Shikaku Brago to Sherry</title>
<summary>The mysterious man, Renji, reveals he is the book user of the dog Mamodo, Gofure. Zatch is unwilling to fight, believing he is a monster and Kiyo would be better off without him. The pair easily defeat Renji and burn his book. During the battle, the pair are revealed to be Sherry Belmont and Brago. Using "Gravirei", they demand Kiyo to surrender his book or be killed by the spell. Kiyo refuses saying Zatch is his friend who saved him and that he will repay the favour. The pair prepare to use their strongest spell, "Gigano Reis". Zatch happy Kiyo considers him a friend, regains the will to fight. Using "Zaker" they were able to cancel the Brago`s spell but Kiyo losses consciousness in the blast. Sherry decides to spare Kiyo and Zatch and leave saying they shall return for Zatch`s book one day.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9498" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えた赤い魔本</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of the Missing Red Book</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère de la disparition du livre rouge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Akai Ma Hon</title>
<summary>Kiyo is hospitalized because of his wounds following the previous battle. A patient next to Kiyo in the hospital room is revealed to be a kid named Yuuta. Yuuta has been hospitalized longer than usual for a broken leg. When Kiyo tells Yuuta he will not heal if he does not eat, Yuuta steals Kiyo`s book and threatens to burn it. Kiyo, Zatch, and Suzy search for Yuuta. When Zatch finds Yuuta, Yuuta pretends he lost the book and Zatch offers to look for it with him as they are friends now. Yuuta touched by Zatch`s words leads Zatch to the book on the roof. Yuuta falls on his way down the roof but is saved by a "Zaker" which destroys the floor under Yuuta and causes him to full into a room full of pillows.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="10106" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">植物園の決闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Botanical Madness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Plantes en folie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shokubutsuen no Kettou</title>
<summary>Zatch becomes friend with a strange-looking horse but the relationship is short-lived when the horse is launched into the sky by Zatch`s bully. Kiyo takes Zatch and Suzy to a botanic garden when a Mamodo attacks everyone in the garden by strangling them with plant roots. Kiyo and Zatch manage to free everyone captured by the tree roots with "Zaker". As Kiyo and Zatch prepare to defeat the Mamodo and his book owner, they are unable to cast the spell "Zaker". The opponent reveals that the book uses energy from the human partner in order to use spells. Kiyo, using his desire to protect everyone, manages to unleash a "Rashield". "Rashield" reflects the Mamodo`s attack back at towards the user and in the process the Mamodo`s book is burned.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="10107" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やさしい魔物コルル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Kind Mamodo, Kolulu</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un gentil Mamodo Kolulu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasashii Mamono Koruru</title>
<summary>A mamodo named Kolulu meets her human partner, Lori, who takes her on as a little sister. When Lori reads a spell from her book, it causes Kolulu to transform into a berserker who wishes to destroy everything. Kolulu cuts down a pillar, causing a car accident before transforming back. Kiyo, seeing the event on the news, investigates the scene. In a nearby park, Lori reads the spell in order to save Kolulu from being run over by a truck. Kiyo and Zatch perceive Kolulu as a threat to bystanders and engage her in battle. Zatch, noticing that Lori and Kolulu are suffering, refuses to fight them. Zatch`s words causes Lori to realize they are not a threat and stops Kolulu from killing Zatch. Kolulu changes back and realizing what has happened reveals that her berserk personality was placed inside her in order to force her to fight in the Mamodo battle. Kolulu asks Kiyo to burn her book and Zatch promises Kolulu he shall become a kind Mamodo king in order to prevent what happened to Kolulu from occurring again.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="11672" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第三の術ジケルド!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Third Spell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La troisième formule</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daisan no Jutsu Jikerudo!</title>
<summary>The next day, Kiyo finds out a new page has become readable, revealing the third spell. Kiyo and Zatch head to a deserted area to practise the third spell "Jikerdor". When cast, nothing occurs and after multiple tries, they decide to give up. On their way home, they are attacked by a Mamodo named Fein and his partner Sebe. Kiyo manages to lead them to an abandoned building to prevent anymore bystanders from becoming injured. The pair manage to overwhelm Kiyo and Zatch with their super-speed spells. Kiyo places his hope on the third spell and uses "Jikerdor" which causes the Mamodo Fein to become magnetized. With Fein`s movements becoming restrained, Kiyo and Zatch are able to burn Fein`s book. Kiyo wondering if all Mamodos are that powerful, tells Zatch he must become stronger.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="11674" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エリート魔物エシュロス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Elite Mamodo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`élite des Mamodos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Elite Mamono Eshuros</title>
<summary>Zatch is helped by a kind man named Shin. Kiyo, noticing that his partner Eshros is holding a mamodo book realizes that Shin is a Mamodo. After secretly following them, they realize that Eshros is actually the Mamodo and that the pair intend to destroy a school tomorrow. Zatch follows the pair believing Shin to be a good person and learns that Eshro is manipulating Shin by making him believe he is fulfilling his mother`s dying wish of becoming a strong-willed person. The next day, Kiyo and Zatch are able to convince Shin that Eshro is manipulating him. Shin realizing his mother wanted him to be like Kiyo, uses his strongest spell to defeat Kiyo and Zatch. Shin then gives Kiyo his book to burn knowing that Eshro is a bad person that does not deserve to be king.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="12312" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無敵フォルゴレ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Invincible Folgore</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’invincible Folgoré</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Muteki Folgore!</title>
<summary>A Mamodo impersonates Kiyo after nailing him to the ceiling and attempts to get information out of Zatch for his book. After fooling Zatch and Suzy into believing he is Kiyo, Kiyo crashes down from the ceiling and the Mamodo reveals his true form. He reveals his name is Kanchome and his partner Parco Folgore came from Italy to defeat Zatch. Two hours later Folgore returns to combat Kiyo and Zatch. Using Poruk, Kanchome transforms into a cannon but it is revealed that his appearance changes but he is still incredibly weak. Kanchome unwilling to lose to Zatch manages to gain a new spell, "Koporuk" which causes him to shrink. Kiyo annoyed, sets up a trap with a frying pan and chocolate and using "Jikerdor" traps Kanchome to the pan. Kiyo decides to let Folgore and Kanchome leave with their book intact.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="13475" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シェリー運命の狂詩曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sherry`s Rhapsody of Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La destinée de Sherry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sherry Unmei no Rhapsody</title>
<summary>Sherry and Brago are in a forest searching for a Mamodo and its partner. While there, Sherry reminisces about the past. In the past, Sherry is going to congratulate her friend Koko when she finds that Koko`s city is on fire. Searching the city, she finds Koko brainwashed by the Mamodo Zofis. In the present time, Sherry and Brago engage in battle with the Mamodo they were searching for. Just then Sherry collapses from exhaustion. Sherry dreams about the time Koko saved her when she tried to commit suicide and how Koko afterwards became her first and best friend. Sherry regains consciousness and uses her new spell "Ion Gravirei" to defeat the Mamodo pair. She collapses soon afterwards with a fever.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="13476" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! ガッシュ対ハイド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rematch: Zatch and Hyde Meet Again</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La revanche: Zatch et Hyde se retrouvent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Gash Tai Hyde</title>
<summary>Eito and Hyde coincidentally find Kiyo and Zatch and wanting revenge, decides to follow them to school. Eito reminisces how he found Hyde`s book and remembers how he wanted power after being bullied. Zatch finds the pair when he smells Eito`s Yellowtail burger and a battle ensues. Hyde amazed at Zatch`s progress flees with Eito. Eito decides to challenge Kiyo and Zatch again by holding Kiyo`s friend`s hostage in a water tower. Kiyo and Zatch gain the advantage during the battle. When Eito sees Hyde`s determination to win, the book glows revealing a new spell. The spell collides with "Rashield" and in the explosion, Eito and Hyde make their escape.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="14605" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おてんばティオとアイドル恵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tomboy and the Popstar</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le garçon manqué et la pop - star !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otenba Tio to Idol Megumi</title>
<summary>Kiyo and Suzy are attending a concert performed by Megumi Oumi. Backstage Megumi and her Mamodo Tia are worried that Maruss, the Mamodo that has been tracking them down to burn their book, may come and disrupt the concert. During the concert, Zatch sneaks in through the back door and meets Tia. Shortly after, Maruss and his book partner appear and start to wreak havoc. Zatch protects her and asks her to bring his book owner Kiyo. Tia, believing Zatch would betray her when his book owner arrives, decides to bring Megumi instead. During the battle, Maruss knocks Megumi unconscious and prepares to burn their book. At that moment, Kiyo intercepts Maruss` attack with "Zaker".</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="14722" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガッシュとティオの新たなる誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Pledge Between Zatch and Tia</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un nouveau pacte entre Zatch et Tia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gash to Tio no Aratanaru Chikai</title>
<summary>Zatch battles with Maruss and gains the advantage. Tia, inspired by Zatch`s courage, decides to help Zatch defeat Maruss. With Maruss defeated, Megumi and Tia prepare to battle Kiyo and Zatch. To their surprise, Kiyo and Zatch wish them well and leave. Tia asks Zatch why he does not fight them and he explains that Tia is a good person, and if she does become the winner of the Mamodo battles, she would be a good and kind ruler. Tia is glad there is someone in the battle she can trust besides Megumi and promises Zatch she will aim to be a kind ruler. Kiyo returns to the concert and notices that Megumi left a note in his pocket promising she will be the one to save Kiyo next time.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="14938" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">冷凍庫対決 不死身のロブノス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Invulnerable Robnos</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Robnos, l’invincible</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reitouko Taiketsu Fujimi no Robnos</title>
<summary>Kiyo comes home and finds a notice demanding Kiyo and Zatch to go to a warehouse for Suzy`s life. Kiyo arrives and meets the enemy Mamodo, Robnos, and his book keeper. A battle ensues and Kiyo is at a disadvantage. During the course of the battle, Kiyo is about unravel Robnos` attacks; He realizes that Robnos` laser attacks are able to reflect off the walls and that there were actually two Robnos firing lasers. Using "Jikerdor" Kiyo pins one of the Robnos down. The two Robnos then fuses into one making "Zaker" infective against him. Kiyo manages to stab a pole into Robnos`s head and with "Zaker" aimed at the pole, overloads the charger in Robnos` head. The pair defeated reveal that they never had Suzy and that a Mamodo that looks like Zatch was spotted in England.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15226" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">清麿のカレーな夏休み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kiyo`s Curry Camping Trip</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le camp d`été saveur curry de Kiyo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiyomaro no Curry na Natsu Yasumi</title>
<summary>Summer Break has begun for Kiyo but he has to fulfill promises he made to people; the promise to help perfect an invisible pitch, catch 500 fish, hunt for a dinosaur, and helping create contact with aliens. With Zatch`s help, he is able to fulfil the promises quickly. The next day, Kiyo goes with his class on a camping trip and Zatch secretly follows him. After cooking curry with his friends, the camp ends in an explosion of fireworks. The next day, Suzy wins a trip to Hong Kong and Kiyo and Zatch are on plane on their way to England. Zatch`s friend is seen stowed away on the plane heading to England.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15355" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">追え! ロンドンのチチもげ魔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">London Calling</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Voyage à Londres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oe! London no Chichi Moge Ma</title>
<summary>In England, Zatch and Kiyo run into Kanchome who asks for their assistance in finding Folgore. Using Zatch`s nose, they track down Folgore by his scent. During their search, Kiyo meets Suzy, Megumi, and Tia who happens to be in England too. Zatch`s nose leads them to a candy shop, a flower shop, and a toy store. The search ends when they find Folgore at a hospital with Suzy. Kiyo thinking that Folgore groped Suzy like he did to the women in the stores he visited, proceeds to attack him with "Zaker". Folgore manages to outrun Kiyo and meets his appointment in the hospital where it is revealed Folgore was buying gifts for sick children. Kiyo, realizing that Folgore is a good person, tells him to make it to the end of the Mamodo battle. While heading to meet his father, Kiyo`s luggage is stolen by a thief.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15533" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪の花咲く呪いの城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dark Lord of the Cursed Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le seigneur des ténèbres et le château maudit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aku no Hana Saku Noroi no Shiro</title>
<summary>Zatch manages to catch the thief whose name is Kory. Kiyo seeing a wound on Kory`s arm takes him along to Kiyo`s father`s university where a doctor can look at it. They enter Kiyo`s father`s office only to find it in shambles. Kiyo notices a flower on the ground and Kory reveals its a flower of the dark lord`s. He reveals that a dark lord is residing in a castle and kidnaps people from the village when they do not meet his demands. Folgore soon arrives and accompanies Kiyo to the castle. Kiyo and Zatch manage to overcome the traps in the castle and reach the final room. Steng, the man living inside the caste, reveals his giant armoured Mamodo Baltro. Seemingly invincible, Kiyo realizes that the Mamodo`s ability is to manipulate armor by using flowers and reveals the Mamodo is actually inside the giant armor. Steng reveals that he has Folgore and Kanchome hostage and if Kiyo attacks, he will kill them.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15658" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大崩壊! バルトロの逆襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flowers of Evil</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les fleurs du mal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Houkai! Baltro no Gyakushuu</title>
<summary>Steng demands Kiyo to surrender his book for Folgore and Kanchome`s lives. Once he has the book, he reveals he has no intention of keeping that promise. Kory suddenly appears and steals Kiyo`s book from Steng and while dodging Baltro`s attacks, returns Kiyo`s book. Folgore and Kanchome meanwhile manage to free themselves allowing Kiyo and Zatch to defeat Steng and Baltro. Kiyo questions Steng why his father was kidnapped, to which Steng replies he was paid to do so. The castle begins to collapse as Steng and Baltro make their escape. Kiyo, Zatch, and Kory manage to rescue everyone in the castle including Kiyo`s father. Steng and Baltro while running away from the castle, meets the Mamodo who hired Steng. The Mamodo fires blue lightning and Baltro`s book is burnt.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15682" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もうひとりのガッシュ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Zatch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un autre Zatch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mouhitori no Gash</title>
<summary>Zatch and Kiyo head towards the forest where Zatch was found. While crossing through a village, the villagers retreat in fear from Zatch`s presence. On the way, they meet Megumi and Tia who reveal that they saw someone who looks like Zatch. In the forest, Zatch attracts snakes with his whistle but is saved by Professor Dartagnian in a fairy suit. Dartagnian reveals that he has been researching the forest since an explosion six months ago. Kiyo and Zatch investigate the site of the explosion. Once there, Zatch suddenly starts to glow gold and when he regains consciousness, regains his memory about his life in the forest. Zatch reveals that another Mamodo who looked like Zatch, attacked him and caused him to lose his memories. Dartagnian who was witnessed the golden light reveals that Kiyo`s book was glowing also. Kiyo opens the book and realizes he can read the fourth spell.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16431" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">踊りつづける緑の戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dancing Mamodo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Mamodo danseur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Odori Tsuzukeru Midori no Senshi</title>
<summary>While practising the fourth spell, Zatch and Kiyo meet a girl named Djem and her Mamodo partner Yopopo. Djem explains that Yopopo`s dance is able to attract Mamodos and that Yopopo is trying to call the Mamodo Kikuropu and his book owner as they attacked Djem`s family. After she finished explaining, Yopopo is missing and Djem realizes that Yopopo found Kikuropu. Yopopo tries to combat Kikuropu without spells but is defeated. He is saved by Kiyo and Zatch and they team up to combat Kikuropu. Zatch`s "Zaker" proves ineffective and Kiyo tries the use the fourth spell "Bao Zakeruga" but nothing occurs. Yopopo`s book is burnt in the midst of the battle and filled with emotions, Kiyo is able to use "Bao Zakeruga" which summons a giant electrical dragon and defeats Kikuropu. Djem tells Yopopo she loves him and cries as he disappears.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16841" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メルメルメ~! 燃えよウマゴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go For It, Ponygon!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On est avec toi Ponygon !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meru Meru Mee! Moeyo Umagon</title>
<summary>Kiyo`s father shows Kiyo a stone tablet that features a Mamodo creature with demonic writings at the bottom and tells Kiyo to phone him if he finds out what the stone tablet is. Kiyo and Zatch return to Japan and while retrieving his baggage, Zatch finds his horse friend. The horse takes an instant dislike to Kiyo but accompanies them home. Kiyo realizes that the horse is a Mamodo when he finds its book. Angered by the Mamodo`s attitude towards him, Kiyo kicks it out of his home. He is then pressured by his friends to find the horse. Kiyo finds the horse trying to find a book owner and Tio explains how lonely it was without a book owner during the Mamodo battles. Kiyo then decides to let the horse stay with him until he can find his book owner. Kiyo then names the horse Mamodo Ponygon.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16874" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自由の旅人アポロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Apollo, the Free Traveler</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Apollo, le voyageur libre comme l`air</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jiyuu no Tabibito Apollo</title>
<summary>After Zatch and Ponygon damage the gate in front of Kiyo`s home, Kiyo goes to the store to buy supplies to fix it. While there, Suzy is almost hit by a car but is saved by a stranger and his Mamodo. Kiyo follows him and realizing that he`s a good person, decides to avoid a battle. The stranger reveals that he knows Kiyo is a book owner. They talk and Kiyo learns that Apollo and his Mamodo is Rops have been avoiding battles whenever possible. Apollo becomes interested in Kiyo`s story and challenges Kiyo to a battle. Apollo tells Kiyo to meet him in two hours with his Mamodo. Zatch when unable to fix the broken gate himself, runs away and wonders whether he should return to the Mamodo world as he is just a nuisance to Kiyo. Zatch meets Lori who reminds him of his goal to become a kind king. Kiyo finds Zatch and they begin their battle with Apollo. Apollo gains the upper hand when he knocks Kiyo`s book out of his hands and threatens to burn it.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="17354" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! 勝利への執念</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Apollo, the Free Traveler: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Apollo, le voyageur libre comme l`air. Deuxième partie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Shouri e no Shuunen</title>
<summary>Apollo allows Kiyo to retrieve his book and warns Kiyo he will not hesitate to burn his book. Kiyo attempts to use "Bao Zakeruga" but nothing occurs once again. Kiyo begins to lose hope but Zatch`s word return Kiyo`s confidence. When Rops is hit by "Zaker", Zatch asks him what kind of king he will be and Rops shows his scarf to Apollo in reply. Apollo reminisces the origin of the scarf and the time his first meeting with Rops; a country has closed itself off from the outside and Apollo who is travelling the world is unable to leave. Apollo meets some kids who are taking care of Rops and asks them for directions out of the country. Apollo led by kids of the village lead him to the country`s boarder but a gate blocks the exit. Rops` book glows and the kids give Apollo the book. When Apollo reads a spell, Rops is able to bring Apollo over the gate. The kids decide to give Apollo Rops and gives him a scarf. Apollo realizes that Rops wishes to be a king of freedom and uses his strongest spell against Kiyo. Kiyo counters with "Bao Zakeruga" and they both become immovable due to exhaustion. That evening, Apollo continues his travels around the world.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="17355" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガッシュの一日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Day with Zatch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une journée avec Zatch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gash no Ichi Nichi</title>
<summary>Zatch is out playing when Naomi chases him down and steals his lunch. Zatch distraught over the loss is comforted by a giant old woman. The woman reveals her name to be Nana Boba and proceeds to tell Zatch she is searching for the Hiromi, the soon to be wife of her son. Zatch volunteers to help her and suggests searching her son`s house. There, Zatch catches Hiromi`s scent and tracks her down. Zatch asks Nana what if Hiromi was someone who wore cheap jewelry and a short skirt, she would beat her up. Zatch spots Hiromi and tells Nana. He then notices the jewelry and short skirt, tries to hold Nana back. When Hiromi enters a bus, Nana runs after it and Zatch tries to stop her. Zatch soon crashes into the bus when it suddenly stops and loses consciousness. When awaken, Zatch sees Nana give Hiromi her old wedding ring and wishes her well. Zatch realizes that Nana was joking about her threat and that she knew her son would choose a good wife.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="18091" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わが息子ダニー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danny Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Danny boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waga Musuko Danny</title>
<summary>A Shemira sculpture is coming to the museum and to describe art to Zatch, Kiyo tells him to imagine a delicious yellow-tail. Meanwhile, A Mamodo named Danny and his book owner Mr. Goldo are delivering the sculpture. Danny meets Zatch while buying fish and fights him thinking Zatch is after his book. Danny stops when Zatch tells him he is at the museum to see the Shemira sculpture. Danny decides show Zatch the sculpture and returns to Mr. Goldo only to find out the sculpture has been stolen by a gang. Zatch follows them through their scent and leads them to a ship. Zatch then gives Ponygon a memo to give to Kiyo. Zatch, Danny, and Mr. Goldo infiltrate the ship. Mr. Goldo is held hostage by the gang but Kiyo arrives and saves him with Zatch`s "Zaker". Once the gang has been apprehended the gang leader attempts to use a truck to escape. He crashes and the cargo falls into the car containing Danny`s book and the Shemira sculpture. Danny manages to hold up the cargo and asks Zatch to destroy it. Zatch does so and the sculpture is saved but Danny`s book is burnt. Before disappearing, Mr. Goldo heals Danny with the spell book and congratulates Danny on a job well done.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="18095" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティオと恵の大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tia and Megumi`s Excellent Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`excellente aventure de Tia et Megumi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tio to Megumi no Dai Houken</title>
<summary>Kiyo, Zatch, Megumi, and Tia made an appointment at go to an amusement park. On the way there, Megumi and Tio enter a clothes shop and meet a person named Maryl Caruno who asks Megumi if they can trade clothes for a while. Megumi agrees and after the trade, Maryl leaves with Megumi`s wallet and book. Megumi chases her but is stopped by a butler who reveals Maryl recently became queen and that assassins are after her. They search for her but Megumi is captured by the assassins who mistook her for the queen. Tia finds Maryl and tells her what has happened to Megumi. Maryl decides to risk her life to save Megumi, but is saved by Tia. The assassins were then captured and Maryl thanks Tia for her help.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="18878" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘! 遊園地バトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Amusement Park Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille au parc d`attractions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitou! Yuuenchi no Battle</title>
<summary>Zatch and Kiyo enter the amusement park. Meanwhile, two Mamodos and their human partner reminisce on how they became allies. Outside, the Mamodo decides to destroy an amusement park ride but is interrupted by Zatch`s "Zaker". Kiyo leads the enemy to an empty part of the park. The pairs Lupa and Purio and Hige and Zoboron overpower Kiyo with their teamwork. Kiyo in the midst of the battle, tells Zatch to fire "Zaker" into the sky. As Kiyo and Zatch are about to be defeated, they are saved by Megumi and Tia`s "Ma Seshield".</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="19612" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガッシュとティオ 最強のコンビネーション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zatch and Tia: A Fierce Combination</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Zatch et Tia: une équipe de choc !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gash to Tio Chiikyou no Combination</title>
<summary>Zatch is still paralysed by Purio`s poison gas attack. With Tia managing to hold off the attacks, Kiyo gets an idea. Using Purio`s slime as glue, Kiyo attaches Zatch to Tia`s back allowing Zatch to move and attack. They manage to defeat and burn Zoboron`s book. Purio who gains a new spell, uses it to create a smokescreen and escapes. Kiyo, Zatch, Megumi, and Tia spend the rest return to the amusement park. Kiyo asks Tia what Zatch was like in the Mamodo world and Tia replies that she does not know Zatch`s family. Later, Megumi takes Kiyo with her to leave Tia and Zatch alone to allow Tia to give Zatch a bentō she made for him. They continue to spend the rest of the day at the park.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="19652" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔境編 カワイイ転校生!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cute Transfer Student</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une jolie nouvelle élève</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makyouhen Kawaii Tenkousei!</title>
<summary>Zatch finds a fragment of a mirror while diving for yellowtail. Kiyo and Zatch befriends a new transfer student, Shion and her cat Nya. Soon they are attacked by a Man and his Mamodo, Cut and Paste, who demands Zatch`s mirror piece. "Zaker" proves ineffective against him as it gets redirected by Cut and Paste`s scissors and "Rashield" is too weak Cut and Paste`s attacks. Cut and Paste use their strongest spell to summon a giant scissor missile. Kiyo and Zatch manage to defeat them by redirecting the scissor towards Cut and Paste with "Jikerdor". In the distance, a mysterious Mamodo pair observe Kiyo and Zatch. Shion with a dark expression asks Zatch if she could have the mirror.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="19861" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔鏡編 詞音の悲しき秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shion`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret de Shion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makyouhen Shion no Kanashiki Himitsu</title>
<summary>Shion and Nya plan to steal the mirror from Zatch. After many failed attempts, Shion decides she must force Zatch into combat to steal the mirror from him. She takes Zatch to a forest and reveals that Nya is a Mamodo. She then proceeds to attack Zatch for the mirror but is saved by Kiyo`s timely arrival. During the battle, Shion reveals that her parents died six months ago and that she wants the mirror in order for Nya to stay with her forever. She reveals a mysterious man told her that if all three pieces of the mirror were gathered, she can be with Nya forever. Zatch decides not to fight Shion and tells her they do not need to fight and that they can trust each other. Zatch then willingly gives her the mirror and Shion accepts.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="19892" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔鏡編 三つのかけらがそろう時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Joining of the Three</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un trio du tonnerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makyouhen Mittsu no Kakera ga Sorou Toki</title>
<summary>Kiyo and Zatch accompany Shion to meet a mamodo named Grisor. Grisor reveals that the demonic mirror has the ability to free a person from the Mamodo battles. He explains that the mirrors must be gathered in a mystical ruin nearby. Grisor meanwhile is revealed to be in contact with his book owner Dr. Hakase. Dr. Hakase reminisces about the first time he met Grisor; Hakase was recently kicked out of an institute and Grisor offers to give him power to get revenge on the institute. Grisor leads Kiyo, Zatch, and Shion to the ruins where the three pieces are then combined into one. At that moment, Grisor makes his escape with the mirror.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21040" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">公園ファイト! ガッシュVS清麿!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle in the Park: Zatch vs. Kiyo!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouen Fight! Gash VS Kiyomaro!?</title>
<summary>Zatch and Kiyo finally have a day to play! Zatch is especially happy because he gets Kiyo all to himself! On the other hand, an over-zealous Zatch is dragging around Kiyo! Eventually the whole gang joins in the fun! Nearing the end of the day, Zatch and K
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21109" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Vの衝撃ベリーメロン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Impact of the V! Very Melon!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">V no Shougeki: Very Melon!!</title>
<summary>Zatch and company proceed through the Devolo Ruins. They stop in a large hall to rest and regain their power from within. As they enjoy a melony snack a new ancient mamodo appears! Victoream is angry that no one notices him, and when they do, he is seethi
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21111" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔鏡編 夕陽に染まった涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunset Soaked in Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un crépuscule baigné de larmes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makyouhen Yuuhi ni Somatta Namida</title>
<summary>Kiyo, Zatch, and Shion chase after Grisor but fail in retrieving the mirror from him in time. Hakase uses the mirror and causes Grisor to grow into a monstrous being which increases his spell power by a hundred fold. They engage in battle but are unable to cause damage to Grisor. When Grisor aims a spell towards Shion, Nya pushes her out of the way but Nya`s book is burnt in the process. Shion holds onto Nya as he disappears from her arms. Grisor then traps Kiyo, Zatch, and Shion on a patch of land by surrounding the area with magma from underground.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21116" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大逆転! 無敵キャンチョメ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invincible Kanchome</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’invincible Kanchomé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Gyakuten! Muteki Kyanchome</title>
<summary>After being severely injured by Bago, Folgore and Kanchome retreat. Rushka arrives to try Kanchome and her sheep but is kicked by Fredo. Kanchome seeing Rushka regains the will to fight. At that moment, the book glows and Folgore is able to read the third spell, "Dika Poruk". The third spell causes Kanchome to seemingly become an invincible giant but in reality, a hologram of Kanchome is actually being projected. While Bago and Fredo are distracted, Folgore runs through fire to reach Fredo. Folgore is able to grab and burn Fredo`s book. After Kanchome says goodbye to Rushka and everyone at the circus, he and Folgore end up at a harbor. Kanchome seeing candy aboard a boat, boards it. At that moment, the boat heads towards the South Pole with Kanchome on it.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21158" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛をつらぬけ! 香港純愛娘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle in Hong Kong</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat à Hong-kong</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai o Tsuranuke! Hong Kong Jun`ai Musume</title>
<summary>Li-en asks her father to return Wonrei to her but he refuses and sends her to Japan. On the way to the movies, Zatch and Kiyo`s book is stolen by Li-en. She then returns their book and tells Kiyo that her father is a mafia boss and that he captured her Mamodo Wonrei. She asks Kiyo to help her free Wonrei. They travel to Hong Kong to an island where Li-en`s father`s mafia keep their treasure and weapons. After defeating some men on the way, they take an elevator to the top of the island where Wonrei is imprisoned. At the top of the island however is the Mamodo Zabas and his partner Galliont are awaiting for the elevator`s arrival.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21159" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バリーからの挑戦状</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invitation to a Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`invitation à un duel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bari Kara no Chousenjou</title>
<summary>A mamodo named Bari and his partner Gustav defeat a Mamodo. Bari feeling unsatisfied in his battles, decides to go to Japan where a strong Mamodo named Zatch resides. Bari finds Zatch and tells Zatch they shall battle in a factory three hours from now. Zatch and Kiyo arrive to the factory where they learn that there are still civilians in the factory. Zatch manages to save the civilian while Kiyo distracts Bari`s attention. As Bari is about to strike Kiyo down, he hesitates due to Kiyo`s eyes. Bari prepares to finish Kiyo off but Zatch manages to stop him in time. With no distractions, Kiyo and Zatch prepare to face Bari and Gustav.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21160" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔鏡編 灼熱の最終決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Mirror Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ultime bataille du miroir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makyouhen Shakunetsu no Saishuu Kessen</title>
<summary>Kiyo and Zatch continue their battle with Grisor. During the battle, Hakase explains the true origins of the mirror; the mirror was stolen by Grisor for the Mamodo battles but during his travel to the human world, it broke into three pieces and scattered across the world. An attack from Grisor knocks Zatch unconscious. As he prepares to knock Kiyo and Zatch into the magma, Shion knocks the mirror out of Hakase`s hands cracking it. Zatch regains consciousness and uses "Bao Zakeruga" to defeat Grisor and the mirror is destroyed in the process. The next day, Shion decides to move in order to become a stronger person without being completely dependent on a person for help.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21161" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メルメルメ~! ウマゴン危機一髪!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ponygon`s Close Call</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`appel désespéré de Ponygon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meru Meru Mee! Umagon Kiki Ippatsu!?</title>
<summary>Ponygon after seeing Zatch depressed about his lost goes and searches for his book owner. Ponygon finds a man named Doronma who resembles Ponygon and assumes he is his bookowner. Zatch following Ponygon`s scent is invited alongside Ponygon to visit Doronma`s house. Doronma asks Zatch and Ponygon to help him in his plan to steal from the rich and give to the poor. Zatch and Ponygon agree to help him and after robbing multiple jewellery stores, Doronma proposes to steal a diamond from a mansion. Zatch and Ponygon assist him in the robbery but end up tripping every alarm. Doronma is later arrested by the police. When Ponygon shows him the book, Doronma replies that he saw a fly in the book and that he was unable to read it.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21322" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブルァアア!! 紳士怒りのチャーグル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burrah! Victoream`s Anger!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Buraaa!! Shinshi Ikari no Chaaguru</title>
<summary>With their strength seriously weakened, everyone must work as a team to maximize their few chances to attack Victoream. Kiyo crafts a tricky plan to take him down but will Victoream catch on before they can pull the wool over his eyes?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21332" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍びよる邪悪! 石版の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of the Stone Tablets</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère de la pierre gravée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinobi Yoru Jaaku! Sekiban no Nazo</title>
<summary>Kiyo while shopping with Suzy finds a stone tablet similar to the one from before. Kiyo buys the stone and brings it home. He decides to use open minded tests on the stone while leaving the scientific methods to his father. Meanwhile, Zatch, Tia, and Ponygon decide to train for the tougher Mamodo battles ahead. Elsewhere, a strange man and his Mamodo Kido are on a plane heading to Japan to meet with Zatch and Tia. At night time, a mysterious Mamodo steals the stone tablet from Kiyo`s room and at the same time in England, the stone piece Kiyo`s father is studying is also stolen. Elsewhere, a masked Mamodo stares at his collection of stone tablets.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21333" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! ガッシュVSナオミちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Collision: Zatch vs. Naomi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`affrontement: Zatch contre Naomi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Gash VS Naomi-chan</title>
<summary>Zatch is haunted by a nightmare about Naomi. The next day he decides to challenge Naomi to a duel, and if he wins, Naomi will have to stop bullying him. Kiyo and his friends meanwhile visit the zoo. There they learn that an African Lion by the name of Gabriel has escaped from the zoo. Back with Zatch, Zatch loses the first and second competition against Naomi. In the third competition, Zatch is left in a pit-hole and Vulcan is tied up on a pole. Later one of the playground kids tell Zatch that Naomi has become stranded on a cliff. Zatch arrives and sees that a lion is with Naomi on the cliff. Wanting to help Naomi, Zatch climbs down but becomes stranded on a tree branch. Naomi seeing Zatch in danger climbs up the cliff and saves Zatch from the lion. Shortly after, the lion is captured and Zatch`s dream about Naomi being the lizard queen comes true.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21334" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">非情なる敵ゼオンとデュフォー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coldhearted Foes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des ennemis au cœur glacial</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hijounaru Teki Zeon to Dyufo</title>
<summary>Zatch has a fever but decides to accompany Kiyo to school anyways. Kiyo and Zatch get into an argument and Zatch collapses from the fever. After placing Zatch in the care of the school nurse, Kiyo finds Apollo at school. Apollo tells Kiyo that after Rops` book was burned, he became the president of his father`s company. He then reveals that the Mamodo who burnt his was someone that resembles Zatch. He reveals that in Holland, the Zatch look-alike ad his partner Dufort mercilessly defeated them in battle. Apollo reveals that the Zatch look-alike`s name is Zeno. Kiyo promises that he will defeat them for what they done to Rops. Zatch wakes up from a nightmare about Zeno and visits Kiyo who tells Zatch to become a kind king.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21335" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガッデーム!! 怒りの水龍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">So Giaku! The Water Dragon of Rage!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">God Damn!! Ikari no Suiryuu</title>
<summary>Penny’s persistent water spells are relentless and Zatch and Kiyo are suffering terribly, while Penny delights in their misfortune. Observant Kiyo realizes that the reason Penny is filled rage is because Zatch doesn`t remember her from the mamodo world. H
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21336" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋の鉄拳! ゴウ・バウレン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle in Hong Kong: Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat à Hong Kong, deuxième partie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Tekken! Gou Bauren</title>
<summary>After exiting the elevator, they meet Zabas who reveals his intention to kill Wonrei while he is in his cell. Kiyo and Zatch decide to distract Zabas while Li-en tries to free Wonrei. Wonrei reveals no intention of escaping fearing that Li-en would be hurt in the Mamodo battle. When Zabas is about to attack Li-en, Wonrei escapes from his cell and defeats Zabas. Zatch asks Wonrei what kind of king he would be and he replies a king which protects all. Li-en and Wonrei leave but Zabas stands up ready to battle. Kiyo and Zatch defeat Zabas with the fifth spell, "Zakeruga", a more powerful and concentrated version of "Zaker". Li-en and Wonrei run into her father. He allows their relationship once seeing Wonrei`s determination to protect Li-en and gives them a boat to leave the island.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21337" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛しのガッシュ! 私はパティ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Beloved Zatch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon Zatch adoré</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itoshi no Gash! Watashi wa Patie!</title>
<summary>Kane, Yamanaka and Iwashima challenge Kiyo to a series of physical contest, wagering sumptuous side dishes from the school lunch on each event. Meanwhile, Penny, a cute girl mamodo, and Uri, her Book’s owner, arrive, looking for Zatch.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21338" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナゾナゾ博士と12人の刺客(マジョスティックトゥエルブ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dr. Riddles and the Majestic Twelve</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Docteur Enigme et les Douze Majestic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazonazo-hakase to Majestic Twelve</title>
<summary>Kiyo and Zatch think of ways to get stronger until they are interrupted by Kido and his book keeper Dr. Riddles, who challenges Kiyo and Zatch to a battle. He reveals that the Majestic Twelve will be the one to fight him. Dr. Riddles then asks Kiyo to solve a riddle. After he answers correctly, Dr. Riddles and the Majestic Twelve leave. Dr. Riddles returns later and challenges Kiyo to a Mamodo battle. He reveals that if Kiyo defeats him, he will reveal the secret of the book. Kiyo and Zatch are at the disadvantage against Dr. Riddles. Dr. Riddles gives Kiyo a hint about the books and Kiyo realizes the truth about the books; the spells in the books are actually manifestations of the Mamodo`s power. Kiyo tells Zatch to believe in the power that is inside him. At that moment, the book glows and Kiyo uses the sixth spell, "Rauzaruk".</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21339" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">発動! 第六の術ラウザルク!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sixth Spell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La sixième formule</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsudou! Dai Roku no Jutsu Rauzeruku!</title>
<summary>"Rauzaruk" surrounds Zatch in a rainbow coloured aura but its effect is unknown. While trying to figure out the effects of "Rauzaruk" the rainbow aura disappears and the effects of the spell wear off. Kiyo and Zatch become overwhelmed by Kido`s army of clones. Kiyo realizes that the power Zatch wished for must be the spell`s effect. Casting "Rauzaruk" again, Zatch is able to defeat all of Kido`s clones. Zatch reveals that he wanted power to protect Kiyo. Kiyo realizes that "Rauzaruk" increases Zatch`s strength, speed, and defense greatly and with that power, they defeat Dr. Riddles and Kido. Dr. Riddles reveals that the latent powers inside Mamodos awaken when they mature spiritually or when the book owner`s feelings reach them. Dr. Riddles then tells Kiyo that the evil one is gathering up minions and that Kiyo`s help will be needed when the time comes.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21340" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャンチョメ, 兄ちゃんになる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother Kanchome</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Grand frère Kanchomé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyanchome, Nii-chan ni Naru</title>
<summary>Kanchome while waiting for Folgore to sign autographs, sees some candy in the back of a truck and climbs into it. The truck`s door closes and Kanchome is driven away. Kanchome ends up at a circus and while wandering around, finds a girl named Rushka. Kanchome then volunteers to be her big brother. He follows her back to her farm where Kanchome learns from her guardian that Rushka`s parents died and the closest thing she has to a family are sheep. Soon after, a Mamodo named Bago and his partner Fredo steals all the sheep on the farm. Kanchome follows the Mamodo in an attempt and return the sheep for Rushka. Folgore finds Kanchome on the way and decides to help Kanchome with his battle. Folgore and Kanchome end up at the cave where Bago and Fredo await.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21341" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">果てなき死闘 ガッシュVSバリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zatch vs. Bari</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Zatch contre Bari</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatenaki Shitou Gash VS Bari</title>
<summary>Kiyo and Zatch are overpowered by Bari`s spells. Kiyo and Zatch resort to their strongest spell "Bao Zakeruga" but Bari is able to block it. Kiyo is unable to move or use spells after using "Bao Zakeruga" thus forcing Zatch to fight Bari hand to hand. Bari hesitates when he sees Zatch`s eyes causing Bari to be knocked down. Zatch moves Kiyo to a safe place and continues his battle. Kiyo attempts to help Zatch by running a Loader into the factory to collapse the ceiling onto them. Bari goes after Kiyo to burn Zatch`s book. As he looks into Zatch`s eyes again, he stops and asks why. Gustav asks Zatch what kind of king he wants to be to which he replies a kind king. Bari finds the idea ridiculous and challenges Zatch whether a kind king or a powerful king will be fit for the throne. He leaves sparing Zatch`s book.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21342" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪原鳴動!! 王者の風格</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rumble in the Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Agitation dans la neige</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Setsugen Meidou! Ouja no Fuukaku</title>
<summary>Sherry and Brago are searching for a Mamodo in the snowy mountains. They come across an injured old man and his grandson, Jeff, who are being attacked by a bear. Sherry and Brago use their spell to scare the bear away and Brago then carries the man back to his house. The man explains that the bear killed the Jeff`s parents and they intended to get revenge with it. Brago leaves to wander around the mountain. Sherry`s butler comments that Brago has changed into a strict and kind person, a perfect king. Brago returns with the bear`s body and tells Jeff he must become a stronger person. The next day, a group of men threaten to bulldoze Jeff`s and his grandpa`s home. Brago defeats them and in vengeance, they detonate the explosives hidden in the mountain. An avalanche occurs but is stopped by Brago and his new spell "Dioga Gravidon".</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21343" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対絶命! 姿なき狩人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Invisible Hunter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chasseur invisible !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Zetsumei! Sugata Naki Hunter</title>
<summary>Zatch loses at a lottery to win a yellowtail fish and a man decides to take pity on Zatch and gives him his tickets to an onsen. At the onsen, Kiyo finds a note in his room revealing the location of a secret onsen and an all you can eat yellow tail buffet. Upon arriving at the location, Kiyo realizes that it`s a trap and they attacked by a Mamodo named Baransha and her human partner Garza. Kiyo and Zatch are at a disadvantage since Baransha can attack from afar and become invisible. As the battle drags on, Kiyo uses ginkgo nuts` strong scent in order to track down the invisible Baransha. Kiyo and Zatch gain the upper hand with "Bao Zakeruga" but Garza and Baransha manage to escape by jumping into the river.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21344" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正義のヒーローカマキリジョー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Praying Mantis Joe: Hero of Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Joe la mante religieuse: opération super justicier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seigi no Hero Kamikiri Joe</title>
<summary>Zatch asks Kiyo to take him to a Praying Mantis Joe show at the mall. Kiyo refuses and Zatch leaves to go watch it with Umagon. Zatch meets Suzy and the teacher`s wife, referred to as Wife, who are both also heading to the mall. Once there, Suzy and Wife realize the merchandise they wanted that was on sale was fake. After watching the Praying Mantis Joe show, Zatch notices that Suzy, Wife, Ponygon, and many kids were upset about the false merchandise being sold. He decides to ask Praying Mantis Joe to help with the merchandise problems. The actor of Praying Mantis Joe tells the kids he is unable to do anything and Zatch with the kids leave determined to face the store manager. The store manager calls his bodyguard to deal with the kids. At that moment, Praying Mantis Joe arrives and is severely beaten by the bodyguard. Wife then throws an unconscious Joe onto the bodyguard knocking him unconscious. The store manager is then forced to give the real merchandise to the costumers.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21345" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強襲!! 仮面の悪魔ロード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Masked Mamodo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Mamodo masqué</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoushuu! Kamen no Akuma Lord</title>
<summary>Suzy comes to visit Zatch and Kiyo, but seems to be under a hypnotic spell. She brings an invitation to a party from a mysterious stranger named Milordo-Z. Kiyo deduces that the invitation is a trick to get them into battle
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21600" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛攻ダルモス! 砂上の決死戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fierce Attack of Dalmos! The Battle on Top of the Sand!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moukou Dalmos! Sajou no Death Match</title>
<summary>Through teamwork, Victoream is successfully defeated. The team decides to withdraw, but two more ancient mamodo, Dalmos and Laila stop them in their tracks! Kiyo tells everyone else to escape and entrusts Zatch’s spell book with Tia. It seems like it’s al
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22157" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パティ逆襲!! とき放たれた刺客たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Penny`s Revenge! Assassins on the Loose!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Patty Gyakushuu!! Toki Hanatareta Shikaku-tachi</title>
<summary>Penny has brought 3 ancient mamodo warriors from a thousand years ago to help her defeat Zatch. Kiyo notices that the mamodo’s partners seem odd. Penny explains to them that Milordo-Z has erased their emotions making them the ultimate fighting machines!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22158" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">希望の光・サイフォジオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light of Hope, Saifogeo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kibou no Hikari: Saifogeo</title>
<summary>Tia and Megumi help defeat Penny’s mamodo warriors with their new spells, Giga La Seoshi, an enhanced shield and Saifogeo, an amazing spell of recovery that helps Kiyo regain his strength from within!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22159" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱砂の闘いブラゴVS静寂の三闘士(サイレント・ルーラー)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle on the Sands: Brago vs. The Silent Rulers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nessa no Tatakai: Brago VS Silent Ruler</title>
<summary>Zatch, Kiyo, Tia and Megumi chase off Penny and her remaining mamodo warriors. Meanwhile in an African savannah, Brago and Sherry battle the “Silent Rulers,” three infamous mamodo feared a thousand years ago for their devastating synchronized attack.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22163" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">打倒ロード! それぞれの決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defeat Milordo-Z! Each Person`s Resolve!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Datou Lord! Sorezore no Ketsui</title>
<summary>Kiyo is immersing himself in his father’s archaeology texts and is closing in on the location of Milordo-Z’s whereabouts. Megumi and Tia also help, but Megumi is feeling the pressure of her busy life as a high school student and pop star. When Ponygon goe
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22164" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">突入デボロ遺跡! キャンチョメ大作戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Breaking into Deboro`s Ruins! Kanchome`s Battle!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsunyuu Deboro Iseki! Kanchome Daisakusen!!</title>
<summary>In the midst of their journey to the ruins, Zatch, Kiyo, Megumi, Tia, and Ponygon run into Kanchome and Folgore, who were also convinced by Dr. Riddles to join in the quest to defeat Milordo-Z. Together they proceed into the ruins where they encounter Gel
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22165" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">攻防! 激流の迷宮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Labyrinth`s Angry Torrent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koubou! Gekiryuu no Labyrinth</title>
<summary>Gantz, another thousand year-old mamodo suddenly appears behind Kanchome and Folgore! Zatch and Kiyo overwhelm Alm with their synchronized movements but surprisingly, Alm rebounds to bark commands at his partner. Kiyo is shocked to find out that not all m
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22205" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メルメルメ~!! ウマゴン電光石火</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ponygon`s Lightning Speed!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Merumerume~!! Umagon Denkousekka</title>
<summary>Ponygon has returned with his partner Kafk Sunbeam to help Zatch and Kiyo! Kafk reads the first spell “Shudoruk,” and Ponygon morphs, armor-clad and battle-ready. He dashes towards Dalmos and fearlessly pounces on him, all the while effortlessly evading h
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26353" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">83</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱き思いよとどけ! 第7の術ザグルゼム!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reach, Burning Feelings! The Seventh Spell, Zaguruzemu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atsuki Omoi yo Todoke! Dai 7 no Jutsu Zaguruzemu!!</title>
<summary>Zofis had attained infinite power with a mask linked to the Stone of Moonlight in Demolt’s chamber. Zofis loses his impregnable shield after the Stone of Moonlight is destroyed. But even so, Zofis pulls out his trump card…Koko his partner, Sherry’s former
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36085" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">91</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナオミちゃんを追跡せよ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Follow Naomi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naomi-chan o Tsuiseki seyo!!</title>
<summary>After Kiyo goes to school, Zatch volunteers to do the shopping for Kiyo`s mother. Ponygon accompanies him, and on the way, he notices that the park has become a mess. One of the playground children notices Zatch and tells him it is his fault.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36086" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">守り抜け! 約束の赤い魔本</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Spell Book of Promise!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamorinuke! Yakusoku no Akai Mahon</title>
<summary>In their short time together Ponygon and Kafk unlock their second spell and win their first battle! Exhausted and relieved, they collapse. Laila brings back a fragment of the Stone of Moonlight to help restore their strength. She also warns them that thei
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36087" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すばらしきかなマジョスティック12</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wonderful Majestic Twelve Return</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subarashikikana Majestic Twelve</title>
<summary>The Ancient mamodo begin their attack on Apollo and the others. Zatch, Kiyo, Sunbeam, and Ponygon arrive just in time to help Tia. A showdown is about to happen when Dr. Riddles quickly summons his twelve super-powered friends!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36088" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">89</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新春スペシャル 華麗なるV(ブイ)よ再び!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Year Special, The Magnificent V Appears Again!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinshun Special: Kareinaru V yo Futatabi!!</title>
<summary>Kiyo and Zatch have at last returned from the fierce battle in the ruins. They are spending a peaceful New Years Day together with Ponygon when Folgore and Kanchomé visit them. Kiyo shrinks back, and grudgingly invites them in. Folgore tells them of a New
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36089" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">84</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">凶獣デモルト最終決戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evil Beast Demoruto, Final Deciding Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoujuu Demoruto Saishuu Kessen!!</title>
<summary>Zatch’s Seventh Spell Zagurzem appears in his spell book! Kiyo realizes it is a powerful spell that charges up electricity and attracts Zatch’s successive spells to the spot initially hit. He firmly believes that Demolt can be defeated by hammering him wi
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36090" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ありがとう僕の王様 ミコルオ・マ・ゼガルガ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dr. Riddles, You`ll Always Be My King</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arigatou Boku no Ou-sama: Mikoruo Ma Zegaruga</title>
<summary>Dr. Riddles` new strategy seems to baffle Belgim, and the team uses this to their advantage. But a surprising miscalculation ends up injuring Dr. Riddles. With the Doctor injured, Kedo utilizes all the wisdom that the Doctor has taught him and comes up wi
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36091" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">90</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ただいま... そして嵐のテストバトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I am Back...And Then a Tempest Test Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tadaima... Soshite Arashi no Test Battle</title>
<summary>Kiyo heads to school, and Zatch tries to follow. Zatch accidentally gets his toy Vulcan stuck on a track that drives away and chases after it. Suzy tries to tell Kiyo "Welcome back" but is constantly interrupted by Kiyo`s friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36092" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">78</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう戻らない! レイラの孤独な闇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Won`t Go Back! Laila`s Dark Solitude</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Modaranai! Reira no Kodoku na Yami</title>
<summary>The reunited team agree to leave Zofis to Sherry and Brago. Laila and Albert return. Kiyo and Zatch are happy to see her, but she sends a spell toward them. Kiyo knows that Laila is betraying them out of fear, so he attempts to regain her trust!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36093" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">94</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">異世界の扉! ガッシュVSブラゴ最強対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Door of the Strange World! Strongest Duel, Zatch vs. Brago</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isekai no Tobira! Gash VS Brago Saikyou Taiketsu</title>
<summary>Sherry reveals that Nicholas and Majirou attacked first. In a flashback, Brago calls Nicholas and Majirou weak and leaves, but counters when they attempt to attack him. Zatch angered by Brago, begins their battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36094" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">95</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">異世界放浪! 襲いかかる鉄の軍団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exile in the Strange World! Attack from the Army!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isekai Hourou! Osoikakaru Tetsu no Gundan</title>
<summary>Maestro tells his servant to call Brago in to talk. He tells Brago how in the In-between World, Mamodos with spell books are able to cast spells without their human partners.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36095" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">98</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">異世界大決闘! ガッシュ・ブラゴ二大奥義炸裂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Duel in the Strange World, Zatch and Brago`s Two Great Mysterious Explosions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isekai Daikettou! Gash, Brago Nidaiougi Sakuretsu</title>
<summary>Sherry and Brago continue their attack on Maestro`s barrier in order to test the limits of the coil. They find out "Ion Gravirei" is the limit which the coils can handle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36096" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">103</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">テッドの哀歌 風の中の少女 運命の再開</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ted`s Blues, The Girl in the Wind, Fate`s Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ted no Aika, Kaze no Naka no Shoujo, Unmei no Saikai</title>
<summary>Ted is bent on finding Cherish, the only mamodo that he looks upon as a family. One day in the city, he smells something that is suspected to be her. Ted and Zatch search everywhere and every suspected people, but it is eventually a mistake. However, Ted deeply believes that one day he will find her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36097" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">97</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">異世界の覇者! 復讐に牙むくマエストロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Leader of the Strange World, Vengeance of the Fanged Maestro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isekai no Hassha! Fukushuu ni Kibamuku Maestro</title>
<summary>Kiyo, Zatch, and Brago battle Maestro. Kiyo realizes that Maestro`s power involves magnetism and that he is using the coils at the side of the battlefield to increase the powers of his spells.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36098" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">99</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と青春のモンモン先生 清麿悲劇の惨敗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Love and Youth of Mr. Mommon, Kiyo`s Disastrous Defeat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Seishun no Monmon-sensei: Kyomaru Higeki no Zanpai</title>
<summary>Kiyo after managing to lose Zatch and Ponygon goes to school. Once there, the teacher Touyama tries to give Kiyo a failing grade by asking him what is his cat`s name. Kiyo manages to figure it out, but Touyama reveals he has a secret weapon
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36099" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶体絶命! 立ちふさがる四天王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Four Supreme Mamodo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Zetsumei! Tachifusagaru Shitennou</title>
<summary>The stairway collapses and the team is scattered but they manage to split up into three groups and escape into separate paths into the ruin. Little do they know that each path will lead to a powerful Ancient mamodo lying in wait for them!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36100" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">100</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もげよフォルゴレ! 愛と悲しみのバグパイプ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Grope It, Folgore! The Bagpipe of Love and Sorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moge yo Folgore! Ai to Kanashimi no Bagpipe</title>
<summary>Nicolas is upset about Majirou`s book becoming burnt. When he plays his depression through his bagpipes, it causes anyone who hears it to become sad too. Folgore volunteers to bring Nicholas to Italy to rid his sadness.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36101" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">77</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シェリー気高き輪舞 炸裂バベルガ・グラビドン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Return of Sherry and Brago</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sherry Kedakaki Rondo, Sakuretsu Baberuga Grabidon</title>
<summary>Zofis summons his Ancient mamodo army to take down Zatch and his team. Weak and out of strength from within, the team finds themselves in a tight spot.  Suddenly a familiar spell rings out…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36102" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">閃光乱舞! 孤高の戦士パムーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pamoon, the Celestial Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkou Ranbu! Kokou no Senshi Pamoon</title>
<summary>Kedo has returned to the mamodo world.  Dr. Riddles quickly picks himself up and leads the way further into the ruin. Kiyo’s team finally encounters the powerful hidden mamodo who has been controlling the deadly stars. His name is Pamoon. While Kiyo is sc
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36103" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">92</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">我が心のキッド ナゾナゾ博士新たなる誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Dear Kid, Dr. Riddles` New Vow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waga Kokoro no Kid, Nazonazo Hakase Aratanaru Chikai</title>
<summary>Zatch is making a new Vulcan 300 when Tia comes over. Elsewhere, Dr. Riddles is depressed over the lost of Kido. Folgore and Kanchome, while in America, decide to visit Dr. Riddles. Once there, the Majestic Twelve ask Folgore to help cheer up Dr. Riddles.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36104" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">93</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">異世界からの声! 命運つきた魔物たち!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Voice from the Strange World! The Fate of the Demons!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isekai Kara no Koe! Meiun Tsukita Mamono-tachi!!</title>
<summary>In a mysterious place, a Mamodo stands above the symbol of a book and announces a message, to the contestants of the Mamodo battle, to assemble at the light.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36105" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">101</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる脅威 風を語る少年 バオウ抹殺!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Threat, The Boy Who Talks of the Wind, Baou Eradication!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata Naru Kyoui, Kaze o Kataru Shounen, Baou Massatsu!</title>
<summary>The sudden appearance of a mamodo named Arth and his partner, Ellie. They approach to Zatch and Kiyo because they want to eliminate people who know how to use the spell of Boa Zakeruga. However, Kiyo does not even understand the real threat and meaning of the spell of Boa Zakeruga. Facing with Arth’s strong attach, Kiyo is no match for him! Fortunately, Ted and Jido come to help in time.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36106" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">102</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月夜の動乱 友情の拳 アース一撃必殺!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moonlit Night`s Disturbance! Fist of Friendship! Earth`s One-hit Certain Kill!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukiyo no Douran, Yuujou no Kobushi, Earth Ichigeki Hissatsu!</title>
<summary>In order to protect their new friend Zatch, Ted and Jido desperately enhance their strength and skills. This surprised Arth. Zatch joins the fight even though he is injured, and he uses the spell of Boa Zakeruga. However, his spell of Boa Zakeruga does not show its real power unexpectedly!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36107" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">82</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わがままパティ 惜別のスオウ・ギアクル!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Selfish Penny, Suou Giakuru of Parting Regrets!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wagamama Patty: Sekibetsu no Suou Giakuru!!</title>
<summary>Penny &amp; Uri and Byonko &amp; Alvin save Zatch and the others from a tight spot! At First they participated in the battle as Zofis’ underlings, but they see the error in their ways.. They rebel against Zofis in the same way as Laila did and appear once again b
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36108" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">96</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">異世界決闘! シェリーのいないブラゴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Duel in the Strange World, When Brago`s Without Sherry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isekai Kettou! Sherry no Inai Brago</title>
<summary>In the Human World, Dr. Riddles, Sunbeam, Folgore and Kanchome are at the structures, investigating them. In the In-between World, Kiyo, Zatch, and Ponygon arrive at the castle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36109" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">85</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷えるシェリー 断ち切れぬ絆!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Perplexed Sherry, The Bond That Cannot be Severed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoeru Sherry: Tachikirenu Kizuna!</title>
<summary>Sherry has lost her power from within and is unable to use spells. She has also lost all will to fight. Brago forsakes her and attempts to confront Zofis just with brute strength. However, nothing is accomplished and Brago just gets hurt. Sherry looks at
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36110" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">打ち砕け! 封印千年 屈辱の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Free Yourself from a Thousand Years of Pain!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchikudake! Fuuin Sennen, Kutsujoku no Kioku</title>
<summary>Pamoon laughs off Zatch and Ponygon’s attacks. He dismisses them as naïve. As Pamoon fires off countless attacks, Zatch counters each blow, determined to stop a battle that’s waged out of fear and intimidation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36111" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">76</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃げ道なし!! 卑劣なるゾフィス再臨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Escape! The Wicked Zofis Returns!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nigemichi Nashi!! Hiretsunaru Zofis Sairin</title>
<summary>The team realizes that Zofis has been using the fear of being imprisoned in stone to manipulate the Ancient mamodo. Zatch begs Pamoon to stop fighting and offers his friendship. Seeing Zatch fight bravely gives Pamoon the courage to break free from his fe
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36112" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走!? ティオの告白大作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tia`s Plan to Confess!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou!? Tio no Kokuhaku Daisakusen</title>
<summary>Back at base, Dr. Riddles talks about meeting Sherry and Brago. All the other mamodo are shocked to hear that Zatch and Kiyo have battled Brago and lived!  Tia wants to thank Zatch for saving her earlier but her shyness prevents her from telling him how s
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36113" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">79</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">うごめく悪魔 最後の四天王登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wriggling Fiend, The Final of the Four Heavenly Kings Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ugomeku Akuma: Saigo no Shitennou Tanjou</title>
<summary>Laila tries to remember the secret passage to the room with the Moonstone. After remembering Zofis` song, she remembers that the door is behind the rightmost statue. Megumi`s team meanwhile end up in a room with three statue heads.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36114" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一千年の悲しき呪縛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tragic Curse of a Thousand Years</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Issennen no Kanashiki Jubaku</title>
<summary>Kiyo and Zatch engage in a fierce battle with Alm and Gelios. They counter Alm’s strongest spell with Bao Zakeruga and eventually overpower the ancient mamodo duo with the help of Tia and Megumi. As Alm’s spell book burns he tells Zatch some very importan
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36115" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">撃破せよ! 邪悪なるゾフィスの野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zofis` Evil Desires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekihaseyo! Jaaku Naru Zofis no Yabou</title>
<summary>The team leave their base and head toward the ruins. They are able to proceed smoothly into the ruin but are stopped by Zofis on a precarious stairway that spans over a lake of lava. After a heated exchange, Zofis proceeds to demolish the stairway!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36116" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">81</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝機を求めて... 湧きあがれふたりの闘志</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seeking the Light to Victory... The Surging Two`s Fighting Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari o Motomete... Wakiagare Futari no Toushi</title>
<summary>Vile’s mind is not being controlled and it seems he supports Zofis and defeats mamodo just for fun. Zatch and the others are outraged at his self-indulgent and arrogant attitude. They make repeated desperate attacks against Demolt, but Zatch and the other
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36117" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛すればこそ... うなれ哀しみの猛虎爆裂拳(ラオウ・ディバウレン)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Roar of Rao Diboren!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aisureba Koso... Unare Kanashimi no Raou Dibauren</title>
<summary>Everyone is having a hard time trying to defeat their respective “Supreme Mamodo.” Zatch’s team is trying to figure out the location of their hidden mamodo. Belgim E.O is terrorizing Dr. Riddles’ team! Lien’s team is trying to defeat Tsao-lon a mamodo ski
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36118" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">86</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆襲のゾフィス 友情の最終決戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zofis` Counterattack, Friendship`s Last Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakushuu no Zofis, Yuujou o Saishuu Kessen!!</title>
<summary>Sherry resolves once again to rescue Koko from Zofis’ mind control. She crushes one of Zofis’ arms with a gravity spell and sets things in motion for a counterattack! However, Zofis attacks utilizing his mobility, he brings Sherry and Brago to a standstil
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36119" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌え歌え! 恐怖のベルギム・E・O</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sing for Your Lives! The Terrible Belgim E. O.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utae Utae! Kyoufu no Berugimu E O</title>
<summary>Belgim E.O. is very bored after being imprisoned in stone for a thousand years. He orders Dr. Riddles’ team to perform for him, if they impress him, he says he will them pass through an entryway, if they bore him, he will destroy them!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36120" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">87</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思いよココに届け! シェリー渾身のディオガグラビドン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thoughts to Reach Koko! Sherry`s Full Strength Dioga Gurabidon!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoi yo Koko ni Todoke! Sherry Konshin no Diogagurabidon!!</title>
<summary>Working together with Laila, Dr. Riddles and the rest, the combined forces of Kiyo and the others overpower Zofis with teamwork. Kiyo and Zatch mercilessly launch an attack on Zofis and Kiyo attempts to land the finishing blow. But Sherry and Brago interf
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36121" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">80</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">野獣デモルト! 戦慄の雄叫び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monster Demoruto! The Hair-Raising Roar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yajuu Demoruto! Senritsu no Otakebi</title>
<summary>Kiyo and company stand unable to move while they face Demolt, the last of the Supreme Mamodo. Laila, who has cast off Zofis’ control, teams up with Kiyo and the others, she notices that there’s a change in Demolt’s attacks. He was infamous for only being
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36122" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">88</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シェリー・ブラゴ 新たなる門出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sherry, Brago, A New Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sherry, Brago: Aratanaru Katode</title>
<summary>Zofis no longer has the upperhand and attempts to distract Sherry by tossing Koko down a cliff. However, Sherry anticipates this and catches Koko in midair averting a tragedy. Zofis is now at the end of his rope, he has his spell book taken way and is for
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36504" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">104</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライバルはアイドル 恋の火花 鈴芽の勝利??</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Rival is an Idol, A Spark of Love, Suzy`s Victory??</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rival wa Idol, Koi no Hibana, Suzume no Shouri??</title>
<summary>That day Mr. Sunbeam moves close to Kiyo’s house. Kiyo, Zatch, Megumi, Tia and Ponygon go to a store and pick a housewarming gift for Mr. Sunbeam, and they help him clean up the house. While watching news during the break time, the news reveals a mysterious building…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36505" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">105</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Q襲! Q極変形? わが名はコーラルQ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Q Attack! Q Ultimate Transformation? My Name is Coral Q</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Q Shuu! Q Kyoku Henkei? Waga Na wa Coral Q</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36738" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">106</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピンチ到来 逆襲のQ! 全呪文封殺!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pinch Arrival, Q Counterattack! All the Spells Forceout!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pinch Tourai, Gyakushuu no Q! Zen Jumon Fuusatsu!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36743" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">107</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">電撃連鎖! 究極進化!? 新たなるバオウ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lightning Chain! Final Evolution!? Baou Renewal!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dengeki Rensa! Kyuukyoku Shinka!? Arata Naru Baou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38264" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">113</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友からの手紙 本を燃やせ!! レインの正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Letter From a Friend, Burn my Book! Rein`s True Face</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo kara no Tegami, Hon o Moyase!! Rein no Shoutai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41165" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">108</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホームシック!? 華と母上 さまよえるガッシュ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homesick!? Hana and Mother. Wanderlust Gash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Homesick!? Hana to Hahaue, Samayoeru Gash</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41166" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">114</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">弱虫カイル ヒゲのパピプリオ ロデュウの罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cowardly Kairu, Bearded Papipurio, Rodeaux`s Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yowamushi Kairu, Hige no Papipurio, Rodeaux no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41167" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">116</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最大呪文炸裂! ガルバドス・アボロディオ レインの夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Spell, Explode! Garubadosu Aborodio, Rein`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saidai Jumon Sakuretsu! Garubadosu Aborodio, Rein no Yume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41168" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">120</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">見られてオヨヨヨ~ ときめくモモン ティオ大爆発!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Was Seen? Oyoyo~, Prospering Monmon, Tio`s Gigantic Explosion!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirarete Oyoyoyo~, Tokimeku Momon, Tio Daibakuhatsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41169" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">112</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">回る! 回る! 転ぶ! 転ぶ! 爆裂アイススケート!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spin! Spin! Fall! Fall! Explosive Iceskate!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mawaru! Mawaru! Korobu! Korobu! Bakuretsu Ice Skate!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41170" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">117</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋愛カンフー 悲劇ウォンレイ 恋歌終章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Passionate Kung Fu, Tragic Wonrei, A Love Song`s Final Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ren`ai Kung Fu, Higeki Wonrei, Renka Shuushou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41171" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">118</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">連れ去られたガッシュ! 海の上の罠 ダルタニアン撃沈</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kidnapped Gash! Trap over the Sea, Sinking Dartagnan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuresarareta Gash! Umi no Ue no Wana, Dartagnan Gekichin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41172" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">110</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛襲カルディオ! 雪原に燃やす闘志 ウマゴン新たな炎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Karudio`s Fierce Attack! Fighters Who Burn Up the Snow Field. Umagon`s New Flame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moushuu Karudio! Setsuken ni Moyasu Toushi, Umagon Arata na Honoo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41173" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">109</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">北国の決闘 宿命のライバル ウマゴン氷結!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel in the Northern Country Fated Rival Umagon Frozen!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitakuni no Kettou, Shukumei no Rival, Umagon Hyouketsu!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41174" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">115</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛攻ロデュウ 瀕死のレイン 目覚めよカイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rodeux`s Fierce Attack. Dying Rein. Awaken, Kyle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moukou Rodeaux, Hinshi no Rein, Mezame yo Kairu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41175" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">119</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティオの元気 ただ一人のパートナー 傷が癒える時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tio`s Spirit, The One and Only Partner, When Wounds Heal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tio no Genki, Tada Hitori no Patner, Kizu ga Ieru Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45255" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">131</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">王の覚悟 友か? 世界か? ガッシュの決断</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The King`s Resolution, Friends? Or the World? Zatch`s Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ou no Kakugo, Tomo ka? Sekai ka? Gash no Ketsudan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45256" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">127</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファウード到着! 決死の突入 待っていた刺客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arrival at Faudo, Desperate Assault, Assassins That Awaited</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Faudo Touchaku! Kesshi no Totsunyuu, Matteita Shikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45257" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">125</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">非情なるリオウ 呪われし魔物 いざファウードへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heartless Riou. The Cursed Demons. Now, to Faudo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hijounaru Riou, Norowareshi Mamono, Iza Faudo e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45258" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">124</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">別れの予感 鈴芽の告白 愛と青春のハイキング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Premonition of Separation, Suzume`s Confession, Hiking of Love and Youth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakare no Yokan, Suzume no Kokuhaku, Ai to Seishun no Hiking</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45259" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">130</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブザライ猛攻 ディオガ対バオウ 逆転への連鎖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Buzarai`s Fierce Attack, Dioga vs. Baou, Chain to Come from Behind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Buzarai Moukou, Dioga Tai Baou, Gyakuten e no Rensa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45260" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">136</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迫るファウード復活 帰還装置始動 立ちふさがるライバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faudo`s Revival Draws Near, Return Device Activated, Rivals Stand in the Way</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Semaru Faudo Fukkatsu, Kikan Souchi Shidou, Tachifusagaru Rival</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45261" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">128</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キース・ブザライ 死の交響曲 さらばキャンチョメ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kiees and Buzarai`s Symphony of Death; Farewell, Kanchome!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieth - Buzarai, Shi no Koukyoukyoku, Saraba Kanchome</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45262" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">129</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡の新呪文 ディマ・ブルク ぼくは弱虫じゃない!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miraculous New Spell Dima Buruk, I Am Not a Coward!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki no Shin Jumon, Dima Buruku, Boku wa Yowamushi ja Nai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45263" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">126</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戻れない旅 ゆれる決意 ファウードの正体!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Journey from Which You Cannot Return, Wavering Determination, Faudo`s True Form!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Modorenai Tabi, Yureru Ketsui, Faudo no Shoutai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45264" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">134</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">誰がために戦う ウォンレイとアリシエ 苦悩の決断</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fighting for Whom? Wonlei and Alishie, Decision of Suffering</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tagatame ni Tatakau, Wonrei to Alishie, Kunou no Ketsudan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45265" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">135</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファウード決死圏 心臓打つ魔物 モモンの涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faudo: Deadly Zone, The Demon That Beats the Heart, Momon`s Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Faudo Kesshiken, Shinzou Utsu Mamono, Momon no Namida</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45266" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">133</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">冷徹ザルチム 呪いの真実 立て! アリシエ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cold-headed Zaruchimu, The Truth of the Curse, Stand Up! Arishie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reitetsu Zaruchimu, Noroi no Shinjitsu, Tate Alishie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45267" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">111</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">踊って! 弾けて! 揺れる! 大空港</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dance! Laugh! Shake! The Great Airport</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Odotte! Hajikete! Yureru! Daikuukou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45268" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">122</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぐや伝説 ガッシュの夏祭り 月へ帰った少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legend of Kaguya, Gash`s Summer Festival, Girl Who Returned to the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaguya Densetsu, Gash no Natsumatsuri, Tsuki e Kaetta Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45269" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">121</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">目覚めよジェラシー 怒れる女神 チャージル・サイフォドン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Awaken, Jealousy. The Angered Goddess. Chaajiru Saifodon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezame yo Jealousy, Ikareru Megami, Chaajiru Saifodon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45270" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">132</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">胃の中の試練 難問突破 ティンティンチャンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Trial Inside the Stomach, Pass the Difficult Problem, Tin Tin Chance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">I no Naka no Shiren, Nanmon Toppa, Tintin Chance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45271" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">123</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">唸れプライド バリーVSテッド 消えるのはどっち?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roar of Pride, Bari vs. Ted, Which Will Disappear?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unare Pride, Bari VS Ted, Kieru no wa Docchi?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48614" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">147</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">反転する未来 雷帝ゼオン 破滅への序曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inverted Future, Thunder Emperor Zeon, Overture to Ruin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanten Suru Mirai, Raitei Zeon, Hametsu e no Jokyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48615" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">142</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">閉ざされた部屋 アリシエの戦 因縁再び!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sealed Room, Alishie`s Fight, Destiny Once More!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tozasareta Heya, Alishie no Tatakai, Innen Futatabi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48616" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">141</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃えろウマゴン 氷結カルディオ 勝利へ走れ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burning Umagon, Freezing Karudio, Run to Victory!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meoro Umagon, Hyouketsu Karudio, Shouri e Hashire!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48617" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">140</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">王にはなれぬ者 決死! ウォンレイ 最後の鉄拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Which Won`t Become King, Do or Die Wonlei, Final Fist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ou ni wa Narenu Mono, Kesshi! Wonrei, Saigo no Tekken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48618" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">146</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファウードの守護者 アースからガッシュへ 託される未来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faudo`s Protectors, From Earth to Gash, Entrusted Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Faudo no Shugosha, Earth kara Gash e, Takusareru Mirai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48619" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">137</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">呪いのタイムリミット 封印を砕け! 届けガッシュの想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Curse`s Time Limit. Crush the Seal! Reach, Gash`s Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Noroi no Time Limit Fuuin o Kudake! Todoke Gash no Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48620" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">143</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">命を燃やせ 戦人アリシエ 決着!? ザルチム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burn Up Life, Warrior Alishie, The Conclusion!? Zaruchimu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inochi o Moyase, Ikusabito Alishie, Kecchaku!? Zaruchimu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48621" update="2006-08-25">
<epno type="1">149</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バオウを継ぐもの ガッシュVSゼオン ジガディラスの雷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He Who Inherits Baou, Gash vs. Zeon, Jigadirasu`s Lightning</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baou o Tsugu Mono, Gash VS Zeon, Jigadirasu no Ikazuchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48622" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">148</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒涛ゼオン 二つの宿命 ガッシュの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zeon`s Raging Waves, Two Fates, Gash`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dotou Zeon, Futatsu no Shukumei, Gash no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48623" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">150</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! ファウード 金色の輝き やさしい王様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deciding Battle! Faudo, the Golden Glow, Kind King</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Faudo, Kin`iro no Kagayaki, Yasashii Ou-sama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48624" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">145</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かない叫び テッドVSチェリッシュ 王より大切なもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Screams That Won`t Reach, Ted vs. Cherish, More Important Things Than King</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokenai Sakebi, Ted VS Cherish, Ou yori Taisetsu na Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48625" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">139</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">脳を目指せ! 爆走ファウード 必死の再突入</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aim for the Brain! Roaring Faudo, Desperate Reentry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nou o Mezase! Bakusou Faudo, Hisshi no Saitotsunyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48626" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">144</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくらは王様 キャンチョメとモモン 倒せキース!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Are Kings, Kanchome and Momon, Defeat Keys!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokura wa Ou-sama, Kanchome to Momon, Taose Keith!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48627" update="2006-07-28">
<epno type="1">138</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔導巨兵ファウード 絶望の中の光 清麿の秘策</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Demonic Giant Soldier, Faudo. Light in the Middle of Despair. Kiyomaro`s Secret Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madou Kyouhei Faudo, Zetsubou no Naka no Hikari, Kiyomaro no Hisaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111003" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">00F 黄金のチチをもつ男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">00F: The Man With the Golden Tits</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">00F: Ougon no Chichi o Motsu Otoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167932" update="2015-04-17">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">走れガッシュ!! 奪われたウマゴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run, Gash!! Umagon Has Been Stolen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashire Gash!! Ubawareta Umagon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171973" update="2017-10-26">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171974" update="2015-09-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192261" update="2017-10-26">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192262" update="2017-10-26">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192263" update="2017-10-26">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192264" update="2017-10-26">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192265" update="2017-10-26">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192266" update="2017-10-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192267" update="2017-10-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
