<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6384" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2009-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ristorante Paradiso</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Rispara</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Paradise Restaurant</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">天堂餐馆</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">リストランテ・パラディーゾ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ristorante Paradiso</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5971" approval="16" total="21">Seiyou Kottou Yougashiten: Antique</anime>
<anime id="6780" approval="1" total="5">Working!!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="261604">Nice Josei</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="161487">a nice slowpaced anime with a nice feeling to it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="342518">Very nice anime. Amazing Italy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="254453">It`s simply a wonderful view of the life of a resturant and the people who work and eat there.  There`s no plot twist, no hidden skeleton in the closet, just a simple wonderful story.

It`s like meeting someone and getting to know them.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.rispara.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1544" type="Original Work">Ono Natsume</name>
<name id="27273" type="Music">Ko-ko-ya</name>
<name id="2887" type="Animation Work">David Production</name>
<name id="6825" type="Character Design">Takeda Itsuko</name>
<name id="7880" type="Series Composition">Inotsume Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="733" type="Work">Yomiko Advertising</name>
<name id="802" type="Work">Movic</name>
<name id="1048" type="Work">Hakuhodo DY Media Partners</name>
<name id="921" type="Work">Sony PCL</name>
<name id="809" type="Work">Shouchiku</name>
<name id="1542" type="Direction">Kase Mitsuko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr1544 [Ono Natsume], serialised in the alternative manga magazine Manga Erotics F.
http://anidb.net/ch5527 [Nicoletta] is a young woman who comes to Rome to confront her mother who abandoned her as a young girl. However, a chain of events leads to her becoming an apprentice chef at a restaurant owned by her mom`s boyfriend instead.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="910">6.49</permanent>
<temporary count="912">7.26</temporary>
<review count="1">5.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>19451.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10449</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5984</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5180</identifier>
<identifier>dlpqef</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.rispara.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ristorante_Paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>リストランテ・パラディーゾ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1602</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>333317</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11124</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2810" parentid="2831" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Italy</name>
<description>Italy, officially the Italian Republic, is a unitary parliamentary republic in Europe. Located in the heart of the Mediterranean Sea, Italy shares open land borders with France, Switzerland, Austria, Slovenia, San Marino and Vatican City.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3119" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>restaurant</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4353" parentid="2810" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Rome</name>
<description>Rome is the capital of Italy and a special comune (named Comune di Roma Capitale). Rome also serves as the capital of the Lazio region. It is also the country`s most populated comune. It is the fourth-most populous city in the European Union by population within city limits. It is the centre of the Metropolitan City of Rome. Rome is located in the central-western portion of the Italian Peninsula, within Lazio (Latium), along the shores of the Tiber.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214356.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5013" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>Noise</name>
<description>Noise was a http://anidb.net/cr741 [Fuji TV] late night anime programming block, broadcast each Wednesday night from 26:08 to 26:38.
It was Fuji TV`s second late night anime-themed time block, after http://anidb.net/t3865 [noitaminA], which airs every Thursday night. It first began on October 15, 2008, with http://anidb.net/a5779 [Michiko to Hatchin]. After broadcasting three anime series, the block was cancelled in favour of extending noitaminA, which started airing two productions at once instead of only one.</description>
<picurl>44912.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5527" type="main character in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="9">6.45</rating>
<name>Nicoletta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5528" type="main character in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="6">3.48</rating>
<name>Olga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5529" type="main character in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="6">7.62</rating>
<name>Santo Claudio Paradiso</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3161" picture="69050.jpg">Yamanoi Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5530" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-05">
<rating votes="3">8.17</rating>
<name>Lorenzo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5531" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="4">7.27</rating>
<name>Gigi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3162" picture="151662.jpg">Kiyama Shigeo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5532" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="3">6.63</rating>
<name>Luciano De Luca</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3163" picture="24161.jpg">Tachikawa Mitsutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5533" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="4">8.60</rating>
<name>Vito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5534" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-12-10">
<name>Francesco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33" picture="133462.jpg">Kimura Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5535" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="4">4.86</rating>
<name>Frio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3157" picture="24155.jpg">Nishimatsu Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5536" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="3">6.21</rating>
<name>Theo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99728" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<name>Gabriela</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25" picture="16608.jpg">Watanabe Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99730" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<name>Angela</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4962" picture="60945.jpg">Toyoshima Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99731" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<name>Enoteca Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99732" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<name>Gianna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6849" picture="186209.jpg">Mori Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99735" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<name>Marzio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2402" picture="186198.jpg">Oka Kazuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99736" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<name>Magomusume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99737" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<name>Vanna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2049" picture="228615.jpg">Soumi Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99740" type="appears in" update="2018-12-09">
<name>Dario</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4270" picture="197671.jpg">Nakagawa Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99741" type="appears in" update="2018-12-10">
<name>Lorenzo no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3100" picture="186161.jpg">Tsuchiya Toshihide</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99742" type="appears in" update="2018-12-10">
<name>Gigi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99745" type="appears in" update="2018-12-10">
<name>Lucia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99746" type="appears in" update="2018-12-10">
<name>Marina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="593" picture="17990.jpg">Honda Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99747" type="appears in" update="2018-12-10">
<name>Lucia no Otto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99751" type="appears in" update="2018-12-10">
<name>Mauro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99752" type="appears in" update="2018-12-10">
<name>Margarita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99753" type="appears in" update="2018-12-10">
<name>Luciano Gitei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4270" picture="197671.jpg">Nakagawa Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99754" type="appears in" update="2018-12-10">
<name>Rossi-fujin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="693" picture="226546.jpg">Igarashi Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99793" type="appears in" update="2018-12-13">
<name>Savina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48" picture="16640.jpg">Yono Hikari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99794" type="appears in" update="2018-12-13">
<name>Margarita Otto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2488" picture="186147.jpg">Matsuda Ken`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="97346" update="2009-03-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99360" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニコレッタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nicoletta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nicoletta</title>
<summary>At Rome`s curiously fabulous ristorante - Casetta Dell`Orso - where all the employees are dreamy spectacle-clad gentlemen, we find the heroine of our story, Nicoletta in search of someone. As it turns out, this woman she`s searching for happens to be the risorante owner`s wife...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>525270</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="99361" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">指輪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yubiwa</title>
<summary>At Casetta Dell`Orso, it seems that the men are the main attraction as the women come to admire the gentlemen here.  Even Nicoletta has fallen under the spell of these gentlemen in glasses as one catches her eye leaving her breathless...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>525272</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="99798" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オルシーニの味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flavor of Orsini</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orsini no Aji</title>
<summary>Gigi`s a master when it comes to selecting the perfect wines for VIP customers, and his quiet nature and mysterious relationship with the restaurant`s owner only make Nicoletta more and more curious about him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528804</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="99799" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カゼッタ・デッロルソ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Casetta dell`Orso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Casetta dell`Orso</title>
<summary>When a special guest visits, Nicoletta is surprised to recognize him from an old photo on the wall. Once they`re introduced, she`s given a glimpse into his relationship with the rest of the staff, along with his place in the restaurant`s history.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>525276</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="99800" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パラディーゾ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paradiso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Paradiso</title>
<summary>Nicoletta contemplates both her new crush and her complicated relationship with her mother, while Claudio struggles to come to grips with lingering feelings from a past relationship.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>525274</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="102655" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ある夫婦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Husband and Wife</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aru Fuufu</title>
<summary>A woman dealing with a floundering marriage finds unexpected solace after meeting Gigi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528816</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="103414" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別な一日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Special Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu na Ichinichi</title>
<summary>Luciano`s grandson is turning 9, and Luciano and the rest of the staff at Casetta dell`Orso are determined to give him a wonderful celebration full of warm memories.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>529178</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="103943" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">昔日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Days of Yore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekijitsu</title>
<summary>A mishap with a pair of glasses leads Claudio to reminisce about his long-time acquaintance with Furio.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>529180</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104113" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘めたる恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himetaru Koi</title>
<summary>A beautiful, widowed violinist admires Luciano, but his heart still belongs to his late wife.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>529184</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104114" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リストランテの休日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Day Off at the Ristorante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ristorante no Kyuujitsu</title>
<summary>When the restaurant unexpectedly closes for the day, Nicoletta spends time experimenting with dishes for the menu and learns about Teo`s struggles when he first joined the staff.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>529182</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104697" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リストランテの人々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The People of the Ristorante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ristorante no Hitobito</title>
<summary>Nicoletta receives an unexpected invitation to her mother`s birthday party, and Claudio wonders if it`s finally time to take off his wedding band.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>529186</identifier>
<identifier>ristorante-paradiso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162898" update="2014-09-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162899" update="2014-09-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162900" update="2014-09-26">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
