<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6389" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-03-06</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hayate no Gotoku!! 2nd Season: Atsu ga Natsui ze - Mizugi Hen!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Hayate the Combat Butler!! OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hayate no Gotoku!! 2nd Season OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">旋风管家ova</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hng ova</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ハヤテのごとく!! Hayate the combat butler 2nd season アツがナツいぜ 水着編!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6413" type="Sequel">Hayate no Gotoku!! 2nd Season</anime>
<anime id="4917" type="Prequel">Hayate no Gotoku!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="101376">Indeed it`s a lot of fan stuff in it. If you like Hayate no Gotoku!! then you have to see the OVA too!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://hayatenogotoku.com/goods/ova.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="1797" type="Direction">Iwasaki Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="1783" type="Original Work">Hata Kenjirou</name>
<name id="3744" type="Character Design">Fujii Masahiro</name>
<name id="1572" type="Series Composition">Kuroda Yousuke</name>
<name id="2841" type="Work">Shogakukan-Shueisha Productions</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch528 [Sanzen`in Nagi] invites all her friends to the private beach inside the vast Sanzen`in estate. Just as Nagi is about to join in the fun, a vengeful spirit intent on disrupting their fun appears.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1779">5.89</permanent>
<temporary count="1790">7.24</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>20826.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10546</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5521</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hayatenogotoku.com/goods/ova.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>338283</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11274</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3004" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-17">
<name>skilled main character</name>
<description>The main character in the show is very skilled in one or more tasks, often to the amazement of those around him/her.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="528" type="main character in" update="2011-05-18">
<rating votes="497">5.90</rating>
<name>Sanzen`in Nagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanzen`in Nagi is the only heir to the Sanzen`in fortune. She has an otaku-level hobby with manga, anime and video games, and draws her own manga, which is called Millennium Legend: Magical Destroy. She is good at finance and likes to learn. She has a crush on Hayate, and has misunderstood that Hayate loves her since they first met. But because this is only a misunderstanding, she often feels that Hayate isn`t interested in her. She sometimes tries to make him have interest in her in many ways. Nagi is afraid of dark places and has absolutely no sense of direction. Her only surviving family is her grandfather, whom she doesn`t like. She regards Maria as a mother or older sister figure, and warns Hayate not to touch Maria in any indecent way or she will never forgive him. She totally lacks experience with cooking and accordingly is prone to making mistakes (such as mistaking dish-washing detergent for cooking oil) when she attempts to cook. She has a pet tiger, Tama, whom she refers to as a cat.</description>
<picture>71769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="529" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-16">
<rating votes="308">7.95</rating>
<name>Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maria is Nagi`s maid and surrogate older sister/mother, and is the only one who understands the problem between Hayate and Nagi. She is the character with the most common sense in the series, and appears to be the one in charge of everything in Nagi`s manor, since everyone from the head butler to the SP either obeys or fears her (or both in some cases). She`s good at general housework and likes games of all kinds, though she is deathly afraid of cockroaches, which she refers to as "the dark life-form that exists in the kitchen and other places". She has also proved capable of self-defence techniques in times of need.</description>
<picture>33340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="530" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="1086">9.09</rating>
<name>Katsura Hinagiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsura Hinagiku is the current http://anidb.net/ch16568 [student council] president, and kendo club president at http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuou Academy], the school that http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi], http://anidb.net/ch531 [Isumi], and eventually http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] attends. She is fifteen and is an expert with swords, specifically kendo. She first meets Hayate when he gets lost on the huge Hakuou campus and ends up rescuing her. She had been helping a baby bird who had fallen out of its nest, but due to her fear of heights, had become stuck without her realising it. Hayate ends up helping her down the tree, and then promises that he will come to help her should she ever call for him. In gratitude, she invites him to the top of the clocktower, where only student council elites are allowed. She allows Hayate to call her by her first name and also seems to be infatuated by Hayate and his attractive personality. Her family, while shown to be well off in volume 8 (chapter 76), does not show any signs of being rich in comparison to much of the cast.</description>
<picture>24934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="531" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-27">
<rating votes="210">8.26</rating>
<name>Saginomiya Isumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saginomiya Isumi is a purple-haired girl who is always wearing a kimono, and sometimes, a stole. She is http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi]`s best friend who they met at a party a long time ago. When all the other children, http://anidb.net/ch613 [Sakuya] included, laughed at Nagi`s first attempt at writing her own manga, Isumi took interest in it and asked Nagi how it ends; Nagi then asked Isumi (in a childish sense) to marry her. Like Nagi, Isumi is very rich. Unlike Nagi, Isumi is soft-spoken, kind, and can cook well. While she does not have an awful sense of direction, she constantly gets lost due to the fact that she is apt to forget her destination, and the fact that she can disappear from people`s eyes instantaneously only complicates the matter. She also has a habit of saying, when she doesn`t understand how to use a machine such as a cellular phone or a vending machine, that the machine is broken. She displays a high level of empathy for Nagi`s feelings; however, she does not recognise http://anidb.net/ch618 [Wataru]`s love for her, a fact that Nagi, Maria, and http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] comment on.</description>
<picture>59761.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="532" type="main character in" update="2010-04-16">
<rating votes="292">6.45</rating>
<name>Ayasaki Hayate</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayasaki Hayate is the butler of the Sanzenin family, Hayate has had to work to support his parents` bad habits since the age of nine, always moving from job to job by the time he is found out to be underage. The experience gained does mean, however, that he of all characters possesses the most extensive practical knowledge as to how the world operates. Hayate`s dad has refused to get employed,while his mother is a compulsive gambler, and the whereabouts of Hayate`s older brother who is not named, are unknown. These events led to their bankruptcy - they abandon Hayate after selling his organs to the Yakuza to ease their financial burdens. With not many choices left to him, Hayate conspired to kidnap someone to get ransom money. He found a girl, http://anidb.net/ch528 [Sanzenin Nagi], and told her that he would kidnap her. However, Nagi mistook his words for his confession of love, so later he was employed as Nagi`s new butler but as the story progresses, Hayate began to like Nagi without realising it. In the beginning of the story he often mentioned Nello and Patrasche from the novel A Dog of Flanders and compared his miserable situation to the characters` life.</description>
<picture>14830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="612" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="32">5.73</rating>
<name>Makimura Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makimura Shiori is a genius scientist with the Mikado Hyper Energy (M.H.E) Electronics Corporation as the Chief of Development, Humanoid Nursing and Battlefield Weapons Department, and Advanced Technology Development Division. Her specialities are computers and mechas. Her development team created Nursing Robot Eight and other mechas seen in the series. She is in fact so talented, that she even built a mecha when she was half asleep.</description>
<picture>14921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="613" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-18">
<rating votes="153">7.05</rating>
<name>Aizawa Sakuya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aizawa Sakuya is a cousin of http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi] and from Kansai. Like Nagi, Sakuya is very rich and has a similar personality — loud, arrogant, abusive of servants, and unwilling to accept defeat in anything. Nagi is one of the only people who can stand up to her, once again showing their similar personalities. Sakuya is the eldest daughter in her family with three sisters and one brother. Her illegitimate half brother http://anidb.net/ch16045 [Gilbert] is one of the people who is constantly harassing Nagi for her fortune. Sakuya is obsessed with stand-up comedy especially Manzai style. She encourages http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] to become a comedian because she believes Hayate`s life up to now is nothing more than a comedy.</description>
<picture>71770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="615" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="76">5.47</rating>
<name>Kijima Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kijima Saki is Wataru`s maid. She is significantly older than Wataru and lives with him in his video-rental store. Her biggest fear is that Wataru will start watching porn when he reaches puberty, which he denies. She takes a mixture of a servant and elder sister role to Wataru, often changing from being subservient to scolding him depending on the situation. She also reacts strongly whenever Hayate touches her anywhere, such as tapping her on the shoulder or carrying her away from danger, worrying about whether or not their physical contact will affect her chances of getting a husband later in life. This is not only limited to Hayate, but other men as well.</description>
<picture>4183.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="215" picture="151687.jpg">Nakajima Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="618" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="64">3.70</rating>
<name>Tachibana Wataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tachibana Wataru is Nagi`s fiancée, but they have no feelings for each other; Wataru claims his parents arranged their future marriage entirely for the money. He lives and runs a video-rental store in the city, the last store owned by the Tachibana group which lost all their assets and is on the verge of bankruptcy due to the recession. His dreams is to make his store great and acquire a fortune greater than Nagi`s. Wataru is in love with Isumi. He first hates Hayate for accidentally stealing Isumi`s affection, but later he looks up to him and strives to be as good as he is. Regardless of that, he still calls Hayate by his own personal nickname for him, "the Butler In Debt" (or a variation thereof), and doesn`t hide his usual irritation.</description>
<picture>14926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="623" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="139">4.49</rating>
<name>Katsura Yukiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsura Yukiji is the twenty-eight year old sister of Hinagiku. She is a world history teacher at http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuou Academy] and doubles as a twenty-four-hour gate guard. She refuses to let http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] enter the school when they first meet because she is afraid that letting unauthorised personnel on campus will result in a salary deduction for her. Her attitude softens after Hayate first saves her from falling off the clock tower, but she still almost causes Hayate to be rejected from Hakuou by unnecessarily making him anxious during his entrance exam. She repays Hayate by telling everyone in her class on Hayate`s first day that he is a super cool person. She has a group of underachieving students (http://anidb.net/ch640 [Izumi], http://anidb.net/ch641 [Miki], and http://anidb.net/ch642 [Risa]) who hang out with her a lot. She lives on the Hakuou campus; she tells Hayate that she does this so that she can save rent money and use that money to buy alcohol instead. It is a recurring gag that she will do anything for money, going as far as to allow an evil spirit to possess her because it told her it would give her a million yen. When http://anidb.net/ch612 [Makimura Shiori] is sent to teach at Hakuou, Yukiji is demoted to sub-homeroom teacher.</description>
<picture>130799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="628" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="154">6.22</rating>
<name>Nishizawa Ayumu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nishizawa Ayumu is a girl from Hayate`s school before he became a butler. She always had feelings for Hayate and is happy when he pays his old school a visit. She violently lashes out at anyone who badmouths her and Hayate, including a teacher who called Hayate a dropout because his parents had refunded all his school fees the day Hayate was sold. She confesses her feelings to Hayate, but Hayate rejects them after getting a vision of Nagi. Undeterred, she tries to talk to Hayate when she sees him a week later, but she runs into Nagi. She is shocked that, in terms of metaphoric strength, Nagi is a dragon while she is a hamster. Nishizawa retreats, vowing next time to bring a stronger hamster. She later challenges Nagi to karaoke, only to lose. In the anime, it is a running gag that she appears in every episode, usually for less than thirty seconds doing something entirely unrelated to the episode`s plot, though always related to food. However, in the manga, she is the only girl who has successfully confessed her love towards Hayate, which often places her in situations where she is alone with him. Most of the time she is shown eating something.</description>
<picture>71942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="630" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="60">4.49</rating>
<name>Klaus Seishirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Klaus is the head butler of the Sanzen`in family, who is usually away on business. He once fell in love with Hayate without knowing that Hayate was forced to crossdress as a catgirl by Nagi and Maria. He is self-centered, has a low alcohol tolerance, doesn`t do well with tobacco or women, and likes cars and bikes.</description>
<picture>14941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="640" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="153">7.72</rating>
<name>Segawa Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Segawa Izumi is the chairman.She is the younger fraternal twin sister of http://anidb.net/ch9408 [Segawa Kotetsu]. She met http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] when they were young (Volume 18 flashback) as she was getting attacked by a dog, although she mentioned nothing about that incident when she first met Hayate at http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuou Academy].</description>
<picture>14952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="641" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="107">4.72</rating>
<name>Hanabishi Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanabishi Miki is a member of the Student Council. She specialises in investigation work, which may be the result of being the daughter of an important government official.</description>
<picture>14953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="218" picture="17036.jpg">Nakao Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="642" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-12">
<rating votes="102">4.57</rating>
<name>Asakaze Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asakaze Risa is the head of the disciplinary committee.</description>
<picture>14954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="679" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-09">
<rating votes="63">7.43</rating>
<name>Tama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tama is a white tiger from Africa, who was rescued by http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi] as a cub, and was raised on Matsuzaka beef and expensive tuna fish, making it incapable for him to go to the zoo or back to the wild. He can speak the human language, though he does not reveal this to http://anidb.net/ch529 [Maria] or Nagi because he doesn`t want to shatter the young girl`s dreams. He will lay his life down to protect Nagi, because his situation was a lot like http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate]`s. To him, Maria is the highest power there is, followed by an impassable wall, Nagi, then himself, and everyone else is below him.</description>
<picture>14973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6695" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-09">
<rating votes="20">5.70</rating>
<name>Sonia Shaflnarz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sonia Shaflnarz comes from a family part of the Sicilian mafia. She moves to Japan in order to get revenge against the Sanzen`in family, because her father died due to the Sanzen`in family, though not directly. In "Extra- Radical dreamers" of chapter 41, her father hid in a trash can to assassinate http://anidb.net/ch528 [Nagi] on Mykonos Island but http://anidb.net/ch532 [Hayate] prevented it and defeated him. After that, he quit the mafia and went to Japan to become a cook. Then he died because he didn`t know that there was poison in blowfish.
She impersonates http://anidb.net/ch6696 [Sister Fortesia], a sister from the Church of Alexander Mark and the Tiger`s Pit for Butlers for the purpose of approaching Hayate and the Sanzen`in family. She speaks fluent Japanese, but she uses harsh words and blames it on the fact that she doesn`t know Japanese very well. Sonia has unbelievable strength and fighting ability and uses tonfas as weapons.</description>
<picture>24530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6778" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-20">
<rating votes="128">9.29</rating>
<name>Ten no Koe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Voice of the Heavens is the narrator of the series.
Throughout both the anime and the manga, he narrates on what happens in the series while at the same time mocking and ridiculing the characters about what they are doing, with frequent snarks at the absurd plot and the silly nature of the story. Some of the cast can hear him and respond accordingly.
He appeared in episode 50 of the anime as a tall man with no face hosting a quiz game.</description>
<picture>35924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7184" type="appears in" update="2009-05-24">
<rating votes="21">6.50</rating>
<name>Shiranui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The "White Kitten" Hayate receives from Hinagiku. He`s black with a small white X-shaped scar in his forehead. His name is referenced from the videogame Okami who`s protagonist is also known as Shiranui. Nagi apparently was playing this game prior to meeting Shiranui.</description>
<picture>25516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9407" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-15">
<rating votes="24">7.25</rating>
<name>Ayasaki Hermione</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28939.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10198" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-16">
<rating votes="113">6.37</rating>
<name>Harukaze Chiharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The secretary of the student council. Secretly, under the alias of "Haruko", she works as Sakuya`s maid. Although nobody in Hakuou is aware of that, with the exception of Aika Kasumi, who found everything about her out soon enough.</description>
<picture>33328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11542" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="20">7.84</rating>
<name>Kasumi Aika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kasumi Aika is the vice president of the http://anidb.net/ch16568 [Student Council]. Like many other http://anidb.net/ch16459 [Hakuo Academy] students, she comes from a rich family. While she may be seen as a sweet, kind, and gentle girl to most people, secretly she is also very manipulative and takes advantage of any situation she sees, a fact only http://anidb.net/ch530 [Hinagiku] and http://anidb.net/ch10198 [Chiharu] are aware of.</description>
<picture>34677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11813" type="appears in" update="2009-09-19">
<rating votes="20">3.90</rating>
<name>Sharna Alamgir</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>35826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11814" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-19">
<rating votes="21">4.37</rating>
<name>Hibino Fumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>35825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="97289" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2009-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99804" update="2010-03-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2009-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハヤテのごとく!!3D</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hayate no Gotoku!! 3D</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hayate no Gotoku!! 3D</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
