<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="642" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>45</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-04-15</startdate>
<enddate>2004-03-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tantei Gakuen Q</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Detective School Q</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">DAQ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">TGQ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">探偵学園Q</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Detective Academy Q</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">โรงเรียนนักสืบQ</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Escuela de detectives</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="266" approval="32" total="35">Meitantei Conan</anime>
<anime id="1240" approval="12" total="12">Kindaichi Shounen no Jikenbo (1997)</anime>
<anime id="245" approval="1" total="3">Spiral: Suiri no Kizuna</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/tantei-q/</url>
<creators>
<name id="5908" type="Original Work">Satou Fumiya</name>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="6428" type="Character Design">Oonishi Masaya</name>
<name id="9130" type="Original Work">Amagi Seimaru</name>
<name id="4566" type="Direction">Abe Noriyuki</name>
<name id="18672" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kitayama Mari</name>
<name id="4051" type="Music">Ikeda Daisuke</name>
<name id="51984" type="Series Composition">Hayashi Makoto</name>
</creators>
<description>The story began in a classroom of a middle school. Our main character, Kyu, when called by the guidance counselor, declared that he wanted to be a detective. He took the entrance exam to Dan Detective School where talented people from the whole country gather. He passed the difficult entrance exam for the so-called "Q class" (Q = qualified), which is personally instructed by the founder and head master of the school, the legendary famous detective, Dan Morihiko. There he got to know Minami Megumi (Meg) with her photographic memory ability, Touyama Kintarou (Kinta) - the descendant of "Kin-san" from Touyama, Narusawa Kazuma (Kazuma) - a genius programmer, and Amakusa Ryu (Ryu) - the weird Todai (Tokyo University) student. The five of them work together, as well as competing each other, heading towards graduation.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="889">6.59</permanent>
<temporary count="911">7.65</temporary>
<review count="3">7.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>245933.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2609</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>407</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1192</identifier>
<identifier>wkufpk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_2000/tv_063.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/tantei-q/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tantei_Gakuen_Q</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>探偵学園Q</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>208</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>241158</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2384" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-22">
<name>prodigy</name>
<description>Character is very good at everything he/she does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4192" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-22">
<name>broadcast cropped to 4-3</name>
<description>Although this anime was created in 16:9 (widescreen) aspect ratio, its Japanese TV broadcasts were all cropped to 4:3 (fullscreen). It was only made available in 16:9 upon its DVD/BD release.
Note: This tag does NOT apply to series that had initial broadcasts in 4:3 and 16:9 broadcasts several weeks later, such as Clannad, Asu no Yoichi, K-On!, etc. For those, use "Delayed 16-9 broadcast".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13820" type="main character in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="2">1.83</rating>
<name>Renjou Kyuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyu is a bright, sweet and optimistic boy who is also a brilliant detective, but a little awkward in social situations. Otherwise, he is considered to be the team`s leader and is known for his logical explanations of cases. His motto (taught by Renjou Satoru (his father)) - "A Detective must never give up or the case will remain unsolved". He has a good sense of judgment regarding people (when everyone distrusted Ryuu, he expressed his open appreciation for him) but often says things that infuriate Megumi such as look at the colour of her panties. But even though he acts this way, he cares for her, as shown when they were trapped in a secret door in the old school building. He did everything he could to help Megumi as she struggled after getting bitten by a pit viper, even opening up the pipe system to send Ryu and the others an SOS. In addition, another such running gag of Kyu`s is his constant misinterpretation of the Japanese language (for example, he said "training pants" when he heard the words "tore han," which means "treasure hunting").
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45773" type="main character in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="5">5.68</rating>
<name>Minami Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Commonly referred by her friends as "Megu", she has a unique talent of having a photographic memory, allowing her to memorize a scene instantly. This allows her to notice if a piece of evidence has been moved or is missing. In the anime, it is believed that she has a crush on Ryu. She also blushes while looking at Kyu hinting that she harbors a secret crush on Kyu. She studied in the Tokyo National Talent Development Research Center alongside Saburoumaru Yutaka. She lives with her older sister Akane (who attends a local university) as her parents work abroad.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45774" type="main character in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="5">3.54</rating>
<name>Amakusa Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuu is very intelligent and handsome, and his dark background somehow links him to the organization known as Pluto. When his parents died, Pluto took care of him. As a child he was never allowed to socialize with others. He often viewed his house as more of a prison than a home. Even with his cold personality he is still friendly with the other members of Class Q, and shares a special link with Kyu, since he was the first one who could understand him. He admits that Kyu is smarter than he is despite his childish behaviour. Ryuu also has a Pluto mark on the back of his neck, which is seen at the Last Opening Video of Detective Academy Q.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45775" type="main character in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="3">2.71</rating>
<name>Narusawa Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazuma is a rich, well known computer games programmer. He often helps find information through his laptop computer, which he carries around with him at all times. At first after learning that he was a member of Class Q (which at the time was believed to be the lowest) he tried to get transferred to Class A. However, when his classmates came to his aid when he was in trouble he changed his mind, preferring to stay with his friends. Kazuma has a friendly rivalry with Kinta due to their different approaches to detective work. Kazuma and Kinta are often the butt of each other`s jokes.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45776" type="main character in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Tooyama Kintarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kintarou is the son of a well-respected police officer, but moved out due to a family dispute. He now lives alone and works part-time in different jobs, going from one to another. Kinta is the strongest member of the class, having had lessons in judo, kendo and karate. He also has superb senses, especially his eyesight and sense of smell. Kinta often mocks Kazuma`s high tech approach to detective work, preferring instead to rely on his "instinct". His tough personality as well as his excellent senses have been very useful at times. He is very strong and sometimes hits either Kazuma or Kyu. He also repeatedly tries to pick up girls (with little success). He has been called pervert in many episodes. His ambition is to touch a girl.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45777" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="2">1.79</rating>
<name>Dan Morihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dan Morihiko is the founder and principal of Dan Detective School, and a famous detective who has solved many cases, and is the only private detective in Japan who is licensed to hold a gun. Dan Morihiko was a former police officer who resigned to open up a private detective company of his own, Dan Detective Company (DDC), the parent company of DDS. He was assisted by a young boy named Renjou Satoru, who acted as his partner, assistant, and apprentice. Together they helped build DDC and DDS into a top level detective company and school (some of the top-level detectives at DDC and instructors at DDS were the first generation students of DDS). Among many criminals they fought, the most powerful one was the crime organization known as Pluto. Although Pluto was finally thought to apparently have been destroyed, it wasn`t without cost. Renjou Satoru, Dan`s most prominent apprentice and heir-apparent was killed, and Mr. Dan was forced to be in a wheelchair for the rest of his life. Years later, there are signs that Pluto is being resurrected. Realizing that his days were numbered due to his old age, Dan Morihiko decided to open a new, special class called Class Q, consisting of several extremely talented persons. He would train them, analyze each one of them, and appoint the best student of this class to be his successor.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45778" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="2">6.51</rating>
<name>Katagiri Shino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The loyal assistant of Dan Morihiko, she assisted Megumi, Kyu and Kinta in getting admitted to DDS, having met them during a case, featured in the first episode of the anime series.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45779" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Maki Shintarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>DDS`s head of forensics, Maki Shintarou is both a skilled teacher and doctor, and is quite intelligent in his knowledge of medical and forensic science.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45780" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Nanami Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nanami is another loyal righthand of Dan Morihiko. He`s very skilled in the art of disguise, and is often ordered by Dan to watch Class Q in cases by disguising as one of the suspects. Nanami`s very carefree, as he loves to show his new tricks (which Ryuu despises) to Class Q, but he can be extremely serious when he needs to be. His favourite disguise is that of a cactus, which is also occasionally accompanied by a flashy, brightly patterned sombrero or Mexican outfit. This usually appears when he is under stress, such as when he had to take Dan-sensei`s place as head of DDS during Dan-sensei`s hospital stay.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45781" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Yukihira Sakurako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The 17-year-old niece of Dan Morihiko is a renowned detective novel author, having published successful books while in high school. She didn`t want to be a detective at all at first, because she wanted to be a mystery novel writer. She`s in her 2nd year in Senior High School in the DDS. She received her first award from the police in 3rd grade in elementary school. She also barely mentions that Dan Morihiko is her uncle, since she desires to ascend in the DDS on her own. Fiercely competitive, more hot-headed than she lets other see, and quite stern on others and herself. She`s a friendly rival of Kyu (the only one who knows her relationship to Dan), and she possibly has a crush on him, and is a good friend of Megu and Kuniko.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45782" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-12">
<name>Shiramine Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiramine Hayato has an astonishing ability to perform magic tricks, inherited from his father (a famous magician), he is 16 years old, and often says that those who master magic are great detectives.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4749" picture="27700.jpg">Katsuragi Masanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45783" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-12">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Gouda Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A puzzle master and a mathematical olympian, Kyousuke is 19 years old.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45784" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-12">
<name>Shishido Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shishido Takeshi went to Harvard University to do a doctorate on criminal psychology before he joined DDS. Quite qualified himself, Takeshi has solved four homicide cases on his own.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2406" picture="83146.jpg">Kuriyama Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45785" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-12">
<name>Saburoumaru Yutaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yutaka studied at Tokyo University. He is arrogant and enjoys boasting about his "superiority". He thinks he will be the qualified detective, often becoming the comic relief in the series. He is initially in Class A after joining DDS, but later gets demoted to Class B in the manga. He knows Minami Megumi via the Tokyo National Talent Development Research Center and has a crush on Megumi`s older sister Akane alongside Kinta in one episode in the anime. Although he has an IQ of 180, he seems too inept in solving mysteries.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>89365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="8081" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目指せ! 世界一の名探偵!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Awaken! The Best Detective in the World!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezase! Sekaiichi no Meitantei!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9192" update="2005-11-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の第一歩・入学試験の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A First Step to Dreams - The Entrance Exam Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Daiippo Nyuugaku Shiken no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9482" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最終試験! 張り巡らされた罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Exam! The Stretched-Around Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saishuu Shiken! Harimegurasareta Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9549" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">入学式の殺意! 学園爆破予告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Intent to Kill at the School Entrance Ceremony! School Bomb Threat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyuugakushiki no Satsui! Gakuen Bakuha Yokoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9682" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗号解読!? 死者のメッセージ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crack the Code!? A Message from the Deceased</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angou Kaidoku!? Shisha no Message</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9711" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">証言者1000人完全なアリバイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Perfect 1000-Witness Alibi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougensha 1000 Nin Kanzen na Alibi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9828" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジグソーパズルの遺言状</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Jigsaw-Puzzle Will</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigsaw-Puzzle no Yuigonjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10100" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの美少年探偵! ついに登場!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pretty-Boy Detective! He Appears at Last!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Bishounen Tantei! Tsui ni Toujou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10146" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! 時を越えた殺人鬼!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown! The Cutthroat Who Crossed Through Time!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Toki o Koeta Satsujinki!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10231" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天才美少年・完全密室を暴く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beautiful Boy Genius - Exposing the Perfect Mystery Room</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensai Bishounen Kanzen Mitsushitsu o Abaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10325" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終決戦! Qクラスの真実!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Deciding Match! The Truth about Q Class!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saishuu Kessen! Q Class no Shinjitsu!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10826" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たたり発生!? 降霊術殺人事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Curse Breaks Out!? The Seance Murder Case</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatari Hassai!? Koureijuu Satsujin Jiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10880" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">密室の悪霊! 止まらない殺人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evil spirit in the locked room! The unstoppable murders</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misshitsu no Akuryou! Tomaranai Satsujin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11044" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霊界が告げる! 禁断の真相!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An announcement from the spiritual world! The forbidden truth!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reikai ga Tsugeru! Kindan no Shinsou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12507" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水深30m・海底密室殺人事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">30 meters under water. The case of the Underwater Locked Room Murder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suishin 30m Kaitei Misshitsu Satsujin Jiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13092" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クラス対抗! 人間消失バトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Class rivalry! Battle of the vanishing person</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Class Taikou! Ningen Shoushitsu Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18766" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死に至る秘境! 神隠し村伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The unexplored region leads to death! - Legend of Kamikakushi Village</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi ni Itaru Hikyou! Kamikakushi Mura Densetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19161" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決定的瞬間! 空に消える死体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defining Moment! Corpse Disappearing into the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketteiteki Shunkan! Sora ni Kieru Shitai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19915" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死のお告げ! 次はお前だ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Revelation of Death!! You`re Next!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi no Otsuge! Tsugi wa Omae Da!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19916" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">発覚! 仮面の教祖―罪と嘘!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Comes to Light! The Masked High Priest - Crimes and Lies!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakkaku! Kamen no Kyouso: Sai to Uso!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19917" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の神隠し! 答えは一つ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Mysterious Disappearance! There`s Only One Answer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Kamikakushi! Kotae wa Hitotsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23456" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死者のディナー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dinner of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shisha no Dinner</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25280" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アリバイ列車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Train Alibi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alibi Ressha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27441" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">呪いのアイドル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cursed Idol</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Noroi no Idol</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28189" update="2007-03-11">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿敵! 冥王星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Old Enemy! Pluto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukutekei! Meiousei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39360" update="2005-07-29">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狙われたメグ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Megu is being targeted</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nerawareta Megu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42608" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えたドラゴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lost Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Dragon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42610" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下牢獄SOS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SOS from the Underground Prison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chika Rougoku SOS</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42611" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">殺人コレクター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Collector of Killers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satsujin Collector</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42612" update="2005-11-30">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死の校内放送</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Broadcast of the Campus of Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi no Kounai Housou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42613" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネットの悲劇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tragic on the Net</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Net no Hibiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42614" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美少女探偵団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beauties Detective Squad</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bishojo Tanteidan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42615" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家庭科室の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mystery of the Home Economics Classroom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kateika Shitsu no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42616" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えた呪い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Curse that Disappeared</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Noroi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42617" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖の宝石爆弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bomb of the Terrifying Gem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyofu no Houseki Bakudan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42618" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻奏館殺人事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Murder Case of the Illusionary House</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gensoukan Satsujin Jiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42619" update="2006-12-25">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死神の旋律</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rhythm of the Death God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinigami no Senritsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42620" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">殺人協奏曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homicide Concerto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satsujin Kyousoukyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42621" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友情の決死行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Death March of Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuujou no Kesshikou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42622" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! 首なし女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel! The Headless Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Kubinashi Onna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42623" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔矢姫殺人事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Murder Case of the Maya Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maya-hime Satsujin Jiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42624" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切り者の里</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Village of the Traitor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragirimono no Sato</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42625" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">リュウの決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ryu`s Determination</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuu no Ketsui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42626" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">団守彦, 誘拐!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dan Morihiko, Kidnapped!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dan Morihiko, Yuukai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42627" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来の名探偵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Future Detective</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai no Meitantei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="100224" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ani-Kuri: Interview with director Abe Noriyuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124532" update="2012-11-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124533" update="2010-10-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140088" update="2012-11-23">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145611" update="2012-11-23">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145612" update="2012-11-23">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145613" update="2012-11-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145614" update="2012-11-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
