<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6424" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2010-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Cross Game</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Перекрестная игра</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">crossgame</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Перехрестна гра</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">四葉遊戲</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">クロスゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Cross Game</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">크로스 게임</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">幸运四叶草</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="241" approval="151" total="156">Touch</anime>
<anime id="352" approval="94" total="97">H2</anime>
<anime id="8181" approval="20" total="53">Ano Hi Mita Hana no Namae o Bokutachi wa Mada Shiranai.</anime>
<anime id="2168" approval="20" total="38">Major</anime>
<anime id="10539" approval="8" total="19">Shigatsu wa Kimi no Uso</anime>
<anime id="5909" approval="5" total="34">Toradora!</anime>
<anime id="9881" approval="4" total="9">Dia no Ace</anime>
<anime id="10244" approval="2" total="3">Baby Steps</anime>
<anime id="3147" approval="2" total="2">Nine</anime>
<anime id="8798" approval="1" total="8">Area no Kishi</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="50">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="144808">Baseball is not my thing but i got hooked to this show somehow....</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="114511">Don`t pass it off just  because it has sport in it, that`s missing the point.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="303972">i hate baseball, but this seems interesting&lt;br /&gt;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="391848">This show hit my weak spot... numerous times. I cried, I tensed up in suspense, I grinned, I laughed... it brought out a lot of emotion and kept me wanting more for the entire series. The simple soundtrack did surprisingly well at setting the mood and the characters were all very likable. I watched Touch after this, but this is tons more enjoyable IMO.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="337307">RECOMMENDED</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="357163">The characters in this show are very very lovable, especially the main characters. I especially love how Kou reacts to the situations he is in.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="381564">this is a really great series, even if youre not a fan of base ball, the histori is catching and fun, the characters are great too, it was a really nice surprice to find this anime for me</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="420391">Can be a bit of a hit and miss with people. It was a hit for me.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="254296">I think it is romance anime with baseball background, but it is really a great story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="249386">The first time I watch one of Adachi-sensei`s works being animated. But to be honest, I think these one is not meant for anime. The manga is way way much better. But regardless, if u dont want to read, this is still a good show.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="302824">I liked the ending, but it seemed like almost 3/4 of the episodes were unnecessary filler episodes. Plus i think there was too much emphasis on baseball. I wished it was more focused on the storyline, because it had a great one. The ending was great even though i  predicted it from the beginning.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="176136">Truly a series that bridges the sports and drama genres. A real gem!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="51414">Great!!!
Definity Recommend</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="394271">One of the best slice of life shows out there. A must watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="84224">had this one for a long time, not an sport fan. Now i have to reduce all my 10 rated anime´s because this is the best i have ever seen, truly an masterpiece in a league of its own..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="437523">Watched the entire season 3 times and I still think it is one of the best animes I have ever watched. You don`t have to like baseball to enjoy it, but if you do it makes it that much cooler. Besides the baseball the story is actually quite deep and the relationships and characters are amazing and very touching. Probably one of the first animes to bring out a large emotional response from me. Great anime.....if you read this far you should just watch it already.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="494108">This anime is simply awesome. The baseball setting is just an overlay of what this anime is actually about:
Adolosence, Love, Tears, Dreams... everything that defines growing up.
The artwork is mediocre, the pace is continious but slowly progressing, the love aspect is subtle - yet I didn`t feel bored any second, it just grabs you until you finished the series.
This anime has this special something, the character development is outstandingly well done, the whole series is overlayed by a good nature feeling. This is an anime I`d even put on my recommendations list for non-anime watchers.
A masterpiece that comes along only once in a while.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="719319">One of the Best series of all time......Just watch the first episode....u will cry!!.....I loved it very much!!.....the setting is baseball but its not just that......romance, comedy are also the best!! a definately 10/10.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="515975">This one took me by a surprise a bit.  I didn`t have any expectations going other than it was another sports/baseball anime but the characters, story, and relationships were really what made this one great.

It`s closer to a slice of life with baseball as the backdrop.  (although baseball does play an important part).

Watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="563093">Cross game is definitely one of the best series I`ve seen in quite a while, though the hardest thing for me is explaining just why I liked it so much. It`s undoubtedly very well-made, but Cross game has something more than that. Because of the dynamic scene transitions, a good usage of flashbacks and perfect music timing I simply couldn`t help feeling emotionally invested in each episode. It`s the kind of series where I`ll go from laughing to crying within just a few seconds, and at the next scene I`m at the edge of my seat in anticipation—a lot of this can be attributed to Sekita Osamu`s excellent directing. 

If you haven`t watched it already I`d highly recommend doing so, at the very least you`ll find it worth seeing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="784472">Baseball, dreams and coping with grief. The show develops almost all of its characters extremely well and isn`t afraid to not strictly state how any one character is feeling. A rare gem.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="111492">Storytelling done right. Alive characters and a compelling setting, with a great storyline. Audiovisually entrancing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="136296">Depictions of baseball are accurate, exciting, and often stunningly majestic.  Character development is masterful.  Story is never boring or predictable.  From beginning to end, a fantastic series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="275417">I barely knew anything about baseball before I watched this! A must watch, whether you like baseball or not!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="70951">unbelievable...
this is...
最高...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="86386">Awesome! Best anime i`ve ever watched.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="65644">This is a MUST SEE. Even if you don`t like baseball, you must see this; the character development is superb, and no anime I have seen so far has come close to this. SEE IT NAOWS!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="414004">definitely my second favorite baseball anime. not as great as Major, but outpaces one outs by a long shot. one of the few shows that i`ve seen in a while that combines a great story with amazing character development. 50 eps, and i`m still wanting more. highly recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="240815">First episode hooked me in. Awesome show, even for people who hate sports. The anime focuses more on the drama/slice of life with the baseball merely supporting the story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="34386">Just what anime is about!
Give it a try, sure you`ll love the characters and the story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="156582">Simply put... spectacular. Don`t be fooled by the gentle story, it`s really awesome.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="418577">A masterpiece in every single aspect. If you can watch just one more anime in your life, look no further.

Just take *everyone`s* advice and watch the show - and don`t look for more info - you really need to stay clear of spoilers on this one...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="206351">I usually avoid sports anime like the plague, but this series is so much more than that. The character development is amazing and the pacing is great over so many episodes. The baseball games are intense and yet there is also great romance and masterfully done sadness.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="67231">Not many Anime deserve a must see recommendation in the past years. Cross game definitely is one one of them though.
Brilliant character development combined with a storyline that is second to none.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="453003">Unbelievable... I couldn`t stop watching it until it finished. It has everything: romance, drama, action, sports...One of my all-time favs!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="77646">couldn`t  stop watching</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="540649">This is an amazing anime. Must see even if not a sports anime fan... You won`t regret it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="135091">great!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="528918">Even if you`re not a fan of baseball, there`s much more to this series. It really does make you laugh and cry. I think it`s one of the best anime I`ve seen so far.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="346924">Stop reading the recommendations and for god`s sake go watch this if you still haven`t! You`ll thank me later - I guarantee!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/crossgame/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1163" type="Animation Work">SynergySP</name>
<name id="2847" type="Series Composition">Tsuchiya Michihiro</name>
<name id="1869" type="Main Character Design">Kondou Yuuji</name>
<name id="1868" type="Direction">Sekita Osamu</name>
<name id="859" type="Original Work">Adachi Mitsuru</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
<name id="6061" type="Chief Animation Direction">Komaru Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="13264" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujisaki Kenji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr859 [Adachi Mitsuru], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23232 [Weekly Shounen Sunday].
Cross Game is the story of http://anidb.net/ch5809 [Kitamura Kou] and the four Tsukishima sisters, http://anidb.net/ch5812 [Ichiyou], http://anidb.net/ch5811 [Wakaba], http://anidb.net/ch5810 [Aoba], and http://anidb.net/ch5813 [Momiji]. The Tsukushima family runs a batting center with an attached coffee shop, and Kou`s father runs a neighbouring sporting goods store. Wakaba and Kou were born on the same day in the same hospital, and have been close friends since childhood — close enough that Wakaba treats Kou as her boyfriend, even though nothing is officially declared. Aoba, who is one year younger than Wakaba and Kou, doesn`t like how Kou is taking her sister away from her and claims she hates him.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2944">9.07</permanent>
<temporary count="3000">8.67</temporary>
<review count="5">7.53</review>
</ratings>
<picture>68290.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10580</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5941</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4456</identifier>
<identifier>ciirix</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/crossgame/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.viz.com/anime/streaming/cross-game</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Cross_Game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>クロスゲーム</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1611</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>333398</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11349</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3431" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>retro</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5809" type="main character in" update="2010-06-04">
<rating votes="54">8.77</rating>
<name>Kitamura Kou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In 5th grade in Part One, enters Seishuu High School at the start of Part Two. Kou lives down the street from the Tsukishima family and is treated like one of the family when he visits their house, batting cage, or coffee shop. He has been practically inseparable from Wakaba since their birth on the same day in the same hospital. While he shows little interest in baseball to outsiders, he has practiced daily at the Tsukishima Batting Center since he was old enough to swing a bat, enough so he is an excellent batter, especially against fastballs.
Kou is inspired by Aoba`s excellent pitching form to become a great pitcher himself, and secretly adopts Aoba`s daily training regimen. Although he doesn`t play baseball in junior high, his friends convince him to join the high school baseball club. Because Kou and his friends don`t take the placement test, they are put on the second string team (called the "prefab" team). With his changeup fastball, he becomes a well-known ace pitcher in the eastern conference.</description>
<picture>22908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5810" type="main character in" update="2009-12-27">
<rating votes="66">8.62</rating>
<name>Tsukishima Aoba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Third daughter of the Tsukishima family, one year younger than Kou and Wakaba. Aoba is jealous of how much time Wakaba spends with Kou, and frequently tells Kou how much she hates him. She is an excellent pitcher, having modeled her pitching form after Junpei Azuma. She has a poster of Ryota Igarashi, a famous fastball pitcher, hanging on her bedroom wall, and says she is only interested in a guy who can pitch a fastball at 160 km/h (about 100 mph). She loves to pitch in practice games, even though as a girl she cannot play in official baseball. However, she rarely shows her real speed as most catchers can`t handle it. Her name means "blue leaf".</description>
<picture>22909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5811" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-04">
<rating votes="13">7.55</rating>
<name>Tsukishima Wakaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Second daughter of the Tsukishima family, in 5th grade in Part One. Through their childhood, Wakaba is constantly with Kou. She constantly talks about their future together, even giving him a schedule of suggested future birthday gifts that includes an engagement ring for her 20th birthday. She frequently kisses Kou, which annoys their mutual friend Akaishi, who has a secret crush on her. For his eleventh birthday (and the second birthday in a row), Wakaba gives Kou an alarm clock because he has a hard time waking up in the morning. Her name means "young leaf".</description>
<picture>22910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5812" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="11">7.56</rating>
<name>Tsukishima Ichiyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First daughter of the Tsukishima family. At the start of Part Two, she is in her third year of college. After her mother`s death, she has run the Tsukishima household, acting as a surrogate mother for her sisters. She treats Kou like a younger brother. Her cooking is generally good, though she sometimes makes something wrong. She likes Junpei Azuma, but has trouble expressing her feelings to him directly. Her name means "first leaf".</description>
<picture>22911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5813" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="12">8.02</rating>
<name>Tsukishima Momiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fourth and youngest daughter of the Tsukishima family. She is in kindergarten during Part One, and in 5th grade at the start of Part Two. Although she lost her mother at a very young age, she has a happy, energetic, and outgoing personality. Despite their difference in ages, Momiji and Kou have a friendly, sibling-like relationship. She catches for him when he practices pitching. Once, while playing catch, Aoba apologizes for throwing the ball so hard and Momiji says she is used to it as Kou`s pitches are harder—to Aoba`s surprise. Momiji grows up to resemble her older sister Wakaba, which surprises Akaishi the first time he meets her. Her name means "maple leaf" or "crimson leaf".</description>
<picture>22912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5814" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="22">6.58</rating>
<name>Azuma Yuuhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Younger brother of Junpei Azuma, in the same year as Kou. Yuuhei transferred to Seishuu High School in order play baseball on the first-string team, and remains after the coach is dismissed. He has trouble recalling other people`s names and faces, but he remembers meeting Kou at the Tsukishima Batting Center several months before transferring to Seishuu. He lost some of his self-confidence after his transfer, but seeing Kou`s abilities during the practice game boosted his spirits.
Junpei injured his leg, ending his rising baseball career, while saving Yuuhei from falling down a staircase. Since then, Yuuhei has been very careful around all stairs and the guilt gave him a renewed drive to make it to the Koushien. He currently has stated romantic interests in Aoba.</description>
<picture>2988.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5815" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-12">
<rating votes="21">6.25</rating>
<name>Akaishi Osamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akaishi is a childhood friend of Kou and Wakaba, the same age as them, whose father owns a liquor/sake store in the neighborhood. In Part One, he has a crush on Wakaba and is jealous of Kou. In elementary school, is able to throw a 100 km/h fastball but is thrown out of Little League for fighting with opposing teams. After Wakaba`s death, Akaishi switches to catcher to fulfill Wakaba`s last dream in which Kou pitches to him at Koushien. At the start of high school, he refuses to take Coach Daimon`s placement test and is placed on the prefab team with Kou, and plans the boys` strategy to get rid of Daimon. Kou describes Akaishi as a brilliant catcher, and according to Aoba, Akaishi is one of the few people able to catch her pitches at full power. Coach Maeno sometimes consults with him over game strategy, and makes Akaishi the team captain during his third year. He is greatly shocked when he meets Akane Takigawa because of her resemblance to Wakaba, and while he has feelings for her, he actively works to bring her and Kou together.</description>
<picture>73266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5816" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-12">
<rating votes="10">6.21</rating>
<name>Nakanishi Daiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="376" picture="53996.jpg">Sonobe Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5817" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-12">
<rating votes="11">2.88</rating>
<name>Senda Keiichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Seishuu baseball team, in the same year as Kou. Senda claims to be a lady`s man, and constantly pursues Aoba as well as other girls. He is the only non-recruit to pass Coach Daimon`s placement test, and is placed on the first-string team as a pitcher. Because of this, during his first semester he frequently brags about how good he must be. Coach Maeno comments that Senda is too much of a showoff to be a good pitcher but would be a good "flashy shortstop". After making too many errors as pitcher during the first scrimmage between the first-string and prefab teams, he is demoted to the prefab team, where Maeno substitutes him as shortstop. After Coach Daimon is fired, Senda becomes the starting shortstop and leadoff batter. In his third year of high school, he becomes impressed by Aoba`s hard work and begins taking practice more seriously.</description>
<picture>73268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5818" type="appears in" update="2011-03-15">
<name>Miya Toshio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12665" picture="227715.jpg">Kawakami Takafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5819" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<name>Tanabe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="5820" type="appears in" update="2010-01-29">
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<name>Makihara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2474" picture="228619.jpg">Endou Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5821" type="appears in" update="2011-03-15">
<name>Sekiguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5410" picture="222917.jpg">Douzaka Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5822" type="appears in" update="2011-03-15">
<name>Tsuneki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2840" picture="22915.jpg">Suzuki Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5823" type="appears in" update="2011-06-13">
<name>Kayama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73343.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5824" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<name>Morinaka Wataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149561.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5825" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<name>Takada Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61519.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="5826" type="appears in" update="2011-06-13">
<name>Iwai Tetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2840" picture="22915.jpg">Suzuki Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5827" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-29">
<rating votes="7">5.68</rating>
<name>Maeno Sentarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5828" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-29">
<rating votes="4">5.57</rating>
<name>Ookubo Hiroko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3786" picture="223623.jpg">Kameoka Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5829" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="10">2.29</rating>
<name>Shidou Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4457.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3424" picture="24518.jpg">Hirata Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5830" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<name>Ookubo Yokomichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5831" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-28">
<rating votes="2">4.35</rating>
<name>Tsukishima Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2401" picture="23194.jpg">Kawazu Yasuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5832" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="5">7.67</rating>
<name>Nomo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Tsukishima`s black-and-white cat. He appears in the background throughout the series. He is named after Nomo Hideo (former Japanese baseball player who had success in the MLB).</description>
<picture>2987.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5833" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-28">
<rating votes="3">3.14</rating>
<name>Kitamura Kensaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1406" picture="18432.jpg">Suzuki Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5834" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-28">
<rating votes="4">3.70</rating>
<name>Kitamura Kimie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5835" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="10">1.45</rating>
<name>Daimon Shuugo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A nationally renowned high school baseball coach, having taken teams to Koushien several times, winning it twice. He is hired by Interim Principal Shidou, replacing Coach Maeno in the process, to build up Seishuus baseball team. He recruits his own players from around the country, including Azuma and Miki, to create a first-string team, relegating the existing baseball club to a second-string squad called the prefab or farm team—which he calls a "cesspool". He is depicted as proud and rigid: Senda tells the rest of the prefab team there is no chance of being promoted back to first-string, because that would require Daimon to admit he made a mistake, and Miki is demoted to the bench for disobeying a direct order to make a play. Akaishi criticizes Daimon for using up players in order to win, noting that despite his career record, none of his former players have succeeded as pros. During the rematch scrimmage with the prefab team, Daimon refuses to acknowledge that Kou has become a better pitcher, that his team needs Miki, or that he must change his set coaching strategy. After losing the scrimmage, Daimon is forced to resign along with Shidou. He then becomes head coach for Kurokoma Jitsugyou, employing the same talent-buying strategy he used in Seishuu, where he loses in the first round of the regional tournament because he refuses to take Miki`s team seriously.</description>
<picture>32011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3124" picture="24096.jpg">Furusawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5836" type="appears in" update="2010-01-29">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Shidou Eitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="324" picture="223539.jpg">Saitou Jirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5837" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-29">
<rating votes="3">4.34</rating>
<name>Miki Tatsumasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3787" picture="25815.jpg">Miyazaki Hiromu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5838" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="13">6.37</rating>
<name>Azuma Junpei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Older brother of Yuuhei Azuma, several years older than him. Junpei was a star pitcher and cleanup batter in high school, who was being scouted by pro teams during his last year of school. His team was on the verge of winning the regional finals when he sustained a career-stopping leg injury while saving Yuuhei from falling down a staircase, and he quit baseball and now runs a small produce distributor. He is depicted as cheerful and feckless, but Yuuhei claims initially his cheerfulness is forced; Kou describes Junpei as unreliable, in part because he never follows through on his promise to find Yuuhei an apartment. Upon meeting Ichiyou, the summer of Kou`s second year of high school, Junpei immediately starts courting her, and they eventually start going out. In Kou`s third year, Ichiyou promises to marry him if Seishuu makes it to Koushien, and Junpei becomes an assistant coach for Seishuu`s baseball team, enthusiastically cheering the team on because his wedding is riding on it.</description>
<picture>32015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5839" type="appears in" update="2011-02-03">
<rating votes="2">2.13</rating>
<name>Hayashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Third strongest fighter at Kou`s grade school and one of Akaishi`s friends.</description>
<picture>22913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2840" picture="22915.jpg">Suzuki Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5840" type="appears in" update="2011-02-03">
<rating votes="1">2.85</rating>
<name>Nawata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fifth strongest fighter at Kou`s grade school and one of Akaishi`s friends.</description>
<picture>22914.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="33300" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-19">
<rating votes="7">7.36</rating>
<name>Takigawa Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl the same age as Ko with an uncanny resemblance to http://anidb.net/ch5811 [Tsukishima Wakaba] as she would be if she had lived. Her parents open a soba restaurant across the street from Kitamura Sporting Goods the summer of Ko`s second year of high school.
She is an excellent artist, and won the grand prize of the Koshien Poster Art Competition using Aoba as the model for a pitcher. She is enrolled in Seisen Private Girl`s Academy.
Akane becomes a waitress at Coffee Clover because she does not get paid working at her parents` restaurant, and becomes close to Aoba, telling her she always wanted a younger sister. Akane has suffered from an unknown disease since childhood, and the summer of her third year of high school is admitted into the hospital for tests leading to surgery. She promises Ko she will go out with him after she is discharged. This is later forgotten as she sacrifices her own feelings towards Ko and helps Aoba show her feelings as well. It is shown that she shows kindness towards Akaishi.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>73270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33301" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-10">
<rating votes="10">1.46</rating>
<name>Asami Mizuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asami Mizuki is Aoba`s cousin, the same age as her. Mizuki`s father, Asami Isamu, is a younger brother of the Tsukishima sisters` mother and a world-renowned mountain climber. As a result of his father`s travels, Mizuki has been raised overseas most of his life, and is an excellent climber.
He returns to Japan to attend high school, living with the Tsukishimas and enrolling in Seishu at the same time as Aoba. He is popular with girls but he claims to be interested in only Aoba. He initially sees Ko as his rival for Aoba, and frequently mentions that Ko does not yet pitch 100 mph, but he comes to recognize Yuhei Azuma as a rival as well.
He is in the mountaineering club at school, which he uses as a cover for his own activities as the club activities are below his skills. He is often depicted free climbing tall structures, such as poles and school buildings, without equipment.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>73271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33331" type="appears in" update="2011-06-13">
<name>Kishibe Keisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5410" picture="222917.jpg">Douzaka Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33332" type="appears in" update="2011-06-13">
<name>Kamikawa Noboru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="324" picture="223539.jpg">Saitou Jirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33552" type="appears in" update="2011-06-18">
<name>Itoyama Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73743.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5410" picture="222917.jpg">Douzaka Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33553" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="2">2.07</rating>
<name>Koganezawa Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Senda`s cousin. She plays in Satomi women`s team.</description>
<picture>73744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33554" type="appears in" update="2011-08-17">
<name>Yashiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of baseball team, same year as Aoba.</description>
<picture>75434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33555" type="appears in" update="2011-08-17">
<name>Mitani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of baseball team, same year as Aoba.</description>
<picture>46344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3787" picture="25815.jpg">Miyazaki Hiromu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33556" type="appears in" update="2011-08-17">
<name>Ehara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of baseball team, same year as Aoba.</description>
<picture>46325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12665" picture="227715.jpg">Kawakami Takafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34538" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<name>Nakagawa Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1693" picture="19890.jpg">Sudou Erika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34542" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<name>Onoda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First-String player: second batter, right fielder.</description>
<picture>75421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12665" picture="227715.jpg">Kawakami Takafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34543" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<name>Kubo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First-String player: fifth batter, third baseman.</description>
<picture>75422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34544" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<name>Takizawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First-String player: sixth batter, catcher.</description>
<picture>75423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1406" picture="18432.jpg">Suzuki Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34545" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<name>Ishiguro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First-String player: seventh batter, second baseman.</description>
<picture>75424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2840" picture="22915.jpg">Suzuki Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34546" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<name>Ogura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First-String player: eight batter, left fielder.</description>
<picture>75425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2474" picture="228619.jpg">Endou Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34585" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<name>Matsuyama Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain and catcher of Satomi women`s team.</description>
<picture>75463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="137" picture="214428.jpg">Sasamoto Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34586" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<name>Kojima Minako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pitcher of Satomi women`s team.</description>
<picture>75464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34592" type="appears in" update="2011-07-21">
<name>Ozaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Right fielder of Ouka women`s team. Clean up hitter.</description>
<picture>75469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9599" picture="222797.jpg">Aoyama Touko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34594" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<name>Sawaguchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pitcher of Ouka women`s team.</description>
<picture>75472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34627" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<name>Sakurakouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pitcher of Kirigaoka West. Also known as "The Smiling Prince". Has his own fanclub within the school.</description>
<picture>75514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2840" picture="22915.jpg">Suzuki Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34855" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="5">7.46</rating>
<name>Mishima Keitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Third baseman of Ryuou Academy.</description>
<picture>75865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34856" type="appears in" update="2011-07-21">
<name>Terada Kantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Baseball coach of Ryuou Academy.</description>
<picture>75867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34857" type="appears in" update="2011-07-21">
<name>Nishiguchi Kantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Baseball coach of Sannou High.</description>
<picture>75868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9546" picture="77661.jpg">Sakaguchi Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34858" type="appears in" update="2011-07-21">
<name>Shimano Tadashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First baseman and clean up hitter of Ryuou Academy.</description>
<picture>75869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35649" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="3">7.30</rating>
<name>Oikawa Takurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Second pitcher of Ryuou Academy. His fastballs exceeds 140km/h.</description>
<picture>45740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35650" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Matsushima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First pitcher of Ryuou Academy. His fastballs exceeds 140km/h.</description>
<picture>45746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2840" picture="22915.jpg">Suzuki Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35651" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Tsuchida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsuchida is a boy who had a crush on Aoba for a long time and gave her a love-letter in the middle of match with Ryuou Academy. He has a friend named Omura with him who also has a crush on Aoba and also has a love-letter for her.</description>
<picture>45752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5410" picture="222917.jpg">Douzaka Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35652" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Akane Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Father of Takigawa Akane.</description>
<picture>45801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2474" picture="228619.jpg">Endou Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35653" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Akane Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of Takigawa Akane.</description>
<picture>45802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10340" picture="222848.jpg">Uetake Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35654" type="appears in" update="2011-12-13">
<name>Keikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A detective who is catching the suspicious guy at school which Akane attends.</description>
<picture>45807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3787" picture="25815.jpg">Miyazaki Hiromu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35655" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Fushinsha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man who was hiding in the girl`s dressing room.</description>
<picture>45822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5410" picture="222917.jpg">Douzaka Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35656" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Take Gen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man who tried to look good to Akane by making some guys scare her.</description>
<picture>45825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2840" picture="22915.jpg">Suzuki Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35681" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Imai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momiji`s friend. He trains aikido.</description>
<picture>46014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10340" picture="222848.jpg">Uetake Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35682" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Shimano Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cousin of Shimano Tadashi and clean-up hitter from Ryuou girls Academy. Known as "Shimakei".</description>
<picture>46055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35683" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Takei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Women national team coach.</description>
<picture>46056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2474" picture="228619.jpg">Endou Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35684" type="appears in" update="2011-08-23">
<name>Fukuda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fukuda Hiromi is the ace of Sapporo Ladybirds, who won last year`s Summer Championship.</description>
<picture>46057.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1693" picture="19890.jpg">Sudou Erika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35685" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Kangoshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A nurse from hospital where Aoba stayed with broken leg.</description>
<picture>46058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35688" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<name>Kojima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Coach of Kinjo High school baseball team.</description>
<picture>46087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35692" type="appears in" update="2011-08-17">
<name>Stalker Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man who stalked Aoba and then Akane.</description>
<picture>46284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12665" picture="227715.jpg">Kawakami Takafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35695" type="appears in" update="2011-08-17">
<name>Hama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of baseball team, same year as Aoba.</description>
<picture>46346.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35722" type="appears in" update="2011-08-18">
<name>Sena Koukou Kantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Coach of Sena High School.</description>
<picture>46748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6082" picture="222919.jpg">Hirano Toshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35723" type="appears in" update="2011-08-18">
<name>Nisikura Kantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Coach of Nisikura High School baseball team.</description>
<picture>46778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5410" picture="222917.jpg">Douzaka Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="97657" update="2009-03-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="28">9.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四つ葉のクローバー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Four-Leaf Clover</title>
<title xml:lang="id">Clover Berdaun Empat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yotsuba no Clover</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97658" update="2009-03-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密兵器</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Weapon</title>
<title xml:lang="id">Senjata Rahasia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu Heiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97659" update="2009-03-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちゃんと?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Real?</title>
<title xml:lang="id">Keras?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chanto?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97660" update="2009-03-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大っ嫌い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Hate You!</title>
<title xml:lang="id">Aku Membencimu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Kirai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99662" update="2009-04-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナベ貸してくれる?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Can I Borrow a Pot?</title>
<title xml:lang="id">Boleh Kupinjam Alat Memasakmu?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nabe Kashite Kureru?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="101598" update="2009-05-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誰だ? おまえ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who Are You?</title>
<title xml:lang="id">Siapa Kau?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dare Da? Omae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102069" update="2013-07-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102070" update="2011-08-19">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102107" update="2009-05-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">面食いなんです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sucker for a Pretty Face</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Menkui Nan Desu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102409" update="2009-05-13">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニヤニヤするな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wipe That Smirk Off Your Face</title>
<title xml:lang="id">Jangan Cengengesan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Niyaniya Suruna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102410" update="2009-05-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冗談はよせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yeah, Right</title>
<title xml:lang="id">Jangan Bercanda</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joudan wa Yose</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102411" update="2009-05-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しまって行こー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Do This!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shimatte Ikou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102412" update="2009-05-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">似てるんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Two Are Alike</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Niterunda</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104287" update="2009-06-19">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">何点?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Many Points?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanten?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104288" update="2009-06-19">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏合宿?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Training Camp?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Gasshuku?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104289" update="2009-06-19">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝負しなさい!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Challenge You!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoubu Shinasai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104941" update="2009-07-05">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もっと楽しめよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enjoy It More</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motto Tanoshime yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105084" update="2009-07-12">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="14">9.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">知るか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Should I Know?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiruka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105189" update="2009-07-18">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シンドイな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s Tough</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shindoi na</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105541" update="2009-07-25">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オーディション?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Audition?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Audition?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105868" update="2009-08-02">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出の...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide no...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106134" update="2009-08-08">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">朝見水輝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mizuki Asami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asami Mizuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106270" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆転するよね?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`ll Make a Comeback, Right?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakuten Suru yo ne?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106271" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なめてたでしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Underestimated Us, Didn`t You?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nameteta Desho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106272" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">何はともあれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Matter What Happens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nani wa Tomo Are</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108308" update="2009-09-06">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やめるなよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t You Quit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yameruna yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108422" update="2009-09-11">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光栄ですね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s an Honor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouei Desu ne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108423" update="2009-09-11">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">知ってるよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Know</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitteru yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108459" update="2009-09-11">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">... かもしんない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He May Be Right</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">... Kamoshinnai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109067" update="2009-10-04">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わらせようぜ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s End This</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owareseyouze</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109316" update="2009-10-11">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="13">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">だれがァ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No I`m Not!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dare ga!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110770" recap="true" update="2009-10-26">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="13">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">若葉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wakaba</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakaba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110883" update="2009-10-25">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">年をとるのかなァ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do Ghosts Grow Older?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toshi o Toru no kana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111126" update="2009-11-01">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちょっと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chotto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111298" update="2009-11-09">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はたまた運命... か</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Or Is It Fate?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatamata Unmei... ka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111389" update="2009-11-13">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あけまして</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happy New Year</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akemashite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111390" update="2009-11-13">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">2月14日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">February 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">2-gatsu Juuyokka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111391" update="2009-11-13">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女子野球へ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Women`s Baseball?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joshi Yakyuu e!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111880" update="2009-12-06">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よく寝たからでしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Guess I Slept Well</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoku Neta kara Desho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111888" update="2009-12-07">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ずっとずっと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Since Forever</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zutto Zutto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111889" update="2009-12-07">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初デートですよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s His First Date</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsu Date Desu yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112213" update="2010-01-28">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの夏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyone`s Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Natsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112214" update="2010-01-28">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">行くぞ甲子園!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Koshien, Here I Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iku zo Koushien!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112215" update="2010-01-28">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バカたれ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Idiot!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baka Tare!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112995" update="2010-01-11">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あいかわらずだな...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She Hasn`t Changed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aikawarazu Da na...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112996" update="2010-01-11">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">失投... か?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Careless Pitch?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shittou... ka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116313" update="2010-02-07">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こっちのセリフだろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s My Line!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kocchi no Serifu daro!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116320" update="2010-02-22">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="15">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウソついてもいいか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Can I Lie?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uso Tsuite mo Iika?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116321" update="2010-02-08">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やーな感じだなァ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ve Got a Bad Feeling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ya na Kanji Da na</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116547" update="2010-02-22">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="20">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界中で一番...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">More Than Anyone in the World...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekaijuu de Ichiban...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116548" update="2010-02-22">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽しんでるか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Are You Having Fun?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanoshinderuka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116549" update="2010-02-22">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Right</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131911" update="2011-08-19">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132538" update="2011-08-19">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132566" update="2013-07-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132567" update="2013-07-14">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132568" update="2011-08-19">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132569" update="2013-07-15">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132570" update="2013-07-15">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4a</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
