<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6438" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-07-06</startdate>
<enddate>2009-09-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Princess Lover!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Любимец Принцесс</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">프린세스 러버</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Princess Lover</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Улюбленець принцес!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">公主恋人</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">プリンセスラバー!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">公主戀人</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7577" type="Alternative Setting">Princess Lover! (2010)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7009" approval="120" total="139">Ladies versus Butlers!</anime>
<anime id="5188" approval="51" total="70">Goshuushou-sama Ninomiya-kun</anime>
<anime id="9931" approval="33" total="37">Walkure Romanze</anime>
<anime id="8830" approval="5" total="12">Kono Naka ni Hitori, Imouto ga Iru!</anime>
<anime id="9855" approval="2" total="17">Outbreak Company</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="421101">a Great Ecchi And Comedy Anime :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="339854">If you like Ecchi, this one is good to get and watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="262878">first ep was superb&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;hope the rest to, at first we ought to think of normal orphan harem anime, but later we figure out that it involve revenge (sweet!!)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="74379">excellent character animation! the girls are just BEAUTIFUL to watch. simple harem anime with generic storyline.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.prilover.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2346" type="Chief Animation Direction">Suzuki Shingo</name>
<name id="2102" type="Animation Work">Go Hands</name>
<name id="2346" type="Character Design">Suzuki Shingo</name>
<name id="1862" type="Series Composition">Nakamura Makoto</name>
<name id="2347" type="Direction">Kanazawa Hiromichi</name>
<name id="3399" type="Music">Kikuya Tomoki</name>
<name id="7044" type="Music">Minami Yoshiki</name>
<name id="18656" type="Original Work">Ricotta</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7008 [Arima Teppei] is a second-year high school student who lost both of his parents in a traffic accident on their way home from a family trip. His grandfather, http://anidb.net/ch10321 [Arima Isshin], happens to wield the puppet strings in Japan`s vast economy and demands that Teppei becomes his successor as the head of the Arima Group. To prepare for his debut into high society, Teppei enrols in an elite academy for the scions of the rich and powerful.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2851">3.86</permanent>
<temporary count="2893">6.54</temporary>
<review count="3">6.05</review>
</ratings>
<picture>52958.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10699</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8231</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6201</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>7468</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4480</identifier>
<identifier>ibbskp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.prilover.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Princess_Lover!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>プリンセスラバー!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1682</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334075</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11642</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>765</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3508" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-09-26">
<name>school for the rich elite</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3908" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>lap pillow</name>
<description>As a sign of closeness the usually male character is encouraged to rest his weary head on the female’s lap.</description>
<picurl>167007.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5820" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-29">
<name>combat butler -- DO NOT ADD -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is meant to be deleted. Please DO NOT add it to further anime. Please tag the relevant characters "butler" and whatever combat- or martial arts-related tag is appropriate. For the already tagged anime, please tag the relevant characters, and then remove this tag from the related anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6345" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-15">
<name>unexpected inheritance</name>
<description>News of a death in the family is rarely well received, especially when its someone who cares very deeply for you. So deeply, in fact, that they have left you with a massive inheritance; but apparently not so much that they ever bother to get to meet you in person. This benevolent but reclusive relative you couldn`t pick out of a police lineup (and trust us, this is something of a Plot Point) is usually an aunt or uncle, grandparent, great aunt or uncle, or related so remotely as to give a team of forensic genealogists weeks of work to find a direct connection.
The inheritance might be wads of cash, a lovely piece of land, and/or a set of family memorabilia. Depending on whether or not your relative was a benevolent anonymous benefactor is whether the money is tainted with the blood of innocents, the land contains a haunted house built on an indian burial ground, and whether the family memorabilia is something beneficial like an ancestral weapon or protective charm, or a higly cursed evil weapon or artifact of death.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>168739.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7008" type="main character in" update="2010-03-30">
<rating votes="38">5.73</rating>
<name>Arima Teppei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main protagonist, prior to the series was the son of a happy family whose father was a noodle shop owner. Coming back from school one day he learns his parents were killed in a automobile accident, he is then picked up by his grandfather, Isshin Arima who is the owner of the Arima Financial Combine, which is a very wealthy and powerful industry in japan. Isshin then demands Teppei to become the successor to the Arima corporation and Teppei is enrolled in the most prestigious private school in japan.</description>
<picture>25271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7009" type="main character in" update="2010-09-15">
<rating votes="95">7.81</rating>
<name>Silvia van Hossen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Silvia van Hossen is one of the four main heroines of the series. Fiancée of Arima Teppei and sparring partner. She is very skilled in sword fighting and enjoys her spars with Teppei. She is a bit reserved and is trying to understand Teppei being a friend first. She is the elder of the two daughters of the Head of Van Hossen Family, Vincent van Hossen. Maria, her younger sister wants her to marry Teppei. She is best friends with Charlotte, the Princess of Hazelrink.</description>
<picture>25273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7010" type="main character in" update="2010-03-30">
<rating votes="76">7.69</rating>
<name>Charlotte Hazelrink</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the four main heroines of the series. The princess of Hazelrink Principality, whom Teppei first meets and saves from a carriage incident involving thugs. She likes to tease Teppei and has a cheery nature.</description>
<picture>25272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7011" type="main character in" update="2010-03-30">
<rating votes="47">7.20</rating>
<name>Fujikura Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the four main heroines of the series. She is the personal maid of Teppei and helps him in his new life as the upcoming heir of the Arima house.</description>
<picture>25274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7012" type="main character in" update="2010-03-30">
<rating votes="36">6.03</rating>
<name>Houjouin Seika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of the Houjouin company and rivals Arima which leads her to dislike Teppei when he first arrives at Shuuhou Academy. She is the `Club Representative` of the `Society Club` at Shuuhou Academy and reserves the right to enroll students in the club only those whom she thinks have what it takes to be eligible for membership of the school`s most extravagance club. Outside school, she is a very popular model and at the same time one of the most gifted young fashion designers in entire Japan.</description>
<picture>25275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10321" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="12">6.50</rating>
<name>Arima Isshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10322" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="7">4.74</rating>
<name>Vincent van Hossen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10323" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-24">
<rating votes="22">5.95</rating>
<name>Maria van Hossen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="269" picture="25727.jpg">Miyake Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10324" type="appears in" update="2009-07-11">
<rating votes="9">7.54</rating>
<name>Teppei no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="628" picture="188442.jpg">Dodo Asako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10325" type="appears in" update="2009-07-11">
<rating votes="5">6.35</rating>
<name>Teppei no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10326" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="8">4.16</rating>
<name>Alfred</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10488" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-16">
<rating votes="9">1.57</rating>
<name>Nezu Haruhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>35650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10489" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-30">
<rating votes="14">5.34</rating>
<name>Kaneko Ayano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the members of Houjouin Seika`s posse.
In the PS2 version of the original game, however, she was promoted from a sub-character to a heroine.</description>
<picture>35652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10490" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-16">
<rating votes="10">5.15</rating>
<name>Takezono Erika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>35651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10493" type="appears in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Kouchou-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11269" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-19">
<rating votes="11">1.25</rating>
<name>Haltman Bezelheim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33507.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11270" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-19">
<rating votes="15">4.34</rating>
<name>Josephine Joster</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27472" type="appears in" update="2011-01-20">
<rating votes="2">5.66</rating>
<name>Otomura Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daughter of Otomura Kenzo.
She say to know Teppei`s father from a long time.</description>
<picture>5701.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27473" type="appears in" update="2011-01-20">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Imai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>5702.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="104909" update="2009-07-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">馬車と姫君</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Noble Girl and a Horse Carriage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Basha to Himegimi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104964" update="2009-07-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園と再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Academy and Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuen to Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105025" update="2009-07-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105026" update="2009-07-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105113" update="2009-07-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">剣と舞踏会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sword and Dance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsurugi to Butoukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105166" update="2010-04-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">湯けむりポロリとラッキースケベ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steam, Crying, and the Lucky Pervert</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukemori PORORI to Lucky Sukebe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105167" update="2009-07-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夕日と観覧車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunset and Ferris Wheel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuhi to Kanransha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105168" update="2009-07-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">薔薇と靴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rose and Shoe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bara to Kutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106325" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">喪失と再生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loss and Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushitsu to Saisei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106326" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤と青</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red and Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aka to Ao</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106327" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽園と真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paradise and Reality</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakuen to Shinjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106328" update="2009-08-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">婚約者と花びら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fiancee and Flower Petals</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kon`yakusha to Hanabira</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108304" update="2009-09-06">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">騎馬隊と列車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cavalry and Train</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kibatai to Rensha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108416" update="2009-09-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリンセスラバー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Princess Lover!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Princess Lover!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111061" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">~乙女の秘密~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl`s Secret 01</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111239" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2009-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ① ブラックホールの秘密編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama 1: Black Hole no Himitsu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111816" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2009-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ② 変身☆魔法少女編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama 2: Henshin Mahou Shoujo Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111817" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マジカル騎士マリアちゃん特別予告 Vol.2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Knight Maria-chan 02</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magical Kishi Maria-chan Tokubetsu Yokoku #2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111818" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">~乙女の秘密~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl`s Secret 02</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111819" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マジカル騎士マリアちゃん特別予告 Vol.1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Knight Maria-chan 01</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magical Kishi Maria-chan Tokubetsu Yokoku #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111832" update="2013-01-17">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">~乙女の秘密~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl`s Secret 03</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111833" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マジカル騎士マリアちゃん特別予告 Vol.3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Knight Maria-chan 03</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magical Kishi Maria-chan Tokubetsu Yokoku #3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111834" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2009-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DVD第3卷特典「Picture Drama③」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama 3: Wish You Were Here Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113036" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2010-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ④ 女だらけの水泳大会! ポロリもあるでよ! 編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama 4: Onna Darake no Suieitaikai! Porori mo aru deyo! Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113037" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マジカル騎士マリアちゃん特別予告 Vol.4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Knight Maria-chan 04</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magical Kishi Maria-chan Tokubetsu Yokoku #4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113038" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">~乙女の秘密~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl`s Secret 04</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116744" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">~乙女の秘密~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl`s Secret 06</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116745" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マジカル騎士マリアちゃん特別予告 Vol.6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Knight Maria-chan 06</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magical Kishi Maria-chan Tokubetsu Yokoku #6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116746" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2010-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ⑥ いまだから言っちゃう? プリラバ感想やら反省会やら! 編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama 6: Imada Kara Icchau? Puriraba Kansou Yara Hanseikai Yara! Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116747" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">~乙女の秘密~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl`s Secret 05</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116748" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マジカル騎士マリアちゃん特別予告 Vol.5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Knight Maria-chan 05</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magical Kishi Maria-chan Tokubetsu Yokoku #5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116749" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2010-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ⑤ 綾乃とエリカの少し奇妙な冒険編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama 5: Ayano to Erika no Sukoshi Kimyou na Bouken Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136403" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ecchi Bonus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136404" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ecchi Bonus 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
