<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6462" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-10-08</startdate>
<enddate>2009-12-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sasameki Koto</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Whispered Words</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">轻声密语</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Sasameki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ささめきこと</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6443" approval="66" total="75">Aoi Hana</anime>
<anime id="4223" approval="51" total="62">Strawberry Panic</anime>
<anime id="9922" approval="22" total="29">Sakura Trick</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="194504">For those who like... soft anime. If you like daily life/romance/shoujo (ai), then this one is definitely worth a try. Nice slow paced, bright story with not-slapstick-like comedy elements that really crack a smile at times. Less cliché too, without an all-girls school/onee-sama!~/Virgin Mary, that shoujo ai shows sooo love to bring up to the center of attention. Overall, a surprisingly satisfying and refreshing series.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/sasameki/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Animation Work">AIC</name>
<name id="1753" type="Direction">Suganuma Eiji</name>
<name id="9271" type="Chief Animation Direction">Inomata Masami</name>
<name id="10183" type="Original Work">Ikeda Takashi</name>
<name id="9271" type="Character Design">Inomata Masami</name>
<name id="21247" type="Music">Hasumi Shigeomi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a seinen yuri manga by http://anidb.net/cr10183 [Ikeda Takashi], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr12274 [Monthly Comic Alive].
http://anidb.net/ch10843 [Sumika] is madly in love with http://anidb.net/ch11618 [Ushio], and has been for some time; but Ushio only shows any interest in cutesy girls. Sumika, a card-carrying badass TDB who helps run her family`s dojo, does not fit this bill even a little. Cue angst, as she is forced to watch from the sidelines as Ushio falls for girl after girl, none of them her. However, it seems that things may take a turn for the better...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1374">5.64</permanent>
<temporary count="1383">7.04</temporary>
<review count="1">6.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>228890.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10701</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6203</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4501</identifier>
<identifier>ceyeun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/sasameki/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Whispered_Words</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ささめきこと</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1704</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334987</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11783</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2405</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2009/sasamekikoto</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11296</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3868" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>sleepover</name>
<description>A sleepover, also known as a pyjama party or a slumber party, is a party where a guest or guests are invited to stay overnight.
Typical participant activities include staying up late, talking, eating and playing until falling asleep, which sometimes never happens for a few high energy guests. Sleepovers are usually held at one participant`s house, with other guests sometimes bringing their bedtime things, such as pillows or sleeping bags. Common activities include playing board games or video games, having pillow fights, watching movies, ordering pizza, eating sweets and playing party games such as Truth or Dare. 
While sleepovers are practised by both girls and boys, in anime it is an almost girls-exclusive event and a good excuse for more fanservice.</description>
<picurl>160892.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4207" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>doujin</name>
<description>Doujin is a general Japanese term for a group of people or friends who share an interest, activity, hobbies, or achievement. The word is sometimes translated into English as clique, coterie, society, or circle (e.g., a "sewing circle").
In Japan the term is used to refer to amateur self-published works, including but not limited to manga, novels, fan guides, art collections, music and video games. Some professional artists participate as a way to publish material outside the regular publishing industry.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>68439.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-03">
<name>sign language</name>
<description>The character can communicate with sign language either instead of or in addition to speech.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6023" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-01">
<name>cosplay restaurant</name>
<description>Cosplay restaurants are theme restaurants and pubs that originated in Akihabara, Tokyo, Japan around the year 1999. They include maid cafés and butler cafés, where the service staff dress as elegant maids, or as butlers. Such restaurants and cafés have quickly become a staple of Japanese otaku culture. Compared with service at normal cafés, the service at cosplay cafés involves the creation of a rather different atmosphere. The staff treat the customers as masters and mistresses in a private home rather than merely as café customers.
The popularity of the cosplay restaurants and maid cafés has spread to other regions in Japan, such as Osaka`s Den Den Town as well as other countries, such as Hong Kong, Taiwan, Singapore, Mexico, and Canada.
Often such cafés or a more simple kissaten, small Japanese-style coffee shops, are part of school festivals where the protagonists` class runs one.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10843" type="main character in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="29">7.40</rating>
<name>Murasame Sumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>35158.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11618" type="main character in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="19">6.39</rating>
<name>Kazama Ushio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sumika`s best friend and classmate, Ushio is a naive girl madly in love with cute girls. She often gets crushes but they are all one-sided. She considers Sumika as a very precious friend, but she`s completely unaware of her feelings and often remarks her for being "cool", "not cute" and "not her type", without knowing Sumika`s inner reaction at these words. She lives alone with her older brother.</description>
<picture>35157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1445" picture="33610.jpg">Takamoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11619" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="3">5.74</rating>
<name>Torioi Kiyori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate and friend of Sumika and Ushio, they often eat lunch between the three of them. She has a happy personality and she loves eating a lot. According to Sumika, she`s straight.</description>
<picture>35163.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11620" type="main character in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="9">7.07</rating>
<name>Hachisuka Tomoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate of Sumika and Ushio who is also a lesbian. She has a relationship with another classmate, Taema Miyako. She is 18 years old, having taken two years off from school to save her family`s corporation from bankruptcy (a feat publicly attributed to her father). Due to this age difference, she has a more mature outlook on life then the other characters. The Hachisuka family is very wealthy and traditional, but they have no choice but to accept Tomoe`s habits. She claims that "high school is all about being in clubs", so she tries to set up a "Girls` Club" for all the "girl-loving girls who had no choice but to enter a co-ed school".</description>
<picture>35161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5878" picture="45926.jpg">Harada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11621" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-16">
<rating votes="7">4.61</rating>
<name>Akemiya Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A shy boy, classmate of the main characters. He likes Sumika, but when he notices that she likes Ushio he tries to crossdress in order to catch her attention. His younger sister however finds out about it and sends some pictures of him to a magazine. He is hired against his will and the pictures start appearing on magazines, where Ushio sees them and gets a crush for "her", wanting to meet "her".</description>
<picture>35654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9510" picture="185781.jpg">Shimizu Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11622" type="main character in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="6">4.00</rating>
<name>Taema Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoe`s girlfriend. While she looks like an innocent and clumsy girl, popular with boys (who nickname her "Princess"), her true self is quite different, having a devilish, bad-mannered personality, always prone to bad-mouth or tease other people. Tomoe seems to be the only one able to "control" her; they are always together, and for this reason they had no friends before knowing Sumika and the others. Miyako is a daughter of Hachisuka family`s driver, a fact that doesn`t sit well with the rest of Tomoe`s household but as with other things, they cannot go against her.</description>
<picture>35160.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11623" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-10">
<rating votes="6">3.29</rating>
<name>Aoi Azusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate of the main characters. Aoi is a yuri fan, in particular she loves the works of the female shoujo novelist Masaka Orino. The real life profile of this author has been kept hidden from the audience, but she figures her as "gorgeous and romantic", living in a "pretty Western-style house, surrounded by flowers or dolls". Masaka Orino, however, is a man, and he`s Ushio`s brother, writing under a pen name. Sumika knows this but she doesn`t want to disappoint her, so she keeps it secret. Aoi thinks that love between girls must be something completely pure and fragile, hidden away from people`s eyes; for this reason she doesn`t like Tomoe and Miyako`s relationship, considering them way too blatant. She likes attending yuri-only events and writing yuri doujinshi, and she wishes to do that together with Sumika.</description>
<picture>35159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2505" picture="141583.jpg">Makiguchi Mayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11778" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-16">
<rating votes="3">4.25</rating>
<name>Yamasaki Akemi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A shy boy, classmate of the main characters. He likes Sumika, but when he notices that she likes Ushio he tries to crossdress in order to catch her attention. His younger sister however finds out about it and sends some pictures of him to a magazine. He is hired against his will and the pictures start appearing on magazines, where Ushio sees them and gets a crush for "her", wanting to meet "her".</description>
<picture>35162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9510" picture="185781.jpg">Shimizu Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13286" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-26">
<rating votes="5">6.50</rating>
<name>Sekidera Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39332.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13287" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-28">
<rating votes="2">3.33</rating>
<name>Hayasumi Noe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13288" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-26">
<rating votes="3">3.23</rating>
<name>Nishikigi Chizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13289" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-17">
<rating votes="5">2.14</rating>
<name>Akemiya Manaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Masaki`s younger sister, and the one responsible for throwing him into the modelling business. Although rather teasing in this aspect, she does try to help her brother in her own ways, proven when she tries to concoct a scheme to get him together with Sumika.</description>
<picture>43133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13290" type="appears in" update="2009-11-26">
<name>Murasame Tenkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13291" type="appears in" update="2009-11-27">
<name>Monkasei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39343.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13316" type="appears in" update="2009-11-28">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Wakaba Kasuga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10974" picture="39418.jpg">Furukawa Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13317" type="appears in" update="2009-11-28">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Furutaka Kako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10951" picture="222825.jpg">Hara Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13318" type="appears in" update="2009-11-28">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Akitsuki Isuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39417.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13319" type="appears in" update="2009-11-28">
<rating votes="3">5.73</rating>
<name>Akemiya Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9510" picture="185781.jpg">Shimizu Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13320" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-01">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Kazama Norio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ushio`s older brother, they live alone in a messy house. He is a writer who publishes shoujo yuri novels under the pen name of Orino Masaka. His true identity isn`t known to his audience, so he`s believed to be a mysterious lady writer.</description>
<picture>84958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13321" type="appears in" update="2014-12-27">
<name>Murasame Ani #1</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brother #1 of 3 triplets.</description>
<picture>39423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13322" type="appears in" update="2014-12-27">
<name>Murasame Ani #2</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brother #2 of 3 triplets.</description>
<picture>39424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13323" type="appears in" update="2014-12-27">
<name>Murasame Ani #3</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brother #3 of 3 triplets.</description>
<picture>39425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13325" type="appears in" update="2009-11-29">
<name>Chouno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13326" type="appears in" update="2009-11-29">
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<name>Joshi Seito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10951" picture="222825.jpg">Hara Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14946" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Azusa Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="12672" picture="42847.jpg">Ozaki Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14947" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Azusa Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14948" type="appears in" update="2010-02-11">
<name>Teruaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14949" type="appears in" update="2010-02-11">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2031" picture="21359.jpg">Hasegawa Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14950" type="appears in" update="2010-02-11">
<name>Oba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10385" picture="77512.jpg">Nakajima Kayou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14951" type="appears in" update="2010-02-11">
<name>Oji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2672" picture="188511.jpg">Endou Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14952" type="appears in" update="2010-02-11">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Konomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41430" type="appears in" update="2012-02-18">
<rating votes="2">7.91</rating>
<name>Akemiya Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9510" picture="185781.jpg">Shimizu Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="108990" update="2009-10-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ささめきこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whispered Words</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasameki Koto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109202" update="2009-10-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かわいいひとたち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pretty People</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaii Hito-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109322" update="2012-02-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109323" update="2012-02-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110702" update="2009-10-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファーストキス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">First Kiss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110819" update="2009-10-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">4+1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">4+1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">4+1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110977" update="2009-10-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">friends</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Friends</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111228" update="2009-11-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Couple`s Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111358" update="2009-11-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boys and Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111569" update="2009-11-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ripple</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ripple</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ripple</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111701" update="2009-11-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひまわりの君</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like a Sunflower</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himawari no Kimi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111836" update="2009-12-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハプニング・イン・サマー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happening in Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Happening in Summer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111969" update="2009-12-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんでもない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Nothing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nandemonai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112008" update="2009-12-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-31</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">CALLING YOU</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calling You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Calling You</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112009" update="2009-12-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨を見たかい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Did You See the Rain?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame o Mitakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216553" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">女の子実験室 あやひーめぐみんエミリー 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ladies` Laboratory with Ayahii, Megumin and Emirii 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onnanoko Jikkenshitsu: Ayahii, Megumin, Emirii 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216554" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2010-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">女の子実験室 あやひーめぐみんエミリー 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ladies` Laboratory with Ayahii, Megumin and Emirii 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onnanoko Jikkenshitsu: Ayahii, Megumin, Emirii 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216555" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2010-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">女の子実験室 あやひーめぐみんエミリー 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ladies` Laboratory with Ayahii, Megumin and Emirii 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onnanoko Jikkenshitsu: Ayahii, Megumin, Emirii 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216556" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2010-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">女の子実験室 あやひーめぐみんエミリー 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ladies` Laboratory with Ayahii, Megumin and Emirii 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onnanoko Jikkenshitsu: Ayahii, Megumin, Emirii 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216557" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">女の子実験室 あやひーめぐみんエミリー 5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ladies` Laboratory with Ayahii, Megumin and Emirii 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onnanoko Jikkenshitsu: Ayahii, Megumin, Emirii 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216558" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2010-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">女の子実験室 あやひーめぐみんエミリー 6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ladies` Laboratory with Ayahii, Megumin and Emirii 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onnanoko Jikkenshitsu: Ayahii, Megumin, Emirii 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216559" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1 (1:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216560" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2 (1:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216561" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216562" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216563" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD CM 1 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216564" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD CM 2 (0:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216565" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD CM 3 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216566" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD CM 4 (0:30)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
