<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6481" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-06-25</startdate>
<enddate>2009-09-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fight Ippatsu! Juuden-chan!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Charger Girl Ju-den Chan</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fight, One Shot! Charger Girls!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">С первого удара! Заряжай-ка!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Разряд! Со всей дури!!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">魔力充電娘</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">魔力充电娘</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">juuden</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ファイト一発! 充電ちゃん!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Juden-chan</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="416687">It`s a shame Ditama Bow puts in so much ecchi, because he`s talented enough to be a mainstream success.  An imaginative and rich premise with a surprisingly heartfelt and touching story, obscured by extraneous ecchi.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="780822">Hilarious, wholesome, sexy. What more could you ask for?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="377192">Very good ecchi with a nice romance history.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="469109">Lol really nice ecchi... and no censorships... well except for the lower area... the S and M are in big red letters of Sento`s workplace... i didnt get the joke until the 10th ep xD really nice show</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/juden-chan/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3012" type="Character Design">Watanabe Atsuko</name>
<name id="123" type="Series Composition">Yamada Yasunori</name>
<name id="2965" type="Direction">Kimura Shin`ichirou</name>
<name id="985" type="Work">Studio Hibari</name>
<name id="582" type="Original Work">Ditama Bow</name>
<name id="3012" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Atsuko</name>
<name id="3672" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugimoto Isao</name>
<name id="2822" type="Music">Tada Akifumi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr582 [Ditama Bow], serialised in Comic Gum.
Juuden-chan is the name given to a group of special girls from a different dimension who use electricity to cheer up suicidal people. To find the people in need, http://anidb.net/ch6417 [Plug] uses a device that tells her a persons level of depression — A being worst, F being happiest. Since Plug and her co-workers come from a different dimension, they can fly, pass through things, and pull magic plugs out of power transformers. Plug tries her best, but encounters, http://anidb.net/ch13461 [Oumi Sento], a boy who can both see and touch her — usually with a baseball bat. Unfortunately for Plug, his sister is her assignment and she has to get past him to `charge` her up.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1115">4.64</permanent>
<temporary count="1128">6.65</temporary>
<review count="3">6.27</review>
</ratings>
<picture>22451.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15715</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10463</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5973</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>7744</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4454</identifier>
<identifier>fmsmcb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/juden-chan/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fight_Ippatsu!_Jūden-chan!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ファイト一発!_充電ちゃん!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1660</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>333975</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11005</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1816" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-09">
<name>uniform -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>The "uniform" tag is to be split and removed. Please help by tagging the character with the appropriate kind of uniform (e.g. school uniform, maid dress, etc) and removing this tag from them, and by not adding this tag to any further characters. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2711" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>urination</name>
<description>Urination, also known as micturition, voiding, peeing, weeing, pissing, and more rarely, emiction, is the ejection of urine from the urinary bladder through the urethra to the outside of the body. In healthy humans the process of urination is under voluntary control. In infants, some elderly individuals, and those with neurological injury or extreme psychological problems, urination may occur as an involuntary reflex. In other animals, in addition to expelling waste material, urination can mark territory or express submissiveness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2824" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>pseudo tentacle rape scene</name>
<description>If this was porn she (or rather the audience) would have even more fun!</description>
<picurl>160554.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6417" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="23">6.92</rating>
<name>Plug Cryostat</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The female protagonist. She is a "Juuden-chan": someone from a world that is parallel to our own, capable of recharging people who are depressed or unlucky. She is however not very good at it and is a bit of an airhead. Because she has the ability to use phasing, she normally can`t be seen by regular humans. This is done so she can do her job without causing distraction. She loves to watch an ecchi anime series called "Miracle Witch Milly". Whilst other Juuden-chan focus on charging people and getting paid, Plug focuses on discovering the root of their problems so that they won`t become depressed again.</description>
<picture>23799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="425" picture="17296.jpg">Fukuhara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6418" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="22">8.36</rating>
<name>Arrester Blanket</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Plug`s fellow Juuden-chan and rival, who becomes her supervisor. She is rather serious when it comes to work and is rather annoyed with how Plug is carrying out her job. In turn, Plug finds Alesta irritating for interfering with her work and the two girls tend to fight a lot. She sometimes ends up crying, which Plug uses as blackmail material. Compared to Plug, Alesta is rather busty, which causes Plug to tease her about that. She has feelings for Sento from the moment she saw him, but he is rather oblivious to this. Following their first meeting, Alesta seems to have garnered a fetish for being hit by a baseball bat.</description>
<picture>23800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6419" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="9">6.18</rating>
<name>Oumi Hakone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sento`s younger sister. She lives together with her brother and wants to do household chores, but Sento told her not to because he feels responsible for her. She cares for her brother and is frustrated that she is not allowed to help him, making her depressed and unhappy (and a prime target for Plug).</description>
<picture>23801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="184" picture="23381.jpg">Miyazaki Ui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6420" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="7">6.20</rating>
<name>Tomonaga Iono</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The best friend of Hakone. She has a crush on Sento and is struggling to confess to him, but Sento seems to be unaware of it and only thinks of her as a little sister, much to her frustration.</description>
<picture>23802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6594" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="225">8.43</rating>
<name>Andou Mahoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mahoro is an android created by VESPER to fight an alien invasion by Saint in the 1980s. She is immensely powerful and fast, and is considered to be a formidable opponent by her enemies.
Being an android, she has a limited life span. At the beginning of the story, she has just 398 days to live, and is given the choice to do anything she wants by VESPER. She chooses to become a maid for Suguru Misato: his father was her superior commander, and she was forced to kill both him and an alien when the alien took him hostage.
Mahoro has a very sunny disposition and is friendly to just about everyone — she becomes a welcome regular at the market and becomes famous at Suguru`s school for working for him. She also quickly becomes an excellent cook, able to emulate and recreate dishes from the best restaurants. She is also quite devoted to Suguru, with feelings for him reminiscent of both doting mother and shy girlfriend.</description>
<picture>28703.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13461" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="11">6.94</rating>
<name>Oumi Sento</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young man who is the only human capable of seeing both Plug and Alesta. He works at a family restaurant and has a rather short temper, which results in frequently hitting Plug (and at times Alesta as well) with a baseball bat or whatever is within reach; this has become a running gag in the series. He occassionally helps Plug and Alesta with their work, teaching Plug that the best way to find an opportunity to charge is to make one yourself. He lives with his younger sister.</description>
<picture>39580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13462" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="6">5.41</rating>
<name>Rona Elmo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Houden-chan (discharger girl) that saps away positive energy from people. She hates being alone, and since noone in the human world can see her, she treats everyone like toys. Despite her small appearance, she is very powerful, being able to defeat Rouden-chan at the snap of her finger.</description>
<picture>39852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13463" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="7">6.26</rating>
<name>Pulse Trans</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The head of the organisation that oversees the Juden-chan and Roden-chan. She has a fierce temper and constantly deducts Plug`s salary due to her incompetence. She does however have good judgement in her commands.</description>
<picture>44165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3374" picture="24704.jpg">Tomizawa Michie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13464" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="8">7.13</rating>
<name>Kuran Shant</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Roden-chan, aka Leakage Girl, who monitors activity such as electrical disturbances, and apprehends criminals suspected of harboring electricity for profit. They have more advanced equipment than the Juden-chan, as well as gadgets to apprehend criminals.</description>
<picture>44148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13465" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="7">6.38</rating>
<name>Reika Galvini</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another Roden-chan, who often partners with Kuran. Both of them seem to take a liking to Sento after their first encounter with him.</description>
<picture>44149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13466" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="6">4.83</rating>
<name>Rinko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13467" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="5">4.39</rating>
<name>Sokko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4634" picture="223664.jpg">Kinoshita Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13468" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="5">4.39</rating>
<name>Taako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13469" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="6">4.83</rating>
<name>Maako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8996" picture="151657.jpg">Ishikawa Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13470" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="6">4.83</rating>
<name>Chiiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13471" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-05">
<rating votes="6">4.30</rating>
<name>Tenchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sento`s boss at a family diner he works at. She appears to have a lolita complex and takes interest in young girls, particularly Hakone.</description>
<picture>44150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13472" type="appears in" update="2009-12-05">
<rating votes="7">8.14</rating>
<name>Sweetie Milly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A magical girl from a rather perverted television show called "Miracle Witch Milly" that seems to be aired at whatever time of day is convenient. Partnered with her insulting sidekick Bitch, she goes her against her arch rival, Bloody Selica, generally having her clothes removed in the process.</description>
<picture>39768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="618" picture="223541.jpg">Okajima Tae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13473" type="appears in" update="2009-12-05">
<rating votes="4">6.80</rating>
<name>Bitch-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sweetie Milly`s animal sidekick. Favourite pasttime: insulting Milly as the failure that she is.</description>
<picture>39766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13474" type="appears in" update="2009-12-05">
<rating votes="6">5.56</rating>
<name>Bloody Celica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Milly`s flat-chested arch rival.</description>
<picture>39765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13475" type="appears in" update="2009-12-05">
<rating votes="2">4.06</rating>
<name>Paita-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Celica`s animal side kick. Unlike Bitch-kun he completely adores his owner.</description>
<picture>39767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13611" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Kajiwara Kenta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young boy who became worried about the prospect of bullies at school, due to the effects of Rona Elmo. He is called a Z rank since the counter-current he gives off to Juden-chan trying to charge him is too powerful. Nonetheless, Plug became determined to save him, even at the risk of burning her arms off.</description>
<picture>39850.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="102031" update="2010-07-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">AT-X Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103069" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぷらぐ・いん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plug in!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Plug in!</title>
<summary>On the way to find the main charging target, Juden chan, or better known as "Plug," met a college student named Sendo. She explains that her job is to give people energy when they feel as if they have none.  Sendo`s younger sister, Hakone, apparently is scouted to be the main charging target. Dismissing Plug`s explanation as nonsense, Sendo argued that he couldn`t believe her whole back story. However he will be changing his mind after things start to transpire...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531452</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="103417" update="2009-07-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミックガム7月号付録</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Comic Gum Appendix No. 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mick Game 7 Tsuki Gou Furoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104707" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たいみんぐ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Timing!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Timing!</title>
<summary>Plug has to notice people who have already been charged are becoming depressed again. Advice shared by Sento helps her realize that simply charging a person does not solve their problems. What can plug do to help her new target?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531454</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104873" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ろっく・おん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lock on!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lock on!</title>
<summary>Aresta reports to the section manager about Plug`s inability to pass the test, resulting in a reduction of her pay as punishment. Furthermore, she decides to add a supervisor to monitor her activity as soon as she heads back home to relax.  As Aresta tries to go stealth, things get all mixed up as usual...eventually Plug gets scolded again...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531456</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104883" update="2009-07-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104884" update="2009-07-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">9.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105049" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">依緒乃, クライシス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Iono Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iono, Crisis</title>
<summary>Hakone`s friend Iono comes to see Sendo, however he becomes extremely cautious. Iono came to express her love for Sendo, disregarding her other ongoing relationship with someone at her school, causing a chaos to breakout. Hearing this situation from Sendo, Hakone goes to confront Iono to explain why her brother acted the way he did...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531460</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="105157" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めいど・いん・アレスタ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maid in Aresta!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maid in Aresta!</title>
<summary>A bug with the new model suits became apparent when searching for the juden target causing injury onto Plug`s arms. Aresta takes time off of work to make sure she`s okay.  With Plug hospitalized and to keep her from boredom, Aresta dresses up in a maid outfit to distract her. However one things leads to another....
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532050</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="105158" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆流</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Counter-Current</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakuryuu</title>
<summary>Neodymium Company, part of Juden-chan`s division, took a hit from the latest accident.  This time, however, the target has changed, becoming Kajihara Kentaro - a countercurrent target - who received the designation of a Z-target meaning that he could possibly be the perfect target they`re looking for.  Unaware of this development, Plug and her team start to investigate on their own...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531462</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="105159" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はぷにんぐ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happening!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Happening!</title>
<summary>Summer`s finally here! Sento, Iono and Hakone head to the beach! But why is Plug and Alester joining them?  Just as the two get into their bikinis, they locate another prime charging target....but will this spoil their vacation at the sea?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531458</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106188" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無茶と優しさ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Craziness and Kindness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mucha to Yasashisa</title>
<summary>After spending time being hospitalized, Plug finally returns back to work, opting out of rehab. Plug, desperate to return back to work, still can`t fully move her arms and is ordered by the section manager to follow through with her rehab under Aresta`s watch. Just as she begins rehab, a new target appears, but before Plug can rush off Aresta stops her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532052</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106320" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">要警戒! 放電ちゃん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vigilance Required! Discharge Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">You Keikai! Houden-chan!</title>
<summary>According to Hoden-chan, the captain of the Juden Division 2 section said that there has been a surge of energy.  Everyone in the division is quickly dispatched out. However, Hoden-chan has a secret ability to alter energy...and will Plug be able to perform her job without getting emotionally involved with her targets?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532058</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106321" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぷれぜんと!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Present!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Present!?</title>
<summary>With Christmas coming around, Juden and her company have been especially busy, as the number increases exponentially around this season.  However, this season there seems to be an over abundance of these targets.  Meanwhile, Juden uncovers the plan by the Roden pair to steal all the life force and energy from people...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532056</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106322" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">監査室特務部・漏電ちゃん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audit Office Special Department - Short-Circuit Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kansashitsu Tokumubu Rouden-chan!</title>
<summary>Plug is fully recovered and has been overzealously trying to work overtime to make up for her absence at work, which catches the attention of their superior.  While waiting in their superior`s office they meet the ultra-beautiful and super elite Roden-chan.  Introductions and formalities can wait as there`s a huge power leakage that Juden and Aresta must attend to...as well as protect Sento?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532054</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="108234" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふぁいと! いっぱつ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fight! One Shot!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fight! Ippatsu!</title>
<summary>A rising sense of precaution starts to surround Hoden-chan, meanwhile Plug and Aresta decide not to be seen by Sento. Aresta tries to restore Sento back to normal, but regardless of how many times she tries, she always seems to fail. Plug on the other hand, has replaced a new employee on tracking down a Z-target, but as usual things start to make a turn for the worse...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>533250</identifier>
<identifier>charger-girl-ju-den-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="108558" update="2009-09-14">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-09-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Promo Teaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111667" update="2009-11-23">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">ELeC TriCk Music Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111734" update="2009-11-28">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Anti-Piracy Promos</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112248" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボーナスチャージ1 「露天風呂で充電~」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus Charge 1: Charging in an Open Air Bath!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bonus Charge 1: Rotenburo de Juuden~</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116584" update="2010-02-25">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボーナスチャージ2 「スィーティ・アレスタ登場」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus Charge 2: Sweety Arrester Entry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bonus Charge 2: Sweety Arrester Toujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116878" update="2010-03-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117033" update="2010-03-21">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボーナスチャージ3 「温泉の夜は更けて!!」 PART I</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus Charge 3: Stay Up Late at Night In the Hotsprings!! Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bonus Charge 3: Onsen no Yoru wa Fukete!! - Part I</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117384" update="2010-04-08">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>7</length>
<rating votes="1">1.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボーナスチャージ4 「温泉の夜は更けて!!」 PART II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus Charge 4: Stay Up Late at Night In the Hotsprings!! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bonus Charge 4: Onsen no Yoru wa Fukete!! - Part II</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118151" update="2010-05-04">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>7</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボーナスチャージ5 「充電ファイト!」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus Charge 5: Charging Fight!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bonus Charge 5: Juuden Fight!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118715" update="2010-06-07">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>7</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラストチャージ 「宴の夜」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Charge: Party Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last Charge: Utage no Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="185150" update="2017-03-02">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Transformation Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
