<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6503" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-08-01</startdate>
<enddate>2009-08-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Naruto Shippuuden: Hi no Ishi o Tsugu Mono</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Naruto Shippuden: The Successor of the Fire`s Will</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Naruto Shippuuden Movie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Naruto Shippuuden: The Will of Fire Still Burns</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Naruto Shippuuden: The Inheritors of the Will of Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Naruto Shippuuden: Die Erben des Willens des Feuers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Naruto Shippuuden - Hi no Ishi o Tsugumono</title>
<title xml:lang="mn" type="synonym">Наруто Шиппүүдэн: Галын Хүслийг Залгамжлагч</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 NARUTO 疾風伝 火の意志を継ぐ者</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Naruto Shippuden the Movie: The Will of Fire</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4880" type="Parent Story">Naruto Shippuuden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="316585">Definitely the best Naruto movie ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="229307">Really Amazing movie the best movie for Naruto so far you must see</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/naruto/movie09/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="2977" type="Original Work">Kishimoto Masashi</name>
<name id="3051" type="Character Design">Nishio Tetsuya</name>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="669" type="Direction">Murata Masahiko</name>
<name id="4455" type="Character Design">Suzuki Hirofumi</name>
<name id="12448" type="Music">Yaiba</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
</creators>
<description>Ninjas with bloodline limits begin disappearing in all the countries and blame points toward the fire nation. By http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Tsunade]`s order, http://anidb.net/ch7248 [Kakashi] is sacrificed to prevent an all out war. After inheriting charms left by Kakashi, http://anidb.net/ch226 [Naruto] fights through friends and foes to prevent his death while changing the minds of those who`ve inherited the will of fire.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1718">4.63</permanent>
<temporary count="1747">6.76</temporary>
<review count="2">4.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>23585.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10757</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6325</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4645</identifier>
<identifier>eoxnrn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/naruto/movie09/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Naruto_Shippuden_the_Movie:_The_Will_of_Fire</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2100</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>333702</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11728</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>naruto-shippuden-the-movie-the-will-of-fire</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-08">
<name>ambitious</name>
<description>having a strong desire for success or achievement; wanting power, money, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1286" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-28">
<name>megalomaniac</name>
<description>Megalomania is a psychopathological condition characterized by delusional fantasies of power, relevance, and omnipotence, and by inflated self-esteem.&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>70559.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3779" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-06">
<name>fight for peace</name>
<description>Don`t they all... 
The protagonists are trying to ensure long-lasting peace by fighting a vicious enemy, hoping to defeat the threat permanently.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5788" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-03">
<name>experiments</name>
<description>Involves (para-)scientific experiments.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5956" parentid="2862" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>broken friendship</name>
<description>For a broken friendship a group of three friends is a must, the break up can be caused by betrayal or death, a love triangle is also possible. The ghost of the old friendship will be the cause of many flashbacks and reminiscences. A dreaded face to face could be a major event or just used as plot device.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="226" type="main character in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="1440">6.74</rating>
<name>Uzumaki Naruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60771.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7213" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="361">8.16</rating>
<name>Jiraiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jiraiya (自来也) is a remarkable ninja and possibly the closest thing to the Hokage that never was, not only trained by the third Hokage but also the trainer of the man who would eventually go on to become the Fourth, as well as a young boy who dreams of one day being the Hokage himself. Since childhood, he has had an eye for the opposite sex and often had conflicts with one of his team, Tsunade, over her figure. Jiraiya was not a model ninja at all and usually ended up as the fall guy, although his master comparing him to Orochimaru, his other team member, didn`t help much.</description>
<picture>54626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7248" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="1671">8.57</rating>
<name>Hatake Kakashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatake Kakashi is the leader and teacher of Team 7, consisting of http://anidb.net/ch7196 [Uchiha Sasuke], http://anidb.net/ch7194 [Haruno Sakura], and http://anidb.net/ch240 [Uzumaki Naruto]. He is initially portrayed as a detached and apathetic figure, but as the series progresses, his loyalty to his friends and students becomes increasingly apparent. Kakashi`s past has been extensively explored in the series, resulting in a gaiden being devoted to his past experiences. Kakashi has appeared in several pieces of Naruto media, including three of the four featured films in the series, all of the original video animations, and several video games.</description>
<picture>54614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7256" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-26">
<rating votes="471">8.04</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hyuuga Hinata is a member of Team 8 who suffers from a lack of self-confidence throughout the series. She is very shy and always reluctant to speak her mind or to do something that might antagonize another character, causing her difficulties whenever she is on a mission. This results in her effective expulsion from her clan even though she is the eldest daughter of the Hyuga clan`s leader and the heiress to the clan. Hinata`s inability to stand up for herself caused her father to disown her at a young age, leaving her in the care of her teacher, Kurenai Yuhi. Masashi Kishimoto had originally intended Hinata to be a regular member of the Hyuga clan but instead made her a ninja. Soon after her introduction, Hinata begins training to become stronger, both to overcome her own weaknesses and to prove her worth to her father. Her efforts begin to prove successful towards the end of Part I, as her father takes a greater interest in her training.
Source: wikipedia.org</description>
<picture>29538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7260" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="325">7.91</rating>
<name>Gaara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7698" type="main character in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="784">2.77</rating>
<name>Haruno Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruno Sakura is the sole female member of Team 7. Kishimoto created her as the heroine of the series, although he has admitted that he has little perception of what an ideal heroine should be. As a child, Sakura was taunted by other children because of her large forehead, a feature Kishimoto has tried to emphasize in Sakura`s appearances. She was comforted by Ino Yamanaka. As the two continued to grow, however, they became increasingly distant due to their shared affection for Sasuke Uchiha. During most of Part I, Sakura is infatuated with Sasuke, and spurns the advances of Naruto Uzumaki. After Sasuke leaves the village, she resolves to become stronger by training with Tsunade. In Part II, she displays highly developed skills from her training, and a more open disposition towards Naruto.</description>
<picture>2928.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="234" picture="244740.jpg">Nakamura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7707" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="77">5.56</rating>
<name>Aburame Shino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aburame Shino (油女 シノ) is one of the members of Team 8 and is fascinated with insects; he spends his free time capturing and studying insects and often uses them as analogies during conversation. A deep connection with insects runs in Shino`s family, as each person born in to the Aburame clan is infused with a special breed of insects known as "destruction bugs" during birth. In exchange for using Shino as a hive, the bugs do as he commands. During a battle, Shino directs his bugs towards an opponent, boxing them in without their knowledge, and absorbing their chakra once they have been surrounded. Shino`s merciless tendencies, in regards to opponents as well as his attachment to insects, have caused other characters to label him as "creepy". Nevertheless, Shino cares deeply for his teammates, being acutely aware of their inner workings and always regretting when he is unable to help them.</description>
<picture>27918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7742" type="appears in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="64">6.36</rating>
<name>Sarutobi Asuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sarutobi Asuma is the son of the http://anidb.net/ch8865 [Third Hokage] and uncle to http://anidb.net/ch10931 [Konohamaru]. He is a jounin shinobi who leads http://anidb.net/ch8615 [Shikamaru], http://anidb.net/ch8617 [Chouji] and http://anidb.net/ch8616 [Ino] in Team Asuma. Asuma is generally quite laid back and gets on well with all of his students, but spends a lot of time with Shikamaru in particular; the pair often plays shogi together, though Asuma has never beaten him in a game. In battle Asuma tends to use a combination of taijutsu and chakra infused blades.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>54647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8604" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="63">4.74</rating>
<name>Inuzuka Kiba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30821.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8605" type="appears in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="15">5.65</rating>
<name>Akamaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27846.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8606" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="419">6.45</rating>
<name>Tsunade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsunade, as well as her former teammates http://anidb.net/ch7213 [Jiraiya] and http://anidb.net/ch8603 [Orochimaru], is a former student of the http://anidb.net/ch8865 [Third Hokage]. She is also the granddaughter of the http://anidb.net/ch8859 [First Hokage], and so many characters in the series refer to her with the Japanese honorific "hime" (meaning "princess"). Despite her connections to past Hokage, Tsunade hates the position when she is first introduced. After her brother and boyfriend died in pursuit of their dreams to become Hokage, she lost faith in the title and the concept of dreams. She regains her faith in both after meeting http://anidb.net/ch240 [Naruto Uzumaki], who consistently overcomes any obstacle in his own dreams of being Hokage. As a result, Tsunade accepts the position of Fifth Hokage to protect http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure] on behalf of everyone she has loved. Despite the importance of her position, Tsunade tends to avoid her duties, instead leaving them for her assistants. She will fulfil her role to address matters important to the village, and throughout Part II leads Konoha in combating http://anidb.net/ch8599 [Akatsuki]. When Konoha is invaded by http://anidb.net/ch11993 [Pain], she uses up all her energy summoning http://anidb.net/ch17274 [Katsuyu], her slug summon, to protect the villagers, and stays in a coma for a long time causing her to be dismissed as Hokage temporarily. Tsunade possesses a number of traits that set her apart from other characters in the series, such as being a compulsive gambler with terrible luck. On the rare occasions that she hits a winning streak she perceives it as a bad omen, and makes it a point to fortify her defences when it occurs. Additionally, although she is in her fifties, she constantly assumes the appearance of a twenty-year-old woman, retaining only her characteristically large breasts. Despite her odd personality Tsunade is a talented ninja; she has superhuman strength that allows her to reduce buildings to rubble and can heal injuries that most others would consider incurable. Her healing abilities are such that she has devised a method of regeneration for herself, making her all but invincible in battle. At the conclusion of Part I, Tsunade takes http://anidb.net/ch7194 [Haruno Sakura] as an apprentice, teaching her how to use both of her trademark abilities.</description>
<picture>27913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8608" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-28">
<rating votes="127">4.91</rating>
<name>Sai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sai is introduced during Part II of the series as http://anidb.net/ch7719 [Uchiha Sasuke]`s replacement in Team 7. Having been a member of The Foundation since he was a child, Sai has been trained to not possess or desire any type of emotion or camaraderie. After spending time with http://anidb.net/ch226 [Uzumaki Naruto], however, he begins to crave bonds with other people, which has since become his primary role in the series. Sai`s attempts to form bonds involve giving pet names to others; however, he often says what he actually thinks of a person, resulting with him choosing names such as "fatso" and "ugly". He eventually learns from his mistakes and attempts the opposite approach, for instance, calling http://anidb.net/ch8616 [Yamanaka Ino] "pretty lady". When not making an attempt to bond with others, Sai spends his time painting and drawing, and has produced thousands of works. His artistic talents extend to his choice of attacks in battles: he can infuse chakra with his inking brush to make his drawings come to life.</description>
<picture>30810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8609" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="171">7.58</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Neji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8610" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="126">6.61</rating>
<name>Rock Lee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4757" picture="46951.jpg">Masukawa Youichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8611" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="92">4.99</rating>
<name>Tenten</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Team Guy. Tenten specializes in the use of ninja weapons. Using the scrolls she carries with her, she is able to summon large amounts of weapons, such as Shuriken and Kunai.</description>
<picture>27984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8613" type="appears in" update="2010-04-28">
<rating votes="50">5.92</rating>
<name>Shizune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizune is a http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure] ninja introduced in the series as http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Tsunade]`s assistant. She left Konohagakure with Tsunade after the death of her uncle, and over the years, Tsunade taught her medical techniques. Despite her medicinal affinity, many of the attacks she uses in the series are poison-based, including using concealed poisoned needles or emitting toxic gas from her mouth. Shizune is one of the few characters that Tsunade trusts with absolute certainty, as she identifies details that Tsunade tends to overlook. In Part II of the series, Shizune`s concern for details causes her to question Tsunade`s judgment, creating interference with Tsunade`s plans and temporarily straining the relationship between the two.</description>
<picture>28660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4725" picture="27575.jpg">Nemoto Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8615" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="331">8.55</rating>
<name>Nara Shikamaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nara Shikamaru was in the same class as http://anidb.net/ch226 [Naruto] at the Ninja academy and is now part of a team with http://anidb.net/ch8616 [Ino] and http://anidb.net/ch8617 [Chouji]. He is very laid back to the point of being lazy; he often sees missions as troublesome. He is quite close to his team leader, http://anidb.net/ch7742 [Asuma], and the pair regularly plays shougi together. Shikamaru specialises in jutsu which manipulate shadows, but his true strength lies in his ability to think up the best strategies for defeating an enemy.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>30812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8616" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-06">
<rating votes="65">5.01</rating>
<name>Yamanaka Ino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamanaka Ino is the only female member of Team 10. She has known Haruno Sakura since they were children, befriending and helping her to develop her own identity. When they discovered that they both liked Uchiha Sasuke, Sakura ended their friendship so they could properly compete for his affection. The two eventually make amends and rekindle their friendship, but still maintain a competitive attitude towards each other. In the anime, when Sakura begins to excel in healing techniques, Ino becomes her surrogate apprentice, hoping to be more useful to her friends and teammates as an able medical ninja. In terms of combat abilities, Ino specializes in mind-altering techniques. To use these techniques, Ino transfers her consciousness to her target`s mind, gaining control over their body which she can then use to attack others.</description>
<picture>27921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8617" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="72">3.06</rating>
<name>Akimichi Chouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akimichi Chouji is a rather large ninja who makes up one third of Team Asuma alongside http://anidb.net/ch8615 [Shikamaru] and http://anidb.net/ch8616 [Ino]. He has a very large appetite and regularly clears out http://anidb.net/ch7742 [Asuma]`s wallet when they go for Korean barbeque. Though he can always be seen eating something, he uses his size to his advantage in battle and gets exceptionally angry when anyone calls him fat. Chouji is able to utilise the ninja techniques of his family that allow him to increase the size of any part of his body.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>27977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8618" type="appears in" update="2011-05-18">
<rating votes="35">5.67</rating>
<name>Kankurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8619" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="77">5.64</rating>
<name>Temari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Temari (テマリ?) is the oldest of the three siblings. Unlike her more combat-loving brothers, Temari values peace, as she questions Sunagakure`s justifications for going to war with Konohagakure. This trait carries over to Part II, in which she begins acting as a liaison between Sunagakure and Konohagakure to help the two villages work together. Like her brothers, Temari does not appear in the series very often, and when she does appear she is commonly in the company of Shikamaru Nara. When they make their Part II debut together, Naruto Uzumaki asks if they are on a date, though both Shikamaru and Temari state that this is not the case. In battle, Temari wields a giant iron fan that can create powerful gusts of wind capable of leveling the surrounding landscape. As she is skilled at deducing an opponent`s strategies and weaknesses soon after a battle begins, she typically uses her winds to remove parts of the battlefield that might be advantageous to the enemy.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picture>54645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8864" type="appears in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="116">7.61</rating>
<name>Konohagakure no Sato</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of the five great ninja villages and said to be the mightiest of the five. As such, it is one of five villages with a Kage as its leader, known as the Hokage. On a mountain overlooking the villages from the north exists the Hokage Monument. The village resides in the Land of Fire. Although Konoha, much like the country in which it resides, has been peaceful for the past sixteen years and has grown accustomed to that peace, it remains one of the most powerful villages in existence and has great military power and influence.</description>
<picture>3846.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="8865" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="89">6.58</rating>
<name>Sarutobi Hiruzen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sarutobi Hiruzen was the student of the first two Hokages, http://anidb.net/ch8859 [Senju Hashirama] and http://anidb.net/ch8862 [Senju Tobirama], and the teacher of http://anidb.net/ch7213 [Jiraiya], http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Tsunade], and http://anidb.net/ch8603 [Orochimaru].</description>
<picture>54650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10292" type="appears in" update="2009-07-09">
<rating votes="12">5.57</rating>
<name>Teuchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6084" picture="186264.jpg">Asakura Eisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10329" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="23">4.33</rating>
<name>Hagane Kotetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hagane Kotetsu is a Chuunin from http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure]. He spends most of the time with his partner, http://anidb.net/ch17145 [Kamizuki Izumo]. Kotetsu wears a bandage across his face over his nose. At one point, http://anidb.net/ch7742 [Asuma], Izumo and http://anidb.net/ch8615 [Shikamaru] asked him about this, and pointed out that he hadn`t worn it when he was a child. Later, he agreed to take the bandage off, but then Shikamaru said that knowing what was under it would only be troublesome, much to Kotetsu`s chagrin, so the reason for the bandage over his nose remains unknown.</description>
<picture>30876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6345" picture="30893.jpg">Kouno Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10927" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-01-30">
<rating votes="29">4.30</rating>
<name>Nohara Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rin was a medical-nin who appeared in the Kakashi Gaiden arc as a former teammate of http://anidb.net/ch7248 [Hatake Kakashi], as well as a member of Team Minato. During the Third Great Shinobi World War, Team Minato was assigned to destroy the Kannabi Bridge. Rin was kidnapped during the course of the mission, and her captors, http://anidb.net/ch12200 [Iwagakure] ninja, tortured her with genjutsu to find out if she knew anything about Konoha`s war efforts. Rin refused to speak, Kakashi and http://anidb.net/ch10928 [Obito] staged a rescue effort, and, although they succeeded, Obito was crushed in a cave-in caused by the fleeing captors. Before he died, he asked Rin to implant his Sharingan into Kakashi`s damaged eye. After the procedure was completed, Rin and Kakashi were forced to flee the continuing cave-in, and, with the help of http://anidb.net/ch8866 [Minato], went on to complete their mission.</description>
<picture>32618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10928" type="appears in" update="2015-04-28">
<rating votes="53">4.44</rating>
<name>Uchiha Obito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uchiha Obito was a chuunin-level shinobi from Konohagakure`s Uchiha clan and a member of Team Minato, together with http://anidb.net/ch31907 [Hatake Kakashi] and http://anidb.net/ch10927 [Nohara Rin], led by http://anidb.net/ch8866 [Namikaze Minato].
After his apparent death during the Third Shinobi World War, Obito took up the aliases Tobi and Uchiha Madara and became an international criminal responsible for various crimes, including the Nine-Tails` attack on Konoha, after he was saved and taken care of by the believed to be dead http://anidb.net/ch8623 [Uchiha Madara]. He eventually became one of the leaders of Akatsuki.</description>
<picture>32623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6992" picture="31978.jpg">Komori Sousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12204" type="appears in" update="2009-10-08">
<rating votes="14">7.03</rating>
<name>Sunagakure no Sato</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>36929.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12324" type="appears in" update="2009-10-15">
<rating votes="25">5.82</rating>
<name>Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37283.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16975" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-23">
<rating votes="2">3.48</rating>
<name>Hiruko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiruko, is a missing-nin who disappeared from http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure] dozens of years earlier after developing the Chimera Technique, a jutsu which allows him to absorb both the chakra and Kekkei Genkai of other ninja.</description>
<picture>46769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17142" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="1">2.05</rating>
<name>San</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>San is an antagonist from http://anidb.net/a6503 [Naruto Shippuuden 3: Inheritors of the Will of Fire]. He is a shinobi and one of http://anidb.net/ch16975 [Hiruko]`s three followers, along with http://anidb.net/ch17146 [Ichi] and http://anidb.net/ch17143 [Ni]. He almost perfectly resembles a mirror image of Ichi, except that he has three marks on his forehead.</description>
<picture>47062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12575" picture="203221.jpg">Watanabe Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17143" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="7">4.16</rating>
<name>Ni</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ni is an antagonist from http://anidb.net/a6503 [Naruto Shippuuden 3: Inheritors of the Will of Fire]. She is a kunoichi and one of http://anidb.net/ch16975 [Hiruko]`s three followers, along with http://anidb.net/ch17146 [Ichi] and http://anidb.net/ch17142 [San].She has two purple stripes on her left cheek, a bodysuit that revealed much, and long brown hair curled into a very intricate spiral. She has a mark on her back that is the same as the one in Hiruko`s left palm.</description>
<picture>47061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17144" type="appears in" update="2010-04-29">
<rating votes="6">1.30</rating>
<name>Taiseki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taiseki was a shinobi from http://anidb.net/ch12200 [Iwagakure] who fought and died during the Third Great Shinobi World War. He formed a team with Kakkou, using their superb diversionary tactics to attack the enemy. With his Hiding with Camouflage Technique he was able to approach his enemies from their blind spot, easily killing them with a single strike. He confronted Team Minato, led by http://anidb.net/ch7248 [Hatake Kakashi], during the Third Great Shinobi World War, managing to take http://anidb.net/ch10927 [Rin] captive. He was later killed by http://anidb.net/ch10928 [Uchiha Obito], however, while he and Kakashi attempted to rescue Rin. Taiseki also injured Kakashi`s eye, leading to him gaining his Sharingan from Obito.</description>
<picture>4360.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="645" picture="18172.jpg">Suzumori Kanji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17145" type="appears in" update="2010-04-29">
<rating votes="13">3.99</rating>
<name>Kamizuki Izumo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamizuki Izumo is a Chuunin from http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure]. He spends most of the time with his partner, http://anidb.net/ch10329 [Hagane Kotetsu]. Izumo is almost always seen alongside Kotetsu, and is characterized as being the more responsible and conscientious of the two. In Shippuuden Episode 81, he angrily burst into the Jounin lounge to drag his partner back to work. Similarly, in another omake, he admonished Kotetsu`s lack of pride in his work when the latter complained that they were simply the http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Fifth Hokage]`s errand-boys or "gophers", before adding sagely that guarding the Leaf and the villagers was "the best mission you can get" as a shinobi.</description>
<picture>47093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1441" picture="18827.jpg">Tsuboi Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17146" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="1">2.05</rating>
<name>Ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichi is an antagonist from http://anidb.net/a6503 [Naruto Shippuuden 3: Inheritors of the Will of Fire]. He is a shinobi and one of http://anidb.net/ch16975 [Hiruko]`s three followers, along with http://anidb.net/ch17143 [Ni] and http://anidb.net/ch17142 [San]. He almost perfectly resembles a mirror image of San, except that he only has a single mark on his forehead. He has a mark on his back that is the same as the one in Hiruko`s left palm.</description>
<picture>47059.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17192" type="appears in" update="2010-04-28">
<rating votes="14">6.81</rating>
<name>Tonton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tonton is http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Tsunade]`s pet pig, often kept in the care of http://anidb.net/ch8613 [Shizune]. She does not speak in any human language, but still manages to get her point across by whining in her own unique tone (a "buhi" or "oink" depending on the language). It seems that Tsunade and Shizune are able to understand what Tonton is trying to say. Tonton`s nose also seems adept at tracking things, such so that http://anidb.net/ch10966 [Pakkun] has some familiarity with her.</description>
<picture>47039.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41296" type="appears in" update="2012-02-12">
<rating votes="14">4.92</rating>
<name>Matsuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2346.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="105731" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2009-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Four Kekkei Genkai shinobi who have been guarding the Hidden Cloud, Stone, Mist and Sand villages disappear without a trace. The Land of Fire comes under suspicion, as it is the only country to have suffered no losses. Mounting suspicion among the four nations is bringing them to the brink of another Great Ninja War. In the Hidden Leaf Village, Tsunade orders her forces to prevent anything from happening that would lead to war, while also trying to discover the truth. At the same time, Naruto and his friends discover some bad news: Kakashi has left the village.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791441</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-shippuden-the-movie-the-will-of-fire</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="105961" update="2009-08-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">1.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
