<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6531" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-07-06</startdate>
<enddate>2009-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kanamemo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Записки Каны</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">卡娜筆記</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">加奈日记</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">かなめも</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9722" approval="9" total="15">Non Non Biyori</anime>
<anime id="6257" approval="2" total="9">K-On!</anime>
<anime id="8117" approval="2" total="8">Nekogami Yaoyorozu</anime>
<anime id="13160" approval="2" total="5">Slow Start</anime>
<anime id="4777" approval="1" total="7">Lucky Star</anime>
<anime id="14156" approval="1" total="4">Watashi ni Tenshi ga Maiorita!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="387237">A very nice, relaxing slice of life anime about young girls and their newspaper delivery service. Kanamemo is very cutesy, and combines all of the elements of a shoujo with a seinen to deliver the cutest experience imaginable.
`Mature` viewers beware, this isn`t for you!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/kanamemo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1006" type="Animation Work">Feel</name>
<name id="3538" type="Original Work">Iwami Shouko</name>
<name id="4302" type="Series Composition">Nakase Rika</name>
<name id="987" type="Work">Gansis</name>
<name id="3073" type="Music">Hashimoto Yukari</name>
<name id="10891" type="Chief Animation Direction">Suzuki Gou</name>
<name id="9176" type="Character Design">Tatsuta Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="7012" type="Direction">Takayanagi Shigehito</name>
<name id="8546" type="Chief Animation Direction">Masuda Kuniaki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the http://anidb.net/cr3538 [Iwami Shouko]`s 4-koma manga by the same name.
The daily life of http://anidb.net/ch6829 [Nakamachi Kana], an orphaned middle school girl, is all but easy. So she begins living and working at a newspaper delivery office with all-female staff.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1112">4.70</permanent>
<temporary count="1121">6.68</temporary>
<review count="1">4.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>24790.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10644</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5914</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4487</identifier>
<identifier>pqawkq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/kanamemo/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>かなめも</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1662</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334076</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11602</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>nopan</name>
<description>The character foregoes underwear.</description>
<picurl>162753.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="569" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-18">
<name>clumsy</name>
<description>A clumsy person is one lacking in coordination, and as such prone to often having accidents such as tripping, bumping into objects, or dropping things. In female characters, this is often thought of as endearing.</description>
<picurl>63355.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="601" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>bicycle</name>
<description>A bicycle, often called a bike or cycle, is a human-powered, pedal-driven, single-track vehicle, having two wheels attached to a frame, one behind the other. A bicycle rider is called a cyclist, or bicyclist.
Souce: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>172772.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1282" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>pet</name>
<description>A domestic animal kept for pleasure or companionship.</description>
<picurl>221616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2461" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>domestic cat</name>
<description>The cat (Felis catus or Felis silvestris catus), also known as the domestic cat to distinguish it from other felines and felids, is a small, usually furry, domesticated, and carnivorous mammal. Cats are valued by humans for companionship and their ability to hunt vermin and household pests, and are often kept as indoor pets, in which case they are also called housecats; they have been associated with humans for at least 9,500 years and are currently the most popular pet in the world, being found almost everywhere on Earth.
Cats are similar in anatomy to the other felids, with light, strong and flexible bodies, excellent hearing, sense of smell, and near darkness eyesight, quick reflexes, sharp retractable claws, and teeth adapted to killing small prey. They are skilled predators and hunt over 1,000 species for food. Despite being solitary hunters, cats are a social species, with communication means that include pheromones, body language and a variety of vocalizations, such as meowing, purring, trilling, hissing, growling and grunting.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>41283.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2780" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>indirect kiss</name>
<description>Comedy element: Especially in a school setting the character who has fallen for a fellow student, but has not yet confessed his/her love, will be desperate for any sign of "closeness".
The indirect kiss: Anything the adored person touches with his/her lips — e.g. a used glass of lemonade, some half-eaten food, a half-emptied can of soda — the love struck will want to touch with her/his own lips.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3305" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>light-hearted</name>
<description>Not being burdened by trouble, worry, or care; happy and carefree.
Just a casual and feel-good watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3694" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>dear mother in heaven</name>
<description>A form of veneration of ancestors, where people call upon their ancestors for help, advice and similar in their everyday life like in other cultures upon God, Jesus, the Virgin Mary or various saints. The veneration of the spirit`s of one`s ancestors is an integral part of Japanese culture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3702" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-12">
<name>swimsuit shopping</name>
<description>To provide additional, potentially ecchi moments, the usually female character(s) go shopping for a new, often quite revealing, swimsuit — as preparation for an upcoming pool or beach episode.</description>
<picurl>166999.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4148" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-11">
<name>late for school</name>
<description>A common device for a series opening or Establishing Character Moment. Things begin in a frantic rush which usually results in taking short cuts, such as eating breakfast on the run. The classic image is of someone running down the street with a slice of toast hanging out of their mouth, dragging their backpack with one hand while trying to put on their jacket or sweater one-handed with the other, bumping into important people in a manner that gets the plot started.
Basically, they`re never on time for school. While some are Heavy Sleepers, it would appear that they may have simply set their alarm clocks so as to give them insufficient time to get to class. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>161002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4352" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-11">
<name>censored uncensored version</name>
<description>Even the DVD and Blu-ray releases do not let you see everything you were expecting to, and you will have to live with censorship in the show. That normally applies to fan service, but may also apply to gore and violence. A very common example is characters without nipples, as in http://anidb.net/a6083 [KissXSis]; in other cases, something such as steam or foam stays in the camera`s way, like in http://anidb.net/a6531 [Kanamemo]. In some shows, the censorship in the disk releases is even stronger than in the TV version, while others may use creative censorship as a replacement for the removed fan service or even as a joke.
This does not apply to censorship of what Japanese pornography laws still require to be censored.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5644" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>musical episode</name>
<description>Everything is going the usual way, until, somebody suddenly bursts out singing and instead of giving him a stare others follow his example. Soon the whole cast, random bystanders, just about everybody, is seen singing. Not only singing but also dancing, carrying out choreography professionals need weeks to train, like it`s the easiest thing to do. And here we are, trapped in a musical episode/scene. 
Sometimes there is a (valid) excuse for this behaviour, most often not. A common occurrence in Disney films and so called Bollywood Cinema.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6829" type="main character in" update="2009-11-01">
<rating votes="12">5.54</rating>
<name>Nakamachi Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main protagonist of the story, Kana lost her parents and, more recently, her grandmother prior to the events of the story. When collectors began taking her grandmother`s possessions, Kana fled, believing they would take her as well. Looking for a new place to live, she ended up at a newspaper distribution center, Fuhshin Shinbun, where the story takes place.</description>
<picture>24782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6830" type="main character in" update="2009-08-16">
<rating votes="15">5.89</rating>
<name>Amano Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saki is the assistant chief of Fuhshin Shinbun, despite still being in grade school. She is the only "serious" one of the group, and frequently reprimands the other girls when they neglect their duties.</description>
<picture>24783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6831" type="main character in" update="2014-07-21">
<rating votes="10">5.33</rating>
<name>Kitaoka Yume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yume works at the Fuhshin Shinbun. She is a student at a patisserie academy, and, whenever cooking, often adds far too much sugar than what the recipe calls for (such as when she added two bags of sugar to a dish of curry). She and Yuuki are lovers.</description>
<picture>24784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6832" type="main character in" update="2014-07-21">
<rating votes="11">6.63</rating>
<name>Minami Yuuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuki works at the Fuhshin Shinbun. Her emotional state is usually placid, except when Yume is doing something with someone else without her. She and Yume are lovers.</description>
<picture>24785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6833" type="main character in" update="2009-08-16">
<rating votes="10">5.29</rating>
<name>Azuma Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinata works at Fuhshin Shinbun. She is rather carefree, and likes to gamble or invest through various means (i.e. Horseracing). She has attempted to join a college numerous times, but has failed entrance exams twice, with a third failure being predicted frequently by the others. She is nice to Kana, occasionally helping her.</description>
<picture>24786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6834" type="main character in" update="2016-01-28">
<rating votes="15">5.81</rating>
<name>Nishida Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruka works at Fuhshin Shinbun. She is an avid drinker of sake, and as such is usually drunk. While intoxicated, she will often make advances on the other women, especially younger girls. For this, Kana fears her greatly. She attends college, studying bio-fermentation, and creates numerous different beverages from biologic substances (the resulting concoction almost always being alcoholic), which she tests on her friends.</description>
<picture>181910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6835" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-01">
<rating votes="17">6.58</rating>
<name>Kujiin Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mika is a newspaper deliverer at another center, although she won`t admit it unless directly confronted. She is quick to blame others, and frequently turns her mistakes into inconveniences. When she becomes lost during a route, she literally runs into Kana, then forgives her by "allowing" her to escort her to her next stop. In the third episode, she and Kana become friends. She seems to have a crush on Kana, although this has yet to be confirmed outright.</description>
<picture>24788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11215" type="appears in" update="2009-08-16">
<name>Fuushin Shinbun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Fuushin Shinbun is the newspaper delivery organization that is lead by Amano Saki, other members include:
Nakamichi Kana
Kitaoka Yume
Minami Yuuki
Nishida Haruka
Azuma Hinata</description>
</character>
<character id="43356" type="appears in" update="2016-05-13">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Marimo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>186726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="102109" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, ひとりぼっち...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Time, All Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Hitoribocchi...</title>
<summary>Kana`s grandmother passed away so she is left by herself. In order to survive, she has to look for a part-time job. However, she`s just a Jr. High School student with no guardian so finding a job proved to be difficult. It was getting late as she was walking back when she suddenly collided into a newspaper delivery person. She sees an advertisement hiring people to deliver newspapers where housing is provided.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531248</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104128" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, 新聞配達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Newspaper Delivery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Shinbunhaitatsu</title>
<summary>Kana has officially become part of the newspaper staff. Saki begins to train her on delivering newspapers. Kana writes down the paper route and pictures the streets in her mind as Saki is telling her. After breakfast, Saki suggested that Kana try the evening route when she confesses to not knowing how to ride a bike. All the bundled up newspapers weigh about the same as a small child so knowing how to ride a bike is quite important. So, Kana had one of the other members help her out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531444</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104129" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, 恐い話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Ghost Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, kowai Hanashi</title>
<summary>After enjoying themselves in the bathhouse, the rain was coming down quite hard and it was extremely windy. It seemed like the typhoon was getting closer and closer. Everyone hurried home and on the way back, Kana ran into some friends she knew from the cooking club she belonged to. Kana noticed that they were wearing their school uniforms even though school was out and found out that they were going to school to make a cake for one of their teachers. Kana was a bit sad that she was not invited. As she tried to get rid of that feeling, there was a power outage at Fushin Newspaper!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532116</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104130" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, みんなでお風呂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Time at the Bath with Everyone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Minna de Ofuro</title>
<summary>There was a huge typhoon coming which would bring extremely strong winds. According to the weather report, it is expected to hit the Kanto region. So everyone at Fushin Newspaper began to prepare for this typhoon by tying up the bikes so they wouldn`t fly away and bringing buckets into the house. In the evening, Saki seemed to be getting better and suggested that everyone go to the bathhouse. Despite the strong winds, Mika showed up and went with the gang to the bathhouse.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531450</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104131" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, プール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Time at the Pool</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Pool</title>
<summary>Saki is distributing newspapers that contain a special promotion which contains a free admission ticket to “Waterland”. The ladies find this ticket and get all excited about going to Waterland. Haruka just wants her and her friends to go so she takes Saki’s ticket. Everyone still wants to go and is willing to pay their own way. Kana is taken to the department store to buy a bathing suit.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531448</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104134" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, スマイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Smile</title>
<summary>Summer School - Kana who has just joined Fushin Newspaper Company is appearing to be filled with emotions on her first day of school. When it seemed like she is getting used to her new life, a transfer student appears. That transfer student is the same person Kana meet on her first paper delivery, Mika. After school, she couldn`t understand why Mika was waiting in front of Fushin newspaper when she works at a competing newspaper company. In order to save the company Mika works for, Kana encourages her to get new customers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>531446</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104790" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104989" update="2011-06-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104990" update="2011-06-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106169" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, お迎え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Welcome</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Omukae</title>
<summary>Today is the Obon holiday. It`s a newspaper holiday for some companies. So the girls at Fushin Newspaper Company are taking it easy and spending their day as they please. For Kana, this was the first Obon without her grandmother so she asked Saki if she could light a welcoming fire which is believed to bring back ancestral spirits. Saki thought it would be a great to make this an important event so everyone began to prepare to build the fire and make an offering to welcome the ancestors. So, on the night of the welcoming, who was the one waiting?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532118</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106329" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, 気持ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Kimochi</title>
<summary>One morning, Yume’s treasured sweets were presented to Kana as she took off in a Rolls Royce. The unexpected event caused Kana to be in a bit of a confused state. As Saki asked about what happened, Yume was on her way to her parents’ home. Will she be returning?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532124</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106330" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, ダイエット?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Diet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Diet?</title>
<summary>The new school term is approaching. One of Kana’s friends asks her to take care of their dog, John, for a short time. Kana really wants to help her friend so she agrees to this even though she’s terrified of dogs! She couldn’t have things her way with John so in order to fulfill her desire to get along with all animals; she had some help learning how to get along with dogs. Mika, who was also not good with dogs, went with Kana to a park nearby to attend a lecture but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532122</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="106331" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, 思い出話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Reminiscent Talk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Omoidebanashi</title>
<summary>One morning, Miss Marimo told the story of “The first bad employee at Fushin” to the girls. However, for some reason, Saki was in a bad mood during this time. Finally, she got up and went to her room. Kana was concerned for her so she asked one of the girls what happened and they all seemed to know. It seemed to be related to an incident that happened a year before Kana arrived during the wintertime.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532120</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="108413" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, 看病</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Nursing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Kanbyou</title>
<summary>Unfortunately, it looks like today is going to rain too. Because of the drastic change in temperature, Saki warns everyone to take care of themselves. The topic of discussion is the members who are caught a cold. Yuuki has a fever. Yume who was taking care of them and is in high spirits is overworked and also breaks down physically. Kana, who is worried about these two, are told by Hinata and Saki that they will be okay. And what do you know, the next day, Yuuki is completely recovered while Yume also seems much better. However, when Kana returns home that day, this time, it’s Saki who is sick in bed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>533286</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="108414" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての, ひと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Person</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Hito</title>
<summary>Under the autumn sky, there’s a flea market in the downtown area. Of course they’re selling newspapers at Fushin Newspaper! In addition, Yume made home-made sweets, Haruka has some feng shui goods, and Saki got various other items from a classmate. This time, the profits will go to something they want, a new air conditioner. In the afternoon, Kana goes to pick up lunch and to get some change at the bank. On her way, she bumps into Mika.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>533284</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="108415" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして, はじめての...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And the First...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite, Hajimete no ...</title>
<summary>A new person entered Fushin Newspaper. Kana is now a senpai and since she’s a bit embarrassed because she can’t ride a bike, she’s been taking some special training all day and night. Since she was really concentrating on this training, it caused her to be late for school. In order to continue her training, she no longer walked with her friends but instead went directly home. Since this was not like Kana, her classmates suspected that she has a boyfriend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534302</identifier>
<identifier>kanamemo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="127700" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127701" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127702" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127703" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127704" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127705" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127706" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127707" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 09</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127708" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 08</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127709" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 07</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127710" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 06</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127711" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 05</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127712" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127713" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127714" update="2011-01-27">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127715" update="2012-06-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2010-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">映像特典: はじめての, きょうてい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no, Kyoutei</title>
<summary>The cast goes to, and bets on a boat race...</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
