<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6552" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>16</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-06-06</startdate>
<enddate>2009-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Weiss Survive</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Weiß Survive</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Игра на выживание</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヴァイス・サヴァイヴ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7207" type="Sequel">Weiss Survive R</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="593" approval="6" total="13">Yuu Gi Ou</anime>
<anime id="2910" approval="2" total="2">Duel Masters</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://ws-tcg.com/anime/ep_01.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="985" type="Animation Work">Studio Hibari</name>
<name id="3730" type="Series Composition">Yoshioka Takao</name>
<name id="6287" type="Original Work">Bushiroad</name>
<name id="3054" type="Direction">Suzuki Iku</name>
<name id="11518" type="Character Design">Higuchi Hiromi</name>
<name id="11518" type="Chief Animation Direction">Higuchi Hiromi</name>
<name id="13378" type="Series Composition">Inoue Tomoyo</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the card game series Weiß Schwarz by http://anidb.net/cr6287 [Bushiroad], illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr11103 [Fujima Takuya].
Teenage boy http://anidb.net/ch8936 [Takeshi] and girl http://anidb.net/ch8873 [Michi] get lost in the Card Battle world and have to win card battles to return home.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="614">2.91</permanent>
<temporary count="620">5.45</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>36388.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10821</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6425</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4514</identifier>
<identifier>wfzxuo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ws-tcg.com/anime/ep_01.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Weiss_Survive</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヴァイス・サヴァイヴ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1643</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334071</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11844</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5763" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>rock-paper-scissors</name>
<description>Whenever a decision has to be made in anime, the Japanese protagonists seem to be awfully fond of playing rock-paper-scissors (or jan-ken-pon) to determine the outcome.</description>
<picurl>62869.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6191" parentid="2881" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>card games</name>
<description>A card game is any game using playing cards as the primary device with which the game is played, be they traditional or game-specific. Countless card games exist, including families of related games (such as poker). A small number of card games played with traditional decks have formally standardized rules, but most are folk games whose rules vary by region, culture, and person.
Many games that are not generally placed in the family of card games do in fact use cards for some aspect of their gameplay. Similarly, some games that are placed in the card game genre involve a board. The distinction is that the gameplay of a card game primarily depends on the use of the cards by players (the board is simply a guide for scorekeeping or for card placement), while board games (the principal non-card game genre to use cards) generally focus on the players` positions on the board, and use the cards for some secondary purpose.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2409" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="39">7.38</rating>
<name>Asakura Otome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asakura Otome is the main heroine in the game and one of Jun`ichi and Nemu`s granddaughters. She is the student of Kazemi senior high class 3-3 and the chairman of the student council. She refers to Yoshiyuki as "otouto-kun", meaning "little brother". Otome inherited her grandfather`s magical abilities.
Otome seems to be one of the two persons, besides Sakura, to have known that Yoshiyuki was created due to a wish upon the Sakura tree.</description>
<picture>17664.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2411" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-01-14">
<rating votes="17">6.83</rating>
<name>Shirakawa Nanaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nanaka is the student of Kazemi affiliated junior high class 2-2 and the school idol. She likes singing, but not in front of others. Nanaka is the lead singer of the school band together with Koko her childhood and her best friend who places the bass. Like Kotori in the previous game, she has the power to read minds (due to a wish granted by the magical sakura tree), but only when she is touching the person whose mind she wants to read.</description>
<picture>17667.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2413" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-01-14">
<rating votes="15">5.86</rating>
<name>Tsukishima Koko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Koko is the student of Kazemi affiliated junior high class 2-3, a childhood friend of Yoshiyuki and Nanaka.</description>
<picture>17666.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8873" type="main character in" update="2014-05-06">
<rating votes="10">5.83</rating>
<name>Michi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4929" picture="41385.jpg">Kitta Izumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8936" type="main character in" update="2014-05-06">
<rating votes="4">5.69</rating>
<name>Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4930" picture="156855.jpg">Nakamoto Nobuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13821" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-06">
<rating votes="3">6.07</rating>
<name>VS-jii-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11272" picture="40742.jpg">Maeda Noboru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13822" type="appears in" update="2014-05-06">
<rating votes="4">4.43</rating>
<name>Cal</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13823" type="appears in" update="2014-05-06">
<rating votes="6">5.94</rating>
<name>Operetta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11274" picture="43050.jpg">Haruka Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13824" type="appears in" update="2014-05-06">
<rating votes="14">7.07</rating>
<name>Sies</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11273" picture="86104.jpg">Miruno Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13830" type="appears in" update="2014-05-06">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Joe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="403" picture="74821.jpg">Horie Kazuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13831" type="appears in" update="2014-05-06">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Coud</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11275" picture="65394.jpg">Suzuki Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31096" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="55">8.11</rating>
<name>Narukami Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156477.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54404" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-22">
<name>Iori Junpei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140316.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54406" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-22">
<rating votes="6">8.15</rating>
<name>Takeba Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140315.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54407" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-22">
<rating votes="10">7.00</rating>
<name>Kirijou Mitsuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140317.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54408" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-22">
<rating votes="8">8.94</rating>
<name>Yuuki Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140314.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54409" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-22">
<name>Sanada Akihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140318.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64372" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-02-14">
<rating votes="2">8.96</rating>
<name>Koromaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150261.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="103860" update="2009-06-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カードゲームに胸きゅん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heartfelt Card Game</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Card Game ni Mune Kyun!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104155" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どこぞのジジイと胸きゅん?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heartfelt Feelings and an Old Man in the End of Nowhere</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokozono Jijii to Mune Kyun?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104658" update="2009-06-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初体験に胸きゅん?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Stopping First Experience</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shotaiken ni Mune Kyun?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104982" update="2009-07-06">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">調教とバトルと胸きゅん☆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Training, Battle and the Excitements</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choukyou to Battle to Mune Kyun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105101" update="2009-07-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">萌×3で(`Д`;)ハアハア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Panting for Triple Moe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mo x3 de Haha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105536" update="2009-07-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">萌える足蹴に(;`Д`)ハアハア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Panting for the Moe Kick</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moeru Ashige ni Haha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105724" update="2009-09-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魅惑のボインだ(*`Д`*)ハアハア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s a Fascinating *Boing* Pant Pant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miwaku no Boin da Haha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106049" update="2009-09-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キタ-(゜∀゜)-!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Here It Comes!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kita!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108190" update="2009-09-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">†ようこそ!アリス×クロス†</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome! Aristocrat x Cross</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso! Alice Cross</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108191" update="2009-09-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">†フィギュアとアリス†</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Figure and Aristocrat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Figure to Alice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108192" update="2009-09-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">†メタモルフォーゼのアリス†</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Metamorphic Aristocrat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Metamorphose no Alice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108193" update="2009-09-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">†アンコールとアリス†</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encore and Aristocrat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Encore to Alice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108497" update="2009-09-27">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108592" update="2009-09-27">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108702" update="2009-09-27">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰還!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108703" update="2009-09-27">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">告白!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confession!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuhaku!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
