<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6564" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2010-06-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Angel Beats!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">エンジェル ビーツ!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Ангельские ритмы!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Пульс ангела!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">엔젤비트!, 엔젤비츠!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Angelo širdies dūžiai</title>
<title xml:lang="lv" type="synonym">Eņģeļa Pulss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Angel Beats</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">天使的心跳</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">天使的脉动</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">AB!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Angel Beats!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Angel Beats!</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Angel Beats!</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Angel Beats!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">엔젤 비트</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">แองเจิลบีทส์ แผนพิชิตนางฟ้า</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">Angel Beats!</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Angel Beats!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9822" approval="46" total="62">Little Busters! Refrain</anime>
<anime id="10997" approval="44" total="53">Charlotte</anime>
<anime id="9132" approval="38" total="69">Little Busters!</anime>
<anime id="271" approval="30" total="61">Haibane Renmei</anime>
<anime id="3651" approval="15" total="44">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu</anime>
<anime id="6367" approval="14" total="43">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu (2009)</anime>
<anime id="2400" approval="7" total="40">Gantz</anime>
<anime id="8852" approval="5" total="23">Tasogare Otome x Amnesia</anime>
<anime id="13592" approval="3" total="3">Caligula</anime>
<anime id="6968" approval="2" total="29">Ichiban Ushiro no Daimaou</anime>
<anime id="6211" approval="1" total="30">Kurokami The Animation</anime>
<anime id="2820" approval="1" total="23">Bokusatsu Tenshi Dokuro-chan</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="84">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="262668">Супер овъррейтед , нито ме разсмя нито ме разплака нито беше някфа интересна история ... ако не беше рейтинга нямаше да го изгледам , до края се си мислих че ще стане нещо интересно ...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="120055">Imho this has to be one of the most overrated anime out there. It certainly wasn`t without its moments, but on top of its, at times, painful unoriginality (best exemplified by Yuri being pretty much a carbon copy of Haruhi Suzumiya), the majority of the cast was made up of 1-dimensional one-trick ponies who were seldom entertaining, and while a few of the back stories were genuinely interesting, far too little time was given to them in favour of juvenile humour and out of place action sequences which ultimately contributed nothing to the show.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="446648">Nice plot, nice characters and nice edning! If you like  romantic animes, dats for you :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="484425">Angel Beats is hard to rank. I sometimes loved it and sometimes hated it.  The characters are all flat, two-dimensional stereotypes or less.  The story is just stupid with a bipolar mix of slapstick comedy and deadly serious drama (which is always melodramatic) that I found really off-putting from the beginning.  

Still, I found the series kind of fun at times.  Some of the jokes were funny.  Some of the action was cool.  The music interludes were out of place but entertaining.

If you don`t mind turning your brain off for some bad jokes and ignoring the bathos-laden drama, you could find some enjoyment here.  There are many better series, but there are many more worse series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="10227">A boring school anime that absurdly mixes band&amp;music with guns&amp;explosions. The "touching" moments seem so out of place that one cannot really sympathize with the characters which are introduced hastily about one per episode. The story has potential but is so distorted that you stop caring at the beginning and are happy to see it concluded in the last episode. Nice animation though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="404129">It`s made by "Key" that`s enough of a reason to see it.
and you won`t be dissapointed, it will make you laugh and cry like a small child (In a good way)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="319303">Simply excellent. The characters led quite tragic lives so its certainly not for those looking for something light.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="164047">Anyone who enjoyed Clannad/Kanon must see this anime too.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="420895">nice one.. this is good.. i like the story of otonashi.. i would be sad if this anime ended up like 12 episodes T_T</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="381564">A good anime, it feels diferent than others key animes, but very interesting in the end</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="357163">A stunning show. If you`re slightly interested in anime, you should watch this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="16819">The first episode is a bit overrated, but after this one, the show gets darker and better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="248024">Light plot, but the story has a good heart. Will make you laugh and cry as others have said. good watch, short series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="251593">Found this to be a great anime, the fights were decent and entertaining, the comedy had me grinning from ear to ear, and the story was exceptional unique and fulfilling. But if you are someone who gets emotional over characters in animes, then you may get saddened at times. Loved the way they wrapped this one up even though it as rushed and alot more of the story could have been told, had me teary eyed and satisfied completely.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="411353">I absolutely loved this anime. Fell in love with every character. I laughed so much in the beginning and cried so much in the end. I want to see it again and again. The soundtrack is unforgettable. Really inspiring.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="417398">Another fantastic job by the Key! I`m amazed how the author created so many tear jerking moments in a short series like this. I had some "wtf" moments and felt that the series was too short to develop more characters but even with that, it was a beautiful anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="420432">Master piece anime !!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="111106">This show wasn`t bad; definately not your average high school comedy. The best way to describe the first half is if Haruhi Suzumiya and Nagato Yui want to kill each other in purgatory. It gets more complicated than that but that`s the basic premise.
There is a pretty big cast, but outside a half of dozen characters there isn`t a whole lot of development. It probably could have done more if it was more than 13 eps long, but at the same time it felt like it was running out of ideas for plot in the second half.
I say give a try, at least.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="464726">Angel Beats! is a proof that good anime with good story can still be created. Great music and animation. Simply a masterpiece!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="608137">The characters are well draw, and the story is meaningful. It is funny and sad.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="441695">This anime portrayed great, very in-depth back stories on the various characters and what they did with their lives.  The background stories, although tragic, were what made this anime spectacular.  The comedy was a bit lacking, but the overall emotional development between the characters made this anime very memorable.  The ending summed up the overall emotional direction of the anime in a sad, although well depicted, way.  I would recommend Angel Beats! for fans of tragedy animes.  Basically, the "comedy" of Angel Beats wasn`t that great, but the "tragedy" was executed perfectly.  Watch it if you want to see an anime that tugs on your heart strings.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="246307">an unexpected good anime.
Only if they made it a 24 ep anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="479958">really good story
The first anime that made me cry XD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="446193">Brimming with unfulfilled potential due to a low episode run, Key`s Maeda approaches drama with a fresh look and impressive character designs, a killer soundtrack, and great characters. It`s hilarious, action packed, energetic, and touching enough to live up to Maeda`s past works.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="177436">I have no idea why this series was so popular when it first released. Don`t get me wrong, it`s good, but I have no idea what the people who say it`s one of the greatest anime ever are seeing that I`m not. Personally, I feel the story would be best suited for a video game, though not a visual novel like most anime, I think it would work quite well in an action game.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="90098">Another good work from Keys, not the best but really enjoayable, pity it was so small, it had potential to be a solid 8 or 9 with 13 more episodes :) none the less still a great show</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="221060">enough w/ all the haters. we`ve already got too much logic to work with ourselves over in the real world. give it a chance and take it for what it is, not what it could have been. rantings aside, this is a short, comparatively light and pretty amusing with enough dose of emotional heart tugging moments, this show is  such a pleasure to watch and one of the memorables for me.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="545305">Beautiful, touching and sad. Highly recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="425228">This was a great anime series. Highly recommended. The last episode will make you want to cry.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="275599">If you don`t care much about unresolved mysteries, and simply enjoys as much as per episode does, I`d recommend this series. If you are very critical about the story, you`d find a lot of holes in this series. But for me who enjoys most when the anime is awesomely animated, and with splice of quick jokes and unreserved drama, it`s a must watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="31156">Had a strong start, but derailed around midway and headed into a rather cliche ending. Still worth the watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="387237">Definitely a must-watch for any Key fans. The romance is mostly implied, but the story is still very tear-jerking.

One of the best anime series of the season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="203171">Another awesome anime from Key. Animation is spectacular. This one has got quite a lot of humour, however it still has the Key`s usual spice - the drama.
Like most of Key`s anime this one most likely will start funny but end tragically.
I highly recommend this but not mark as must see - there are people who are not interested in comedies or tragedies.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="338163">Great show I was blown away. Watched in one sitting and went to work for 12 hrs on 3 hrs of sleep. Just wish we could of got to know some of the co-stars better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="425531">As a fan of all of Key`s previous works I knew I had to see this. I liked it a lot initially and seem to love it more each time i re-watch it. I just wish it had been longer!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="414179">In a 13-series frame this one is probably ranked best i`ve seen. It may not have tons of action, but the story is flawlessly executed and leaves warm feelings.

Good timekiller certified.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="328815">A must see, especially if your life is just garbage and unfair, easy to relate, amazing story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="484892">Angel Beats had more interesting and tragic back stories about its main characters than any anime I have seen.  The story takes place in an afterlife that resembles a High School, and it has a student council who is at odds with a resistance club.  Many hilarious battles ensue since none of the players can die.  However, be warned:  although there is a lot of awesome comedy, there are also very tragic moments that will leave you needing a box of tissues.  This anime does an excellent job of not just tugging at your heart strings but yanking at them until you burst into tears.  I loved this anime very much, and a second season would be a blessing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="574466">One of these animes you start watching just because has good quality graphics and once the band starts, you realize there`s also a good sountrack, you keep watching and thinking "oh there it goes, another nonsense comedy", give it time to reach you and enjoy till the very end.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="636420">An absolutely beautiful story and action to go along with it. A must see anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="496405">One of the best.
`Nuff said.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="444838">...extremely inspiring, showing that hope can always be found in in life, be in this life or in the next.

Loved it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="488989">WOW! this is the first anime in a while that left me like WOW!
 Awesome story! comedy drama romance slapstick shonen not to mention the perfect ending (which is almost extinct in recent anime)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="613777">Simply incredible. The music is top notch and the plot is well thought out. I can appreciate the characters and the theme of this anime. It is rare to find a decent 13-er that is impactful. This is well executed, a true gem!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="427495">Great anime! The last episode was unforgettable (I was almost crying). Maybe it`s not perfect for everybody, but still this is the "must see" anime ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="172854">OMFG MASTERPIECE! Visually stunning and the story itself is exquisite! - for the lack of a better word - This one will touch your heart, even if it is as hard and cold as mine.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="368156">Love it. 
At first it made me laugh (well...it`s typical of Key), but then...damn. I cried a lot.
It really teaches us about life. ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="533674">It can really make you cry on how life can be unfair and on moments make you fall of the chair in laughter.
The most perfect match of comedy, drama and the  action I have found yet.
Amazing plot, amazing animation.
Sad ending ;(</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="201805">the animation is great. it is very funny but at the same time theres no episode that doesn`t have a sad part..you`ll cry in the end for sure in the end</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="58620">funny as hell at the right parts, but also just as good at making you cry. 
if you loved clannad or kanon, this is a must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="301049">The only other anime that made me cry this much was Beck. But it was a happy cry. You have to see this anime. If you ever felt like death was the end this will make it seem like its not so bad. Very good with lots of great music and awesome character development. The guy that dances and speaks english all the time is hilarious. Don`t pass this one up.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="328918">This made me cry more than to the ending of clannad. The storyline and the characters are, if I had to use words to describe, amazing. How everything connects in the end. 
You simply have to see this. 
Key did it again, they made me cry.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="366429">A must-see. If you like KEY, you`ll love this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="525522">This is the first series from KEY that I had seen, and it started my love affair with the company. This series suffers from one thing, though: Its too short. I really wish this series had been made into a 26 episode season. There are a good number of plot holes in the last few episodes and some of the characters needed to be more fleshed out. That being said, this series was amazing despite its flaws. It has everything a good show needs: comedy, good characters, character development, a good plot , good premise, and all the emotions. That being said, it felt rushed in points, but it was an amazing series that I think everyone should watch at some point.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="467939">its the bomb guys its such a powerful anime anyone whos seen it will agree!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="565826">The whole battle thing was lame. Turns into a masterpiece later. 

You should watch this unless you`re a panda, because that would not make sense.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="558965">you could see Key`s works in here...if you watched the other Key`s works, then you`ll gonna love this..
the characters are well drawn, they`re so good and cute for the girls..
it also has light comedies, you`ll find it funny if you`re a lover of light comedy anime..
the story it self really unique, so pls don`t ask for a reasonable anime...it`s Key`s after all...his works has their own charm, and they`re all good anime...
you`ll get really much of feels in here...and you`ll dumbfounded by the ending..
it`s too good it breaks my heart after watching this..the feels...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="422558">At first i was a little prejudiced because almost all anime with a student council as a theme are mostly one of the same.This series shows it`s potential at 6th episode and thereafter where it actually makes sense.Good job from Key as expected.Nice ending by the way...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="382948">A tutorial of how to make a 13 episode story unforgettable. Starts peculiar and ends awesomely.
A must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="264318">Nice anime for this year, that`s what i believe</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="112916">I started out watching this with no particular reason and thought that some characters were bad copy`s of Haruhi`s characters... Boy was i ever wrong.

You got a whole lot of fun moments, a good number of action scenes, and some sad scenes as well. I gotta say, i consider myself a pretty hard guy, but i cried like a litttle girl watching the last episode!

Beatiful stuff!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="458655">I was blown away by the show`s performance! sure, there are things that the audience is curious about that leaves a fatal mark but if you really look at the characters that are portrayed in this, you will see examples of the lives of others` lives struggles fail regardless of the amount of effort in their lives. that is what makes this show amazing</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="333272">KEY has done it again; they made a wonderful anime, and this time it`s not originated from a visual novel. Full of action and drama, this short season is short but not to miss. Great animation, great music, great story although short, what else stops you from trying it out?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="293766">Key... You`ve really out done yourself with this one. Angel Beats is a prime example of what Key can do. A good balance of dramatic release, and dramatic irony. Great character development. And a very good back line story with an emotional twist! Angel beats is a must see, end of story..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="366583">I truly loved this anime the action was good and the storyline was outstanding but what really caught my attention and caused me to think so high of this anime was the ending. If you`re looking for non-stop action animes this is not for you but if instead you are looking for slow developing romantic types with a tad bit of comedy and action then this is the anime for you.

Also if you have a weak heart then I suggest you don`t watch it because there are some major "sad" parts.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="221579">Simply astonishing.
There are few anime series around that are able to make you get teared up during an episode and next make minute make you laugh your pants off, but this is one of those.
Highly recommended for everyone.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="520037">A very beautiful combination of comedy, drama and romance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="297053">A story which can make you laugh and cry at the same time. 

Must see series, Very nice soundtrack</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.angelbeats.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3067" type="Character Design">Hirata Katsuzou</name>
<name id="1855" type="Original Work">Maeda Jun</name>
<name id="3067" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirata Katsuzou</name>
<name id="9486" type="Music">Anant-Garde Eyes</name>
<name id="1385" type="Animation Work">P.A. Works</name>
<name id="9861" type="Chief Animation Direction">Miyashita Yuuji</name>
<name id="12540" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawatsura Kousuke</name>
<name id="4489" type="Direction">Kishi Seiji</name>
<name id="1855" type="Music">Maeda Jun</name>
</creators>
<description>* A mixed media project originally conceived by http://anidb.net/cr1855 [Maeda Jun] with original character designs by http://anidb.net/cr9839 [Na-Ga], from http://anidb.net/cr1046 [Visual Art`s/Key].
Death and reincarnation are inescapable, but what happens in between? Without warning and without his memories, a boy who only recalls his last name - Otonashi - wakes up next to a girl named Yuri who offers him a gun and tells him to shoot an angel. Assuming it must be a misunderstanding, Otonashi is then almost killed by the angel and is drawn into Yuri`s army to battle to delay the beginning of his next life. Immortality is within reach, but if Otonashi remembers how he died, will he keep fighting or allow himself to vanish?
Note: The first episode was pre-aired during a special event for the Angel Beats multimedia project, held in Tokyo on March 22, 2010 to a selected number of lucky first-time viewers, who were chosen from a nationwide postcard lottery held until March 12.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9611">7.63</permanent>
<temporary count="9745">7.98</temporary>
<review count="9">7.20</review>
</ratings>
<picture>36637.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10885</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9062</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10067</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6547</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4656</identifier>
<identifier>otwnzu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.angelbeats.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Angel_Beats!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Angel_Beats!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1896</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336371</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12530</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2569</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13774</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19694</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>11652</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1032" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-10">
<name>fishing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3135" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>hero complex</name>
<description>A hero complex is a state of mind in which an individual believes they need to save or assist others, uphold morals, serve justice, or perform other such supposedly hero-like acts, often at any cost. That is a common trait among vigilantes. Those with a hero complex may feel personally accountable for any failure at those self-assigned duties. Their main concern is performing their supposedly heroic deeds; any questions others might raise about such actions are all secondary concerns at best. Such questions can include, but are not limited to: who is to be saved; what are they to be saved from; why are they being saved; whether or not the other person needs or wants to be saved at all; whether or not others share in the sense of morals and justice being upheld; how people feel about the so-called heroic actions; whether people feel like those actions are being forced down their throats; what negative effects can arise from such actions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3481" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-04-19">
<name>recruiting teammates</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3758" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-28">
<name>concert</name>
<description>The main characters play one or more live music performances during the show. This mostly happens for anime with the main focus on music.</description>
<picurl>169133.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4151" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>German suplex</name>
<description>A wrestling move commonly used in a slapstick manner by one of the more unique characters in a series. The move typically signals a strong and coordinated individual (who may or may not actually be a wrestler). Often the move will be deployed on the same person over and over again as part of a running gag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5914" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-05">
<name>afterlife</name>
<description>The afterlife is the continued existence of an essential part of an individual`s identity or consciousness after the death of the body. When people continue existing beyond the death of their physical bodies, they may or may not keep interacting with the realm of the living and/or retain their memories. It is possible for them to start a new life without a physical body in a spirit realm, and they may or may not be able to understand that they`re already dead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-02">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your month and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6039" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-18">
<name>piggyback ride</name>
<description>One of the protagonists (usually male) gives another character (usually female) a ride on the back. Can be interpreted as a sign of closeness or endearment in a romance setting.
Reasons: The female character is exhausted from previous running, or has a fit of anaemia, or hurt herself and no longer can walk.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3527" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-02-18">
<rating votes="21">5.38</rating>
<name>Potato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Potato is the town`s stray puppy dog that lives in town mostly with Kano. Potato seems to follow Kano a lot, and was the reason that Kano and Yukito met due to his interest in Yukito`s puppet show. Potato makes frequent appearances throughout the series though he exists mostly as a minor character for comic relief in the visual novel and anime. Potato`s only `word` is "piko", though sometimes he will say the variations "pika" or "pikori".</description>
<picture>19301.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12092" type="main character in" update="2010-07-11">
<rating votes="184">7.05</rating>
<name>Nakamura Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuri, also known as Yurippe, is a girl with a determined personality who is attending the afterlife school, where she meets http://anidb.net/ch12094 [Otonashi] and invites him to join the SSS — http://anidb.net/ch15364 [Shinda Sekai Sensen] — an organization she leads which fights against God. She carries a silver Beretta 92.</description>
<picture>36636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12093" type="main character in" update="2010-07-17">
<rating votes="325">8.31</rating>
<name>Tenshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Angel is the student council president at the afterlife school. This places her at odds with the SSS as her responsibilities require her to suppress delinquency and other disruptive activities that the team does. The SSS initially calls her "Angel" since they do not know her real name, but they still refer to her by it even after finding out her real name to be Kanade Tachibana. It is difficult to understand what she is thinking due to her rarely showing any outward emotions. Despite her gentle demeanor and small frame, she is incredibly powerful and near indestructible to the point of ejecting bullets out of her wounds during battle. She creates her powers through a program called Angel Player. She is personally dedicated to helping others overcome their regrets and pass on. She has an affinity for eating mapo doufu, a spicy dish.</description>
<picture>36638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12094" type="main character in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="135">7.55</rating>
<name>Otonashi Yuzuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Otonashi Yuzuru is the main protagonist of Angel Beats!. Due to his past, he has a caring personality and does not want anyone to experience pain or sadness. After dying, he lost his memories of the time when he was still alive, but later regains them. He had a younger sister, http://anidb.net/ch17917 [Hatsune], who died of an illness and who he cared for very much. When she died, he decided to go to school to become a doctor, but died before he could take the entrance exam to college. Initially unskilled in any equipment, he starts to practice his marksmanship, and pulls through for the team when they are in danger. He carries a Glock 17. His love to http://anidb.net/ch12093 [Kanade] is expressed later on in the anime.</description>
<picture>53263.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13572" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="45">5.27</rating>
<name>Botan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Botan is Kyou`s pet baby boar, and is a comic relief character. Botan will sometimes go to Kyou`s school just to see her. Due to its small size and the fact that it is a baby boar, it is sometimes captured by several characters who talk of eating it. Botan hates Ryou because it mistook Ryou for trying to eat it when she took it for a warm bath. In the After Story, Botan has become an adult boar, but still acts the same. Botan has seven different skills, told him by Kyou, one of them being able to take the appearance of a stuffed animal by being extremely still. Another skill is called "Rugby Ball" in which Botan shrinks his legs until he resembles a ball, allowing Kyou to use him as a projectile. These skills are considered to be animal cruelty by Tomoya. Two other skills are mentioned in the visual novel, but never shown, called "massager" and "pillow".</description>
<picture>39770.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15118" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="126">7.44</rating>
<name>Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yui is a big fan and initially an assistant of http://anidb.net/ch15363 [Girls Dead Monster]. She enjoys playing guitar and singing on the street. She is known to be hyperactive and talks extremely fast. http://anidb.net/ch15355 [Hinata] finds her annoying, which results in bouts between the two of them. She wears a devil tail and shackle bracelets on her wrists, giving her an image of an imp or devil. She also has wings hidden by her hair on her back. After http://anidb.net/ch15354 [Iwasawa]`s departure, Yui becomes the new rhythm guitarist and vocalist of http://anidb.net/ch15363 [Girls Dead Monster], as well as assuming the leader position. Yui plays a Gibson SG Special electric guitar. She later becomes a part of the main http://anidb.net/ch15364 [SSS], following them along on missions. In life, Yui was paralyzed from the neck down after being hit by a car, which caused her to be bedridden. She wanted to do a lot of things in her life, such as performing a German suplex, playing soccer, and hitting a home run, inspirations she witnessed on television while bedridden and were left unfulfilled due to her paralysis. Her most important dream of all was to get married. This dream was fulfilled by http://anidb.net/ch15355 [Hinata], who stated that he would marry her, even if she was paralyzed. Yui finds peace in http://anidb.net/ch15355 [Hinata]`s words and passes on in episode ten.</description>
<picture>53266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17439" picture="51335.jpg">Lisa</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15349" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="99">7.51</rating>
<name>TK</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>TK is a mysterious character who wears a large bandanna over his eyes and tends to break out in dance every so often. No one knows his real name or past. He speaks in semi-nonsensical English phrases depending on the situation, but apparently does not know English fluently. He saves the team many times and does know some Japanese but rarely speaks it, though he seems to understand what others say to him. He carries Browning Hi-Power and LAR Grizzly handguns or a PP-19 Bizon submachine gun during missions.</description>
<picture>53275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13964" picture="43748.jpg">Michael Rivas</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15350" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="33">6.16</rating>
<name>Hisako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hisako is second-in-command of http://anidb.net/ch15363 [Girls Dead Monster] who plays a Fender Jazzmaster electric guitar as lead guitarist. She has a candid personality and likes to play mahjong, which she has incredible luck with. As noted by http://anidb.net/ch15355 [Hinata], Hisako is also athletic and is greatly admired by http://anidb.net/ch15118 [Yui] for her guitar riffs.</description>
<picture>53282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4983" picture="171535.jpg">Matsuura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15351" type="appears in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="15">4.41</rating>
<name>Chaa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chaa is the leader of the Guild. Despite looking much older, he is about the same age as http://anidb.net/ch12094 [Otonashi] and the others attending the afterlife school.</description>
<picture>53278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15352" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="31">5.68</rating>
<name>Irie Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Irie is the drummer of http://anidb.net/ch15363 [Girls Dead Monster] who, despite being dead herself, is bad with hearing stories about ghosts or spirits, which http://anidb.net/ch15361 [Sekine] likes to take advantage of. She is best friends with http://anidb.net/ch15361 [Sekine] and joined http://anidb.net/ch15363 [Girls Dead Monster] at the same time as her. Her full name is Irie Miyuki.</description>
<picture>53283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15353" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="34">2.90</rating>
<name>Ooyama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ooyama is an ordinary boy who has no special talents. He does not excel at anything, but is as capable as any normal person; in other words, he is a Jack of all trades. He is a pure boy whose feelings will get hurt from things like a making fake confession or watching his teammates "die". He carries a Remington 700 sniper rifle or a P226 handgun.</description>
<picture>53277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15354" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="96">6.94</rating>
<name>Iwasawa Masami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iwasawa is the initial leader of http://anidb.net/ch15363 [Girls Dead Monster] who is in charge of the vocals and is the rhythm guitarist. She also writes the lyrics and composes the music for the band`s songs. She plays a Sienna Sunburst/Maple Fender Stratocaster guitar. While usually a quiet girl, she is able to fascinate listeners by striving to create music that speaks her thoughts. She used music as an escape from her constantly fighting parents in life. Her full name is Iwasawa Masami.</description>
<picture>53279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20030" picture="51333.jpg">Marina</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15355" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-08">
<rating votes="87">7.08</rating>
<name>Hinata Hideki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinata Hideki is a bright, dependable boy who is the closest to http://anidb.net/ch12094 [Otonashi]. He always tries to save his friends if he can and is a reliable force in the team. He and http://anidb.net/ch15118 [Yui] constantly irritate one another on a daily basis, but deep down, he cares for http://anidb.net/ch15118 [Yui], as shown when he helps her pass on. He is a talented baseball player. He nicknamed http://anidb.net/ch12092 [Yuri] as Yurippe when they co-founded the http://anidb.net/ch15364 [SSS] as he did not feel comfortable calling her http://anidb.net/ch12092 [Yuri], because his mother has the same name.</description>
<picture>53264.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15356" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="37">3.41</rating>
<name>Matsushita Godan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsushita, also known as "Matsushita 5-dan", has a large build and is a master at judo. He never forgets a debt he owes, especially when it involves food (specifically gyuudon). He carries heavy weapons such as rocket launchers or machine guns into battle. He later loses weight after training in the mountains.</description>
<picture>53276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13954" picture="186143.jpg">Tokumoto Eiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15357" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="88">8.00</rating>
<name>Shiina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiina is a female ninja who fights with dual-wielding kodachi and shuriken. She is able to sense when danger is coming and is a highly capable fighter. Despite her serious demeanor, she has a weakness for cute things like stuffed animals. She is strict in her training and is very self-critical when she fails, especially to a newcomer like http://anidb.net/ch12094 [Otonashi]. She rarely speaks but will normally remark that those around her are "shallow-minded" whenever the obvious or something stupid is said.</description>
<picture>53271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1619" picture="157173.jpg">Saitou Fuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15358" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="38">3.01</rating>
<name>Fujimaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujimaki is a delinquent who fights with a long shirasaya. He picks on new people like http://anidb.net/ch12094 [Otonashi] but does not seem like a bad person himself. He cannot swim.</description>
<picture>53274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="606" picture="18011.jpg">Masuda Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15359" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="34">4.57</rating>
<name>Yusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yusa is an operator in the http://anidb.net/ch15364 [SSS] who conveys the state of the battlefield to http://anidb.net/ch12092 [Yuri]. She is a calm and gentle mannered girl with a straightforward character. Much like http://anidb.net/ch12093 [Tenshi], she does not express her emotions and is called scary by http://anidb.net/ch12094 [Otonashi] and http://anidb.net/ch15355 [Hinata]. She cannot calm down without her earphone. She rarely talks, and she sometimes hurts others` feelings even though she does not mean it.</description>
<picture>53272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15360" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="45">3.92</rating>
<name>Noda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noda is a self-reliant boy who executes the strategies formed by the http://anidb.net/ch15364 [SSS] and fights with a halberd. He does not listen to anyone other than http://anidb.net/ch12092 [Yuri], for whom he has adoration, and is antagonistic to almost everyone else. He has a one-sided rivalry with http://anidb.net/ch12094 [Otonashi]. He is a complete idiot whose weakness is education. He is not afraid to harm or kill anyone who gets in http://anidb.net/ch12092 [Yuri]`s way.</description>
<picture>53269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3502" picture="24684.jpg">Takagi Shun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15361" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="34">4.57</rating>
<name>Sekine Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sekine plays a G&amp;L L-2000 bass guitar in http://anidb.net/ch15363 [Girls Dead Monster]. She likes to play pranks on those around her to see the surprised faces of her victims. She also likes to abruptly improvise during performances, which makes http://anidb.net/ch15350 [Hisako] get mad at her. Her full name is Sekine Shiori.</description>
<picture>53284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15362" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="41">5.21</rating>
<name>Takamatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takamatsu is an honor student who has a polite personality and wears glasses. He mainly contributes to the http://anidb.net/ch15364 [SSS] through intelligence gathering and other affairs, but does not actively fight. http://anidb.net/ch12092 [Yuri] herself says to not be fooled by his glasses and that he is actually an idiot. Though appearing to be slender, he works out and is actually well-built muscle-wise. After he first reveals this, he tends to take his shirt off, much to everyone`s discomfort.</description>
<picture>53267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15363" type="appears in" update="2010-07-11">
<rating votes="11">8.03</rating>
<name>Girls Dead Monster</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Girls Dead Monster is a four-girl musical band whose objective in SSS is to cause a diversion from other activities http://anidb.net/ch15364 [SSS] is engaged in, while on the surface appearing to be a normal all female band.</description>
<picture>46908.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15364" type="appears in" update="2010-07-11">
<rating votes="27">7.96</rating>
<name>Shinda Sekai Sensen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>SSS or long Shinda Sekai Sensen, literally Afterlife War Front is an organisation which fights against God. It is being led by http://anidb.net/ch12092 [Yuri].
Note: rebels against the god is written on their logo.</description>
<picture>46127.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17062" type="appears in" update="2010-04-25">
<rating votes="6">1.27</rating>
<name>Iwasawa no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17063" type="appears in" update="2010-04-25">
<rating votes="6">1.60</rating>
<name>Iwasawa no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1619" picture="157173.jpg">Saitou Fuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17064" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-25">
<rating votes="30">2.81</rating>
<name>Takeyama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the new member to SSS who appears in Episode 3. He is good at hacking computers. He insists everyone call him by his handle name "Christ".</description>
<picture>46871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="71" picture="171537.jpg">Ichiki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17065" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="69">5.03</rating>
<name>Naoi Ayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naoi Ayato is a human originally thought to be a non-player character (non-human) who initially is the vice president of the student council, but becomes the student council president after http://anidb.net/ch12093 [Tenshi] is demoted thanks to http://anidb.net/ch12092 [Yuri]`s plan to demoralize her. He is much stricter than http://anidb.net/ch12093 [Tenshi] was and his first action as president is to punish the http://anidb.net/ch15364 [SSS] for their constant disobedience. After he died, Naoi developed hypnotic powers that allow him to control others and cause them to enter a dream-like state. In life, he replaced his older twin brother after he died in an accident and become his father`s apprentice in pottery, but Naoi was not as good at the craft as his brother had been. After his father became ill and died as well, Naoi got the impression that his entire life was fake.</description>
<picture>46872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17517" type="appears in" update="2010-05-10">
<rating votes="9">3.98</rating>
<name>Naoi Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naoi Hayato is a http://anidb.net/ch17065 [Naoi Ayato]`s twin brother.</description>
<picture>47641.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17518" type="appears in" update="2010-05-10">
<rating votes="8">2.31</rating>
<name>Naoi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch17065 [Naoi]`s father.</description>
<picture>47642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17718" type="appears in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="11">3.71</rating>
<name>Fish Saito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17917" type="appears in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="16">5.97</rating>
<name>Otonashi Hatsune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48350.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17918" type="appears in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="5">2.32</rating>
<name>Otonashi no Sobo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18271" type="appears in" update="2010-05-31">
<rating votes="10">3.00</rating>
<name>Igarashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20558" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="9">3.17</rating>
<name>Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20559" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="11">4.73</rating>
<name>Nazo no Seinen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41872" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="5">6.37</rating>
<name>Danshi A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2487" picture="23183.jpg">Akabane Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41873" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="2">1.34</rating>
<name>NPC Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>NPC teacher.</description>
<picture>82435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11041" picture="82436.jpg">Ooshita Kouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103790" type="appears in" update="2019-06-22">
<name>Yuri`s Sister A</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17860" picture="57847.jpg">Yamamoto Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103793" type="appears in" update="2019-06-22">
<name>Yuri no Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235242.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="103794" type="appears in" update="2019-06-22">
<name>Yuri no Kyoudai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235243.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="109045" update="2009-10-03">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109046" update="2009-10-03">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109047" update="2009-10-03">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109048" update="2010-03-29">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109049" update="2010-03-29">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112323" update="2009-12-29">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116758" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="47">5.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aufbruch</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ayrılış</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Departure</title>
<summary>After a mysterious accident, a young high school student wakes up to discover he is caught in some kind of violent afterlife where a strange and avenging Angel is pursuing him. Confused and afraid, he joins a band of gun-toting teens intent on destroying the Angel and taking their destinies into their own hands.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601699</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117222" update="2010-03-29">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117223" update="2010-03-29">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117225" update="2010-03-29">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">30s Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117397" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="42">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Graduation</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduation</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abschlussfeier</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Mezuniyet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Graduation</title>
<summary>When she awakens from her dangerous solo mission, Yuri finds her surviving friends in Battlefront seem to have found peace. In an impromptu “graduation” ceremony, they all take steps to move on to the next level of existence. But this transition seems most difficult for Otonashi, as it means losing his newly formed bond with Angel.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601723</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117398" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="45">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Knockin` on heaven`s door</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Knockin` on Heaven`s Door</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Knocking on Heavens Door</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Knocking on Heaven`s Door</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Knockin` on Heaven`s Door</title>
<summary>The Shadow monsters show no signs of stopping as more Battlefront members and NPCs fall victim to their strange, marauding power. Yuri takes a dangerous trip into the darkened Guild. In her search to find out just who—or what—is behind these new events, she discovers even darker secrets about herself.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601721</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117399" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="32">6.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Change the World</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Change the World</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ändere die Welt</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Dünyayı Değiştir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Change the World</title>
<summary>As Hinata and Otonashi talk with Naoi, something strange happens: his shadow takes an enormous, evil form and engulf him. Weapons are powerless to stop the creature. Making matters worse, the Shadow monsters are multiplying and taking control of the members of Battlefront and the NPCs.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601719</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117400" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="39">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Goodbye Days</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye Days</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abschiedstage</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Veda Günleri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goodbye Days</title>
<summary>Otonashi decides that the high-strung singer, Yui, needs to be pushed into finding peace and “moving on." To do so, he enlists Angel who shows him her new weapon: the dark and evil-looking Hand Sonic 5. But Yui has other plans—namely to beat the boys of Battlefront in a violent game on the soccer field.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601717</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117401" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="37">9.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">In Your Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Your Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Erinnerungen</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Hafızanda Kalanlar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">In Your Memory</title>
<summary>With the Angel clone situation becoming uncontrollable, Naoi proposes that they once again call upon the genius hacker, Christ. Meanwhile, Otonashi begins to remember his past.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601715</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117402" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="34">7.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dancer in the Dark</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dancer in the Dark</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Dancer in the Dark</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Karanlıkta Dans</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dancer in the Dark</title>
<summary>With Otonashi`s and Angel’s newly formed alliance, dark and powerful clones of Angel have begun attacking the Battlefront with greater aggression. They must return to the trap-rigged Guild once more and risk heartbreaking, violent losses.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601713</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117403" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="33">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Alive</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alive</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lebendig</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yaşamak</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alive</title>
<summary>Now that Naoi has seemingly joined Battlefront, Yui persuades Otonashi to let his powers of hypnosis help him recover his memories. But Otonashi may not be ready to remember such a tragic, painful past. But there are other issues at hand for the group—such as banding together to capture the mysterious creature from a nearby river known only as the Monster Stream.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601711</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117404" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="33">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Family Affair</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Family Affair</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Familienangelegenheit</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Aile Meselesi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Family Affair</title>
<summary>When Angel is believed to be breaking scholastic code, Naoi uses this infringement to exert his growing power and places both Angel and Otonashi in a prison within the school. They discover that Naoi is using his power in violently, and Angel and Otonashi must escape or risk heavy casualties.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601709</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117405" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="35">8.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Favorite Flavor</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Favorite Flavor</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Geschmackssache</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">En Sevdiği Yemek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Favorite Flavor</title>
<summary>To strip Angel of her scholastic power, Yui devises a plan for the Battlefront to replace Angel’s test results with bogus ones. She will be shamed, stripped of her title of Student Body President, and be out of their way for good. But they never realize the one who replaces her may be even more sinister than Angel could ever be.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601707</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117406" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="35">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Day Game</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Day Game</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Spieltag</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Maç Günü</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Day Game</title>
<summary>With the lead singer of Gldemo now obliterated, a replacement must be found. The manic, high-strung Yui tries desperately to assume the role. Hinata, meanwhile, seeks to avenge a mistake made long ago on the baseball field by assembling the strongest team possible to defeat the other teams in the school. Otonashi worries the game could strike Hinata out in more ways than one.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601705</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117407" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="41">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">My Song</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Song</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mein Song</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Benim Şarkım</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">My Song</title>
<summary>With the aid of a new member, the genius hacker, “Christ”, Yuri and the Battlefront decide to break into Angel’s lair and steal secrets from her hard drive. To distract the NPCs, they use the girl group Gldemo. But when the teachers interfere, the lead singer suffers a shocking fate.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601703</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117408" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="40">5.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Guild</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guild</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Gilde</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Lonca</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guild</title>
<summary>Realizing they need more weapons in their battle against Angel, the group descends into the Guild. But once there, they realize that all of the hallways, staircases, and passageways have been rigged with deadly traps. It’s a race against time to see if they can get through the violent maze before Angel catches up with them.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601701</identifier>
<identifier>angel-beats</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117617" update="2015-09-08">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="3">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Maeda Jun and the Director</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118412" update="2010-05-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118413" update="2015-09-08">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video: Brave Song</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119354" update="2010-06-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119641" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 03 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119642" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 02 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122456" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 07 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122457" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 06 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122458" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 05 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122459" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 04 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124196" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T21</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 08 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124197" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T22</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 09 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125133" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T23</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125134" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T24</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126072" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T25</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126073" update="2015-09-08">
<epno type="4">T26</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126311" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="30">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Stairway to Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stairway to Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Stairway to Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Stairway to Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Stairway to Heaven</title>
<summary>Yuri comes up with "Operation High Tension Syndrome", encouraging the other members to behave as wildly as possible, so they would appear to be enjoying school without disappearing. Yuri hopes this will make Tenshi wonder what is happening and lead them straight to God, threatening the others with no food for a week if they fail.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="126387" update="2010-12-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="31">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANOTHER EPILOGUE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Epilogue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Another Epilogue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126593" update="2015-09-08">
<epno type="4">T28</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode "Stairway to Heaven" Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126698" update="2011-01-08">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9 April Fools</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130159" update="2014-12-22">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">週刊トロ・ステーション第29号 Angel Beats!ごっこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Weekly Toro Station 29: Angel Beats! Joint</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuukan Toro Station Dai 29 Gou: Angel Beats! Gokko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138901" update="2015-09-08">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138902" update="2015-09-08">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138903" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138904" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1l</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138905" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1k</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138906" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138907" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138908" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138909" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138910" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138911" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138912" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138978" update="2015-09-08">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139006" update="2012-04-21">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139007" update="2012-04-21">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">15s Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139008" update="2015-09-08">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Angel Beats! The Making 創り手たちの肖像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel Beats! The Making 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angel Beats! The Making: Tsukuri Te-tachi no Shouzou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140520" update="2015-09-08">
<epno type="4">T27</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode "Stairway to Heaven" Original Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140521" update="2015-09-08">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Angel Beats! The Making 創り手たちの肖像 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel Beats! The Making 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angel Beats! The Making: Tsukuri Te-tachi no Shouzou 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164820" update="2017-08-20">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2015-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Hell`s Kitchen</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell`s Kitchen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hell`s Kitchen</title>
<summary>Set between episodes two and three during Golden Week, Yuri arranges for the SSS to go on a deadly picnic, which involves most of the members trying to kill each other with various traps and gadgets. Sensing an opportunity, Girls Dead Monster members Irie and Sekine conspire to kill Iwasawa and seize control of the band from her. As the boys largely fall victim to various traps, leaving just Otonashi alive, Irie and Sekine attempt to lead Iwasawa into various pitfalls, but she survives each one while remaining completely oblivious. With Shiina`s help, they attempt to use their last trap, a dreadful concoction of raw liver, but it instead lands on Hisako, who transforms into a bloodthirsty monster that not even Tenshi can stop. Sometime later, Irie and Sekine explain the events of the picnic to Yui and how they inspired the band to take on their current name.
Source: EN Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="165075" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Blu-Ray Box CM (29 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165076" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell`s Kitchen CM (32 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168637" update="2015-05-24">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別篇第2話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell`s Kitchen PV2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Hen Dai 2 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179338" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Afterlife Battlefront Skit Collection</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
