<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6589" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-08-15</startdate>
<enddate>2009-08-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mai Mai Shinko to Sennen no Mahou</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Шинко с вихром и тысячелетняя магия</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マイマイ新子と千年の魔法</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mai Mai Miracle</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Das Mädchen mit dem Zauberhaar - Mai Mai Miracle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mai Mai Miracle</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Mai Mai Miracle</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Šinko a kouzelná šošolka</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Mai Mai Stebuklas</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8832" approval="7" total="9">Ookami Kodomo no Ame to Yuki</anime>
<anime id="4895" approval="1" total="1">Kaze no Shoujo Emily</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://mai-mai.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="219" type="Direction">Katabuchi Sunao</name>
<name id="8466" type="Original Work">Takagi Nobuko</name>
<name id="9594" type="Music">Murai Shuusei</name>
<name id="14875" type="Character Design">Tsuji Shigehito</name>
<name id="14875" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tsuji Shigehito</name>
<name id="9013" type="Music">Minako "mooki" Obata</name>
</creators>
<description>In 1955 in western Japan, nine-year-old http://anidb.net/ch34772 [Shinko] knows she comes from a family that dates back to over a thousand years. This long genealogy and stories about it feed her daydreams: she invents an imaginary friendship with a young girl in the Japan of a thousand years ago. One day, http://anidb.net/ch34773 [Kiiko], a timid child from Tokyo, is transferred into Shinko`s class at school. Struggling to fit in, she finds a friend in Shinko. They set off together on a magical adventure into a story from ancient history.
Note: Adapted from the http://anidb.net/cr8466 [Takagi Nobuko] novel Mai Mai Shinko — winner of the prestigious Akutagawa Prize[i] — this animated feature film portrays the relationship of two children linked not only by friendship, but also by that power that transcends eras: imagination.
European premiere — 15.08.2009 at the [/i]Locarno International Film Festival, Japan premiere — 21.11.2009</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="457">6.87</permanent>
<temporary count="459">7.19</temporary>
<review count="1">5.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>238951.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10975</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5084</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mai-mai.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mai_Mai_Miracle</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マイマイ新子と千年の魔法</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2608</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334304</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11857</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3869" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>mono no aware</name>
<description>Literally "the pathos of things", also translated as "an empathy toward things," or "a sensitivity of ephemera"; a Japanese term used to describe the awareness of the transience of things and a gentle sadness (or wistfulness) at their passing.
Also frequently been translated as "the `ahh-ness` of things".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3931" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-27">
<name>magical realism</name>
<description>Magical realism is fiction that portrays magical or unreal elements as a natural part in an otherwise realistic or mundane environment, in particular when a highly detailed, realistic setting is invaded by something too strange to believe. Magical realism is often associated with Latin American literature, particularly authors including Gabriel García Márquez and Isabel Allende.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="34772" type="main character in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="3">5.68</rating>
<name>Aoki Shinko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinko is the main heroine of the story.</description>
<picture>75743.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39813" picture="153826.jpg">Fukuda Mayuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34773" type="main character in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">5.93</rating>
<name>Kiiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42129" picture="167354.jpg">Mizusawa Nako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34774" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">2.32</rating>
<name>Fujiwara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiwara comes from the General Affairs Section. He`s fetching Kiiko and Shimazu-sensei up from the train station.</description>
<picture>75745.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34775" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">4.86</rating>
<name>Aoki Mitsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mitsuko is Shinko`s little sister.</description>
<picture>75747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="635" picture="18162.jpg">Matsumoto Tamaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34776" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">5.93</rating>
<name>Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shigeru is a classmate of Shinko and Kiiko. He`s carrying around a turtle on a string. It seems that his mental abilities are not fully developed.</description>
<picture>75749.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42128" picture="167353.jpg">Nakajima Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34777" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">5.20</rating>
<name>Mitsuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mitsuru is from class 6.</description>
<picture>75750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42126" picture="167351.jpg">Nishihara Nobuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34778" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">9.39</rating>
<name>Tatsuyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75751.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34779" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">6.31</rating>
<name>Hitsuru-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the teachers at school. She smells very good.</description>
<picture>75752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42125" picture="167350.jpg">Wakita Miyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34780" type="main character in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">4.18</rating>
<name>Kiyokawa Nagiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of the gouvernour of Suou. After her father became the governour they moved away from Tokyo to Kokugai 1000 years ago.</description>
<picture>75753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27882" picture="75699.jpg">Morisako Ei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34781" type="appears in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">6.66</rating>
<name>Tatsuyoshi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuyoshi`s father. He`s also a police officer.</description>
<picture>75754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42124" picture="167346.jpg">Setoguchi Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34782" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">5.93</rating>
<name>Hitoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the kids.</description>
<picture>75755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42123" picture="167344.jpg">Kawakami Satoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34785" type="appears in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Bar California no Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60052" picture="203738.jpg">Kitamura Shizue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34787" type="appears in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">6.31</rating>
<name>Aoki Tousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinko`s papa. He researches green algae at Yamaguchi University.</description>
<picture>75766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34788" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">8.03</rating>
<name>Aoki Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinko`s grandpa.</description>
<picture>75767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2981" picture="23711.jpg">Noda Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34789" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="2">4.86</rating>
<name>Aoki Kazuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinko`s mama.</description>
<picture>75768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34975" picture="130925.jpg">Honjou Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="105852" update="2009-08-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2009-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
