<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6609" restricted="false">
<type>Music Video</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-05-27</startdate>
<enddate>2009-05-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann Kirameki Youko Box: Pieces of Sweet Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gurren Lagann Sparkle Youko Box: Pieces of Sweet Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">천원돌파 그렌라간 반짝☆요코 Box- Pieces of Sweet Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">天元突破グレンラガン キラメキ☆ヨーコBOX~Pieces of sweet stars~</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4575" type="Other">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.gurren-lagann.net/yoko/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="155" type="Direction">Imaishi Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="1414" type="Music">Iwasaki Taku</name>
</creators>
<description>A music video by character designer http://anidb.net/cr3078 [Nishigori Atsushi] for "S.t.a.r.S", the new song that the voice actress http://anidb.net/cr11 [Inoue Marina] sings in her http://anidb.net/ch470 [Youko] persona. Nishigori personally planned and directed entirely new footage for the music video. The bundled DVD includes a video interview with Inoue and a booklet with over 130 pages of storyboards, original drawings, and designs.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1022">5.52</permanent>
<temporary count="1027">6.64</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224565.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6548</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gurren-lagann.net/yoko/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>List_of_Gurren_Lagann_episodes#Music_videos</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>天元突破グレンラガン#キラメキ☆ヨーコBOX</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11470</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="183" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-25">
<name>boxing</name>
<description>Boxing is a combat sport in which two people, usually wearing protective gloves, throw punches at each other for a predetermined set of time in a boxing ring.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="468" type="appears in" update="2016-10-26">
<rating votes="1619">8.82</rating>
<name>Kamina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamina is a young man from Jeeha village who dreams of leaving the village and go to the surface, which he saw as a child. He`s very passionate about his goals, expressing his wishes through energetic speeches, which seem to affect all those who hear them.
As the leader of the "Gurren Brigade", he convinces Simon to aid him in his plan to drill through the roof of the village and get to the world above, but the plan fails and he is imprisoned. After defeating an invading Gunmen, he leaves the village with Simon and Yoko, in the cockpit of a tiny but powerful Gunmen Simon unearths and Kamina names "Lagann".
Kamina is extremely impulsive, and sometimes acts with little regard for his life. His plans are rarely well thought-out, often relying solely on brute strength and determination to win, but for some strange reason or another, they seem to work most of the time. It is revealed that Kamina`s impulsive confidence is mostly a show to give Simon the courage to act. He believes that in reality, all he can do is give Simon the motivation to "reach the heavens"; he couldn`t do it himself.</description>
<picture>14764.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="469" type="appears in" update="2016-10-26">
<rating votes="660">7.68</rating>
<name>Simon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Simon is a fourteen year-old digger from Jeeha village. Although he is initially looked down upon because of it, Simon excels at drilling through the ground, and the drill quickly becomes his trademark symbol. One day, he finds a mysterious drill-shaped item, which is later revealed to be the "Core Drill", for a head-shaped Gunmen he also finds buried in the soil. With the help of the small Gunmen, Kamina, and Yoko, he fights off a much larger Gunmen that falls into the village. In the process of defeating the invader, they reach the surface world. Prior to the time-skip, Simon is mostly depicted as merely following Kamina`s lead and often acting as a counter-balance to Kamina`s impulsiveness. An unfortunate accident forces Simon to mature and take up a leadership role within Team Dai-Gurren.</description>
<picture>14766.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="470" type="main character in" update="2020-01-16">
<rating votes="1477">8.55</rating>
<name>Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl from Jeeha`s neighbouring village of Littner, who had been chasing the Gunmen which entered Jeeha village. She wields an extensive arsenal of firearms and has previous experience fighting Gunmen. She uses her marksmanship from afar to assist Kamina and Simon, while they pilot their respective Gunmen.</description>
<picture>14767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="471" type="appears in" update="2008-12-10">
<rating votes="530">6.69</rating>
<name>Nia Teppelin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nia is a mysterious young girl found by Simon sleeping in a capsule in the middle of a dump site. She has had no prior contact with humans except her father. She is very curious, pure and innocent, because of a sheltered childhood in a peaceful environment away from all the battles occurring in the outside world, and because she had only recently gained sentience. During her travels with Team Dai-Gurren, she discovers the harsh realities of the world and has a very close relationship with Simon throughout the story.</description>
<picture>14768.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="508" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="184">6.95</rating>
<name>Kittan Bachika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kittan Bachika is the oldest of the Black Siblings. During his first encounter with Team Gurren, he mistakenly confuses Kamina for a Beastman. This is reconciled, when it is discovered that Kamina is piloting the Gunmen, Gurren. Shortly after, the two teams (the Black Siblings and Team Gurren) come into contact with the sixteen-headed enemy Gunmen, whom the Black Siblings had crossed paths with earlier. After the eventual defeat of the enemy Gunmen, the two teams part ways.</description>
<picture>14807.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="514" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="102">3.22</rating>
<name>Kinon Bachika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinon is the second oldest of Kittan`s younger sisters. After Team Dai-Gurren`s capture of Dai-Gunzan, she takes up a position within its control tower, monitoring the radar. She seems to be the calmest and smartest member of the Black Siblings.</description>
<picture>14812.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1503" type="appears in" update="2009-12-19">
<rating votes="299">8.29</rating>
<name>Viral</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Viral is a member of the Human Eradication Army, who regards Kamina as a strong rival. Though being among the more humanoid of the Beastmen, his DNA contains aspects of shark and feline genetics. He pilots Enkidudu, which mainly utilizes swords and a powerful laser. He is extremely loyal to Lordgenome and the four supreme generals, and he does his best to serve them. After Kamina`s death, he continues to fight Gurren-Lagann, thinking that Kamina is still alive, and he is shocked once he learns the truth. He is given the gift of immortality by Lordgenome, so that he could spread his legacy. After the fall of the empire, he resurfaces and causes an uproar with his Gunmen, calling Simon out to fight him. He is later taken into custody, and pilots Gurren during the battle against the Anti-Spirals. Viral thus becomes a `reformed villain` of sorts. It is also shown that his deepest desire is to get married and have children, but cannot do so as Beastmen lack the spiral energy necessary for reproduction. In the epilogue, he becomes the captain of the Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren and an emissary for Earth.</description>
<picture>16029.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1541" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="93">5.91</rating>
<name>Darry Aday</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darry Aday is a girl from Aday Village, who used to be cared for by Rossiu. She is Gimmy`s twin sister and has a good bond with him. As a young girl, she was shy and quiet and used to cling to a plush doll, which she carried with her at all times. After the timeskip, however, she is much more confident and has left her old personality behind. As a Grapearl pilot, she is careful, calm and perceptive, and puts more thought and planning into her actions than Gimmy.</description>
<picture>16077.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1543" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="79">3.78</rating>
<name>Gimmy Aday</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gimmy Aday is a boy from Aday Village, who used to be cared for by Rossiu. When new children were born into the village, the population exceeded its limit of 50, which mandated that two people be removed and sent to the surface. Since Gimmy and Darry had no parents, the village elder chose them to leave the village, however, Rossiu decided to go with them. The pair of twins have a very good bond with each other, and were often left to their own devices around Dai-Gurren, except when they were with older girls, such as Yoko or Nia. After the timeskip, Gimmy and Darry become important Grapearl pilots, often fighting together. Gimmy tends to be more impulsive and reckless, which sometimes puts the duo in trouble.</description>
<picture>16078.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1544" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="88">6.20</rating>
<name>Kiyal Bachika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest of the Black Siblings.</description>
<picture>16079.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1545" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="74">5.94</rating>
<name>Kiyoh Littner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The oldest of Kittan`s younger sisters.</description>
<picture>16080.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1546" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="35">5.25</rating>
<name>Dayakka Littner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dayakka Littner is the former leader of Littner Village, abandoning his post, when most of Littner joined Team Dai-Gurren. His Gunmen is the Dayakkaiser, but after the seizure of Dai-Gunzan, he acted as the captain of Dai-Gurren during battles, while Kiyoh piloted the Dayakkaiser in his stead.</description>
<picture>16081.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1580" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="212">5.63</rating>
<name>Leeron Littner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leeron Littner, or simply "Ron", is the village mechanic of Littner, who is able to repair and scavenge the various Gunmen he and his group encounter. Quite knowledgeable, and very flamboyant, Leeron was the first one to join Kamina, Simon, and Yoko on their quest to defeat the Beastmen. He has become the main technician for Team Dai-Gurren, as well as being in charge of coordination and communication between the Gunmen during battle from Dai-Gurren. His ability to learn and adapt is incredibly great, seeing as he once mentioned that he didn`t even know how to read before becoming a mechanic.</description>
<picture>16119.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1825" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="9">6.21</rating>
<name>Makken Jokin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makken is a fairly silent man who is an important part of Team Dai-Gurren, but has rarely spoken or gotten much screen time whatsoever. He has his own Gunmen, Moshogun, which is based on an ancient samurai.
After the timeskip, Makken is married to Leite with three children. Sadly, he is killed in the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, after sacrificing himself to stop a large Anti-Spiral missile from destroying the Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren.
In the epilogue, a memorial site, in the form of a sword, is seen in his honour right alongside Kamina and the other members of Team Dai-Gurren.</description>
<picture>27556.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1826" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="10">5.57</rating>
<name>Zorthy Kanai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zorthy Kanai appears at the end of episode seven as a new addition to Team Dai-Gurren. His most recognisable quality is his smoking habit, which is unique to every other character in the series. The name of his Gunmen is the Sozoshin.
Zorthy is killed during the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals.</description>
<picture>27550.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1827" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="14">6.08</rating>
<name>Iraak Coega</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iraak Coega is a member of Team Dai-Gurren. He pilots a Gunmen that serves Youko as a mobile rifle platform. Together, they assaulted Dai-Gunzan with the rest of the Team Gurren. The name of his Gunmen is Ainzer.
Iraak is killed during the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, after he and Kid attempted to avenge Zorthy.</description>
<picture>27555.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1828" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="11">6.88</rating>
<name>Kid Coega</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kid Coega is another new member of Team Dai-Gurren. His Gunmen utilises two pistols to attack enemies, the Kid Knuckle.
Kid is killed during the first deep space battle versus the Anti-Spirals, when he and Iraak attempt to avenge Zorthy`s death.</description>
<picture>27552.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1831" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="70">3.44</rating>
<name>Attenborough Cortitch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Attenborough Cortitch is a hyperactive, impulsive, trigger-happy man, who is the gunner of Dai-Gurren`s control team. He tends to fire at enemies or move Dai-Gurren without warning. After the timeskip, he joins Leeron`s science team and still appears to have his hyperactive nature. After Team Dai-Gurren moved to Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren, he assumed the same position he had before at the weapons control. Curiously, this trait became one of Tengen Toppa Gurren-Lagann`s attacks. He randomly showed up in the series one day, later it was confirmed that he sneaked into some bozo`s luggage, and that is how he joined Team Dai Gurren.</description>
<picture>16423.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1832" type="appears in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="9">5.80</rating>
<name>Tetsukan Littner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tetsukan Littner is a member of the control team for Dai-Gurren. He is in charge of monitoring the condition of the ship. After the timeskip, he becomes a part of Leeron`s science team. Also due to being attracted to the fast-food restaurants that were built in the new city he became obese.</description>
<picture>27871.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1833" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="14">5.84</rating>
<name>Gabal Docker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gabal Docker is Team Dai-Gurren`s helmsman, in charge of Dai-Gurren`s steering and manoeuvring.</description>
<picture>16422.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1834" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="11">5.48</rating>
<name>Cybela Kuto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cybela Kuto is mainly seen at a computer, where she can communicate with Grapearls or do analysis tasks. Later, she joins Team Dai-Gurren, assuming a position at Super Galaxy Dai-Gurren`s bridge.</description>
<picture>16419.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="103934" update="2009-06-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
