<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6621" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-08-22</startdate>
<enddate>2009-08-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hachigatsu no Symphony: Shibuya 2002-2003</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">8-gatsu no Symphony: Shibuya 2002-2003</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">8月のシンフォニー -渋谷 2002~2003</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Symphony in August</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Srpnová symfonie</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="554857">Very personal movie based on the autobiography of Kawashima Ai. Don’t expect anything overly dramatic, but it’s gentle and bittersweet and upbeat at the same time and definitely deserves a recommendation.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.8gatsu-eiga.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1276" type="Work">Wao World</name>
<name id="45940" type="Work">Okutsu Sakiko</name>
<name id="34072" type="Work">Kawakita Masato</name>
<name id="5028" type="Original Work">Kawashima Ai</name>
<name id="3123" type="Direction">Nishizawa Akio</name>
<name id="5944" type="Character Design">Ryuuno Tatsuo</name>
<name id="5944" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ryuuno Tatsuo</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the autobiography Saigo no Kotoba (最後の言葉, "The Last Words") of singer-songwriter http://anidb.net/cr5028 [Kawashima Ai].
The Saigo no Kotoba book follows Kawashima`s life after her mother`s death, and her pursuit of her singing dreams by performing free concerts on the streets of Tokyo`s Shibuya district.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="38">7.64</permanent>
<temporary count="38">7.45</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>233410.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10908</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6670</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.8gatsu-eiga.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.8gatsu-eiga.com/english/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8月のシンフォニー_-渋谷2002〜2003</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2012</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334036</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11455</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2420</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11220</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17898</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4616" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>based on real events</name>
<description>Contains content based on real-life events.
Depending on the creators` wishes those events may have been altered. In the most substantial cases, expect many things to have been changed from the original events.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4814" parentid="4616" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>biographical film</name>
<description>A biographical film, or biopic, is a film that dramatizes the life of an actual person or people. Such films show the life of a historical person and the central character’s real name is used. They differ from films "based on a true story" or "historical films" in that they attempt to comprehensively tell a person’s life story or at least the most historically important years of their lives.
(Source: en.wiki)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="23536" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="2">6.02</rating>
<name>Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She came alone to Tokyo from Fukuoka when she was just 15 years old. She has a strong dream to be a professional singer, which is also her mother`s. She started hopeful life in Tokyo. However, she was fired by her agency. Nevertheless, she didn`t give up on her dream. She decided to do 1000 times street performances.</description>
<picture>58085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23537" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<name>Ai no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She loves Ai. Ai is her everything. She had a strong dream that Ai would be a singer. So she overworked because her husband had died of. She financially helped Ai`s going to high school in Tokyo in spite of her poor health. She cheers her up over the phone from Fukuoka.</description>
<picture>58086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22136" picture="58088.jpg">Takahashi Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23538" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-27">
<name>Akiba Shachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is 35 years old, a young capable president of a marketing company. On the other hand he supports a student business seminar and offers a part of his office for the students aiming to be entrepreneurs. He is so unconventional and openhearted that the students respect him. When he speaks passionately, his tone gradually gets rude, but he is mentally romantic and is easily moved to tears.</description>
<picture>58087.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="104828" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>120</length>
<airdate>2009-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111373" update="2009-11-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">15s TV commercial</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
