<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6628" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-04-19</startdate>
<enddate>2000-04-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Virtual Star 2000</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">バーチャルスター2000</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Virtually Real - Virtual Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Virtually Real - Virtual Stars</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1558" type="Other">Cybervenus FeiFei</anime>
<anime id="4629" type="Other">Yuki Terai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.ponycanyon.co.jp/wtne/video/000419virt.html</url>
<description>Meet mysterious Miharu, awesome Aya, ruthless Ryoko, mind-blowing Misty, youthful Yukari and heavenly Hikary in a stunning series of computer-generated femininity.
In Super Sonic Jet Girl, you`ll enter a hellish nightclub where lingerie-clad Miharu defends herself in a most personal fashion. Chat places the longingly lovely Aya on the streets of your dreams. In Run &amp; Run, Yukari breathes hard and races fast - to nowhere. A Jellyfish Day finds the blonde bombshell Hikary starring in a music video about her private passions. Ryoko inhabits Yamag`s Garage, an arena of "Pure Mind," "Love," and a very "Beautiful Face." And Misty mesmerizes in a music video in which she brags: "I`m your magnet of love, and I`m here to serve you."</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="11">4.00</permanent>
<temporary count="11">4.54</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>28855.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22561</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ponycanyon.co.jp/wtne/video/000419virt.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4199" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-20">
<name>live-action closing -- TO BE MOVED AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be removed. For each tagged anime, please tag the corresponding ending/credits episodes with the http://anidb.net/t6679 [live-action episode] tag (adding them and their relation to the ending songs if necessary) and then remove this tag from it. Please do not apply this credit to the main episode that has the live-action ending, only to the corresponding credits episode. For example, if episode 22 has a live-action ending, and that ending is also credits episode C7, tag episode C7, not episode 22.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="104162" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Aya - Chat</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104163" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukari - Run &amp; Run</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104164" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ryoko - In Japan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104165" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Sonic Jet Girl</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104166" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Misty</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104167" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Hikary - A Jellyfish Day</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104168" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Aya: Making of - Editing with real pictures</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104169" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Aya: Making of - Facial expression</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104170" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Aya: Art Gallery</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104171" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukari: Earlier Clips</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104172" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukari: Making of - Polygon pattern</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104173" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukari: Making of - Computer graphics model</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104174" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukari: Art Gallery</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104175" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ryoko: Making of - Control Link</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104176" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ryoko: Making of - Blinking Eyes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104177" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ryoko: Art Gallery</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104178" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Sonic Jet Girl: Jet Girls</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104179" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Sonic Jet Girl: Steel Heart</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104180" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Sonic Jet Girl: Making of - Morph Gizmo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104181" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Sonic Jet Girl: Making of - Zero object</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104182" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Sonic Jet Girl: Art Gallery</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104183" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Misty: From the Producer of Misty - X-RIDERS</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104184" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Misty: Project Wivern</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104185" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Misty: Other Images from ICEMAN</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104186" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Misty: Making of - Meta NURBS</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104187" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Misty: Art Gallery</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104188" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Hikary: Escalator</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104189" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Hikary: The First Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104190" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Hikary: Making of - Animating Hair</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104191" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Hikary: Making of - Composition with Motion Designer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="104192" update="2009-06-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Hikary: Art Gallery</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
