<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6637" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-03-13</startdate>
<enddate>2010-03-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Higashi no Eden: Gekijouban II - Paradise Lost</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Eden of the East Movie II: Paradise Lost</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Eden Movie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">東のエデン 劇場版II Paradise Lost</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Eden of the East: Paradise Lost</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Eden of the East - Das verlorene Paradies</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">동쪽의 에덴 극장판 2 : Paradise Lost</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6636" type="Prequel">Higashi no Eden: Gekijouban I - The King of Eden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://juiz.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1606" type="Character Design">Morikawa Satoko</name>
<name id="3033" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakamura Satoru</name>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="205" type="Direction">Kamiyama Kenji</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="205" type="Original Work">Kamiyama Kenji</name>
</creators>
<description>The story of political and subversive intrigue in the series finally reaches endgame. Even as the law enforcement net tightens around http://anidb.net/ch5628 [Saki] and her fellow Eden of the East associates over alleged terrorist activities, the complex web surrounding the mysterious Mr. Outside is finally untangled as the remaining Selecao attempt to outmaneuver one another. http://anidb.net/ch5629 [Takizawa]`s memories and identity are also finally revealed including his association with a former Prime Minister and his request to be the King of Eden.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2339">6.52</permanent>
<temporary count="2350">7.35</temporary>
<review count="1">8.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>233332.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10919</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6637</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4585</identifier>
<identifier>dbdeko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://juiz.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Eden_of_the_East</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>東のエデン#.E3.80.8E.E6.9D.B1.E3.81.AE.E3.82.A8.E3.83.87.E3.83.B3_.E5.8A.87.E5.A0.B4.E7.89.88II_Paradise_Lost_.E3.80.8F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2184</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334512</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12404</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2387</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11642</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1528" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-12">
<name>artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligence of machines and the branch of computer science that aims to create it. AI textbooks define the field as "the study and design of intelligent agents" where an intelligent agent is a system that perceives its environment and takes actions that maximize its chances of success. John McCarthy, who coined the term in 1956, defines it as "the science and engineering of making intelligent machines."
The field was founded on the claim that a central property of humans, intelligence—the sapience of Homo sapiens—can be so precisely described that it can be simulated by a machine. This raises philosophical issues about the nature of the mind and the ethics of creating artificial beings, issues which have been addressed by myth, fiction and philosophy since antiquity. Artificial intelligence has been the subject of optimism, but has also suffered setbacks and, today, has become an essential part of the technology industry, providing the heavy lifting for many of the most difficult problems in computer science.
AI research is highly technical and specialized, and deeply divided into subfields that often fail to communicate with each other. Subfields have grown up around particular institutions, the work of individual researchers, the solution of specific problems, longstanding differences of opinion about how AI should be done and the application of widely differing tools. The central problems of AI include such traits as reasoning, knowledge, planning, learning, communication, perception and the ability to move and manipulate objects. General intelligence (or "strong AI") is still among the field`s long term goals.</description>
<picurl>71305.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2620" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-21">
<name>battle royale</name>
<description>Many characters are removed from their normal lives or lifestyles and thrown into a game where they are forced to battle each other until one survivor remains. Much like the famous film `Battle Royale`.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5628" type="main character in" update="2010-09-15">
<rating votes="140">6.76</rating>
<name>Morimi Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morimi Saki is in her last year in university. After her parents died she lived with her elder married sister and her baby. She visited New York City as part of her graduation trip with her friends and after visiting Washington D.C. alone, she meets Takizawa Akira who helped her out when she threw a coin in the grounds of the White House and is questioned by the police. After noticing that she left her passport in the coat she gave to Akira, she follows him and then decides to go back with him to Tokyo, Japan. She plans to work in the company her brother-in-law owns, because she is ashamed of living off their money. She could only go to university with the aid of her sister and her brother-in-law.</description>
<picture>28393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5629" type="main character in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="153">7.75</rating>
<name>Takizawa Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5630" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="39">2.25</rating>
<name>Oosugi Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend of Saki and also in the last year of university. He went together with her to the graduation trip to New York. He has an unrequited love for Saki and is both suspicious and jealous of Takizawa Akira. After seeing him several times with Saki, he decides to find out more about Akira`s past.</description>
<picture>28392.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5631" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="39">4.73</rating>
<name>Hirasawa Kazuomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He appears to be the de facto leader of Eden of the East. However, he admits that he has no inherent talents and that most of the credit to Eden of the East`s success belongs to Micchon and Saki. His ultimate goal is to create a paradise for NEETs.</description>
<picture>28391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="92" picture="53209.jpg">Kawahara Motoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5632" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="63">7.60</rating>
<name>Micchon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very shy girl, who is only open and frank when around people she is close to. She is apparently a genius programmer, as she is the person who programmed Eden of the East`s image recognition software. She is also very good when it comes to working with computers.</description>
<picture>28390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="397" picture="43234.jpg">Saitou Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5633" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="23">4.58</rating>
<name>Onee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Onee appears to be an older member of the club.</description>
<picture>28389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5634" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="26">3.56</rating>
<name>Kasuga Haruo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kasuga is Oosugi`s friend, and seems to possess a great insight into the qualities of others. For some unknown reason, he hides under a desk during club meetings.</description>
<picture>28388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2574" picture="171787.jpg">Taya Hayato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5637" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="68">7.67</rating>
<name>Shiratori Diana Kuroha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiratori is president of a model agency by day; however by night, she is actually a serial killer. She is also Selecao`s No. 11, and uses the cellphone to clean up evidence of her murders and cover up her crimes. She kills men by chopping off their penises ("Johnnies") with a cigar cutter. However, she only targets men who have victimised women, like rapists, and it is implied that she had been a victim herself, inspiring her current actions as a Selecao.</description>
<picture>28395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="693" picture="226546.jpg">Igarashi Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5638" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-14">
<rating votes="28">7.66</rating>
<name>Mameshiba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28396.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8953" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="10">1.74</rating>
<name>Yuuki Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Selecao No. 10. The perpetrator responsible for the missiles fired on Careless Monday. He also appears to be collaborating with Mononobe.</description>
<picture>28380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8954" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="6">1.35</rating>
<name>Tsuji Jintarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Selecao No. 2.</description>
<picture>28381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8955" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="10">2.35</rating>
<name>Mononobe Daiju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Selecao No. 1.</description>
<picture>28382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="623" picture="18148.jpg">Miyauchi Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8956" type="appears in" update="2010-09-15">
<rating votes="2">1.83</rating>
<name>Selecao</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Selecao are twelve individuals (including Akira) which are each given 10 billion yen by the mysterious Mr. Outside for them to spend. This huge sum is in digital currency only and cannot be exchanged for real world money. The Selecao are allowed to spend the money how they see fit, but they must make use of the money to find a way to save the country. The supporter who is hiding as one of the Selecao will be sent by Mr. Outside himself, to assassinate one of the other participants if they try to escape, use the money wrongly or fails with his/her mission to help society; it is also mentioned that when one of them successfully saves Japan, the other remaining ones will be eliminated as well, regardless of their less than complete successes.
Note: The name Selecao comes from the Portuguese word Seleção (Selection).</description>
<picture>28385.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8957" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="45">6.28</rating>
<name>Itazu Yutaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A prodigious yet reclusive hacker that the Eden club nicknamed "Pantsu" based on an alternate reading of the Kanji in his name. Once an engineering student, Yutaka became a recluse after losing his only pair of pants. Takizawa offers him Kondou`s Selecao phone to aid in his investigation of the events surrounding Careless Monday.</description>
<picture>28383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8984" type="appears in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="9">7.38</rating>
<name>Morimi Asako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saki`s elder sister. Works at the family bakery - "Sangetsu Pan". After her parents died, she and her husband took care of Saki.</description>
<picture>28431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4956" picture="28490.jpg">Matsutani Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8985" type="appears in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="11">7.60</rating>
<name>Morimi Ryousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saki`s brother-in-law, whom Saki had a crush on.</description>
<picture>28432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2671" picture="151652.jpg">Iwao Mantarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9763" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-08">
<rating votes="45">8.38</rating>
<name>Juiz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious female voice who is connected to the twelve Selecao. She gives them information and provides for their requests to be answered, from bribing authorities to assassination orders. Her name comes from the Portuguese word for "Judge".
In episode 10, it is revealed that Juiz isn`t an actual person, but an advanced artificial intelligence.</description>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16574" type="appears in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Naomoto Taishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naomoto intends to film the "ideal movie" with Akira and Saki as the main characters, and to ultimately kill them in such a way that has never before been seen in film. For that reason, he causes them a lot of problems, especially for Saki, because he figures that the prince will come to save `the damsel in distress`. His ill-conceived plot is foiled thanks to Shiratori`s intervention. Amusingly, his Juiz seems be uncooperative and usually ridicules his requests.</description>
<picture>46067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20539" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Kitabayashi Toshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20566" picture="206821.jpg">Senou Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20540" type="appears in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="4">2.68</rating>
<name>Iwashita Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4897" picture="67088.jpg">Andou Mabuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20541" type="appears in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="2">4.14</rating>
<name>Iinuma Chigusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3104" picture="157226.jpg">Akimoto Chikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20545" type="appears in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="2">2.61</rating>
<name>Atou Saizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3384" picture="24411.jpg">Arikawa Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27087" type="appears in" update="2011-01-17">
<name>Iinuma Seijirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63584.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27088" type="appears in" update="2011-01-17">
<name>Hirose Yuudai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35890" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">7.64</rating>
<name>Juiz?</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A woman who appears in episode 10 and sounds like Juiz.</description>
<picture>48417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36003" type="appears in" update="2011-08-28">
<name>Atou Ke Yon Shimai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>These four sisters are granddaughters of Atou Saizo. Their voices were sampled into Juiz voice, and they are also involved in the management of Selecao game.
They consist of:
Akane (アカネ) the first daughter. She has studied musical abroad at Broadway.
Fumie (フミエ) the second daughter. Former library staff member.
Yuuko (ユーコ) the third daughter. Former staff member in school where English is spoken. She is also the lady at the reception desk at ATO Harima Brain Science Institute.
Akiko (アキコ) the fourth daughter. Former announcer.
They are all voiced by http://anidb.net/cr471 [Tamagawa Sakiko].</description>
<picture>49598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36005" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-08-26">
<name>Selecao No.8</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Only shown at the end of the second film listening to Mr. Outside`s closing statement of the game.</description>
<picture>49601.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="110547" update="2018-08-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2010-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Who is Mr. Outside? Who will win his twisted game? How did Takizawa become a pawn in the mastermind’s hidden plan? The answers are revealed and the conspiracy unravels in Paradise Lost, the thrilling feature-length conclusion to Eden of the East.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="116603" update="2010-02-27">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117211" update="2010-04-14">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121409" update="2010-12-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
