<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6655" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-11-21</startdate>
<enddate>2009-11-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Macross F: Itsuwari no Utahime</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Macross Frontier the MOVIE ~The False Diva~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Macross Frontier: The Songstress of Lies</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Macross Frontier: The False Diva</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Macross Frontier Movie: The False Songstress</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">극장판 마크로스 F 허공가희 ~거짓의 가희~</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Macross Frontier: Itsuwari no Utahime</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 マクロスF 虚空歌姫~イツワリノウタヒメ~</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7959" type="Sequel">Gekijouban Macross F: Sayonara no Tsubasa</anime>
<anime id="5415" type="Alternative Setting">Macross Frontier</anime>
<anime id="8049" type="Other">Nyankuri: Nyan x 2 Music Clip</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5025" approval="8" total="17">Heroic Age</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="262593">Contray to what was believed, not a recap of the TV series but a completely alternative version with almost everything being newly animated. It even improves on the TV in several points such as pacing and character design, while the story is obviously way too condensed for a feature film. Still, a good watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="85705">Good to see, but honestly i prefer the serie`s plot</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="421198">Macross fan or not, this is a movie that you shouldnt let it pass. This piece of work shows how anime is far from beign dead, well at least the mecha genre ffs.

Deculture !!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="286166">Great music combine with HQ CG`s</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="467099">Macross F with major differences with the plot the animation is top notch the music is triple AAA and the plot is outstanding i honestly prefer this telling of the macross f story its just freaking awesome check this one out its one of the best movies you will see</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.macrossf.com/movie/</url>
<creators>
<name id="152" type="Original Work">Kawamori Shouji</name>
<name id="241" type="Music">Kanno Youko</name>
<name id="152" type="Direction">Kawamori Shouji</name>
<name id="3539" type="Character Design">Ebata Risa</name>
<name id="1126" type="Original Work">Studio Nue</name>
<name id="8023" type="Character Design">Takahashi Yuuichi</name>
<name id="3539" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ebata Risa</name>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="21883" type="Animation Work">8bit</name>
</creators>
<description>Half retelling of the original Frontier series, half new story.
Conspiracies arise within the Frontier government when http://anidb.net/ch30 [Sheryl Nome] arrives to the colonial fleet for her concert and is soon marked as a spy for Galaxy while childhood friends, http://anidb.net/ch2167 [Saotome Alto ]and http://anidb.net/ch2166 [Ranka Lee] both try to achieve their dreams as the battle between Frontier and the Vajra draws closer.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1189">7.78</permanent>
<temporary count="1194">7.79</temporary>
<review count="1">8.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221831.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10930</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5310</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4525</identifier>
<identifier>ccaufv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.macrossf.com/movie/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2753</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334380</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11784</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="505" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-08">
<name>giant</name>
</tag>
<tag id="520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>nopan</name>
<description>The character foregoes underwear.</description>
<picurl>162753.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2309" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>insecure</name>
<description>Not confident or assured; uncertain and anxious.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3459" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-20">
<name>space monsters</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3516" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>insects of doom</name>
<description>Concerns insects, be them biological, magical or robotic in nature, that are either the bane, or a major stepping stone in the way of the main character(s) of the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3758" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-28">
<name>concert</name>
<description>The main characters play one or more live music performances during the show. This mostly happens for anime with the main focus on music.</description>
<picurl>169133.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3798" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>giant insects</name>
<picurl>222266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3852" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>Bright slap</name>
<description>"You hit me! Not even my father ever hit me!" 
You are the commander of a spaceship, leader of a faction or a team and your best mecha pilot stops fighting and grows increasingly hysterical and angsty, while the enemy could strike you at any time. What are you going to do? 
You slap or punch him, preferably in the face, and back to his senses while delivering a heroic speech that would turn any wimp into a man of destiny.
Named after Bright Noa of Mobile Suit Gundam, a prominent user of this for-sure method.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3874" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>bridge bunnies</name>
<description>A term and English nickname describing the attractive girls who manage the various functions aboard a ship`s/starship`s bridge area. 
Although it originated in reference to characters from Macross, it does not exist among Japanese fans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4004" parentid="2638" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>organic mecha</name>
<description>An organic mecha is a mecha that has organic tissue in its composition. The most prominent historical example is http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion].</description>
<picurl>224892.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4149" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>non-blood-related siblings -- DO NOT USE -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be deleted. Please add char-char relations of the "is family of" type with the http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Content:Characters#is_family_of [appropriate relation comment] to the relevant characters and remove the tag from the corresponding anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5767" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Itano circus</name>
<description>The Itano circus is named after Itano Ichirou, a Japanese animator, and refers to a highly stylized and acrobatic method of depicting aerial combat and dogfights in many anime, particularly the Macross series, where it was utilised by Itano for the first time and was ground-breaking.
The Itano circus is characterized by detailed, fluid shading of the mecha, the close-range acrobatic moves the duelling fighters make in combat, as well as twisting contrails left by fighters and missiles. It is also commonly used in specific reference to an attack where a mecha or spaceship launches a large swarm of missiles with meticulously animated spiralling smoke trails and erratic trajectories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30" type="main character in" update="2016-07-18">
<rating votes="327">8.18</rating>
<name>Sheryl Nome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as the "Galactic Fairy", she is a pop idol from Macross Galaxy fleet who had constantly topped music charts leading people to say that it was impossible not to hear her songs if you lived in this galaxy. As such, her popularity was soaring just as high in the Galaxy`s sister fleet, Macross Frontier. Due to her beauty and singing talent, she is a very proud and self-assured person. Sheryl recognizes the singing talent of Ranka Lee and often offers to help her `behind the scenes` to realise her dream of singing. Sheryl`s first encounter with Alto Saotome was when he served as a backup `performer` at her first concert in Frontier. Eventually, she also develops a crush on him.</description>
<picture>66116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4266" picture="26548.jpg">May`n</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2166" type="main character in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="208">7.23</rating>
<name>Ranka Lee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranka Lee is a petite, lively and cheerful (although naive) teenage girl with green hair.
She suffered from amnesia as a result from witnessing the destruction of the 117th Long Distance Research Fleet in which her biological family perished. She is one-quarter Zentradi, which gives her the ability to have her hair move on its own according to her feelings as well as an above-average resistance to the vacuum of space.
As the adopted younger sister of S.M.S. ace Ozma Lee, she initially attends an all-girl`s high school at the urging of her brother while working part-time at the Chinese restaurant "Nyan-Nyan". She later transfers to the Mihoshi Academy to facilitate her singing career after being discovered at the Miss Macross contest. Later she played a role of http://anidb.net/ch14112 [Mao Nome] in the Bird Human movie.
Ranka started off as a huge fan of Sheryl Nome as she loved singing since her childhood and had dreamt of becoming a singer. She develops a crush on Alto Saotome, especially after being rescued by him when the Vajra first attacked the Macross Frontier fleet.</description>
<picture>66114.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="423" picture="37799.jpg">Nakajima Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2167" type="main character in" update="2011-02-20">
<rating votes="112">4.02</rating>
<name>Saotome Alto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school student in the Mihoshi Academy Pilot Training course. As a result of his fine features and long hair he is often mistaken for a girl at first glance, even receiving the nickname `Hime` (Princess). His appearance was revealed to have been inherited from his late mother, Miyo. Despite this, he is otherwise a rather normal, though somewhat aloof and standoffish, boy. Born into a well-known Kabuki family, his persistent yearning for the skies has made for a thorny relationship with his father. Alto is now undertaking pilot courses at Mihoshi Academy.</description>
<picture>66115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2168" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-20">
<rating votes="41">5.33</rating>
<name>Mikhail Blanc</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alto`s classmate and friendly rival. He is an excellent marksman, and his motto is to always acquire his targets, be it an enemy or a woman—maintaining his reputation as a considerable ladies` man. He is the originator of Alto`s nickname, "Alto Hime" (Princess Alto). Aside from leading a normal school life, he is also the 2nd Lieutenant of the S.M.S. Skull Squadron and pilots a blue VF-25G (gunner/sniper version). He initially expresses doubt over Alto joining the Skull Squadron, but later accepts him.</description>
<picture>66090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2169" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-20">
<rating votes="30">1.69</rating>
<name>Luca Angelloni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alto and Michael`s junior classmate. He is often frustrated with his seniors, who like to give him a hard time. He is a genius with computers and military electronics. As with Michael, he is a member of the S.M.S. Skull Squadron. He pilots a green RVF-25 (reconnaissance version). His fighter is custodied by three pet Ghost Drones (which he calls Shimon, Johanne and Petero, or Simon, John and Peter) that respond to his verbal commands. His penchant for naming objects with Biblical names extends to his EX-Gear, which he calls "Samson". He is also the heir to the L.A.I. corporation, which means he has access to exotic, prototype technologies and is somewhat involved in Grace and Leon`s plans.</description>
<picture>66117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2171" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="35">8.39</rating>
<name>Ozma Lee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The top ace in the S.M.S. private military company and leader of Skull Squadron, he holds the rank of Major and is an experienced former N.U.N.S. pilot. He is an avid fan of Fire Bomber and often plays their songs in his car or while at home, and also names Skull Squadron`s battle formations after their songs (i.e., "Planet Dance", "Totsugeki Love Heart"). Although laid-back and careless on the outside, he knows when to be serious, and believes that the real duty of a soldier is to care for his subordinates and civilians. He is somewhat overprotective of his sister Ranka Lee, and lies to her about his work so she will not worry about him, telling her he has a desk job in a company`s personnel department.</description>
<picture>17280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2172" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="9">4.41</rating>
<name>Canaria Berstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First lieutenant in the S.M.S. and the pilot of Skull Team`s VB-6 König Monster variable bomber. Although she rarely speaks, when she does her words have great weight and she often advises Ozma. Canaria also serves as a military medic for S.M.S. She is married and has a young son named Eddie.</description>
<picture>17295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2173" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-20">
<rating votes="106">8.67</rating>
<name>Klan Klan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blue-haired Zentradi female (Meltrandi) who is in command of the all-female S.M.S. Pixie Squadron, with the rank of captain. As a childhood friend of Michael Blanc, she actually harbours a crush on him that does not seem to be reciprocated until too late. She is also a top ace Queadluun-Reapower-armour pilot. Due to a certain genetic anomaly, she appears her age as a fully-developed Meltrandi while macronised, but becomes physically a juvenile in her micronised form. This makes her the perfect target for Michael`s mockery.</description>
<picture>66118.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2176" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="19">8.77</rating>
<name>Jeffrey Wilder</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain of SMS Macross Quarter. A colonel in the S.M.S. ranks, he used to be a pilot in an U.N. Forces aircraft carrier early on his career. A seasoned veteran, he has a beard and a horizontal scar across his face as proof of his previous combat experience. Though a very polite officer, he can become highly mischievous when the situation requires it. It is mentioned that he lost his wife some time ago.</description>
<picture>17285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2177" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="36">5.70</rating>
<name>Bobby Margot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Helmsman of the S.M.S. mothership, SMS Macross Quarter. Somewhat stern in appearance, he is "just like a girl inside", as he often says. He was a hair stylist, as well as a make-up artist, somewhere in the past. He is well-liked by female crew members for his good understanding of others. He is an open homosexual and has not-so subtle feelings for Ozma, though he claims to be "Way beyond the point in life where [he] needs [his] love to be reciprocated."</description>
<picture>17287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2178" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="10">5.24</rating>
<name>Monica Lange</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the bridge operators of SMS Macross Quarter. In charge of the main search radar and chief of the main operator group, she has a serious leader personality type.</description>
<picture>17289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2179" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="18">5.52</rating>
<name>Mina Roshan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the bridge operators of SMS Macross Quarter. Currently in charge of internal warship status management. Despite having an IQ of 180, she sometimes has trouble adjusting to the pace of her fellow teammates.</description>
<picture>17291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2180" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="13">6.12</rating>
<name>Ram Hoa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the bridge operators of SMS Macross Quarter. In charge of communication and main weapons control. A person of not too many words that tends to classify everything that she comes into contact on a regular basis.</description>
<picture>17293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="425" picture="17296.jpg">Fukuhara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2181" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="30">5.23</rating>
<name>Catherine Glass</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A N.U.N.S. General Staff second lieutenant attached to the Macross Frontier, she is also the President`s daughter. Both beautiful and intelligent, Catherine is revealed to be a former Miss Macross winner, and later went on to serve on the judging panel in the 2059 contest. After having graduating from university with honors, she joined NUNS and is being fast-tracked into the elite. Though a very competent officer, she sometimes lacks flexibility. She had a relationship with Leon Mishima without her father`s knowledge and was formerly in a relationship with Ozma Lee before that. She became part of the SMS Macross Quarter crew during a mission to rescue the Macross Galaxy fleet from the Vajra. Like Ozma, she had grown suspicious of Leon`s intentions and confronted him only to be arrested by his men.</description>
<picture>17281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2182" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="7">3.01</rating>
<name>Howard Glass</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fourth elected president of the New United Nations Government and also the administrative director of the Macross Frontier fleet. His administration was responsible for the creation of the Frontier colony fleet. As president, he shoulders all political decisions to ensure the security and well-being of his citizens. He is also Cathy`s father.</description>
<picture>17298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2183" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="13">1.46</rating>
<name>Leon Mishima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The President`s aide and Chief of Staff. An ever calm and composed man, he is President Glass` close associate. He is a constant source of all political trends and winds, and is in a relationship with Cathy Glass. He knows far more about the Vajra than it seems and apparently is working in secret with Grace O`Connor.</description>
<picture>17299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2184" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="31">1.92</rating>
<name>Grace O`Connor</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The series` main antagonist, Grace first appears as Sheryl`s manager from Galaxy Fleet and as a person with a gentle and calm attitude. She seemed to often upset her employer despite having considerable abilities. Grace also had cybernetic implants that allowed her to directly interface with any computer terminal. She also appeared to be secretly working with Brera Sterne as his superior.</description>
<picture>17300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2185" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="25">5.70</rating>
<name>Brera Sterne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the mysterious pilot of the crimson VF-27 variable fighter that Alto Saotome encounters for the first time inside a Vajra carrier. Brera seems to know how to play the first part of Ranka`s song "Aimo" using his harmonica, claiming that the song is the only fragment of his past he still has after memory modification. After saving Ranka from a wild beast attack, the injuries Brera sustained revealed that he is also a cyborg. He harbours a great deal of concern for Ranka`s well-being, but he doesn`t exactly know why.</description>
<picture>17301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2186" type="appears in" update="2009-01-11">
<rating votes="8">3.54</rating>
<name>Elmo Kridanik</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Zentradi president manager of the small talent agency "Vector Productions". He heard Ranka`s singing by chance and scouted her, becoming her manager.</description>
<picture>17302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14112" type="appears in" update="2012-11-10">
<rating votes="26">6.23</rating>
<name>Mao Nome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Mayan people who live in an island on the South Pacific, Mao initially knows nothing but her home, like her older sister http://anidb.net/ch14111 [Sara]. Mao`s fascination with the technology that the outsiders bring masks her deep mystical link to the island`s mysterious alien ruins, a link she shares with her sister. The sudden arrival of http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Kudou Shin] to the island in 2008 sparks dreams of freedom in eleven year old Mao, who then yearns for a life in the cities beyond the island. Unlike her older sister http://anidb.net/ch14111 [Sara], she is carefree and spritelike. She becomes infatuated with http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Shin], impressed by his skill in manipulating and repairing the island`s scarce machinery.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>41483.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41949" type="appears in" update="2012-03-02">
<name>Henry Gilliam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Henry Gilliam is a tough pilot in the S.M.S. Skull Team and Ozma Lee`s second in command. He lost his life in Episode 01 while defending the Macross Frontier fleet in the first Vajra attack of 2059. His VF-25 Messiah variable fighter is now piloted by Alto.</description>
<picture>82713.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41958" type="appears in" update="2012-03-03">
<name>Saotome Ranzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saotome Ranzou is Alto`s father and the 18th souke of the Saotome family. A very strict man, he has trained his son harshly in the art of kabuki since youth which has resulted in their current estranged relationship. However, after a close brush with death, Ranzou is willing to make amends with Alto and officially name him successor to the Saotome family.</description>
<picture>82715.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42040" type="appears in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="2">7.67</rating>
<name>Ai-kun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A little something that seems to chase after Ranka.</description>
<picture>82806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10854" picture="38961.jpg">Sasaki Hinako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42138" type="appears in" update="2012-03-08">
<rating votes="3">6.09</rating>
<name>Ranshe Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranshe Mei is Ranka`s mother.</description>
<picture>83101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42232" type="appears in" update="2012-03-10">
<name>Tokugawa Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83271.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42809" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>VF-25</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84457.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42810" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>VF-25</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84458.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42811" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>VF-171</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84459.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42812" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>VF-25G</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84460.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42813" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>VF-25G</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84461.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42814" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>VF-25S</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84462.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42815" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>VF-25S</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84463.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42816" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>RVF-25</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84464.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42817" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>RVF-25</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84465.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42818" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>VF-27</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84466.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42819" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>VB-6 Koenig Monster</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84467.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42820" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>Macross Quarter</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>84468.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42821" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>Macross Frontier</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>84469.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42822" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>Queadluun-Rher</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84470.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42823" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>Queadluun-Rher</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>84471.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42824" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>Ghost</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>84472.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42825" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>Vajra</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84473.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42827" type="appears in" update="2012-03-23">
<name>S.M.S</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="110763" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">News Flash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110764" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">予告編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokokuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110765" update="2009-10-18">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場版告知CM (30秒)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Movie notice CM (30 seconds)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Grkijouban Kokuchi CM (30 Byou)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117003" update="2015-10-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>120</length>
<airdate>2009-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125414" update="2010-11-23">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Sheryl Warning</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125415" update="2010-11-23">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ranka Warning</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125416" update="2010-11-23">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Theater Version PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125417" update="2015-10-16">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Sheryl CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125418" update="2010-11-23">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ranka CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125419" update="2010-11-23">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>35</length>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Toro Station Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125420" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Live Speech &amp; Promotion</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
