<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="667" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-04-25</startdate>
<enddate>2001-07-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">El</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">[él]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Elle</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">엘</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">エル</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">EL</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Él</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">X Humanus</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<creators>
<name id="725" type="Unknown Relation">Green Bunny</name>
<name id="878" type="Original Work">Elf</name>
<name id="1505" type="Direction">Kanazawa Katsuma</name>
<name id="12981" type="Character Design">Kawai Masaki</name>
<name id="12029" type="Character Design">Segami Yukio</name>
</creators>
<description>In 2030, nuclear war broke out over the environmental pollution issue. Many people lost their lives due to radioactivity. The people, who survived the barren Earth, started the "Megaro Earth Project" to save human existence. In a last hope for survival against nuclear war, a city was built in a dome in order to save civilization. Gimmick, a mysterious man who leads a secret organization called "Black Widow", is planning to obstruct the implementation of the "Megaro Earth Project". In order to oppose Gimmick`s organization, members of the counter terrorism group, led by the lady sniper "EL", were formed. Occasionally, EL helps the beautiful girl Parsley who was once attacked by the Black Widows. Parsley tries to take advantage of EL after getting drunk at "Club 1991". Meanwhile, Natsuki is being sexually tortured for information by the Sniper Control Office.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="417">3.36</permanent>
<temporary count="429">5.66</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>81589.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2122</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4357</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>829</identifier>
<identifier>seesqi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>El_(hentai)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ELLE_(アダルトゲーム)#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.80.E3.83.AB.E3.83.88.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>233918</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2293</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2225" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>whipping</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2708" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>uncensored version available</name>
<description>There`s an uncensored version available of the porn anime this tag is added to, which in most cases means, that there was a region 1 DVD (R1 DVD = North America) release.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2711" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>urination</name>
<description>Urination, also known as micturition, voiding, peeing, weeing, pissing, and more rarely, emiction, is the ejection of urine from the urinary bladder through the urethra to the outside of the body. In healthy humans the process of urination is under voluntary control. In infants, some elderly individuals, and those with neurological injury or extreme psychological problems, urination may occur as an involuntary reflex. In other animals, in addition to expelling waste material, urination can mark territory or express submissiveness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2719" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-19">
<name>gang bang</name>
<description>A situation in which one person has sexual intercourse and performs other sex acts with a number of people, either in turn or at the same time.</description>
<picurl>181529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2905" parentid="2729" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-14">
<name>erotic torture</name>
<description>Erotic torture involves deliberately using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure. Examples include, among others, hot wax on skin, nipple clamps, electricity, extreme verbal and derogatory abuse, forced public exhibition, etc.
This is distinct from the common, non-erotic http://anidb.net/t6730 [torture], which is generally for the purpose of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or to apply coercion to compel action from the victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4318" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-28">
<name>plot with porn</name>
<description>Any adult-rated work where porn is not the only point to it. As in, it has a plot that is not merely an excuse for having sex on screen. Even better if the sex is actually plausibly worked into said plot or used for characterization.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="53242" type="main character in" update="2013-02-25">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Miles El</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tough and beautiful, El Miles is a member of the Sniper Control Board, charged with protecting a city of nuclear war survivors against the "Black Widows." Unlike many of her male coworkers, who often engage in sexually torturing female suspects, El is all business. She does, however, chafe at the constant survelence that goes on in the city; she likes her privacy.
She is very good at her business, but sometimes she has a problem staying conscienous during a takedown - and always at a certain location. It was at this particular locale were she saved the singer Parsley from being raped by "Black Widows."
But something else is bothering El now - the spells that often have her landing in the hospital are happening more frequently, friends and coworkers that she has known for years are suddenly becoming "Black Widows"... and Parsley is openly trying to seduce her! What is going on? Is there something else that is affecting her future... or is her world a huge illusion?
(source: Absolute Anime)</description>
<picture>132783.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64001" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Carlos Rivera</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154292.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64002" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Chris Ronstadt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154286.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64003" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-08">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Parsley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152905.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64004" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Bicks Lightfoot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154290.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64005" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Phyllis Lloyd</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154293.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64006" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Reinhart Buckmaster</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154288.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64007" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Linda Walker</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154294.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64008" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Lucca Spahn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154291.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64009" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Rob Makonai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154289.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64010" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Loris Kapirosch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154295.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64011" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Mita Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154287.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64012" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="2">9.02</rating>
<name>Minami Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154284.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64013" type="appears in" update="2014-02-09">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Kyokuchou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="64014" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Shimano Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154285.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="7236" update="2007-09-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2001-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7237" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2001-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
