<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6685" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2009-12-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kampfer</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kaempfer</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Kämpfer</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Kaempfer</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Кемпфер</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">캠퍼</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Kovotoja</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">Luptătoarele</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kenpufaa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kenpufer</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">肯普法</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">けんぷファー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kampfer</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ผู้พิทักษ์สลับขั้ว</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8163" type="Sequel">Kampfer: Fur die Liebe</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10323" approval="13" total="21">Ore, Twintail ni Narimasu.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="553946">If you like animes with a twist on them, then be my guest and go for it, you might like this anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="29122">Very nice anime with alot of laughing moments and references, but also weird story ending and worthless last episode. When I say "weird" I mean story turns out in somehow predictable, yet unpleasing manner with some sort of open ending (2nd season hint?). Still worth watching, though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="427466">Nice Anime.
Waiting for Season 2.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="183638">its funny and interesting 
watch it :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="366535">The anime is very funny and had a good story, but the last episode was unnecessary.....</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="158613">This anime may sound crap or gender bender but its not... it`s probaly one of the best animes out this winter, its funny and well check it out.....</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/kenpu/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1055" type="Animation Work">Nomad</name>
<name id="6028" type="Character Design">Fujita Mariko</name>
<name id="3724" type="Series Composition">Fudeyasu Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="3632" type="Original Work">Tsukiji Toshihiko</name>
<name id="5483" type="Direction">Kuroda Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
<name id="7781" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakamura Naoto</name>
<name id="6028" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujita Mariko</name>
<name id="3644" type="Chief Animation Direction">Koga Makoto</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr3632 [Tsukiji Toshihiko]`s light novel series Kämpfer.
http://anidb.net/ch11056 [Senou Natsuru] is your normal, everyday high school student. However, one morning he wakes up and finds himself turned into a http://anidb.net/ch11057 [beautiful girl]. A stuffed tiger http://anidb.net/ch13734 [Harakiri Tora] tells him then, that he has been chosen to be a Kämpfer (German for "fighter"), who has to fight other Kämpfer with either guns, swords or magic.
Natsuru has been granted great strength and fighting abilities on top of the power to use magic, but finds out that only girls can be a Kämpfer. Left without a choice, he is forced to turn into a girl again and again to fight other Kämpfer — to survive.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3474">3.41</permanent>
<temporary count="3515">6.22</temporary>
<review count="3">4.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>52826.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10861</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7782</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6205</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4551</identifier>
<identifier>lujhjr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/kenpu/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kämpfer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>けんぷファー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1717</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334951</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11835</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="235" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-05">
<name>waitress</name>
<description>A female attendant who serves customers in a restaurant, café, or similar.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>163704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="920" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-22">
<name>perverted</name>
<description>Is a concept describing those types of human behavior that are excessive or deviated from what is considered to be orthodox or normal.</description>
<picurl>245189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2467" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-22">
<name>sword</name>
<description>A sword is a long, edged piece of metal, used as a cutting, thrusting, and clubbing weapon in many civilizations throughout the world. Before firearms became commonplace, and fast enough to render other weapons pointless in the battlefield, they were the main kind of weapon for war and duels alike. A sword fundamentally consists of a blade and a hilt, typically with one or two edges for striking and cutting, and a point for thrusting. That aside, however, they may come in all sorts of designs: the medieval European swords used to be big, heavy weapons that did not actually cut but instead broke the enemy`s bones under their armor; conversely, the Chinese jian sword (called "ken" in Japanese) attempted to exploit the armor`s joints and perforate the enemy`s flesh in those places, but was useless against the armor itself, and did not take the strikes, preferring to redirect them, to this day being considered a highly "circular" weapon and associated to taijiquan; on the other hand, the Japanese katana was a balanced all-purposes weapon that could be used even in an axe-like way, but which a master swordsman could use in many other, more elaborate manners.</description>
<picurl>127113.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2578" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-12">
<name>vulgar</name>
<description>Talking (and acting) in a way that is considered uncultivated, bawdy, common, coarse or unrefined, or "taboo" according to existing cultural standards. Includes boorish manners and obtrusive display of carnal "assets".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2780" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>indirect kiss</name>
<description>Comedy element: Especially in a school setting the character who has fallen for a fellow student, but has not yet confessed his/her love, will be desperate for any sign of "closeness".
The indirect kiss: Anything the adored person touches with his/her lips — e.g. a used glass of lemonade, some half-eaten food, a half-emptied can of soda — the love struck will want to touch with her/his own lips.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3121" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-05">
<name>twisted ending</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3197" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-19">
<name>guro</name>
<description>Ero guro or just guro, from the English "ero(ticism)" and "gro(tesque)", is a literary and artistic movement with a focus on eroticism, sexual corruption, and decadence that originated circa 1930 in Japan. While the name speaks of erotic and grotesque, that comes through the display of the malformed, the unnatural, and the horrific, and not necessarily through the pornographic, the bloody, or the gratuitous violence. While Western audiences often incorrectly use the term guro to mean http://anidb.net/t4096 [gore], the two concepts are unrelated and should not be confused.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3374" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>civil war</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3550" parentid="6021" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-05">
<name>sex change</name>
<description>Someone in this anime has his/her body changed to the opposite gender.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3818" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-21">
<name>kids in war</name>
<description>When minors participate in armed conflict.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4350" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>imperial stormtrooper marksmanship academy</name>
<description>When only the Bad Guys suffer from A-Team Firing. Also called The Principle of Evil Marksmanship. The good guys (the non-Red Shirt ones, at least - and sometimes even them, too) can stand in the middle of the firefight and never get hit, and can pick off any bad guy with even the most casually-aimed shot while the bad guys seem unable to hit the broad side of a barn.
This is a degree of Truth in Television, as by far most shots fired in firefights or combat are misses. Some sources report that in WWII, the average soldier needed to fire two hundred rounds for every hit scored on an enemy; numerous other examples are mentioned in the Real Life section of this page. So the fictional bad guys don`t actually suffer from unrealistic inaccuracy; rather, the heroes`s fictional performance would count as Improbable Aiming Skills in real life. Or they were instead ordered not to shoot the person. 
Source: TVTropes</description>
<picurl>162915.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4352" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-11">
<name>censored uncensored version</name>
<description>Even the DVD and Blu-ray releases do not let you see everything you were expecting to, and you will have to live with censorship in the show. That normally applies to fan service, but may also apply to gore and violence. A very common example is characters without nipples, as in http://anidb.net/a6083 [KissXSis]; in other cases, something such as steam or foam stays in the camera`s way, like in http://anidb.net/a6531 [Kanamemo]. In some shows, the censorship in the disk releases is even stronger than in the TV version, while others may use creative censorship as a replacement for the removed fan service or even as a joke.
This does not apply to censorship of what Japanese pornography laws still require to be censored.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4543" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-11-04">
<name>even the girls want her</name>
<description>A female character is presented as so uniquely spectacular that even some (or all) other female characters wouldn`t mind making her their (girl)friend-with-benefits.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5838" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-26">
<name>fire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5915" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>French kiss</name>
<description>A kiss in which the tongue enters the partner`s mouth.</description>
<picurl>238326.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5971" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>red ones go faster</name>
<description>Red things just seem to go faster. In fiction, make something red and you can almost guarantee it`ll move quicker, as if the colour itself reduces drag, lowers inertia and increases forward momentum. A visual shorthand for getting the point across that an object is zippy.
Truth in Television: Red apparently promotes adrenalin release and feelings of excitement or intensity, which can certainly give the appearance that a red object is moving faster, as well as possibly encourage the drivers of red vehicles to push the envelope more. Also, the Doppler Effect makes things red-shifted if they`re moving away from you at a high speed (read: significant fraction of the speed of light). Don`t expect there to be any evolutionary basis for this, however, as it`s unlikely any human would ever get to see it with the naked eye. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6328" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-01">
<name>biological weapons</name>
<description>Use of biological agents (bacteria, viruses, fungi, etc.) to inflict harm on humans and/or other targets.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11056" type="main character in" update="2009-10-17">
<rating votes="53">3.17</rating>
<name>Senou Natsuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The series` main protagonist. Second year student of Seitetsu Gakuin High School. He is chosen as a Blue Kämpfer by Moderator and setup as a Zauber type with power based on fire. In keeping with the rule that all Kämpfers are females, he turns into girl upon transformation. After a fight with Shizuku exposed his Kämpfer form to other students of the school, Shizuku arranged to have him enrolled in girl`s class to fulfill public curiosity in a way that diverts attentions away from Kämpfer battle. His Kämpfer form has subsequently been ranked among the Three Beauties of Seitetsu (there used to be only two) and, much to his own dismay, become subject of intense affections from Kaede Sakura (whom he has a crush on).</description>
<picture>32938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11057" type="main character in" update="2009-08-10">
<rating votes="141">7.52</rating>
<name>Senou Natsuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11058" type="main character in" update="2009-10-17">
<rating votes="107">6.32</rating>
<name>Mishima Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>School librarian and Natsuru`s friend, she is also a Blue Kämpfer like Natsuru. Normally very shy and soft-spoken, she becomes foul-mouthed, bitter, vindictive, and trigger-happy upon transforming into a Kämper. She explained most of the rules of being a Kämpfer when Natsuru`s own Messenger gave no such details. She is a Gewehr type Kämpfer who uses an automatic handgun and appears to be ambidextrous. She later begins to harbour feelings for Natsuru (normal form), eventually becoming jealous and easily irritable when he talks about another girl (most if not all of the time being Kaede) in front of her or when another girl takes an interest in him (whether that interest is romantic in nature or not).</description>
<picture>32941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11059" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-10">
<rating votes="94">7.95</rating>
<name>Mishima Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11060" type="main character in" update="2009-10-17">
<rating votes="206">9.05</rating>
<name>Sangou Shizuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>President of the Student Council and one of the Three Beauties of Seitetsu, she is a model student with perfect attendance record. In addition, however, she is also a Red Kämpfer fighting with the Schwert ability of wielding two chained daggers at will. She wants to expose Moderator`s intentions but has no problem fighting Blue Kämpfers until that goal was accomplished. After being spared following a defeat, she enters a truce with Natsuru and Akane and has since taken an interest in Natsuru despite being constantly treated with suspicion.</description>
<picture>32943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11061" type="main character in" update="2009-10-17">
<rating votes="77">4.29</rating>
<name>Kondou Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuru`s childhood friend who only recently reunited with him due to her father being an archaeologist who lives abroad. She appears to have feelings for Natsuru and is more than a bit bothered by the presence of a girl with the same name as his (who in reality is Natsuru in his Kämpfer form). When she was seeing Miss Seitetsu contest of the school festival, she caught a bouquet that Kaede tossed with a Messenger hidden in it, consequently being turned into a Schwert-type Red Kämpfer armed with a Japanese sword.</description>
<picture>32944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11062" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-11">
<rating votes="58">5.59</rating>
<name>Kondou Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11063" type="main character in" update="2010-12-22">
<rating votes="109">2.40</rating>
<name>Sakura Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizuku`s childhood friend and one of the Three Beauties of Seitetsu, she has many admirers, Natsuru being one of them. She has a large collection of stuffed Zoumotsu Animal dolls and likes to present them to her friends; those who receive the dolls, however, tend to end up becoming Kämpfers. She began to develop a crush on Kämpfer Natsuru after being saved from Kämpfer Akane at the beginning of the series, later coming under the mistaken impression that the normal Natsuru is her rival for Kämpfer Natsuru`s affection and consequently becoming somewhat hostile to him. Later in the series, it is revealed that she leads the white Kämpfer, who enforce the proxy war.</description>
<picture>32946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="423" picture="37799.jpg">Nakajima Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11064" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-24">
<rating votes="19">5.02</rating>
<name>Nishino Masumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the school`s News Club, she is always after the scoops and has a habit of exaggerating her findings.</description>
<picture>32947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4007" picture="25937.jpg">Mikami Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12084" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-09">
<rating votes="14">4.91</rating>
<name>Harakiri Tora</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Messenger for Natsuru in the form of a tiger which wears an eye-patch.</description>
<picture>36590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24" picture="16606.jpg">Nomura Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12085" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-09">
<rating votes="13">5.88</rating>
<name>Seppuku Kuro Usagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Messenger for Akane in the form of a rabbit which has bloodshot eyes. It speaks with a sarcastic tone although it is on good terms with Harakiri Tora.</description>
<picture>36591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12086" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-09">
<rating votes="14">4.38</rating>
<name>Kanden Yamaneko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Messenger for Shizuku in the shape of a wildcat bristling hairs.</description>
<picture>36592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12087" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-09">
<rating votes="10">3.96</rating>
<name>Chissoku Norainu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Messenger for Mikoto in the appearance of a strangled dog. It speaks with a subdued voice.</description>
<picture>36593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12208" type="appears in" update="2009-10-17">
<rating votes="6">2.38</rating>
<name>Higashida Mikihito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuru`s classmate who is the president of the bishoujo research club.</description>
<picture>36958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12341" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-16">
<rating votes="16">4.26</rating>
<name>Iinchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10081" picture="223564.jpg">Kobayashi Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12342" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-16">
<rating votes="18">5.77</rating>
<name>Fuku-iinchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12343" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-16">
<rating votes="14">2.61</rating>
<name>Kaikei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10080" picture="235712.jpg">Aranami Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12349" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-17">
<rating votes="106">8.88</rating>
<name>Sangou Shizuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3634.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12974" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-22">
<rating votes="11">5.05</rating>
<name>Ueda Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Schwert user armed with a kusarigama.</description>
<picture>39146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13309" type="appears in" update="2016-01-23">
<rating votes="7">6.14</rating>
<name>Nakao Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Schwert user armed with a sabre.</description>
<picture>181620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="218" picture="17036.jpg">Nakao Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13310" type="appears in" update="2010-12-23">
<rating votes="9">5.43</rating>
<name>Yamakawa Ryouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gewehr user armed with a submachine gun resembles Uzi.</description>
<picture>61279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1875" picture="151654.jpg">Yamakawa Kotomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13311" type="appears in" update="2009-11-29">
<rating votes="9">5.68</rating>
<name>Minagawa Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zauber user. She attacks by launching energy bolts against her enemies.</description>
<picture>39429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13697" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="6">4.25</rating>
<name>Hiaburi Lion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The oldest Messenger, its existence said to pre-date the Zoumotsu Animal toyline. The novel version of it does not have its guts hanging out of its body like the Zoumotsu Animals after it, but the anime version does. It has the same shape as a character which Kaede imagined before, with a voice similar to that of a voice actor who performs voice-overs for foreign movie stars. Kaede got it by mere chance though it is very scarce.</description>
<picture>40907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13698" type="appears in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="2">4.06</rating>
<name>Hikinige Kaba</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>It was the Messenger for Tamiko Shinomiya. It has turned back to a plain doll since she disappeared. Kaede presented another Hit-and-run Hippopotamus to Midori Kuzuhara.</description>
<picture>73559.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13699" type="appears in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="4">4.67</rating>
<name>Shinomiya Tamiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zauber-type Red Kämpfer whom Shizuku adored. She was shot dead in Shizuku`s presence by a Blue Kämpfer whom she defeated and let go off.</description>
<picture>73558.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13730" type="appears in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="4">6.34</rating>
<name>Senou Natsuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harakiri Tora turns into a Senou Natsuru with tiger ears and tail.</description>
<picture>73556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24" picture="16606.jpg">Nomura Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13731" type="appears in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="6">5.69</rating>
<name>Mishima Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seppuku Kuro Usagi turns into a Mishima Akane with bunny ears and tail.</description>
<picture>73554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13732" type="appears in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="6">6.77</rating>
<name>Sangou Shizuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanden Yamaneko turns into a Sangou Shizuku with cat ears and tail.</description>
<picture>73555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13733" type="appears in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="4">5.45</rating>
<name>Kondou Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chissoku Norainu turns into a Kondou Mikoto with dog ears and tail.</description>
<picture>73553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13734" type="appears in" update="2009-12-19">
<rating votes="3">2.75</rating>
<name>Harakiri Tora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Senou Natsuru switched her body with Harakiri Tora due to unknown reasons.</description>
<picture>36590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13735" type="appears in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="2">4.06</rating>
<name>Seppuku Kuro Usagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mishima Akane switched her body with Seppuku Kuro Usagi due to unknown reasons.</description>
<picture>36591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13736" type="appears in" update="2009-12-19">
<rating votes="3">4.70</rating>
<name>Kanden Yamaneko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sangou Shizuku switched her body with Kanden Yamaneko due to unknown reasons.</description>
<picture>36592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13737" type="appears in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="3">2.33</rating>
<name>Chissoku Norainu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kondou Mikoto switched her body with Chissoku Norainu due to unknown reasons.</description>
<picture>36593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="108382" update="2010-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="17">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Schicksal ~選ばれし者~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Schicksal: The Chosen Ones</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Schicksal: Erabareshi Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108784" update="2012-06-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109018" update="2009-12-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Glühen ~死闘の開幕~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Glowing: The Death Match Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gluehen: Shitou no Kaimaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109115" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109116" update="2010-09-04">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109212" update="2009-10-31">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Lilie ~秘密の花園~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lily: The Secret Garden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lilie: Himitsu no Hanazono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110709" update="2009-12-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Kriegserklärung ~戦う乙女たち~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Declaration of War: The Battling Maidens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kriegserklaerung: Tatakau Otome-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110821" update="2009-12-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Komödie ~ファーストキス~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Comedy: First Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komoedie: First Kiss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111046" update="2009-10-31">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Heimkehr ~敵か味方か~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homecoming: Friend or Foe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heimkehr: Teki ka Mikata ka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111234" update="2009-11-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Einladen ~招かれざる客たち~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invite: The Uninvited Guests</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Einladen: Manekarezaru Kyaku-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111405" update="2009-11-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Liebste ~初めてのデート~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sweetheart: First Date</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Liebste: Hajimete no Date</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111571" update="2009-11-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Hochsommer ~恋の熱帯低気圧~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mid-Summer: Tropical Depression of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hochsommer: Koi no Nettai Teikiatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111706" update="2009-11-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Falle ~ひと夏の経験~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trap: A Summer Experience</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Falle: Hitonatsu no Keiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111846" update="2009-12-29">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Wählen ~歓喜の歌~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Election: The Song of Joy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waehlen: Kanki no Uta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111853" update="2009-12-29">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="21">1.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Weihnachten ~臓物たちの奇跡~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas: The Miracle of the Entrails</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Weihnachten: Zoumotsu-tachi no Kiseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113020" update="2012-08-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2009-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぞうもつ奇想天外!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Entrails Fantastic Idea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zoumotsu Kisoutengai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119001" update="2012-06-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121743" update="2011-06-16">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変身シーン集 (雫ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shizuku Transformation Scene</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henshin Scene Shuu (Shizuku Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121744" update="2011-06-16">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変身シーン集 (紅音ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akane Transformation Scene</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henshin Scene Shuu (Akane Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121745" update="2011-06-16">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変身シーン集 (水琴ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mikoto Transformation Scene</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henshin Scene Shuu (Mikoto Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121746" update="2011-06-16">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変身シーン集 (ナツルver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Natsuru Transformation Scene</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henshin Scene Shuu (Natsuru Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121747" update="2011-06-16">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三郷雫 禁断のシャワールーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shizuku Shower Scene</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sangou Shizuku Kindan no Shower Room</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121748" update="2011-06-16">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナツル&amp;紅音 秘密の更衣室 妄想バージョン その1/その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Natsuru &amp; Akane Secret Changing Room Delusion Version</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsuru &amp; Akane Himitsu no Kouishitsu Mousou Version Sono 1/Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121749" update="2011-06-16">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三郷雫生徒会長を気持ち良くしてあげました (別カメラバージョン)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shizuku`s Groping</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sangou Shizuku Seitokaichou o Kimochi Yokushite Agemashita (Betsu Camera Version)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
