<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="67" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>1994-08-25</startdate>
<enddate>1995-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Macross Plus</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Макрос плюс</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">MP</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マクロスプラス</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Macross Plus</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Макросс Плюс</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Macross Plus</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Macross Plus</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Macross Plus</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Macross Plus</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="442" type="Sequel">Macross 7</anime>
<anime id="77" type="Prequel">Choujikuu Yousai Macross</anime>
<anime id="3392" type="Alternative Setting">Macross Plus Movie Edition</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="89596">Way... i`m not macross fan but this is must see for all !!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.macross.co.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="152" type="Original Work">Kawamori Shouji</name>
<name id="129" type="Direction">Watanabe Shin`ichirou</name>
<name id="152" type="Chief Direction">Kawamori Shouji</name>
<name id="241" type="Music">Kanno Youko</name>
<name id="789" type="Work">Triangle Staff</name>
<name id="1126" type="Original Work">Studio Nue</name>
</creators>
<description>In 2040 AD on the colonial planet Eden, the Ministry of Defence is testing and developing a transforming super-stealth aircraft, a new advanced weapon to counter alien attacks. http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu Dyson] is an extrovert jet fighter maverick assigned as a new test pilot on project Super Nova. Competition heats up when he discovers that his old rival http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld Bowman] is the test pilot for the competing project. The arrival of http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung Fang Lone], a mutual ex-girlfriend, adds more tension to the conflict.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2255">6.88</permanent>
<temporary count="2263">7.58</temporary>
<review count="3">8.27</review>
</ratings>
<picture>152813.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>501</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>474</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>252</identifier>
<identifier>xlwruk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.macross.co.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Macross_Plus</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マクロスプラス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88321</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1692</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5046</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3758" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-28">
<name>concert</name>
<description>The main characters play one or more live music performances during the show. This mostly happens for anime with the main focus on music.</description>
<picurl>169133.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4538" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>long episodes</name>
<description>Long episodes are regular episodes that are much longer than the standard 25-30 minutes, usually 45-60 minutes. 
Not to be used if a show has occasional 45-60 minute specials. Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5767" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Itano circus</name>
<description>The Itano circus is named after Itano Ichirou, a Japanese animator, and refers to a highly stylized and acrobatic method of depicting aerial combat and dogfights in many anime, particularly the Macross series, where it was utilised by Itano for the first time and was ground-breaking.
The Itano circus is characterized by detailed, fluid shading of the mecha, the close-range acrobatic moves the duelling fighters make in combat, as well as twisting contrails left by fighters and missiles. It is also commonly used in specific reference to an attack where a mecha or spaceship launches a large swarm of missiles with meticulously animated spiralling smoke trails and erratic trajectories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5868" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-14">
<name>rogue artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence devices may at times act outside their intended parameters. While this normally doesn`t mean much in reality aside from forceful shutdowns and loss of productivity, in fiction this may go as far as turning against their own human creators/masters, and, in extreme cases, even exterminating them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="21733" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<rating votes="9">8.06</rating>
<name>SDF-1 Macross</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>For thousands of millennia, an ancient war raged across the Milky Way Galaxy unbeknownst to the human race. In July 1999, that war came to humanity`s doorstep when a super-light-velocity spaceship crash-landed on Earth. The United Nations commences an investigation of the crash site located on South Ataria Island in the North Pacific Ocean. The spacecraft is given the code name Alien StarShip-1 (ASS-1) and investigations in the months following the crash uncover startling discoveries. Giant aliens, some five times the size of a human, crewed the craft which is revealed to be a warship; a Gun Destroyer from a faction called the Supervision Army. Most important of any discovery found in the alien spacecraft is the advanced technology contained within it. Given the name "OverTechnology," the United Nations Government (U.N.G) coordinates research quickly to understand it.
In 2001, several countries including Japan, United States, Russia, Germany, Britain, and France collaborate to establish an alien technology research institute called OTEC. Less than a year later, the OTEC commences a project to restore and reconstruct the ASS-1 to be commissioned as a capital ship for the newly formed United Nations Government. From February 2001 forward, the spacecraft is designated as the SDF-1; Super-Dimension-Fortress-1. Incredible advances are made from the research including the thermonuclear reaction system used to power the craft, the gravity control system, the space fold system for traveling faster-than-light and the super-dimension-energy cannons, the main weapon of the SDF-1. These technologies are adapted quickly and soon OverTechnology is being utilized in dozens of industries, notably super-small-scale thermonuclear reactors and the development of thermonuclear reaction bombs. Despite these unprecedented leaps of progress, many problems arise and threaten to undermine the launch of the SDF-1.
Originally set to launch in 2006, civil unrest abroad and the outbreak of the Anti-Unification Wars slows the SDF-1 restoration project. Eventually, the "UN Wars" cease on January 20th 2007 and the SDF-1 is rescheduled for launch in February 2009. It is the day of the launching ceremony that the opposing faction of the ancient war tracks the residual energies left by the ASS-1`s space fold and follow it to the Sol system. The newly christened SDF-1 Macross, armed with a heretofore undiscovered automated defense system, activates in response to the approaching enemy forces known as the Zentradi. The main cannon of the SDF-1 Macross fires from the surface of the Earth and destroys two Zentradi ships some 280,000 km out in space. The remaining Zentradi retaliate and intense fighting ensues. In an attempt to maneuver and regain the initiative, Captain http://anidb.net/ch10507 [Bruno J. Global] activates the space fold system to transport the SDF-1 Macross into Lunar orbit. Due to limited human understanding of the space fold system and improper instrumentation, the SDF-1 Macross folds far beyond the Moon, transporting the ship and much of the surrounding surface of South Ataria Island out past Pluto. This single engagement initiates the beginning of Space War I between the UN Spacy and the Zentradi.Over the length of more than a year during which Space War I is fought, the SDF-1 Macross travels from the outskirts of the Sol system back to Earth, fighting the forces of the Zentradi. The Zentradi are determined to capture the vessel, obsessed with the secrets of the ship`s obvious reconstruction and reaction weapons. This advantage allows the Macross to effectively use it`s formidable defenses, thwarting many attempts to be captured by the enemy. After Space War I ends on March 10th 2010, the Macross landing site is chosen as home for the reconstruction of Macross City. The Macross takes part in one more major engagement against rogue Zentradi Kamjin Kravshera`s forces during the Defensive Battle of Macross City in January 2012. Despite extensive damage following the battle, the Macross is repaired and undergoes a major refit. To this day, the Macross remains the home of the U.N. Military Command Center and is berthed in Macross City on Earth.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/macross.htm</description>
<picture>93969.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48619" type="main character in" update="2012-09-09">
<rating votes="11">2.42</rating>
<name>Isamu Alva Dyson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born on Earth, March 27, 2015, Isamu Dyson grew up with his two friends http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung] and http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] on the rural planet of Eden. A student of Della Musica High School, he shared a fascination for flying with http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld], and would often go chasing the planet`s indigenous giant birds just to watch them fly. Another thing he shared with http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] was his love for http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung]. When he and http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung] finally had a tender moment, http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] walked in on them and exploded with rage attacking his former friends. The trio broke up and both http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung] and Isamu leave planet Eden separately.Not long after, on September 1, 2034, Isamu realized his dream of flying by joining the U.N. Spacy as a fighter pilot. He showed his extraordinary skill again-and-again as he fought renegade Zentradi in his http://anidb.net/ch48620 [VF-11 Thunderbolt] variable fighter leading to an astronomical kill count. However his skill came with a penchant for showmanship, dare devilry, and an independent smart-mouth personality. Vices that did not endear him to his superiors, no matter how skilled he was. An incident during an asteroid skirmish finally convinced his superiors to get rid of him by assigning him to Project Super Nova as a test pilot, ironically something Isamu had desired for a long time.
The move transferred him January 5, 2040, to New Edwards Test Flight Center on his home planet of Eden. There he becomes Shinsei Industries` newest test pilot, flying their prototype the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19]. To his surprise he finds that his former friend http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] is the test pilot for the opposing team vying for the contract, and a bitter rivalry-fueled by old differences- arises between the two that gets transferred to the competition. A rivalry that soon comes to low blows. Things get further complicated when http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung] shows up in Eden as well as the producer for the galaxy sensation http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple]. Meanwhile, Isamu also develops what he perceives as a rivalry with the base commander, Col. Millard Johnson, who uses a gruff demeanor and feigned disdain for the hotheaded young pilot to push him to try and use his airframe to its utmost limits.
When Project Super Nova is cancelled due to the introduction of the unmanned X-9 "Ghost" drone, hot headed Isamu steals the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19], aided and abetted by its chief engineer Yang Neumann, and heads to Earth to disrupt the Ghost`s inauguration. There he finds that he was followed by http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] who was sent to bring him back and a dogfight breaks between them. During the fight, the two finally confront each other with their grievances and in the end manage to settle them and become friends again. The new alliance is tested when the crazed http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple] takes control of the Ghost and attacks them. http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] however convinces Isamu to leave and rescue the imprisoned http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung]. There he is faced by intense fire from the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] itself, also controlled by http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple]. Soon after, Isamu succumbs to http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon]`s hypnotizing powers and takes his fighter into a death plunge. But thanks to http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung]`s singing he breaks from http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon]`s hold and destroys her. Unfortunately http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] is killed during his battle with the Ghost in a kamikazee like attack destroying both himself and the drone.
In the movie version, Isamu is last seen standing with http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung] on the platform of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross], and she promptly sings "Voices", as he puts an arm around her shoulder, winning her at last. Isamu also made a brief cameo appearance in http://anidb.net/a7959 [Macross Frontier: The Wings of Goodbye] as a Member of S.M.S fighting against the Vajra.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>93772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48620" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>VF-11B Thunderbolt</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>In the early 2020`s, the U.N. Government found itself requiring a new type of variable fighter with a combat profile much different from that of the current VF-5000 fighter. In 2022, development began on the VF-11 Thunderbolt, a design descended directly from the original VF-1 Valkyrie (though the two Battroid mode silhouettes are similar, the structures vary greatly). After the VF-1, few variable fighter airframes were multi-environment and were limited operating either in the air or in space. The VF-11 Thunderbolt broke from the norm and was a legitimate multipurpose successor to the VF-1. The program proceded on schedule and the VF-11`s first flight was made in 2028. Early in the development process, then Captain Milia Jenius of the Eagle Nest Aerial Tactics Center became one of many vocal advocates for the inclusion of the forward canard wing on the VF-11, a design choice which caused heated debate. While the canard wing enhanced the VF-11`s maneuverability considerably in an atmosphere, the increased air resistance also limited the fighter`s maximum speed. Fortunately, Captain Jenius piloted the No. 2 VFX-11 prototype (fitted with a canard, unlike the No. 1 prototype) in an operation to rescue a U.N. chief advisor. The flight data collected during this operation convinced the U.N.G. to adopt the VF-11 with the canard wing implemented. In December 2030 mass production of the VF-11 began and the Thunderbolt officially replaced the http://anidb.net/ch49112 [VF-4 Lightning III] as the main variable fighter of the U.N. Spacy.
The VF-11 was deployed on long-distance immigration ships, colonized planets and deep outer space forces where it served well as a variable fighter with emphasis on speed, maneuverability and economy of design. The Thunderbolt excelled in all respects such as firepower, maneuverability and maintainability while showing high comprehensive performance for a general purpose machine both inside and outside of atmosphere. The http://anidb.net/ch49112 [VF-4 Lightning III] and the VF-5 emphasized deployment in outer space and the VF-5000 Star Mirage focused on atmospheric performance. By contrast, one of the factors which granted the VF-11 high-deployment status was the Thunderbolt`s multipurpose design and high level of comprehensive performance in any operational environment (similar to the superior flexibility of the VF-1 Valkyrie). Utilizing a 30 mm gun pod as it`s primary weapon, the VF-11`s had as much destructive power against modern enemy mecha in a much smaller caliber than the VF-1`s 55 mm cannon. The smaller shell size also granted the VF-11 a much greater ammunition payload and the gun pod design included extra magazines for reloading in battle. An emphasis on close-range combat capability in Battroid mode was also featured by way of an anti-mecha bayonet. In addition to the anti-aircraft pulse laser, the VF-11 included the first hard defense feature in the form of an anti-projectile shield for GERWALK and battroid modes that dramatically improved resilience. The success of the anti-projectile shield prompted implementation in future variable fighters. The success of the VF-11 also saw the development of a modern Super Part system (which gave the Thunderbolt missiles in space) and the APS-11 Protect Armor system for special operations.
The VF-11 Thunderbolt served with distinction for over a decade and operated as the main variable fighter of the U.N. Spacy all throughout the 2030`s. Eventually, the VF-11`s lack of missile weaponry and aging design prompted new priorities for the U.N.G. military. In 2040 the VF-11 was scheduled to be replaced pending the winning design of the Super Nova AVF project, a competition between the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] and http://anidb.net/ch48623 [YF-21] variable fighters in development since the mid-2030`s. In 2041 the formal decision was made to adopt VF-19 as the next generation of main variable fighters but while the VF-11 would be slowly replaced, the Thunderbolt continued operational deployment in many fleets well into the 2040s.Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossplus/vf-11b.htm</description>
<picture>94685.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48621" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<name>YF-19 Alpha One</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The YF-19 Prototype Advanced Variable Fighter (AVF) was designed and built in 2039 by Shinsei Industries as their entry into the Project Super Nova design contest being conducted by the UN Spacy. Project Super Nova`s main purpose was to develop a new variable fighter to replace the aging http://anidb.net/ch48620 [VF-11 Thunderbolt] as the main fighter for UN Spacy military forces. The YF-19 was one of two fighters selected for the final competition at the New Edwards Flight Center on planet Eden; the other design being the http://anidb.net/ch48623 [YF-21 AVF] developed by General Galaxy. The YF-19 was developed by Yan Newmann, the child genius of Shinsei Industries.
The YF-19 was plagued with problems and mishaps throughout the course of the contest. Due to difficulties in controlling such a powerful variable fighter, the prototype was damaged several times and several test pilots were killed during the early trials of the aircraft. Eventually http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Lt. Isamu Dyson], a talented but reckless UN Spacy pilot, was assigned to test the YF-19 and quickly proved himself to be a competent pilot for the prototype.However, during a mock duel between the YF-19 and http://anidb.net/ch48623 [YF-21], the YF-19 was damaged by a discharge from its own GU-15 gun pod, almost killinghttp://anidb.net/ch48619 [ Lt. Dyson] in the process. Shortly thereafter, Project Super Nova was halted under direct order of the UN Spacy after the development of the Ghost X-9 Unmanned Fighter in February 2040 was completed. Not satisfied with the cancellation of the project, http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Lt. Dyson] and Yan Newmann stole the YF-19 and its fold booster and made an unauthorized fold from Eden to Earth. The http://anidb.net/ch48623 [YF-21] prototype was ordered to pursue the YF-19, and the two prototypes engaged in combat again during the Macross 30th Anniversary Celebration on Earth. However, the grudge match between the two pilots was interrupted by the newly completed AI system for pop singer http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple] who took control of the entire computer system for Earth and attempted to enslave its entire population through holographic hypnosis. The two prototypes fought against http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon] and the Ghost X-9 prototype she controlled, and the YF-19 managed to break through the AI`s defenses and destroy her CPU aboard the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF Macross].
After the smoke from the incident had settled, the YF-19 was declared the winner of the Project Super Nova competition. Dubbed the VF-19 Excalibur, the new fighter has begun slowly replacing the http://anidb.net/ch48620 [VF-11 Thunderbolt] as the main tactical superiority fighter for the UN Spacy since 2040. However, it will be several years before the new design comes into service with all deep space forces and colony missions spread throughout the galaxy. Several variations of the new design have begun to appear already, including the VF-19 Kai "Fire Valkyrie" variant aboard the Macross 7, operating near the core of the galaxy. Most of these variants are one-of-a-kind special operations fighters and are not widely distributed.Source: http://gioco.net/macross/varitech/yf19.htm</description>
<picture>93775.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48622" type="main character in" update="2012-09-09">
<rating votes="3">8.30</rating>
<name>Guld Goa Bowman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Zentradi/human hybrid, Guld grew up with his two friends Myung and http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] on the rural planet of Eden. He shared a fascination for flying with http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu], and the two managed to build a man powered flying machine together. Another thing he shared with http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] was his love for Myung. One day Guld walked in on http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] and Myung sharing a tender moment. His Zentradi warlike tendencies explode with jealous rage and he attacks his two former friends. As a result, Guld knocks out http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] and attacks Myung. The trio broke up, Myung and http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] leaving Eden. Alone on Eden, Guld`s psyche managed to suppress the memories of his assault, convincing him that he was protecting Myung from http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu]`s unwanted advances.
Years later, he became an employee for General Galaxy, both as a designer of variable fighters and a test pilot. His pet project, the controversial mind controlled YF-21, became General Galaxy`s entry in the Project Super Nova competition. Much to his distaste his rival, the test pilot for Shinsei Industries` http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19], is none other than his old rival http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu]. The competition between the two, flamed by their old rivalries becomes a bitter one. Things get even more complicated when Myung shows up in Eden as well, now the producer for the popular AI singer Sharon Apple who is on tour. In an early test flight of the YF-21, Guld fantasizes about forcing Isamu`s http://anidb.net/ch48620 [VF-11 Thunderbolt] to crash (having been rescued from a certainly fatal crash by http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu]`s quick thinking himself moments earlier). The YF-21`s control system interprets this as a command and pushes down hard on Isamu`s fighter, forcing it to crash, which Isamu survives with only superficial injuries. Guld, determined to win, even manages to sabotage one of the tests in his favour by swapping live ammunition into http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu]`s gun pod, which he later uses to fire into the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] and nearly kills Isamu (he had been originally intending for the ammunition to be used by http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] against him, to make it look as though http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] had plotted to murder him). Just as Guld is starting to patch things up between him and Myung, she leaves for Earth to attend the anniversary of the end of the Space War. Meanwhile, Project Super Nova is cancelled when U.N. Spacy announce that they will go for the A.I. controlled X-9 Ghost. While Guld is mulling this, http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] steals the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] to stop the Ghost`s inauguration on Earth. Guld is then tasked to bring him back using the YF-21. He succeeds in tracking down his rival and an intense dogfight ensues. During the duel, Guld accuses http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] of stealing Myung from him, of ruining everything. Just as Guld landed a mortal shot on http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu], all the suppressed memories flood back in, and Guld realizes his mistake.
Luckily for the grieving Guld, http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] managed to escape in the last moment. But just as they start to bond again, the X-9 Ghost appears, now controlled by the crazed Sharon Apple and attacks the two. Guld manages to convince http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] to leave this fight to him, and go rescue Myung instead. The fight goes in the Ghost`s favour in the beginning, as Guld can barely keep up with the Ghost`s aerobatics. In one last act of sacrifice, Guld removes all the inhibitors from the YF-21, allowing him to execute dangerously high-G maneuvers. He reconciles himself with both http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] and Myung over the radio and destroys the X-9 Ghost, killing himself in the process.</description>
<picture>93776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48623" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<name>YF-21 Omega One</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The YF-21 Advanced Variable Fighter (AVF) Prototype was designed and built in 2039 by General Galaxy as their entry for the Project Super Nova design contest. Project Super Nova was sponsored by the UN Spacy to develop the next generation variable fighter that would replace the aging http://anidb.net/ch48620 [VF-11 Thunderbolt] as the main variable fighter for terran military forces. The YF-21 was one of two designs selected for the final competition at the New Edwards Flight Center on planet Eden; the other design being the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19 AVF] designed by Yang Neumann of Shinsei Industries.
Unlike the more traditionally designed http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19], the YF-21 is literally a showcase of leading-edge combat technology. Many of fighter`s systems are advanced prototypes, which gives the YF-21 a definite edge in terms of technology. The fighter also includes a significant amount of Zentraedi overtechnology in its flight systems, including a revised version of the inertia vector control system used in the Quimeliquola Quaedlunn-Rau (Female Combat Armor) battlesuit. The alien technology gives the YF-21 a strong resemblance to Zentraedi battlesuits in soldier mode. The AVF is also equipped with many cutting-edge human technology systems, including a revolutionary active stealth system that can absorb radar and other sensor waves, rendering the fighter invisible to most electromagnetic sensor systems.
However the most advanced systems in the YF-21 AVF are the Brainwave Control System (BCS) and Brain Direct Imaging (BDI) system. The BCS allows the pilot to control all functions of the aircraft literally with his thoughts, while the BDI feeds sensor data directly into the pilot`s mind, providing far more information than traditional HMD (head-mounted display) or HUD (heads-up display) systems are capable of. When used together, these two systems allow the pilot to sense and react to situations with the speed of thought while flying the YF-21. The new systems require some time to get accustomed to, however, and only certain disciplined pilots are able to use them to their full potential. In addition, these systems have occasionally exhibited feedback and control problems with some pilots, including chief test pilot http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld Boa Bowman].
Two prototypes of the YF-21 were constructed, with the first one having a conventional flight control system and the second one equipped with the BCS and BDI systems. YF-21 Prototype No. 2 and its pilot, http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Chief Bowman], were invited to the New Edwards Flight Center on planet Eden for final testing. At first, the YF-21 (codenamed "Omega One") performed flawlessly, but then began to develop problems due to incompatibilities between http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Chief Bowmann] and the BCS/BDI systems. Later during a impromptu duel between the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] and YF-21 the YF-21`s right arm was torn off and the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] was severely damaged by a discharge from its own GU-15 gun pod. This disaster made the UN Spacy high command nervous, prompting them to halt Project Super Nova and approve the newly-developed Ghost X-9 Unmanned Fighter as its replacement for the http://anidb.net/ch48620 [VF-11].
Unsatisfied by the program`s cancellation, http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Lt. Isamu Dyson] and Yang Neumann stole the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] and its fold booster and made an unauthorized fold from Eden to Earth. http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Chief Bowman] was ordered to pursue in the YF-21, which at the time was the only aircraft capable of keeping up with the hijacked http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19]. The two prototypes engaged in a final combat during the Macross 30th Anniversary Celebration on Earth, but their grudge match was interrupted when the newly-awakened AI system for popular rock star Sharon Apple took control of Earth`s computer systems and enslaved the entire populace via holographic hypnosis. http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Lt. Dyson] and http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Chief Bowman] overcame their differences and banded together to stop Sharon, and the YF-21 engaged the prototype Ghost X-9 in combat while the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] confronted the AI at the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross]. In order to stop the Ghost and give http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Dyson] more time, http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Bowman] rammed the X-9 with the YF-21, which stopped the renegade prototype at the cost of his own life. Because of this sacrifice http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Lt. Dyson] in the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] was able to destroy the Sharon Apple AI, ending the crisis.
After the smoke from the Sharon Apple incident cleared the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] was declared the winner of Project Super Nova, and was put into production with the intention of replacing the http://anidb.net/ch48620 [VF-11 Thunderbolt]. However the loss of the YF-21 did not discourage General Galaxy, and two years later the company released the VF-22 Sturmvogel II, an advanced combat aircraft based on the YF-21 prototype. Although the VF-22 did not include the controversial BDI and BCS control systems of the second YF-21 prototype, it proved to be an extremely able aircraft and was purchased by the UN Spacy on a limited basis as a special forces fighter.
Source: http://gioco.net/macross/varitech/yf21.htm</description>
<picture>93777.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48624" type="main character in" update="2019-05-22">
<rating votes="7">5.63</rating>
<name>Myung Fang Lone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Myung grew up on the planet Eden with her two best friends http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu Alva Dyson] and http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld Goa Bowman]. Singing was her passion, and her song "Voices" was a hit during her school`s festival. She, http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] and http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] were a love triangle that eventually exploded when http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] found Myung and http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] having a tender moment, and ended with http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] assaulting his two friends. The trio broke up and Myung left Eden soon after.Years later, Myung returned to Eden as the producer for http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple], the computerized singer on tour. The secret was that http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple] was incomplete. She had no emotions. Myung`s real job was to supply these emotions. On Eden, Myung is shocked when she meets http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] and http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] there, the two now pilots competing in the Super Nova Project. The reunion brings back the old rivalry between the two and feelings that Myung thought she had left behind.Before settling matters between her and her two suitors, she leaves Eden with http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple] for Earth to celebrate the anniversary of the armistice between the humans and the Zentradi. There, the awakened http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple] imprisons Myung so she can have free rein with http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] and http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld]. It also reveals Myung`s love for http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld], but greater love for http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu]. Myung manages to free herself and stop http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple], but not before she settles all the lingering emotions with her two friends.
http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] is later seen in the second movie of Macross Frontier, http://anidb.net/a7959 [Sayonara no Tsubasa]. Flying his old YF-19. Revealing that http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu], left the conventional military sometime between 2040 and 2059 and joined the S.M.S.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>233795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48625" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-09">
<rating votes="4">4.56</rating>
<name>Sharon Apple</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sharon Apple is an artificial idol. She exists as a computer which produces a hologram. While her producers say that she has an artificial intelligence that includes emotional programming, it is later revealed that this programming is incomplete and her emotions are provided by http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung Fang Lone]. In public, Sharon appears as a black box, with a red optical sensor for a `face`.
http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung Fang Lone] masquerades as Sharon`s producer, and during the concerts she is connected to Apple`s system to create the unique music that has swept the galaxy. However, the lead scientist on the project, Marge Gueldoa, goes against the wishes of others on the project and implants an illegal chip into her system. This chip makes Apple an artificial lifeform complete with sentience and emotion.
Because of the close connection with http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung], Apple becomes intrigued by http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung]`s childhood friends, the test pilots http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu Alva Dyson] and http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld Goa Bowman]. Apple causes a fire, and warns the two of the danger to see how they react.
When Gueldoa takes Apple to earth for a concert in Macross City, she begins a plan to take over the city by hacking into the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] and a new experimental X-9 Ghost drone ship. http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] and http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] both arrive to stop her. During the course of the battle, she traps http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung] and reveals her plan to show her love for http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] by giving him the ultimate thrill that he has been looking for. Her plan is to kill him, and she uses the defenses of the Macross as well as her own hypnotic powers.
http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] is killed in the battle, and through the efforts of http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung] and http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu], Apple is defeated and destroyed.</description>
<picture>93780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2184" picture="49347.jpg">Hyoudou Mako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48626" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-09">
<rating votes="5">5.02</rating>
<name>Milliard Johnson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Col Millard Johnson is in charge of Project Super Nova, a UN Spacy program deployed to determine the next generation of Variable fighter. Col Millard is most often found in the anime trying to control the feud between http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld Goa Bowman] and http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu Alva Dyson], many times counseling http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] with words of wisdom that mostly infuriate the young pilot.In http://anidb.net/a3392 [Macross Plus the Movie], after http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] stole the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] to interfere with the introduction of Ghost X-9 UCAV and http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld] was sent in the http://anidb.net/ch48623 [YF-21] after the runaway VF, Millard commented that he used to steal planes as well and decided to cover up for the two of them just like his then-superiors did for him. Whether he stole planes as a covert job or simply as an act of misconduct remains unexplained.</description>
<picture>93781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48627" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-09">
<rating votes="2">1.32</rating>
<name>Marge Gueldoa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marge Gueldoa is an assistant producer and a lead scientist on the http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple] Project under http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung].</description>
<picture>93783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48628" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<name>Ghost X-9</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Ghost X-9 was developed as an unmanned combat aerial vehicle for use within and outside of atmosphere to replaced the manned aircraft VF (Variable Fighter). It possesses incredible maneuverability and firepower with no restriction of a living pilot and boasts the performance that exceeds in all areas of the next generation variable fighters (AVF). Furthermore, the http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon]-type artificial intelligence (AI), a completely autonomous-control-type AI applied from the http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple] core was mounted, demonstrating combat ability unlike earlier with Ghosts equipped with conventional semi-autonomous AI, like the QF-3000E Ghost.
The unmanned combat aerial vehicle with the nickname "Ghost Bird", which the U.N. Spacy was further developing in the shadow of the next main variable fighter selection trail, "The Supernova Project". Senior UN leadership, led by General Gomez, pushed development in secret on Earth achieving favorable results in tests. It is equipped with an autonomous-type artificial intelligence adapted from data obtained from the virtual idol http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple] and demonstrates acceleration performance and combat ability exceeding manned aircraft. Since it performed with favorable results in simulated combat, it was designated unofficially as the next main fighter for the UN Forces with with plans to reveal to the public in 2040, following the conclusion of the 30th Anniversary Space War I Memorial Ceremony. It was manipulated by http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple] who controlled the UN Command central functions including communication facilities, but 2 test aircraft descended to Earth (http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] and http://anidb.net/ch48623 [YF-21]) and engaged in combat. It was shot down, receiving a ramming (suicide) attack from the http://anidb.net/ch48623 [YF-21], which released its limiter. Because dependence on artificial intelligence was reviewed after this case, adoption of the X-9 was canceled, but development of unmanned aerial combat vehicles was continued afterwords.
Source: http://macross.anime.net/wiki/X-9</description>
<picture>4628.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="48629" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-09">
<rating votes="5">7.11</rating>
<name>Lucy Macmillan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lucy is a researcher for Shinsei Industries assigned to the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] project. It is there that she meets the young and rough test pilot http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] who immediately attracts her by his roguish nature and the bold way he asked her out for a date. She unwittingly gets herself entangled in the bitter love triangle between http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] and his two ex best friends http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung Fang Lone] and http://anidb.net/ch48622 [Guld Goa Bowman].In the end she reluctantly relinquishes her hopes for a romantic relationship with http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu].Source: wiki</description>
<picture>93786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48630" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-09">
<rating votes="3">5.83</rating>
<name>Yang Neumann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yang Neumann is a brilliant variable fighter designer and a genius hacker at only sixteen, he is a true prodigy by all standards. Shinsei Industries was confident enough in his genius to make him the chief engineer for their experimental fighter; the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19], their entry for the competition to select U.N. Spacy`s next gen fighter known as Project Super Nova. Due to his age, he is the butt of a lot of jokes, especially from his test pilot http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] who likes nothing better than to ruin Yang`s precious prototypes with his dare devil antics.Yang is also a huge fan of http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple], and has used his hacker skills to infiltrate her highly guarded computer systems in an effort to steal her AI. He has all the parts except her emotions module which has proven to be beyond his skills since, unbeknownst to him, it doesn`t actually exist (http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon]`s emotions are actually provided by her alleged producer http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung Fan Lone]).
When Project Super Nova gets cancelled, he correctly predicts that http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] is going to steal the http://anidb.net/ch48621 [YF-19] to stop the inauguration of its replacement, the http://anidb.net/ch48628 [X-9 Ghost], back in Macross City and manages to convince the hot headed pilot to take him along for the ride. When the crazed http://anidb.net/ch48625 [Sharon Apple] takes control of the city she also successfully hypnotizes Yang into shooting http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu]. He misses and http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu] ejects him from the plane, presumably landing somewhere safe.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>93787.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8058" picture="17124.jpg">Nishimura Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48631" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<name>Reymond Marley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A leader in the Sharon Galaxy Tour.</description>
<picture>93788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48632" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<name>Kate Masseau</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school friend of the main characters who remained on Eden.</description>
<picture>93789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="685" picture="24841.jpg">Takano Urara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48633" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<name>Morgan Masseau</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school friend of the main characters who married http://anidb.net/ch48632 [Kate] and had two children.</description>
<picture>93790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48634" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<name>Dr. Wirth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48635" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<name>Gomez</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>UN superior officer supervising http://anidb.net/ch48626 [Colonel Milliard Johnson].</description>
<picture>93797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3284" picture="24296.jpg">Kitamura Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48636" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<name>Higgins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross].</description>
<picture>93798.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48789" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<name>VF-1J Valkyrie</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Shinnakasu Heavy Industry`s VF-1J (the "J" speculated as a prideful designation of the fighter`s region of origin) is an upgraded version of the standard VF-1, typically assigned to the senior officer of an air team or to a squadron leader. Unlike Stonewell/Bellcom`s VF-1D, the VF-1J remains a single seat fighter but shares the slightly increased firepower of that variant. The new head unit of the VF-1J (developed by Kyuusei Industry) features two Mauler RÖV-20 anti-aircraft laser cannons in a slightly improved configuration. Naturally, when the Shinnakasu-designed GBP-1S "Armored" system was given first operational deployment, it was installed on a VF-1J.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/vf-1j-valkyrie.htm</description>
<picture>94007.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48791" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<name>ARMD</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The ARMD Class vessels were designed as space carriers for variable fighters and other U.N.S. spacecraft. The ARMD began construction in April 2003 at the Lagrange Point 5 manufacturing station. The first two carriers ARMD-01 and ARMD-02 were commissioned in July 2008 and October 2008 respectively and were opertaional prior to Space War I in February 2009. Built by OTEC Company, the ARMD carriers featured OverTechnology with gravity control systems, a reaction heat pile system and even the fold drive (though this super dimension navigation system was never implemented). At 430 meters in length, the ARMD carriers were much smaller than the large http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] and both ARMD-01 and ARMD-02 were originally meant to dock with the larger craft when the ship achieved orbit during its maiden voyage.
As a carrier vessel, the ARMDs held numerous ships and mecha. ARMD-01 held 78 SF-A3 Lancer II space fighters and 270 QF-3000E Ghost fighters (as well as an unknown number of VF-1A variable fighters) just prior to Space War I. In addition to several hundred fighters, the ARMD carrier was armed with many weapons including beam cannons, small anti-aircraft cannons and launchers as well as large anti-ship reaction warheads. The ARMD possessed many large vernier thruster nozzles positioned all over the craft. These powerful thrusters granted the ARMD excellent maneuverability in space and also proved very useful for combat engagement and evasion.Both ARMD-01 and ARMD-02 were destroyed in the first battle of Space War I on February 7, 2009. However, both vessels engaged in combat with the Zentradi fleet and proved quite successful in destroying several large Zentradi capital warships with their anti-ship reaction warheads. Eventually, six more vessels of the ARMD Class were commissioned and both the original ships were replaced. To this day, ARMD-01 and ARMD-02 remain docked with the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] on Earth.Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/armd.htm</description>
<picture>94009.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48862" type="appears in" update="2012-09-14">
<name>HWR-00-Mk.II Monster</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>An immense mecha, the Heavy Weight Robot (HWR) Monster Mk II is a heavily armed "land battleship" with a name matching the great size of the destroid. Very shortly after the initial research into the destroids began in 2000 the HWR-00 series began development in December that year. After a lengthy design phase trial production began in October 2005 and the HWR-00 Monster first rollout was in September 2008. The Monster is the largest mobile ground weapon to ever be fielded in battle by mankind, over 41 meters long and weighing almost 300 tons. The Monster was envisioned as a trackless, self-propelled heavy weapon system to be utilized for attack and point defense. In actuality, the Monster`s massive size, poor maneuverability and dedicated long-range weaponry saw the mecha used as a semi-mobile artillery unit best utilized while avoiding uneven ground and any close-range engagement. When put to best use with supporting units in a combined arms role, the Monster is able to field incredible firepower equal to strategic bombing.
The Monster was originally designed to use 50cm linear cannons, but was scaled down with smaller guns when problems arose with system strength and insufficient power for continuous firing. Armed with four 40cm cannons, the Monster can fire a variety of munitions with the primary guns, including anti-armor shells, anti-aircraft munitions, howitzers and even nuclear reaction warheads (OverTechnology reaction warheads have an explosive yield rated at 0.1 kilotons to 50 kilotons). In addition to the main guns, the Mk II features a pair of 3-barreled missile launchers not originally included in the design but incorporated into the two arm units. To compensate for the Monster`s vulnerabilities such as the intense heat emissions of the unit (which prevented effective use of counter measures such as chaff or smoke), the armor was designed to be extremely thick and even capable of withstanding a near hit from a reaction weapon.
Though mass-produced like the other destroids, only two Monster Mk II units were onboard the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] during the outbreak of Space War I. During the conflict, the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] onboard factories made use of equipment for several more Monster mecha and produced a third unit to accompany the original two. Most of the other Monster units were destroyed by orbital bombardment from the Zentradi fleet. The few Monster Mk II units aboard the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] distinguished themselves as very capable war machines during Space War I. While most destroid units suffered heavy losses, the Monsters aboard the ship remained in active service for most of the war and the capability to launch reaction warheads was put to use during the battle with the http://anidb.net/ch17601 [Boddole Zer] Main Fleet in February 2010.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/destroid-monster.htm</description>
<picture>94097.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49049" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Nousjadeul-Ger</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Similar in function and armament to the television series version, the Nousjadeul-Ger film version featured a more organic redesign for the movie. The Nousjadeul-Ger was also more visible in the film http://anidb.net/a996 [Macross: Do You Remember Love?] proven by it`s inclusion in three major combat sequences in the first two acts of the film. The film version of the Nousjadeul-Ger is also seen using rifles (in addition to a redesigned mecha pistol) and a barely seen variant featuring a 6-rack missile launcher mounted on the top left thruster is also briefly glimpsed during the initial combat scene.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/nousjadeul-ger-dyrl.htm</description>
<picture>94422.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49190" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Battle Suit</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Deployed during the late 2030`s and early 2040`s, the Zentradi Battle Suit was a hostile mecha active within the U.N. Spacy sphere of influence, though it was mostly encountered in deep space due to strong U.N.S. interplanetary security. The Battle Suit itself, while clearly a powered armor in appearance, resembles an amalgamation of previously encountered Zentradi mecha such as the http://anidb.net/ch48998 [Nousjadeul-Ger] and http://anidb.net/ch48911 [Queadluun-Rau] units. The Battle Suit lacks large-bore, long-range weaponry and functions mostly as a medium-to-close range war machine, though many U.N.S. analysts have debated whether the Battle Suit is a new design based upon a http://anidb.net/ch48998 [Nousjadeul-Ger] or a http://anidb.net/ch48911 [Queadluun-Rau] (given the many structural similarties the Battle Suit shares with both mecha). One popular theory designates the Battle Suit as a http://anidb.net/ch48998 [Nousjadeul-Ger] suit designed to function like a http://anidb.net/ch48911 [Queadluun-Rau].
Regardless of the mecha`s design lineage, the Battle Suit operates much like the http://anidb.net/ch48911 [Queadluun-Rau] and shares a similar weapons load. Most notably, the Battle Suit has two large primary micro-missile launchers mounted on either side of the back torso with a smaller third launcher situated in the front of the upper chassis. On either side of the front torso are cannons, two small-bore guns on the right side and one triple-barreled cannon on the left. For additional firepower, the Battle Suit also features a pair of cannons mounted one in each arm (though these weapons are ballistic, not energy based). In combat, the Battle Suit can unleash large torrents of missile fire, launching literally dozens of micro-missiles at single or multiple targets. The Battle Suit is also highly maneuverable and can utilize it`s eleven thrusters to position itself for superior angles of attack in both missile and melee combat. The Battle Suit is a proven and dependable combat unit, able to operate with modest damage and in virtually any combat environment.
A http://anidb.net/ch48620 [VF-11] squadron encountered a large group of Zentradi Battle Suits during a deep space operation in 2040. The Battle Suit easily proves the equal of the http://anidb.net/ch48620 [VF-11 Thunderbolt] variable fighter and some U.N.S. analysts have suggested the http://anidb.net/ch48620 [VF-11] is outgunned despite stronger defensive options and a much larger ammunition payload. However, the rogue group of Battle Suits soon found themselves outmatched against the skills of ace pilot http://anidb.net/ch48619 [Isamu Dyson] in unit 107, who single handedly destroyed seven Battle Suits and rescued a fellow pilot hindered by a malfunctioning gun pod.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossplus/enemybattlesuit.htm</description>
<picture>94686.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49191" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Uraga-kyuu Goei Uchuu Kuubo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Uraga Class Escort Battle Carrier is the next generation stealth carrier built to replace the Guantánamo Class Stealth Carriers. The Uraga Class, built with weaponry, armor and maneuverability comparable to a cruiser, is often used as the flagship of small fleets. At 550 meters long, the Uraga Class ships are much larger conventional spacecraft but still significantly smaller than the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] or the later New Macross Class ships. The Uraga is built with a stealth composition and features a dual deck launching system for variable fighters; one deck running the latter dorsal two-thirds of the ship and an internal deck underneath with a launching deck in the forward third. This efficient deck design allows rapid deployment of multiple craft simultaneously and has become common on many UN Spacy carrier vessels.
These ships are rare among colonization fleets due to their high costs compared to the http://anidb.net/ch48791 [ARMD] carriers but the UNG remains committed to replacing the older http://anidb.net/ch48791 [ARMD] carriers one by one with Uraga Class vessels. As more Uraga Class Escort Battle Carriers are built, they are poised to become the mainstay combat and carrier ship for the UN Spacy. Many Uraga Class vessels are part of Earth`s defense fleet in 2040 and are found serving as command ships for large groups of Guantánamo Class Stealth Carriers and Stealth Frigates. Several Uraga Class Escort Battle Carriers are also in active service with the 37th Long-Distance Colonization Fleet, serving as defensive stations docked to unarmed core ships such as the Riviera and Hollywood.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossplus/uraga-escortbattlecarrier.htm</description>
<picture>94687.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49192" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>SB-10/10 Starwing</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>An enormous aircraft with the capacity to carry a vast array of weapons, the SB-10/10 Starwing is a heavy bomber used by the U.N. Forces in 2040. The Starwing is both an advanced bomber craft and a throwback to the flying wing design of the pre-Space War I era. Utilizing modern stealth technologies, the Starwing can carry a very large payload of bombs and missiles inside internal bays as well as act as a carrier craft for up to four drone fighters docked via pylons attached to underwing hard points.
The SB-10/10 Starwing was used extensively during the Project Super Nova AVF competition in early 2040. During testing of the http://anidb.net/ch48623 [YF-21] fighter, a flight of five Starwings were used as carriers for 20 drone fighters meant to engage the test fighter with unarmed ordnance. Bomber Nine initiated the sham attack with it`s remote control drones, but the command craft and it`s flight remained outside the testing zone.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossplus/starwing.htm</description>
<picture>94689.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49194" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Drone Fighter</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>These small and deadly unmanned fighters were used extensively by the U.N. Forces, mostly as training craft. At some 10-12 meters in length, this small aircraft featured a retractable small-bore beam cannon under the front nose and could carry up to six AIM-225 high-maneuverability missiles upon the dorsal/ventral wing hardpoints. Typically, the drone fighter was not outfitted with live ammunition and carried mostly unarmed missiles used specifically in combat exercises. The drone fighter required the use of specialized equipment to land and to transport into combat zones so these fighters were often dependent upon larger aircraft for proper deployment. A small boom mounted on the dorsal fuselage was used to mount the drone fighter under the wings of larger carrier craft, like the http://anidb.net/ch49192 [SB-10/10 Starwing Bomber], and thus carry the craft much like ordnance.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossplus/dronefighter.htm</description>
<picture>94690.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49195" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>QVF-11</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>When testing the next generation of advanced variable fighters and other spacecraft, the U.N. Spacy often employs various unmanned fighter craft as material for space flight exercises. In the early 2040`s an unmanned version of the VF-11 produced by the UN Forces saw active use in such test exercises. The cockpit pod is removed and is replaced by an automated control module. A simpler forward nose with smaller canard wings is installed and two smaller sensors are fitted on either side of the forward nose. This new autonomous hardware is used to control the craft without the need for a pilot. A set of FAST Packs (without armament or missile launching ports) is installed to provide optimal performance for the target craft in space. Once complete, the VF-11 unmanned target craft can be launched and take part in any test exercise required. During the 2040 space combat trials of the http://anidb.net/ch48628 [Ghost X-9] Fighter in Earth orbit, the U.N. Spacy made use of dozens of these VF-11 unmanned target craft to act as stationary and mobile targets for live fire tests.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossplus/vf-11-target.htm</description>
<picture>94691.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49196" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Stellar Whale</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Following the mass migration into outer space, the U.N. Government soon controlled many worlds covering many light years. As these colonies became established, civilian travel quickly surpassed military space travel and the need for interplanetary passenger transport became a priority. The Stellar Whale Passenger Boat was an interplanetary liner operating in the 2040`s that featured large, spacious interiors and room for hundreds of passengers. Using now commonplace OverTechnology, the Stellar Whale liner featured a gravity control system for surface-to-orbit flight and a space fold system cluster for travel between star systems. On her flight from the planet Eden, music producer http://anidb.net/ch48624 [Myung Fang Lone] traveled in the Stellar Whale flying from the Groombridge 1816 system to Earth in the Sol system some 11.7 light years distance.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossplus/stellarwhaleliner.htm</description>
<picture>94694.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49233" type="appears in" update="2012-09-23">
<name>Guantanamo-kyuu Uchuu Kuubo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>In the years following Space War I, the United Nations Government (UNG) quickly rebuilt much of the lost infrastructure and soon the UN Spacy was rebuilding the fleet. Impressed with the initial combat performance and multi-functionality of the http://anidb.net/ch48791 [ARMD] Class Space Carriers, the UN Spacy pursued design and construction of a next generation http://anidb.net/ch48791 [ARMD] Class vessel. The result is the Guantánamo Class Stealth Carrier, an improved space carrier with stealth capabilities and its own Space Fold System for interstellar travel. As a carrier, the Guantánamo Class has a large launch bay in the forward section, a dock in the aft section of the ship (to link with large vessels) and large external fuel tanks with stealth covers. Though this class of vessel utilized many new technologies, the economy of design proved relatively inexpensive and the UN Spacy deployed massive numbers of Guantánamo Stealth Carriers. These ships are found primarily as the main-force carrier in the colonization fleets, but the Guantánamo Class Stealth Carrier is also used extensively for planetary defense. In 2040, Earth has a vast defense fleet stationed in orbit consisting of numerous vessels that included the Guantánamo Class ships as well as thousands of armed defense satellites spread amongst the fleet.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossplus/guantanamo-stealthcarrier.htm</description>
<picture>94751.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49234" type="appears in" update="2012-09-23">
<name>Northampton-kyuu Stealth Frigate</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The smallest of the UN Spacy ships of the line, the Northampton Class Stealth Frigate is an easily constructed vessel and functions as the main-force warship for colonization fleets. The main engines are built around the center circumference of the rear hull and supply the 250-meter long frigate with excellent speed and maneuverability that compensates for a lack of heavy firepower. Like many of the next generation space vessels of the UNG, the stealth frigate features a stealth composition and functions as a carrier ship for variable fighters. In battle the stealth frigate utilizes several concealed launch bays for the fighters and has several anti-ship missile launchers and converging energy beam cannons. The widespread use of this class has lead to the deployment of numerous modified Bolognese frigates such as firepower-enhanced, reconnaissance and early-warning variants. The stealth frigates have also been adopted by Zentradi crews and these ships feature more Zentradi technology with distinctive hull designs. The stealth frigate fulfill a primary operational role and thus there are large numbers of these ships serving in the UN Spacy fleets, from planetary defense around Earth to far reaching colony fleets like the 37th long-distance colonization fleet. Stealth Frigates serve as the first defensive line in the emigration fleets, with aircraft carriers forming the second defense line. Additionally, a squadron of stealth frigates will operate as "pilot fish" for surveying routes and securing supplies ahead of a emigration fleet.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossplus/stealthfrigate.htm</description>
<picture>94752.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="458" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1994-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA 01</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Projet Super Nova</title>
</episode>
<episode id="459" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1995-01-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA 02</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Programme virtuel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="460" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1995-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA 03</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Intelligence artificielle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="461" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1995-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA 04</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épilogue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19404" update="2005-06-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Extra</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120922" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120923" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120924" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
