<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6716" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2010-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Inuyasha Kanketsuhen</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Инуяся: Последняя глава</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Инуяша: Последняя глава</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">إينوياشا : الفصل الاخير</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Инуяша - последната арка</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">犬夜叉 完结篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">iy2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">犬夜叉 完結編</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">InuYasha: The Final Act</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Inuyasha: The Final Act</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">犬夜叉 完結篇</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="144" type="Prequel">Inuyasha</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="558" approval="2" total="2">Kishin Douji Zenki</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="379712">If you were ever a fan of Inuyasha then I highly suggest you watch this. Even if your like me and dropped the original because it was so long and drawn out you`ll like this infinitely better. There are no monsters of the week, everything is direct and to the point and, the best part of all, there a definite end to it. &amp;gt;X D  The Final Act is only 26 episodes long so you dont have to worry about another 200 episode run.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="526796">If you watched the original series, this is a must-see. If you didn`t, well, think carefully if you wanna go through the really slow-paced 167 original eps to be able to catch up and watch this nice piece of anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="455194">Imho totally overrated. Now we have a conclusion of the story, but thats all i liked about it. it was by far tooo rushed. no more epic moments, no more epic powerups, no more funny real world fillers, ...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="760053">must see!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="613777">A great conclusion to a great series. If you watched the prequel this one is a must. Although 26 episodes may seem extremely condensed compared to the 167 epi prequel, the creators did a fine job.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="375005">If you are a die hard Inuyasha fan then this series is a must see...XD</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ytv.co.jp/inuyasha/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="3412" type="Character Design">Hishinuma Yoshihito</name>
<name id="3748" type="Series Composition">Sumisawa Katsuyuki</name>
<name id="818" type="Original Work">Takahashi Rumiko</name>
<name id="5680" type="Direction">Aoki Yasunao</name>
<name id="3412" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hishinuma Yoshihito</name>
<name id="2703" type="Music">Wada Kaoru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on volumes 36 to 56 of the manga by http://anidb.net/cr818 [Takahashi Rumiko].
At long last, http://anidb.net/ch12167 [Kagura] has revealed to http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Kagome] and http://anidb.net/ch7245 [Inuyasha], frequent time-travellers to the civil war period, the location of http://anidb.net/ch11091 [Naraku]`s Heart.
http://anidb.net/ch10477 [Sesshoumaru], http://anidb.net/ch12166 [Kohaku] (holder of a Shikon shard), Kagura (whose involvement with http://anidb.net/ch12169 [Kouga] resulted in her betrayal of Naraku), and the plotting of Moryomaru will all affect the choices made by Kagome and Inuyasha.
Should the Shikon Jewel be forged, http://anidb.net/ch10909 [Kikyou] should be able to destroy Naraku. However, Naraku exercises great influence over evil men. When the Shikon Jewel is completed, the final battle will begin!
What does the future hold for Kagome, Inuyasha, http://anidb.net/ch12161 [Miroku], http://anidb.net/ch12162 [Sango] and http://anidb.net/ch12160 [Shippou]?
~ translated and adapted from the official Japanese site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1653">7.49</permanent>
<temporary count="1673">7.82</temporary>
<review count="2">7.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>204851.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10970</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6811</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4540</identifier>
<identifier>vdkebd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ytv.co.jp/inuyasha/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Inuyasha_final_act</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>犬夜叉#.E5.AE.8C.E7.B5.90.E7.B7.A8</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1740</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334965</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11891</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1783" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>immature</name>
<description>Marked by or indicating a lack of maturity</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-24">
<name>kitsune</name>
<description>Kitsune is the Japanese word for http://anidb.net/t191 [fox], which are a common subject of Japanese folklore. This term in English specifically refers to kitsune as demon foxes or fox spirits. Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t1814 [foxpersons], a http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin] with fox characteristics.
Stories depict them as intelligent beings and as possessing magical abilities that increase with their age and wisdom. Foremost among these is the ability to assume human form.</description>
<picurl>226225.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3926" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-06-05">
<name>wardrobe limited to school uniform</name>
<description>The main characters only wear school uniforms, even though other clothes would be more appropriate.
Example: Kagome in Inu Yasha, wears her uniform in Inu Yasha`s world, although she is shown to own other clothes at home.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4517" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>inter-dimensional schoolgirl</name>
<description>One, or more, schoolgirls cross through time, space or some dimension using a space-warp-magic-portal-wormhole-singularity-thing to save one, or more, worlds, or planets.
A major twist could be that the schoolgirl might originate from that very magic-futuristic world, bearing one great secret legendary power to defeat one big bad legendary foe. The return back home is the leitmotiv of the whole series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5822" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>series end</name>
<description>This marks the end of the anime series. The series may include many types, (TV, OVA, movies, etc.) but this marks the wrap-up point for all of the major story threads. The entire thing feels complete at the conclusion of this. It may or may not be the actual end of the anime series. Sometimes the producers will try to milk a dead cow and add extra episodes at the end of an anime run but those only open up new threads that usually never get closed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7245" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="411">7.31</rating>
<name>Inuyasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>InuYasha is a hanyou (half-demon), the product of an inu-youkai (犬妖怪, dog demon) and a human. He wields Tetsusaiga, a supernatural sword made from one of his deceased father`s fangs. When properly wielded, the sword can destroy one hundred demons with a single swing. InuYasha can quickly recover from injuries that would be fatal to a human, largely due to his demonic blood. During the first night of each lunar month (new moon), InuYasha changes into a normal human with black hair and black eyes and loses his demonic powers.
InuYasha was bound to Goshinboku by Kikyo`s arrow for fifty years until Kagome freed him. InuYasha wears a special bead necklace that forces him to respond to Kagome`s command "Osuwari!", which translates to "Sit!" in English. In the English-dubbed version, "InuYasha, sit!" or "Sit, boy!" are sometimes used instead. Following the command, InuYasha is thrown to the ground. Kaede had placed the necklace upon InuYasha because he had threatened to kill Kagome if she refused to give the Jewel of Four Souls to him. As the series goes on, he begins to like Kagome more and more, shown when he will leave a battle to save her from being hurt.</description>
<picture>36855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7246" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="314">5.44</rating>
<name>Higurashi Kagome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Higurashi Kagome is one of the main protagonists of the series. Born in modern Japan as the reincarnation of the priestess Kikyo, Kagome has the Shikon Jewel unknowingly hidden inside her body until 1997, when a demon pulls her into the Bone Eater`s Well and 500 years back through time. They emerge in the Feudal Era about 50 years after Kikyo`s death, where the demon extracts the jewel from Kagome. When another demon seizes the jewel, Kagome shoots it with a bow and arrow.
While trying to protect the jewel using a bow and arrow, she accidentally shatters it into numerous shards that disperse throughout the country. She agrees to help find them, as she can sense the presence of nearby shards. As the series progresses, she falls in love with InuYasha, and finds herself competing with the revived Kikyo for his affections. During the search for the jewel, Kagome`s own spiritual powers and archery skills continue to improve.
At the end of the series, Kagome returns to her own time for three years. She is then able to return to the Feudal era where she and InuYasha acknowledge their love for one another and she chooses to remain there with him.</description>
<picture>36854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10477" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="591">8.49</rating>
<name>Sesshoumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sesshoumaru is InuYasha`s older half-brother. Like their father, he is the Lord of the Western Lands, although Sesshoumaru maintains no permanent home. As a full-blooded Inu-yokai, he is a very powerful demon and nearly unequalled in raw power, but is unable to defeat Naraku in volume twenty-three of the manga. He has no interest in possessing even one shard of the Shikon Jewel to enhance his powers, since he is already supremely confident of his own strength.</description>
<picture>36856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10909" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="171">6.97</rating>
<name>Kikyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kikyou is a powerful shrine maiden, or miko, who is given the task of guarding the Shikon Jewel. She falls in love with InuYasha and considers using the jewel to turn him from a half-demon into a full human; this would cause the Shikon Jewel to vanish, allowing her to live as an ordinary woman by his side. However, Naraku disguises himself as InuYasha to attack her village, mortally wounding her. With her last strength, Kikyou shoots a charmed arrow into the real InuYasha to seal him to a sacred tree, then orders the Shikon Jewel to be burned with her on her funeral pyre. The jewel disappears and is apparently destroyed, but is reborn 500 years later in the body of Higurashi Kagome, her spiritual reincarnation.
After Kagome travels back through time and reappears fifty years after Kikyou`s death, an ogress tries to pull her reincarnated soul into a clay body made with Kikyou`s bones and ashes. Kagome appears to suffer no permanent harm, but a small part of her soul detaches and reanimates the new body with Kikyou`s memories, personality, and human appearance. Although Kikyou retains some of her old powers in this form, she remains technically "dead" and must absorb the souls of dead women in order to move. At first, she wants to vengefully drag InuYasha to hell and kill Kagome to recover the rest of her soul. However, Kikyou gradually returns to her former compassionate nature and learns the real circumstances of her death was caused by Naraku.
She is also the sister of Kaede.</description>
<picture>36877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11091" type="main character in" update="2017-07-10">
<rating votes="60">5.80</rating>
<name>Naraku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naraku is the series` primary antagonist. Naraku is responsible for most of the characters` misfortunes, including the death of http://anidb.net/ch10909 [Kikyou], the sealing of http://anidb.net/ch7245 [Inuyasha] to the sacred tree, http://anidb.net/ch12161 [Miroku]`s curse, and the death of http://anidb.net/ch12162 [Sango]`s family. Naraku was born from the fusion of http://anidb.net/ch72625 [Onigumo], a crippled human bandit tended by Kikyou, and a horde of weak demons. Driven by frustrated lust for Kikyou, Onigumo made a bargain with the demons: His soul would allow the demons to combine into one entity and he would become part of that new body. However the resulting half-demon promptly caused Kikyou`s death in an attempt to corrupt and possess the Shikon Jewel.
Naraku is driven by three goals: To become a full demon, to possess a fully-corrupted Shikon Jewel, and to possess Kikyou. The third goal was a result of the fact that Onigumo`s heart remained a vital part of Naraku`s body, causing an obsession with Kikyou that prevents him from killing her. He attempts to rid himself of Onigumo`s heart multiple times, eventually succeeding in separating it into The Infant. With his heart freed from his obsession, he is able to later kill Kikyou. At the end of the manga, however, he expressed regret at not being able to have her for his own.
Throughout the series, Naraku creates many subordinate beings from his own body to aid his goal of killing his opponents and reuniting the shards of the Shikon Jewel, whose corrupted form he hopes to use to gain ultimate power.</description>
<picture>36852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12156" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-27">
<rating votes="23">7.44</rating>
<name>Toutousai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A youkai (probably) swordsmith. He forged both Inuyasha`s Tessaiga and Sesshoumaru`s Tenseiga. Toutousai generally appears with his flying, three-eyed cow.</description>
<picture>36861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12160" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="90">3.82</rating>
<name>Shippou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shippou is an orphaned young fox demon who attempts to steal the Shikon Jewel from Kagome and InuYasha, wanting to become stronger and avenge his father`s death. Though his plan fails, Kagome and InuYasha aid him after hearing his story, and he becomes their companion for the rest of the series.
Shippou normally appears to be a young boy with certain fox-like features: his legs, feet, ears, and tail. He can shape-shift, but his other forms (such as a large pink flying balloon) are temporary and often ineffective, usually given away by his lingering fox tail. He can also create illusory duplicates of himself, as well as weak fox-fire magic and toy-based tricks such as his giant spinning top attack. Naively observant, he often directs cheeky comments to InuYasha, earning a smack on the head. InuYasha and Kagome serve as older sibling figures to Shippou. Because of his small size, Shippou often rides on Kirara or the shoulders of others. His actual age is never stated in the series; according to the official InuYasha guide by Takahashi Rumiko, his appearance is equivalent to that of a seven year old boy.</description>
<picture>36876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12161" type="main character in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="135">6.04</rating>
<name>Miroku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miroku is a Buddhist monk who travels the countryside performing services such as exorcisms and demon exterminations, although sometimes he deliberately falsifies these to earn comfortable rewards. Miroku can attack enemies with his holy staff and sutra scrolls, but his greatest weapon, the Wind Tunnel embedded in the palm of his hand, is also a hereditary curse originally inflicted by Naraku upon Miroku`s grandfather Miyatsu. The Wind Tunnel sucks in almost anything in its path and is a powerful weapon against demons; however, it grows larger with increasing use, so that Miroku`s grandfather and father were eventually consumed by their own Wind Tunnels. Miroku hopes to break the curse by killing Naraku.
Miroku first meets InuYasha by stealing the Shikon Jewel, causing them to fight one another until Kagome leaps between them. After Miroku explains his situation, InuYasha allows him to join their group as a valuable ally. Miroku`s lechery is a recurrent habit, usually manifesting as shameless flattery, semi-surreptitious groping, and asking random women to bear him a child; he learned these bad habits from the monk Mushin who raised him, but he also has the more serious motive of wanting an heir to follow him if he dies without defeating Naraku.</description>
<picture>36866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12162" type="main character in" update="2017-01-11">
<rating votes="186">7.10</rating>
<name>Sango</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sango is a demon slayer who hails from a village of professional demon slayers. Naraku wipes out her entire family and village, then causes Sango to blame InuYasha and try to kill him. When the plot fails, Naraku revives Sango`s little brother Kohaku, controlling him as a pawn to manipulate Sango`s emotions and attack the rest of InuYasha`s group. Sango seeks vengeance against Naraku, but her primary goal is to rescue Kohaku from Naraku`s influence and save his life.
Of her broad repertoire of tools and tricks for fighting demons, her most powerful weapon is the Hiraikotsu, a massive boomerang made of purified demon bones. She is accompanied by the demon cat Kirara. Sango is often the victim of Miroku`s lecherous tendencies and slaps him for it.
She has three kids with Miroku by the end of the series, twin girls and a boy.</description>
<picture>36867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12163" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="92">3.99</rating>
<name>Jaken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jaken is a small green imp-like youkai who is extremely loyal to Sesshomaru, often praising his master`s greatness although Sesshomaru usually ignores him. Jaken himself is not especially powerful, despite bearing a weapon known as the Staff of Two Heads. He seldom engages in battle and is actually killed by Kaijinbo with Toukijin, but Sesshomaru resurrects him with Tenseiga.</description>
<picture>46124.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12164" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-11-11">
<rating votes="97">7.25</rating>
<name>Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rin is an orphan girl who finds http://anidb.net/ch10477 [Sesshomaru] in the woods after he is badly injured by InuYasha. Although Sesshomaru snubs her, she visits him regularly and attempts to take care of him, even stealing fish from the village for him until she learns that he doesn`t eat human food. The villagers beat her for the theft, but when Sesshomaru idly inquires about her injuries, she seems strangely happy about his interest in her welfare. During this time, she never speaks, only communicating with hand gestures and smiles.
Later, the wolf-demon http://anidb.net/ch12169 [Kouga] chases a thief to her village, then lets his wolves kill and eat the villagers. Rin flees through the forest towards Sesshomaru, but the wolves catch up to her. Recovered from his wounds, Sesshomaru is leaving when he catches Rin`s scent and follows it to her mauled corpse. Remembering her smile, he retests Tenseiga by using it to resurrect her. After setting Rin on her feet again, Sesshomaru walks away, leaving the dumbfounded http://anidb.net/ch12163 [Jaken] and a wide-eyed Rin standing on the path. After a moment, they both follow. The next time Rin appears, she is clean, wearing a new, colourful kimono, and talking and acting more like a typical child. Throughout the series, she continues to follow "Lord Sesshomaru", as she calls him; when he is away on dangerous tasks, she waits for him with Jaken and a two-headed dragon which she names "Ah-Un".
Though Sesshomaru never states any feelings for her, he displays a strong protective instinct and Rin is obviously devoted to him.</description>
<picture>36875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12165" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="31">5.77</rating>
<name>Myouga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Myouga is a flea demon who appears randomly and gives InuYasha information on current events, foes, and the shards of the Shikon Jewel. Assigned to protect Tetsusaiga`s hiding place in the grave of InuYasha`s father, he runs away when Sesshomaru comes there in search of the sword. Myoga often flees before or during a battle, which the others recognize as a sign of pending danger; his mere presence in any area is enough to determine its safety. Myoga enjoys drinking demon blood, and actually saves InuYasha`s life at one point by drinking a spider demon`s venom out of his blood. He can save the others in a similar manner, but often gets slapped for drinking their blood without permission. In the anime series, he is engaged to another flea demon named Shoga, but continually runs from her to avoid the marriage.</description>
<picture>36874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12166" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="23">4.06</rating>
<name>Kohaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kohaku is Sango`s younger brother. Disguised as the young nobleman Kagewaki Hitomi, Naraku summons Sango`s family and companions to slay a false demon, then controls Kohaku with a Shikon shard and makes him kill all of the other demon slayers (Sango survives solely by sheer luck). Castle guards also kill Kohaku that night.
Naraku resurrects him as an amnesiac puppet, but after several encounters with Sango and her friends, Kohaku begins to recover his painful memories. Kagura helps him escape from Naraku, who kills her for the defection. Hoping to redeem himself, Kohaku travels with Kikyou until she tells him he must leave her to keep his shard pure. He later joins Sesshomaru`s group and becomes Rin`s friend and co-protector.</description>
<picture>36872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12167" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="66">5.20</rating>
<name>Kagura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kagura is a creation of Naraku`s, his second "detachment" although she is introduced before her "elder sister" Kanna. A wind sorceress, Kagura uses a fan to enhance her powers; she can create a blade-like tornado or use wind to animate dead bodies. She can also use her feather hair-ornaments as transportation, enlarging them to ride in the wind. Kagura hates Naraku and wishes to be free from him, covertly opposing him to the point of offering aid to both InuYasha and Sesshomaru in hopes that they can kill him.</description>
<picture>36870.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10018" picture="37130.jpg">Oogami Izumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12168" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="30">5.54</rating>
<name>Kanna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanna is the first detachment of Naraku. She appears to be a ten-year-old girl with white hair and clothing. As a "concealed incarnation" of Naraku, Kanna has no scent and no demonic aura, making her undetectable to InuYasha`s senses and immune to demonic aura-related effects such as the Hakurei-zan barrier. Kanna is the only incarnation that Naraku trusts with important information about his actions, allowing her to give orders in his place.
Kanna carries a demonic mirror that can steal the souls of those reflected in it. Once a soul is trapped by her mirror, Kanna can control that person`s body to carry out her bidding. However, the mirror can be overwhelmed by an especially powerful soul such as Kagome`s, forcing Kanna to release all of the trapped souls before the glass shatters. The mirror can also create a glass demon to copy the abilities of whatever it reflects, though Kanna herself suffers damage when the glass demon is wounded.</description>
<picture>36871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12169" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="25">1.47</rating>
<name>Kouga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouga is the young leader of the southern youkai-wolf tribe, which is nearly wiped out by Kagura and Naraku. He first meets InuYasha as an opponent in battle, but becomes a reluctant, occasional ally despite maintaining a strong sense of rivalry with the "useless mutt" about their relative combat strengths as well as Kouga`s persistent courtship of Kagome.
After suffering serious wounds, Kouga is partially restored by three Shikon shards embedded into his legs and right arm. The shards are eventually taken away from him by Naraku, gravely weakening him; he leaves and disappears from the manga, after telling Kagome that she may leave InuYasha and come to him at any time.</description>
<picture>36873.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2799" picture="23198.jpg">Matsuno Taiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12170" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-11-10">
<rating votes="24">2.89</rating>
<name>Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaede is http://anidb.net/ch10909 [Kikyou]`s younger sister and assists her with various tasks such as gathering herbs or holding her arrows. After Kikyou`s death, Kaede becomes a miko in her own right and defends the village against demons. When Kagome arrives, Kaede recognizes her as the reincarnation of Kikyo. After Kagome frees InuYasha, Kaede puts the "Beads of Subjugation" onto him to give Kagome the power to control him with a spoken word. Kaede is well-respected and held in high regards by the villagers and the members of InuYasha`s group, which she often advises about demons and other spiritual anomalies. Though InuYasha is easily annoyed with her, he listens to her when necessary and doesn`t hesitate to protect her from a threat.
Kaede loses an eye sometime during her life. In the manga, her eye appears to be freshly bandaged and bleeding shortly before Kikyo`s death, suggesting that the wound occurs when "InuYasha" (really http://anidb.net/ch11091 [Naraku] in disguise) attacks the village to steal the Shikon Jewel; supplementary information states that she "lost her elder sister and her eye in an incident fifty years ago." The anime simply says that she lost it during a demon attack on the village.</description>
<picture>36869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12171" type="appears in" update="2014-11-14">
<rating votes="9">3.26</rating>
<name>Mama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kagome`s mother.</description>
<picture>164097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="628" picture="188442.jpg">Dodo Asako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12172" type="appears in" update="2009-10-08">
<rating votes="6">3.49</rating>
<name>Jii-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kagome`s grandfather.</description>
<picture>36912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3196" picture="218728.jpg">Suzuki Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12173" type="appears in" update="2010-01-05">
<rating votes="6">4.96</rating>
<name>Higurashi Souta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kagome`s brother.</description>
<picture>41079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="396" picture="151685.jpg">Nakagawa Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12174" type="appears in" update="2010-01-17">
<rating votes="6">3.10</rating>
<name>Ginta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Kouga`s wolf pack.</description>
<picture>41081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12175" type="appears in" update="2010-01-17">
<rating votes="8">2.90</rating>
<name>Hakkaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Kouga`s wolf pack.</description>
<picture>41604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12192" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-08">
<rating votes="7">4.79</rating>
<name>Byakuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naraku`s ninth and final detachment, meant to replace Kagura. His main purpose is to observe InuYasha and Mouryoumaru`s growing powers and report back to Naraku. He has an incredible power to create illusions, but has many other powers as well: he can possess people with paper soldiers, summon vines to entrap his enemies, teleport others to different dimensions, detach organs from his body, and erect barriers. He travels on a giant origami paper crane.</description>
<picture>36909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12193" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-08">
<rating votes="42">6.93</rating>
<name>Kirara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sango`s faithful demon-cat companion. Kirara usually appears to be a small kitten-sized feline with two tails, but can become large enough to carry several passengers (usually Sango, Miroku, and Shippou). Her full-sized form has more prominent fangs, flames around her feet and tail, and enough power to fly through the air fast enough to keep up with InuYasha`s top speed.</description>
<picture>36910.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12194" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="12">4.29</rating>
<name>A-Un</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A two-headed dragon demon and Sesshomaru`s beast of burden. He is one of two youkai in the series who is explicitly stated to be an herbivore. Despite travelling with Sesshomaru for centuries, he has no name until Rin gives him one, calling the right head "A" and the left head "Un". A-Un can fire youkai energy from both mouths. The right head shoots blue beams of lightning, while the left shoots green lightning that can control clouds and possibly the weather. A grey cloud-like gas trails from his legs in flight, similar to Kirara`s flames.</description>
<picture>36911.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15613" type="appears in" update="2010-03-07">
<rating votes="2">6.73</rating>
<name>Magatsuhi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17327" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="7">7.64</rating>
<name>Jinenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hanyou, Jeninji lives with his mother on the edge of a town, where they grow many medicinal herbs. At first, he is feared and attacked by the villagers, but is later to be more understood.</description>
<picture>47273.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="71328" type="appears in" update="2014-11-13">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Sesshoumaru no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71330" type="appears in" update="2014-11-13">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Yakurou Dokusen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72603" type="appears in" update="2015-01-07">
<rating votes="4">1.84</rating>
<name>Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167261.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10852" picture="38959.jpg">Okamoto Nami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72605" type="appears in" update="2015-01-07">
<rating votes="4">2.72</rating>
<name>Yuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167263.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="108361" update="2009-09-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奈落の心臓</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Naraku`s Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Narakus Herz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naraku no Shinzou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108561" update="2009-10-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神楽の風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kagura`s Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kaguras Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagura no Kaze</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110725" update="2009-10-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冥道残月破</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meidou Zangetsuha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meidou Zangetsuha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110790" update="2009-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖霊大聖の試練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Holy Demon Spirit`s Test</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yourei Taisei no Shiren</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110791" update="2009-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜鱗の鉄砕牙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dragon-scaled Tessaiga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuurin no Tessaiga</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110792" update="2009-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魍魎丸の最期</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of Moryomaru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mouryoumaru no Saigo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110793" update="2009-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">梓山の霊廟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mausoleum of Mount Azusa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Azusayama no Reibyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110794" update="2009-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星々きらめきの間に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Among the Twinkling Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshiboshi Kirameki no Aida ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111323" update="2009-11-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冥界の殺生丸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sesshomaru in the Underworld</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meikai no Sesshoumaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111325" update="2009-11-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しみに濡れる花</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flowers Drenched in Sadness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi ni Nureru Hana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111489" update="2009-11-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神無の墓標</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kanna`s Gravestone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanna no Bohyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111849" update="2009-12-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">珊瑚の想い 弥勒の覚悟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sango`s Feelings, Miroku`s Resolve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sango no Omoi Miroku no Kakugo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112011" update="2010-01-01">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奈落の追撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Pursuit of Naraku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naraku no Tsuigeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112012" update="2009-12-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">完全な冥道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Complete Meido</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanzen na Meidou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112708" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かぬ想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thoughts Fall Short</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokanu Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112709" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奈落儚き望み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Naraku`s Uncertain Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naraku Hakanaki Nozomi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112710" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奈落 光の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Naraku: Trap of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naraku Hikari no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112711" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奈落 闇の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Naraku: Trap of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naraku Yami no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112712" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奈落の体内へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inside Naraku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naraku no Tainai e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112713" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四魂の玉が完成する時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When the Jewel is Whole</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikon no Tama ga Kansei Suru Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112714" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">琥珀の欠片</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kohaku`s Shard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kohaku no Kakera</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112715" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人生の一大事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day of Days</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinsei no Ichidaiji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112716" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">曲霊の邪念</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magatsuhi`s Evil Will</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magatsuhi no Janen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112717" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">瞳子の結界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hitomiko`s Barrier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitomiko no Kekkai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112718" update="2010-01-06">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正統なる継承者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Heir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seitounaru Keishousha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116931" update="2010-03-25">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Towards Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120121" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120122" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120123" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120124" update="2010-07-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121575" update="2010-08-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
