<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="675" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2001-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Taiho Shichau zo: Second Season</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">You`re Under Arrest! Second Season</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">You`re Under Arrest 2nd Season</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">You`re Under Arrest! 2nd Season</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">You`re Under Arrest: Season 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">yua2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">YUA TV2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">逮捕しちゃうぞ Second Season</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">You`re Under Arrest: Fast &amp; Furious</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5234" type="Sequel">Taiho Shichau zo: Full Throttle</anime>
<anime id="438" type="Prequel">Taiho Shichau zo: You`re Under Arrest (1996)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="97536">I actually like it even more than the first season. It`s light, it`s fluffy and it has just the right mix of humour and drama.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/taiho/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="817" type="Original Work">Fujishima Kousuke</name>
<name id="1419" type="Character Design">Nakajima Atsuko</name>
<name id="3465" type="Series Composition">Yokote Michiko</name>
<name id="6283" type="Direction">Koumoto Shougo</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
<name id="1551" type="Music">Iwasaki Yasunori</name>
</creators>
<description>Aa! Megami Sama creator, http://anidb.net/cr817 [Fujishima Kousuke], is back with the second season of Taiho Schihauzo (You`re Under Arrest). Same characters, two policewomen, the gentle Miyuki and the wild Natsumi teamed up together in Bokuto police station`s traffic division.
Other characters including Kenichi, the motorcycle cop who has a feeling for Miyuki; Yoriko with her gossip and Aoi, a transvestite. They are all ready to take on harmless criminals and costumed weirdos... You think you can have a better police station?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="669">6.66</permanent>
<temporary count="673">7.49</temporary>
<review count="1">7.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>2176.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>621</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2014</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>832</identifier>
<identifier>vbwaae</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/taiho/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>You're_Under_Arrest</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>逮捕しちゃうぞ_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234292</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3489" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>car chases</name>
<description>Car chases occur as part of the action setting in this anime.</description>
<picurl>211263.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11779" type="main character in" update="2010-08-15">
<rating votes="159">8.73</rating>
<name>Tsujimoto Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsumi is an officer stationed at the fictional Bokuto Station in Tokyo`s Sumida Ward. She is very outgoing as well as very laid back. She often demonstrates superhuman strength second only to Shoji Tokairin and is a motorcycle enthusiast, capable of high-risk maneuvers on both bikes and mopeds. Natsumi has a prodigious appetite for food and alcohol, and has been known to show up at work with a hangover. She is also a chronic late sleeper. Despite having many bad habits, she is a very capable police officer and does her job seriously when needed. She keeps a mini-moped, a Honda Motocompo (JR-2) in Miyuki`s Honda Today squad car and uses it when a flanking strategy is required. It is prominently labeled "NATUMI" (in the Nihon-shiki transliteration system) before her first day at Bokuto in the beginning of the first anime, later re-coloured and re-labeled "POLICE" in the later appearances and on the Bandai Model kit of the Honda Today. When off-duty, she operates a Yamaha RZV motorbike until it is damaged beyond repair during later part of the first season. She is subsequently tricked into buying a Subaru R-2, which is in a near-non-functioning state. This car is then thoroughly renovated and heavily modified by Miyuki into a patrol car. She uses the wrecked motorbike`s engine, modifying the car to make its operation follow closely to that of a motorbike. In the manga version, this car operates with double engines.
Natsumi is also familiar with judo and kendo, being able to defeat her opponents during training sessions. Her strength and her familiarity with hand-to-hand combat complement Miyuki`s brilliant mind in creating devices or modifying known vehicles very well, making her and Miyuki famous throughout Bokuto Station. She is also the only person in this series able to consistently defeat Strikeman`s fastballs and is called Home-Run Woman by Strikeman for this very reason.</description>
<picture>35664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11848" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="170">8.45</rating>
<name>Kobayakawa Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyuki is Natsumi`s partner and roommate. Miyuki is not as physically tough as Natsumi, but she is much smarter and more polite. A technical genius, Miyuki frequently performs custom vehicle modifications for various people at the precinct, as well as being an expert with computers. Miyuki is a superb driver, almost as daring as Natsumi, and very difficult to shake in a pursuit. She is also punctual, shy and diligent - in contrast to Natsumi, who is tardy, brash and frequently lazy. Her mini patrol car, a Honda Today, is a heavily modified version for patrol duties. Normally the engine is a 554cc, but Miyuki has stroked it out to 700cc(although still having a yellow number plate for K-cars) and added twin cams, a turbo-charger, and nitrous oxide boost. Such a car could theoretically be built given current technology, but would be impractical at best in reality. She also has a blue Toyota Sports 800 as her personal car.
Unlike Natsumi`s infatuation towards the chief (Kachou) of Traffic Division, Miyuki admires and respects him because of his dedication in working with the division. During situations where force was the only solution, Miyuki uses airsoft guns with paintball bullets in order to incapacitate or to leave a homing beacon on the opponents. Her love interest happens to be with the "White Hawk" Ken Nakajima but has initial difficulty in telling him until the end of the series. Her feelings for Ken were driven to the point when she pointed an air gun on Natsumi`s head when she joked that she would have to marry Ken in the future.
Miyuki is fearful of anything that cannot be explained by science, such as the Paranormal, Supernatural or anything that was similar to science fiction. She is also afraid of reptiles.
Her character design was also used as the template for a goddess whom the characters prayed to in a four panel gag strip added to a version of YUA who eventually became Belldandy when the strip proved popular and was developed into Oh! My Goddess.</description>
<picture>35890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16044" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="88">7.26</rating>
<name>Aoi Futaba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An officer who joined Bokuto Station in the first season, Aoi is originally mistaken for a woman. In fact, Aoi is a man. He had cross dressed to go undercover as a decoy to catch a serial rapist in the vice unit and, in the process, "went native". Now, Aoi is more feminine in appearance and personality than any of the women in the station. Aoi`s romantic gender preferences are often speculated on by the Bokutou police, but in the end it is discovered that Aoi prefers men.</description>
<picture>45063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18842" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="27">5.65</rating>
<name>Kachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The section chief of Bokuto Station`s Traffic Control Department is usually referred to simply as "chief" (課長, kachou). His name was first revealed to indeed spell "Kachou" (花蝶, kachou, lit. "Flower butterfly") in the second season by his monk uncle (a.k.a. FOX). He is a stern, but fair leader who uses a relaxed touch to keep his team of misfit officers in line. Natsumi had a long-standing crush on him before she met Toukairin. Though he allows his subordinates to do as they normally please in the station, he reminds them of their priorities as police officers.
In the movie, he got in trouble with Superintendent Arizuka when he was linked to Emoto, who was suspected of starting the Hachi-Ichi-Go (Bee Number 1) crisis in the Greater Tokyo Area. First stripped off his command and thrown into a cell by Arizuka due to suspicion of coercing with Emoto, he eventually disclosed details regarding both Emoto and Project "Hachi-Ichi-Go", as well as the fact that Emoto severed connections with him as well. During the final confrontation in Tokyo Tower, Emoto shot him in the leg, reinforcing the fact that he was not Emoto`s accomplice.
He uses a Honda NSX as his personal car when doing police work in the OVA. In the rest of the series, he uses a Honda Legend.</description>
<picture>49714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3248" picture="157354.jpg">Masamune Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18859" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="12">6.68</rating>
<name>Kinoshita Kaoruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An assistant inspector from the Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department, this charming lady first appeared in the last few episodes of Season 1 with a car theft case in tow. A strict, no-nonsense kind of person, she initially comes off as cold-hearted, but beneath that imposing demeanor is actually a woman who is selflessly dedicated to her duties and those that fall under her command. She is ready to help the females of Bokuto Station and is approachable whenever she is around at the station.
During the course of her career, Kaoruko had participated in at least one Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department Color Guard parade.</description>
<picture>49742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18860" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="65">2.85</rating>
<name>Nakajima Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A motorcycle patrol officer stationed in Bokuto Precinct who is such a gifted rider that he might have a successful racing career if he wanted it. Ken is strong, tough and handsome but at the same time, was terribly shy. He and Miyuki share strong feelings for each other, but have difficulties expressing them. He is the only son of Daimaru Nakajima, managing a motorbike shop called ZAPPER, and the stepson of his teenaged stepmom Sena Wakabayashi. Details on his mother was not revealed, but it is known that his father became a widower before the OVA and first season series started. His peers call him "White Hawk" for his skills as a motorbike officer in chasing down various offenders. His family was from the Mie Prefecture.</description>
<picture>49744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18861" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="3">6.80</rating>
<name>Nakajima Daimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The father of Ken Nakajima and the owner of the ZAPPER motorbike shop in Sumida`s Bokuto district, he is an old man who is an expert on motorcycles and was an excellent rider in his younger days. Now widowed, he is currently remarried to his second wife, Sena Wakabayashi. Though he is senile at certain times and his unthoughtful on certain matters, Daimaru still cares about Ken and Sena as they are his only remaining family left. He had a good impression on Miyuki when she kindly called him father, indicating that he still liked the younger generation to appreciate him like a caring parent.
He has a Ducati motorcycle that he uses personally. During his first encounter with Miyuki and Natsumi, Daimaru initially thought that Natsumi was Ken`s girlfriend until realizing Miyuki was the better choice.
Due to his knowledge of motorbike handling, Daimaru tries to teach Ken techniques to befit his duties as a motorbike officer, to the point of "breaking him." He has a scar over his left eyebrow.</description>
<picture>49746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18862" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-08">
<rating votes="82">5.50</rating>
<name>Nikaidou Yoriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A dispatcher at Bokuto Station who later becomes a patrol officer and partner of Aoi Futaba, Yoriko is an incorrigible gossip who pokes her nose into everything that happens at the precinct. Unfortunately, she frequently misinterprets things she sees and hears about, resulting in embarrassment and complications. She keeps an especially close eye on Miyuki and Ken. Yoriko also enjoys heckling her colleagues, especially when she talks about anything supernatural or paranormal.
She is also clumsy in anything she does but always can somehow cover the trouble created with her luck, which made her the top in class during her years in the Metropolitan Police Department Academy and earned the ire of her classmate Chie Sagamiono, who had aspired to become valedictorian back in their academy days. She is also insecure about her job for a short period of time when she saved an elementary student from Yakuza thugs.</description>
<picture>49747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18863" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="6">1.18</rating>
<name>Gentuki Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An old woman who spends the majority of her time going after discounts and sale events. To the annoyance of every Traffic Division officer in the Bokuto Precinct, she does so relentlessly and is perfectly willing to commit any traffic violation in order to get to the sales location faster, having proven herself just as aggressive on the road as Natsumi or Nakajima (except that she does it all the time) and counting on the reflexes of people or vehicles she was about to collide with rather than her skills in operating a scooter to avoid accidents. However, another situation would intervene (such as repeating motorcycle thefts or bomb threats against a department store) whenever there`s an attempt to apprehend her, allowing her to go off the hook. Her name was never revealed.
For transportation she uses a motor scooter (with a 50cc engine, hence her nickname), which tends to be overloaded with groceries and other merchandises that she purchased during discount events.</description>
<picture>49748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18864" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="8">6.55</rating>
<name>Saga Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school student who had trouble with the law during the 1st Season. After reforming herself, Saori graduated from high school and studied in the Metropolitan Police Department Academy since she admired Natsumi and Miyuki for their hard work in the force and was assigned to Bokuto Station`s Traffic Division. On her first day, she got into trouble with them after trying to make a big impression by making the Traffic Division office neat (unwittingly getting rid of many personal belongings from others while she is at it). In the first few days of work, she scorned her colleagues and superior for being lax in their duties in the office and constantly reminds them of their responsibilities as police officers, even though Natsumi and Miyuki advised her to relax a bit since she was taking police work too personal. As time went on, Saori had learned to accept them and became fast friends with her Bokuto station co-workers, especially with Natsumi and Miyuki.
When she noticed that Miyuki wanted to break up her partnership with Natsumi, Saori was the only persistent one in convincing her to amend their ties since she couldn`t see to see her get depressed over Natsumi`s supposed selection into the Special Assault Team. She is Miyuki`s new partner before being transferred to a different station.</description>
<picture>49749.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2138" picture="21613.jpg">Iizuka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18865" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="12">3.94</rating>
<name>Toukairin Shouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mountain rescue specialist and lieutenant, he met Natsumi during a rescue mission on a tower. They would later encounter each other once again when Shouji is temporarily stationed at Bokuto Precinct as an instructor for rescue courses. It is then discovered that Shouji is the only character that has the physical strength and appetite to surpass Natsumi`s. Although Natsumi initially views him as a nuisance and a rival, they eventually fall in love. Despite being frequently absent in places like the Himalayas, he and Natsumi have a strong relationship. Later on, Shoji named a monkey he befriended as Natsumi[19]. He enjoys eating bananas.
Shoji is an expert in mountain climbing and rappelling and, one time, uses his time in Bokuto Station to practice these two techniques.
He is also an expert in Kendo, being able to cut a banana in half with a Shinai with extreme concentration (self-proclaiming that he can only do it at a 50% success rate) but admitted defeat against Kachou at his challenge against him despite Kachou was not in his best shape.</description>
<picture>49750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18866" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">9.13</rating>
<name>Wakabayashi Sena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 20-year-old woman who owns a Lotus Super Seven racer vehicle, she was married to Daimaru after meeting him in a highway where she usually drives around before being in love with him. Sena was soon married to Daimaru and was also the co-owner of the ZAPPER motorbike shop. She manages the place if Daimaru is not around.
Though she and Ken had their differences, mostly in age, Sena truly cares for him like he was her own son.</description>
<picture>49751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18867" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Strike-Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A costumed vigilante who calls himself a superhero, Strikeman uses baseballs and related items to punish offenders such as public drunks, flashers, and parking violators. He has come to the attention of Bokuto Precinct on several occasions, earning notoriety as a major nuisance and complete loon. He seems to have a fixation on Natsumi, considering her both his nemesis and his sidekick while referring to her as "Home-Run Woman." As of Full Throttle, there has been no clue so as to who the identity of Strikeman is. At one time during the 1st season, Nakajima was even suspected by his colleagues to be Strikeman, due to some events and a very similar appearance, but was found to be not the case.
Many attempts were placed to apprehend him, but Strikeman escapes due to the various fastball pitches that he uses as weapons. When he tries to enact "proper justice" on the offender`s property such as their cars, Strikeman uses baseballs with sharp spikes on them and in fact, has used them against Miyuki and Saori as a means of distraction. He uses a Harley-Davidson Softail motorbike, designated FLSTF. He had recently returned after months of self-exile into the mountains to defeat Natsumi in another game of baseball.</description>
<picture>49752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="417" picture="24695.jpg">Hori Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18868" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="4">10.00</rating>
<name>Maho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49753.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18869" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="4">4.13</rating>
<name>Yuuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49754.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18870" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="4">4.13</rating>
<name>Shou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49755.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18871" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="12">2.96</rating>
<name>Tokuno-keibu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A plainclothed inspector stationed at Bokuto Police Station`s Investigations Division, he happens to be the only known officer in Bokuto be married and with a family and an old veteran at the station since it was established. Most of the younger officers in the station look up to him as a mentor whenever they need help or advise from him. Like Kachou, Natsumi was infatuated with him since she liked older men before meeting with Shoji[10]. Tokuno is partnered up with a younger detective named Sugihara when attending to cases in the field. Like Kachou, he appears to be lenient with most of the officers in their capacity to be good officers in their speciality.
He uses a Honda Legend as his personal police vehicle whenever he is conducting detective work.</description>
<picture>49756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18872" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="3">9.13</rating>
<name>FOX Osyo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19515" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">5.07</rating>
<name>Sagamiono Chie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only daughter of the rich Sagamiono family, Chie entered the Metropolitan Police Department Academy in hopes of winning a suitable, preferably rich, husband and making herself a bit more popular to society, earning questions from some of the officers as to why a rich girl would join the police force. She had lost her chance to graduate on top of her class when Yoriko earned it via luck, marking her as Chie`s rival. She uses her family`s financial position to use a modified Porsche 911 outfitted with sirens and a radio for police use.
The two had been at odds with each others from catching crooks in a contest, to playing wargames to a Color Guard parade contest.</description>
<picture>51060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19683" type="appears in" update="2010-07-16">
<name>Tanaka Natsuyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19727" type="appears in" update="2010-07-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Honda Toshuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3242" picture="41841.jpg">Mitsuoka Yuutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19728" type="appears in" update="2010-07-18">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Honda Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="397" picture="43234.jpg">Saitou Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19902" type="appears in" update="2010-07-22">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Hasumi Yuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19903" type="appears in" update="2010-07-22">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Mushu Yanagawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24990" type="appears in" update="2010-11-09">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Kaneko Ruriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13061" picture="43055.jpg">Shimazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28552" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<name>Endou Yuukou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5815" picture="30271.jpg">Oono Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28556" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<name>Noguchi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5650" picture="30095.jpg">Murozono Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28557" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<name>Nega Nebashi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2192" picture="196332.jpg">Kashii Shouto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28558" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<name>Nakahara</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2047" picture="68288.jpg">Domon Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28559" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<name>Tsurijin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5626" picture="29921.jpg">Fujimoto Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28560" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<name>Samejima</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5626" picture="29921.jpg">Fujimoto Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="9239" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">墨東署交通課に配属を命ず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assignment: Bokutou Police Station Traffic Section</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutousho Koutsuuka ni Haizoku o Meizu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9240" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東京野獣捜査線</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dragnet for the Beast of Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokyo Yajuu Sousasen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9241" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">回れ二人のコーヒーカップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spin! Coffee Cup for Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maware Futari no Coffee Cup</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9242" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">墨東署ベストパートナー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bokutou Police Station`s Best Partners</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutousho Best Partner</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9243" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニセ警官VSなりきり女刑事(デカ)!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fake Officer vs. Actor Cop</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nise Keikan vs Narikiri Onna Deka!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9244" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">男, 中嶋やせがまん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nakajima Swallows His Pride</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko, Nakajima Yasegaman</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9245" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女の闘い! ライバル再び!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Women at War! Return of the Arch-Rival!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna no Tatakai! Rival Futatabi!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9246" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seperate Ways</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Michi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9247" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正しいメル友の作り方(^◇^;)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Proper Way to Make an E-Mail Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tadashii Mail Tomo no Tsukurikata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9248" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">合コン勝利の方程式</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Formula for a Successful Social</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goukon Shouri no Houteishiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9249" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コンビ解消!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is the Partnership Breaking Up?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Combi Kaishou!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9250" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイバーポリス24時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">24-Hour Cyber Police</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cyber Police 24-ji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9251" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日に架ける橋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crossing the Bridge to Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita ni Kakeru Hashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9252" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれ違いの停車場(バスストップ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Missing the Bus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigai no Bus Stop</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9253" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉・浴衣・告白?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot Springs, Summer Kimono, Marriage Proposal?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsen, Yukata, Kokuhaku?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9254" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">セ・シヴォン・揺れる恋心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">C`Est Si Bon. Wavering Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">C`est Si Bon, Yureru Koigokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9255" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出は鮮やかに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Keep the Memories Brilliant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide wa Azayaka ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9256" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">墨東線大パニック! 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Panic on the Bokutou Line! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutousen Dai Panic! Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9257" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">墨東線大パニック! 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Panic on the Bokutou Line! Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutousen Dai Panic! Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9258" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽霊窃盗団を追え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chase the Ghost Thief Gang!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuurei Settou Dan o Oe!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9259" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絆のために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Their Bond</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizuna no Tame ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9260" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スクープ! 恋の大暴走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scoop! Big Escape of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Scoop! Koi no Daibousou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9261" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰ってきたストライク男!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Return of Strike Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaette Kita Strike Otoko!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9262" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケーキとステーキ運命の選択!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cake or Steak: The Fateful Choice!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cake to Steak Unmei no Sentaku!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9263" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆれる想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vacillation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yureru Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9264" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真夏の夜の呪い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Midsummer Night`s Curse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manatsu no Yoru no Noroi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140004" update="2012-06-03">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">1-14話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">AMV - Overview Ep 1-14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1-14 Wa Digest</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140005" update="2012-06-03">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">辻本夏実の華麗なる日々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsujimoto Natsumi Wonderful Everyday Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsujimoto Natsumi no Karei Naru Hibi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151330" update="2013-06-27">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151331" update="2013-06-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
